<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>USDT Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/usdt/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 09:03:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Exchange AdvCash to Tether USDT [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-tether-usdt/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-tether-usdt/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 08:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AdvCash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6389</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking for the ultimate platform to exchange AdvCash to Tether USDT? CoinCannon is the ultimate platform for the job! So far, AdvCash has been one of the most crypto-friendly payment processors out there. Regardless, the anonymity factor remains an issue as users may be concerned with their privacy. Fortunately, our platform eliminates all the downsides [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-tether-usdt/">&lt;strong&gt;Exchange AdvCash to Tether USDT [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking for the ultimate platform to exchange AdvCash to Tether USDT? <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is the ultimate platform for the job! So far, AdvCash has been one of the most crypto-friendly payment processors out there. Regardless, the anonymity factor remains an issue as users may be concerned with their privacy. Fortunately, our platform eliminates all the downsides associated with converting AdvCash to crypto assets. You can instantly convert your AdvCash to Tether USDT with the lowest exchange fees and a hassle-free KYC process that maximizes privacy. On top of that, you will have 24/7 online support for the utmost reliability. In this article, we will go over everything you need to know on how to exchange AdvCash to Tether USDT.</p>



<p>So get started! Head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select AdvCash on the left box and Tether on the right one and you’re good to go!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">how to exchange AdvCash to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange AdvCash to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange direction, you will need a verified and active AdvCash account. Make sure that the transaction amount does not exceed your withdrawal limit. In order to receive Tether (USDT), you will need a reliable crypto wallet. There are too many options out there, but CoinCannon suggests customers to use Trust Wallet. Furthermore, make sure you pay attention to the TRC20 and ERC20 variants for Tether as they use different networks for transactions and require different wallet addresses.</p>



<p>On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is AdvCash?</strong></h2>



<p>Before we talk about how to convert AdvCash to Tether USDT, let’s have a brief introduction on what the payment processor is. AdvCash is a currency used for online payments. It is based in Belize which provides immunity from national laws of other countries for it. As an offshore currency, it is also encrypted much like cryptocurrencies and benefits from better anonymity and security. The Advance Cash company provides an account for users that allows for a variety of currencies to operate through it. In many ways, it is a lot like the payment processor Payeer.</p>



<p>And much like Payeer, AdvCash supports transfers in both fiat and cryptocurrency form. With a virtual wallet, users can transfer funds and make payments with very low commission. What makes it interesting, is that Advance Cash is also compatible with other payment systems such as WebMoney or Perfect Money. With free international transfers, users get to enjoy a wide variety of currencies all in a virtual wallet. Furthermore, there are both physical and virtual bank cards available for quick and cheap international Visa/Mastercard payments.</p>



<p>The company was founded in 2014 as a competitor for PayPal and much like its peers, it has gained notable success in the past few years. As the need for virtual banking grows, online payment processing companies continue to narrow the gap with PayPal. Although, such companies are not as popular as PayPal, they offer a lot more freedom.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange AdvCash to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon is the Best Exchange!</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange AdvCash to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select AdvCash on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>By now, you will go to the AdvCash gateway. Transfer your AdvCash to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-you-re-all-set"><strong>You’re all Set!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-tether-usdt/">&lt;strong&gt;Exchange AdvCash to Tether USDT [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-tether-usdt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT Instantly</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether-usdt/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether-usdt/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 07:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6386</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>CoinCannon is the ultimate platform to exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT instantly! Exchanging crypto assets into one another is a seemingly simple task. However, finding a platform that offers the best exchange rates and anonymity at the same time is no easy feat. With all the strict user verification out there, user privacy is slowly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether-usdt/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT Instantly&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>CoinCannon is the ultimate platform to exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT instantly! Exchanging crypto assets into one another is a seemingly simple task. However, finding a platform that offers the best exchange rates and anonymity at the same time is no easy feat. With all the strict user verification out there, user privacy is slowly losing its value. Fortunately, our platform provides a hassle-free KYC process that speeds up your exchange process and massively improves security. On top of that, we offer 24/7 online support to ensure the utmost reliability for our customers. In this article, we will go over everything you need to know on how to exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT on CoinCannon.</p>



<p>So get started, head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Ethereum ETH on the left box, and Tether USDT on the right one and you’re good to go!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-paypal-2/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Ethereum to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-do-i-need-to-exchange-ethereum-to-tether-usdt"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive USDT. In case your Ether wallet supports ETH, you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-dai/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Ethereum (ETH)?</strong></h2>



<p>As an open-source decentralized blockchain platform, Ethereum is perhaps the most diverse and innovative one out there. In its essence, it is a decentralized public ledger for verifying and recording transactions. The Ethereum is considered as a second-gen blockchain platform, improving upon the high gas fees, scalability issues and high transactions fees of previous platforms. This open-source platform has no geographical restrictions and has always been the tip of the spear as far as innovation goes. Essential services such as Smart contracts, NFT`s and decentralized apps were first introduced on the Ethereum platform. As for the cherry on top, the native token of the Ethereum platform called Ether or ETH is second in terms of market value standing only behind Bitcoin.</p>



<p>With the Ethereum 2.0 launch in August 2022, the network totally switched to proof of stake. With that, Ethereum network will have much better scalability and very low gas fees. On top of that, all the criticism regarding energy consumption will go away. Many consider the 2.0 upgrade as a great investment opportunity since ETH is very much likely to have a rally. Nonetheless, Ethereum is the second most popular cryptocurrency in the world for good reason. Their team has always been on the forefront of innovation which could potentially attract capital and provide great returns.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT, let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Ethereum on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your Ethereum to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether-usdt/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT Instantly&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether-usdt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Tron with Tether USDT [Instant]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tron-with-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tron-with-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 08:42:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tron (TRX)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6373</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking to buy Tron with Tether? Look no further than CoinCannon. Generally speaking, buying cryptocurrencies and exchanging them into one another is an easy task. However, most exchange platforms tend to compromise on security or offer high exchange rates. With that, it can be difficult to find an online exchange platform that offers everything you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tron-with-tether/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Buy Tron with Tether USDT [Instant]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking to buy Tron with Tether? Look no further than CoinCannon. Generally speaking, buying cryptocurrencies and exchanging them into one another is an easy task. However, most exchange platforms tend to compromise on security or offer high exchange rates. With that, it can be difficult to find an online exchange platform that offers everything you need. Subsequently, CoinCannon provides unparalleled anonymity all while charging no hidden fees on your transaction. With all that, you can easily Buy Tron with Tether (USD) in only a matter of minutes. So head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Tether USDT on the left field, and Tron on the right and start the action!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Tron with Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive Tron (TRX). In case your USDT wallet supports Tether, you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Tron (TRX)?</strong></h2>



<p>Tron is a decentralized, blockchain-based platform that aims to build a free, global entertainment system for digital content with distributed storage technology and enables digital content to be shared easily and cost-effectively.</p>



<p>The TRON ecosystem basically acts as a platform for content-sharing. In this platform, TRX is the payment for users who create or post content, resulting in a fairer and more open monetization mechanism than those that control conventional social media networks. It also allows users to share their content without having to go through a middleman, such as the Google Play Store or Apple Store. This means that TRON is helping to push the decentralized application market (dApps).</p>



<p>Tron was founded by a non-profit organization based in Singapore called the Tron Foundation in September 2017. This foundation is led by Justin Sun, CEO, and benefits from a dedicated in-house development team that includes distinguished stalwarts in technology.</p>



<p>Tron attempts to CoinCannon the gap between content creators and content consumers by eliminating the middleman by using the features of the blockchain and peer-to-peer (P2P) network technology. The result is an overall cost reduction for the consumer and better collection for the content producer through direct receipts, which offers a win-win situation.</p>



<p>To learn everything about Tron (TRX) continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-tron-trx/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Tron?</a>”</p>



<p>If you are interested in investing in Tron (TRX), you can easily and instantly buy Tron with Tether (USDT) or a variety of other digital currencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Buy Tron with Tether (USDT)?</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to buy Tron (TRX) with Tether (USDT), let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon is the Best Exchange!</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Buy Tron with Tether (USDT)?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">Homepage</a> on CoinCannon. Select Tether USDT on the left field and Tron (TRX) on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your TRX wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your USDT to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-that-s-it"><strong>That’s It!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tron (TRX) to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tron-with-tether/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Buy Tron with Tether USDT [Instant]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tron-with-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Crypto to Tether USDT [Lowest Fees]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-to-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-to-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 07:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange crypto to tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5617</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Very often, you will have to exchange crypto to Tether USDT in order to avoid market volatility. As of 2022, Tether USDT is still the dominant stablecoin in the market and the top US dollar crypto equivalent. Whether you trade or hodl, Tether USDT is the ultimate mediator apparatus for everyone. However, although making the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-to-tether/">How to Exchange Crypto to Tether USDT [Lowest Fees]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Very often, you will have to exchange crypto to Tether USDT in order to avoid market volatility. As of 2022, Tether USDT is still the dominant stablecoin in the market and the top US dollar crypto equivalent. Whether you trade or hodl, Tether USDT is the ultimate mediator apparatus for everyone. However, although making the exchange is easy, it matters a lot which platform you choose to exchange crypto to Tether. For one, not all platforms offer the same exchange rates and you may have to pay more for the order. More importantly, anonymity is also a key feature user should keep in mind. For that, a reliable exchange platform like <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is absolutely necessary. In this article, we will go over how to exchange crypto to Tether and why CoinCannon is the best platform to do the job.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/how-exchange-tether-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How To Exchange Tether USDT To PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Crypto to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>Generally speaking, exchanging assets to Tether is for times when you want to pay less commission and be ready for the next purchase. When you <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange cryptocurrency to PayPal</a>, the cost for the exchange is considerably higher and it takes a longer time to have the assets in your account. On top of that, the next time you want to buy cryptocurrencies, you will once again have to pay high commission and wait longer. With Tether, the transactions are almost immediate and have a very low cost of transaction.</p>



<p>Comparatively, Tether is good for those who are actively monitoring the market to make their next move. Thankfully, numerous Forex platforms also accept Tether as payment so it has even more utility. On the other hand, PayPal is generally a safer method to store assets with much more regulations. Naturally, it is good for those looking for better security and purchasing options.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Tether (USDT)?</strong></h2>



<p>&nbsp;Before reading about how to exchange crypto to Tether (USDT), let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Crypto to Tether on CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p>very exchange platform must maintain three important characteristics. Anonymity, affordability and reliability. We pride ourselves as a professional platform that offers all three.</p>



<p>For anonymity, CoinCannon requires no KYC or even a sign up process. The best way to protect your information is to not share them with anyone. And for that, we respect our customers and do not ask for their personal info.</p>



<p>As for affordability, CoinCannon utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. By doing so, we have managed to stay on top of the ranks on websites such as Bestchange and OkChanger.</p>



<p>Lastly, reliability is ensured for our customers with 24/7 online support. In case anything goes wrong, you will have our immediate support until the issue is resolved.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Crypto to Tether (USDT) on CoinCannon</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the homepage first, then select the cryptocurrency you want on the left field and Tether TRC20 or ERC20 on the right. Enter the amount you want to exchange and wait for the exchange rate to apply.</li>



<li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Tether wallet details, email, and phone number.</li>



<li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li>Complete the captcha and click on “exchange” to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. At this point, you will have the CoinCannon wallet address to send the cryptocurrency to. &nbsp;After you have transferred your cryptocurrency, click on Pay Order button. Don’t forget to attach the screenshot for the payment. your order will process swiftly.</li>



<li>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the Tether to your wallet ASAP.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>And Done!</strong></h2>



<p>Usually, Tether payments are very quick to go through. For that, give it a few minutes and you will have the USDT in your wallet. In the meantime, you can follow up on your order using the Track ID provided for you. Simply enter the track id in the required section on homepage to see at which point your order is. Remember not to share your Track ID with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-to-tether/">How to Exchange Crypto to Tether USDT [Lowest Fees]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-to-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Bitcoin with Tether (USDT) [Video]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 08:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Videos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6332</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Here is a full guide on how to buy Bitcoin with Tether on CoinCannon platform with a whole slew of unique benefits. Perhaps, to exchange Tether to Bitcoin can be the most popular exchange direction in crypto market. Both being the first of their kind, both BTC and USDT remain the king of the category. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-tether/">How to Buy Bitcoin with Tether (USDT) [Video]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Here is a full guide on how to buy Bitcoin with Tether on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">HiEx</a><a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">c</a><a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">hange</a> platform with a whole slew of unique benefits. Perhaps, to exchange Tether to Bitcoin can be the most popular exchange direction in crypto market. Both being the first of their kind, both BTC and USDT remain the king of the category. With that, everyone will need a great platform like CoinCannon to buy Bitcoin with Tether without any compromise. Subsequently, we will go over how easy it is to do that in only a matter of few minutes.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/how-exchange-bitcoin-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Bitcoin to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="Exchange Tether to Bitcoin   Buy BTC with USDT" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xh0FlrOrGnw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Bitcoin with Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive Bitcoin that is reliable and secure. Although there are thousands of options at this moment, we advise you to pay extra attention when choosing a Bitcoin wallet. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon. Want a good reason why? How about winning $100 ever month!</p>



<p>Learn more about our <a href="https://hi.exchange/campaign/tether-giveaway" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Tether Giveaway</a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Bitcoin (BTC)?</strong></h2>



<p>Well, there is hardly anyone these days who is not familiar with the definition of Bitcoin and what the cryptocurrency is capable of carrying out. However, let’s briefly go through what bitcoin is and where it comes from, then we can focus on the benefits of using this cryptocurrency and explain why to buy Bitcoin with Perfect Money.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a Cryptocurrency that was created after the housing market collapse in January 2009. It follows the ideas set out by the enigmatic and pseudonymous Satoshi Nakamoto in a whitepaper. The identity of the individual or individuals who developed this cryptocurrency is still under wraps. Unlike government-issued currencies, Bitcoin provides the guarantee of lower transaction costs than conventional online payment systems and is regulated by a decentralized authority.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a tempting opportunity for investment and great tool for doing financial transactions. Everything is in favor of exchanging your Perfect Money for some BTC when possible.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Pay with Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>Owning Tether is basically like having digital dollars in your pocket, only without needing a bank. Recently, there has been lots of talk about how we do not actually own our money when they are in the banks. Digital money means that banks and governments can freeze our access to our funds for whatever reason they seem justifiable. In 2022, Canada denied protestor’s access to their bank accounts and cut out their rightful ownership of their capital. Such incidents are not rare and should be treated seriously. But, political motivation aside, banks are not always available. For example, we saw how the Ukrainians lost all their capital within the banks as soon as the war started. Once again, the decentralized nature of cryptocurrencies meant that the bankless were the lucky ones in that incident.</p>



<p>Thankfully, the list of online merchants and service providers who accept Tether USDT is sufficiently long. With Tether, you can make purchases online and in person almost anywhere. Be it through a direct wallet address or a payment gateway, USDT is as good as cash these days.</p>



<p>Lastly, USDT offers an extra layer of protection for the user with blockchain technology. As a cryptocurrency, it is anonymous and secure. On top of that, the transaction fees for Tether are very low, as long as you use the TRC20 variant based on the Tron network.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon FTW!</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Buy Bitcoin with Tether?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Tether on the left field and Bitcoin on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your Bitcoin wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your Tether (USDT) to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-easy-as-that"><strong>Easy as That!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the BTC to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-tether/">How to Buy Bitcoin with Tether (USDT) [Video]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Buy Tether USDT with Lowest Possible Fees on CoinCannon</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-usdt/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-usdt/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 08:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy USDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5640</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Whether you’re a trader or an avid investor, there are solid reasons to buy Tether USDT. As of 2023, USDT has a lot more utility than what it had only a few years ago. Basically, the dollar-pegged cryptocurrency is accepted in a wide variety of online platforms for shopping and services. Today, you can pay [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-usdt/">Buy Tether USDT with Lowest Possible Fees on CoinCannon</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Whether you’re a trader or an avid investor, there are solid reasons to buy Tether USDT. As of 2023, USDT has a lot more utility than what it had only a few years ago. Basically, the dollar-pegged cryptocurrency is accepted in a wide variety of online platforms for shopping and services. Today, you can pay for almost anything from flight bookings to a Cappuccino with Tether. On the other hand, Forex traders have also been using Tether as a medium on their traders. However, if you are looking to Buy Tether USDT, not all exchanges are equal! For that, you will need an exchange platform that offers the best exchange rates. And more importantly, a platform who doesn’t sell you private data to the highest bidder! Fortunately, <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is the ultimate OTC platform to buy Tether USDT from and this article will tell you why.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Learn <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-crypto-to-tether/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Crypto to Tether</a> on CoinCannon</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-tether-usdt"><strong>What is Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to buy Tether USDT, let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>Learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/how-exchange-tether-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange Tether USDT to PayPal</a></p>
</blockquote>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-should-i-buy-tether-usdt"><strong>Why Should I Buy Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>Owning Tether is basically like having digital dollars in your pocket, only without needing a bank. Recently, there has been lots of talk about how we do not actually own our money when they are in the banks. Digital money means that banks and governments can freeze our access to our funds for whatever reason they seem justifiable. In 2022, Canada denied protestor’s access to their bank accounts and cut out their rightful ownership of their capital. Such incidents are not rare and should be treated seriously. But, political motivation aside, banks are not always available. For example, we saw how the Ukrainians lost all their capital within the banks as soon as the war started. Once again, the decentralized nature of cryptocurrencies meant that the bankless were the lucky ones in that incident.</p>



<p>Thankfully, the list of online merchants and service providers who accept Tether USDT is sufficiently long. With Tether, you can make purchases online and in person almost anywhere. Be it through a direct wallet address or a payment gateway, USDT is as good as cash these days.</p>



<p>Lastly, USDT offers an extra layer of protection for the user with blockchain technology. As a cryptocurrency, it is anonymous and secure. On top of that, the transaction fees for Tether are very low, as long as you use the TRC20 variant based on the Tron network.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-where-do-i-buy-usdt"><strong>Where Do I Buy USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>Every exchange platform must maintain three important characteristics. Anonymity, affordability and reliability. We pride ourselves as a professional platform that offers all three.</p>



<p>For anonymity, <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> requires no KYC or even a sign up process. The best way to protect your information is to not share them with anyone. And for that, we respect our customers and do not ask for their personal info.</p>



<p>As for affordability, CoinCannon utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. By doing so, we have managed to stay on top of the ranks on websites such as Bestchange and OkChanger.</p>



<p>Lastly, reliability is ensured for our customers with 24/7 online support. In case anything goes wrong, you will have our immediate support until the issue is resolved.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-is-tether-a-safe-investment"><strong>Is Tether a Safe Investment?</strong></h2>



<p>Generally speaking, Tether has remained reliable and solid since the initial introduction. While there are numerous controversies, USDT has been consistently stern as an investment option. Most of the controversies come from a lack of transparency regarding Tether’s funds. Basically, there is not much information about what funds are actually held by Tether to back their stablecoin. However, Tether has assured investors that they hold the majority of their funds in the form of cash and investors have no reason to worry.</p>



<p>Regardless, there is still some risk associated with stablecoins, especially after the Terra USD collapse. With that, while there is no clear and imminent risk, make sure to thread carefully and keep some of the risks in mind before you buy Tether USDT.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-usdt/">Buy Tether USDT with Lowest Possible Fees on CoinCannon</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-usdt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Tether with Payeer USD [No KYC]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-payeer/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-payeer/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 11:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy USDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5774</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you already have a Payeer account, you can buy Tether with Payeer USD on CoinCannon. On CoinCannon platform, you will pay the lowest exchange fees on your transaction and don’t have to compromise your personal information. On top of that, all transactions will have 24/7 online support to ensure the utmost quality of service. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-payeer/">How to Buy Tether with Payeer USD [No KYC]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you already have a Payeer account, you can buy Tether with Payeer USD on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>. On CoinCannon platform, you will pay the lowest exchange fees on your transaction and don’t have to compromise your personal information. On top of that, all transactions will have 24/7 online support to ensure the utmost quality of service. Since the early days of crypto, Tether (USDT) has been so inevitably utilitarian that all of us have to use it. Basically, it is a stablecoin that we buy and sell to hedge against the market volatility. In this article, we will go over everything you need to buy Tether with Payeer USD on our platform.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/buy-cryptocurrencies-with-payeer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Buy Cryptocurrencies with Payeer</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Tether with Payeer?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange direction, you will need a verified and active Payeer account to make the payments. Plus, you will also need to have a secure crypto wallet that supports Tether (USDT). As for the CoinCannon, all you need is an email address since no KYC (know your customer) is mandatory. Having said that, there are many advantages for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. By signing up, you will take part in our monthly airdrops with multiple $100 gifts!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Tether (USDT)?</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to buy Tether USDT, let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/how-exchange-tether-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Tether to PayPal</a></p>
</blockquote>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Buy Tether with Payeer?</strong></h2>



<p>First and foremost, Payeer is considered an online digital wallet for better asset management. Be it crypto of fiat, the payment processor is quick, reliable and cheap. In that regard, in a short lifespan of almost 8 years, Payeer is now recognized as one of the very best amongst competitors. Payeer utilizes built-in payment services with giant financial services such as Mastercard, VISA and PayPal.</p>



<p>As of 2021, the Payeer has approximately 7 million users which can transfer funds to each other with extremely low fees. The strength however, lies in diversity. Payeer is far ahead of any similar platform in terms of scale of operation and diversity in supported payment methods. With more than 50 payment approaches, the Payeer wallet offers users various services in one place.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>To learn more about Payeer, continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-payeer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Payeer</a>?”.</p>
</blockquote>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Number One!</strong></h2>



<p>Here’s the deal, exchange platforms are plenty, but the good ones are hard to find. Essentially, what you should be looking for is good exchange rates, anonymity and of course reliability. While these three qualities sound obvious, it’s actually not that easy to find a platform that offers them all at once. With that, platforms often tend to compromise on one of these above-mentioned factors.</p>



<p>Here at CoinCannon, our goal is to provide the ultimate exchange experience. Subsequently, the platform offers all the three important characteristics together.</p>



<p>We respect our customer’s privacy by not asking for their personal information. The best way for anyone to protect their information is to not disclose them at all. In that regard, not having KYC or sign up is the best method.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the platform utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at all times. Our words sound too good? Just pay a visit to ranking websites such as BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>Lastly, according to Murphy’s law “anything that can go wrong will go wrong”. To stay ahead of any problems, we offer 24/7 customer support.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Buy Tether with Payeer USD?</strong></h2>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Step 1</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Select Payeer USD on the “I Give” field on the left and Tether (USDT) on the “I Get” field on the right.</li>



<li>Enter the desired amount for the exchange and wait for the site to calculate the amazing exchange rates!</li>



<li>Click “Exchange”</li>
</ol>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Step 2</strong></h3>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter your Tether Wallet address and E-mail address</li>



<li>Click “Exchange”</li>
</ol>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Step 3</h3>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Read the Information</li>



<li>Complete the CAPTCHA</li>



<li>Click “Exchange”</li>
</ol>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Step 4</h3>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>At this point, please check the transaction information and terms and conditions carefully.</li>



<li>You will be able to see the track id and CoinCannon Payeer account</li>



<li>Open your Payeer account, click on the account menu and copy the account number that begins by the letter “p” and paste it in the required field.</li>



<li>Go back to your Payeer account and send the exchange amount to CoinCannon Payeer account.</li>



<li>Once you have sent the exchange amount, go to the history menu on your Payeer account and copy the operation id for the payment. Then paste the operation id in the required field.</li>



<li>Kindly agree to the terms and conditions and click on “Pay Order.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the USDT to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-payeer/">How to Buy Tether with Payeer USD [No KYC]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-payeer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Tether to USDC (USD Coin)</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-tether-to-usdc/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-tether-to-usdc/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6218</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is this time to exchange Tether to USDC? USD Coin has been on a steady rise as the second biggest stablecoin in the market. For the most part, USDC has maintained better transparency about their mostly dollar-backed and liquid reserves. In the meantime, Tether (USDT) has proven to be reliable, but they have come short [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-tether-to-usdc/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange Tether to USDC (USD Coin)&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Is this time to exchange Tether to USDC? USD Coin has been on a steady rise as the second biggest stablecoin in the market. For the most part, USDC has maintained better transparency about their mostly dollar-backed and liquid reserves. In the meantime, Tether (USDT) has proven to be reliable, but they have come short when it comes to being transparent. Following the <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/ftx-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">collapse of FTX</a>, investors are now looking to convert Tether to USDC for a variety of reasons. In case you like to learn more about this, keep reading about Coinbase’s warning about <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/tether-usdt-coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Tether (USDT)</a>. Regardless, we will go over everything you need to know on how to exchange Tether to USDC on CoinCannon platform. And guess what, you get full anonymity, no added fees and 24/7 online support around these parts partner!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="Exchange Tether to USDC (USD Coin) on CoinCannon - USDT to USDC" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/DNdcxNkzbFg?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Tether to USDC?</strong></h2>



<p>This one’s easy! You need a crypto wallet to send and receive the digital assets. Thankfully, it’s quite a difficult job to find a crypto wallet that doesn’t support both USDT and USDC. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon. Want a good reason why? How about winning $100 ever month!</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Learn more about our <a href="https://hi.exchange/campaign/tether-giveaway" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Tether Giveaway</a></p>
</blockquote>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is USD Coin (USDC)?</strong></h2>



<p>USD Coin owns the world’s largest stablecoin industry ecosystem in the world. It is a cryptocurrency that is pegged to US dollar in terms of value. That means that each USCD will always be worth $1. Stablecoins are used as a hedge against inflation and volatility in the crypto market. However, they can also be used as an alternative way to hold assets on the blockchain network.</p>



<p>As good as stablecoins might sound, there has always been concern about the companies not being honest about their dollar reserve. Basically, for every 1 USDC the company issues, they must hold $1 in their accounts. As a matter of fact, there are rumors regarding some large companies not having the dollar equivalent of their stablecoin. If a solid reserve does not back a stablecoin, the currency will lose value and seriously damage the investor’s funds. In that regard, USD Coin aims to provide full transparency about their reserves.</p>



<p>USDC is managed by a consortium called Centre which is a part of the payment technology company Circle. Much like TrueUSD, they offer monthly attestation reports by Grant Thornton to ensure investors regarding their reserves. Where they differ from TrueUSD, is that TrueUSD only holds dollar in different accounts but USD Coin also holds other assets such as gold.</p>



<p>You can also exchange <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-usd-coin-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">USD Coin to PayPal</a> with very low exchange fees.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Is Tether USDT any Different?</strong></h2>



<p>In short, both USDC and USDT are basically the same idea. They are both stablecoins backed by a reserve of US dollar or liquid assets. Basically, for every Tether or USD Coin, their companies hold $1 in their reserve. Statistically speaking, Tether has never depegged from US Dollar. Furthermore, it is the oldest stablecoin to date with quite a solid reputation.</p>



<p>Before reading about how to convert Tether to USDC, let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon is Better!</strong></h2>



<p>Cryptocurrencies are a financial apparatus to maximize privacy and efficiency. Sadly, regulations have been severely disrupting the market as they compromise both.</p>



<p>CoinCannon seeks to be a platform that offers privacy and efficiency simultaneously while offering some of the most aggressive exchange rates in the market.</p>



<p>To make this happen, the platform does not require KYC or a sign up process. This way, all customers can easily make transactions without a possible compromise on their personal information.</p>



<p>However, privacy is a crucial element and not a luxury. In that regard, the platform offers some of the most competitive rates amongst all online exchanges. The rates are automatically determined utilizing an automated system and are updated as soon as change in value is detected.</p>



<p>Last but not least, by offering true 24/7 support, all customers will be in touch with the team in case anything goes unplanned.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Tether to USDC?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the homepage first, then select USDT (Tether) on the left field and USDC or on the right. Enter the amount you want to exchange and wait for the exchange rate to apply.</li>



<li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your USD Coin wallet details, email, and phone number.</li>



<li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li>Complete the captcha and click on “exchange” to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. At this point, you will have the CoinCannon wallet address to send the Tether to.&nbsp; After you have transferred your cryptocurrency, click on Pay Order button. Don’t forget to attach the screenshot for the USDT payment. your order will process swiftly.</li>



<li>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the USDC to your wallet ASAP.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-that-s-it"><strong>That’s it!</strong></h2>



<p>Just like that, you have now converted USDT to USDC. In general, crypto payments don’t take very long to process. Give it a few minutes and the USD Coin will be in your wallet quickly. In the meantime, you can follow up on your order using the Track ID provided for you. Simply enter the track id in the required section on homepage to see at which point your order is. Remember not to share your Track ID with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-tether-to-usdc/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange Tether to USDC (USD Coin)&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-tether-to-usdc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Tether to Webmoney WMZ [No KYC]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-tether-to-webmoney/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-tether-to-webmoney/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 07:39:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Webmoney WMZ]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5693</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you’re looking for WMZ, you can instantly exchange Tether to Webmoney on CoinCannon. Webmoney is an online system based in Russia and is a favorite among Forex traders. The transactions are quick and cheap. Furthermore, numerous online merchants accept WMZ for online purchases. In this article, we will go over how to exchange Webmoney [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-tether-to-webmoney/">How to Exchange Tether to Webmoney WMZ [No KYC]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you’re looking for WMZ, you can instantly exchange Tether to Webmoney on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>. Webmoney is an online system based in Russia and is a favorite among Forex traders. The transactions are quick and cheap. Furthermore, numerous online merchants accept WMZ for online purchases. In this article, we will go over how to exchange Webmoney to Tether on CoinCannon with full anonymity.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/how-exchange-webmoney-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Webmoney to PayPal</a></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Tether to Webmoney?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange direction, you will need a Webmoney account and a crypto wallet. Make sure that your WMZ account is verified in order to receive the deposit. Bear in mind that CoinCannon platform does not require KYC or sign up but there are many benefits for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Webmoney WMZ?</strong></h2>



<p>WebMoney is an online payment system and a comprehensive tool for online business operations. It was originally developed as a money transfer system for US dollars in Russia in 1998 and since then, nearly 40 million people from all over the globe have joined the program.</p>



<p>WebMoney provides digital currency purses that can hold popular national currencies. The payment platform provides a P2P credit purse, global payment solutions, retail services, local payment products, online billing, and direct integration with other global financial service providers. On top of that, a number of countries worldwide are currently working on WebMoney and consumers pay WebMoney for the services of different companies from Spain, Poland, and Belgium.</p>



<p>Continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-webmoney/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Webmoney</a>”.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Tether Used for?</strong></h2>



<p>To answer this question, we must first talk about what Tether is. To put it simply, Tether is a stablecoin. The term stablecoin refers to the stable value of the currency. To make that happen, the value of a stablecoin like Tether is pegged to a fiat currency which it represents. In case of Tether, it is pegged to US dollar. For every 1 Tether that is out there, there is $1 USD held by the company.</p>



<p>This stable value gives investors the opportunity to benefit from a blockchain based coin that does not fluctuate in value.</p>



<p>Furthermore, Tether simultaneously operates on two blockchains. ERC20 which is on Ethereum network and TRC20 that is on Tron network. Generally speaking, TRC20 Tether is much faster in transactions and maintains much lower transaction fees. We recommend you to use TRC20 as much as possible due to better performance.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p>Every exchange platform must maintain three important characteristics. Anonymity, affordability and reliability. We pride ourselves as a professional platform that offers all three.</p>



<p>For anonymity, CoinCannon requires no KYC or even a sign up process. The best way to protect your information is to not share them with anyone. And for that, we respect our customers and do not ask for their personal info.</p>



<p>As for affordability, CoinCannon utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. By doing so, we have managed to stay on top of the ranks on websites such as Bestchange and OkChanger.</p>



<p>Lastly, reliability is ensured for our customers with 24/7 online support. In case anything goes wrong, you will have our immediate support until the issue is resolved.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Tether to Webmoney WMZ?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Enter the homepage first, then select Tether (either TRC20 or ERC20) on the left field and Webmoney WMZ on the right. Enter the amount you want to exchange and wait for the exchange rate to apply.</li><li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Webmoney address details and email address.</li><li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li><li>Complete the captcha and click on “exchange” to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. At this point, you will have the CoinCannon wallet address to send the Tether to.&nbsp; After you have transferred your USDT, click on Pay Order button. Don’t forget to attach the screenshot for the Tether payment. your order will process swiftly.</li><li>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the Webmoney to your wallet ASAP.</li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Mission Complete!</strong></h2>



<p>Just like that, you have now exchanged Tether to Webmoney. In general, Webmoney payments don’t take very long to process. Give it a few minutes and the WMZ will be in your wallet quickly. In the meantime, you can follow up on your order using the Track ID provided for you. Simply enter the track id in the required section on homepage to see at which point your order is. Remember not to share your Track ID with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-tether-to-webmoney/">How to Exchange Tether to Webmoney WMZ [No KYC]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-tether-to-webmoney/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
