<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>DOT Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/dot/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 10:09:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>How to Buy Polkadot with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-polkadot-with-perfect-money/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-polkadot-with-perfect-money/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 11:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy Polkadot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perfect Money]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4387</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you’re looking to know how to buy Polkadot with Perfect Money look no further as we will provide a full 2024 guide and the best platform to make the exchange. DOT has been amongst the very best altcoins in the past two years. Utilizing a revolutionary idea as well as great leadership by Gavin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-polkadot-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy Polkadot with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you’re looking to know how to buy Polkadot with Perfect Money look no further as we will provide a full 2024 guide and the best platform to make the exchange. </p>



<p>DOT has been amongst the very best altcoins in the past two years. Utilizing a revolutionary idea as well as great leadership by Gavin Wood, the network is reaching new heights. </p>



<p>In this article, we will guide you on how to buy Polkadot with Perfect Money and to avoid sky-high exchange rates. Furthermore, you don’t have to share your personal information with the platform unlike big trading apps.</p>



<p>Get started right now, head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> to buy DOT.</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-1 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button is-style-outline is-style-outline--1"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-black-color has-text-color has-background has-link-color wp-element-button" href="http://www.hi.exchange/" style="background-color:#f49d3f">Buy <strong>DOT</strong> with <strong>Perfect Money</strong> Right Now!</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-buy-polkadot-with-perfect-money"><strong>Why Buy Polkadot with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>Perfect Money is an e-currency used for making payments on the internet. It is widely accepted as payment option by countless platforms. With Perfect Money, you can do a lot! Be it transferring funds to others or pay for goods and services. Or how about buying cryptocurrencies or even buying fiat currencies. It is a seriously popular payment method for online users. An additional capability is to loan and receipt issuance throughout the system.</p>



<p>The biggest downside of Perfect Money, however, is that you cannot cash Perfect money to your bank account on its website directly. For that, you will need a platform like CoinCannon to exchange your Perfect Money to PayPal and other e-currencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-buy-polkadot-with-perfect-money"><strong>How to Buy Polkadot with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>Here are the five easy steps to make the purchase:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 1 : </strong>Enter the homepage first, then select Perfect Money and Polkadot from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of DOT you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>



<li><strong>Step 2 : </strong>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Polkadot wallet details, email, and phone number.</li>



<li><strong>Step 3 : </strong>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li><strong>Step 4 : </strong>Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the Perfect Money gateway and make the payment to our Perfect Money account. Having transferred your Perfect Money to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>



<li><strong>Step 5 : </strong>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the Polkadot to your wallet ASAP.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-that-was-easy"><strong>That Was Easy!</strong></h2>



<p>The sales team will immediately process the exchange and make the DOT payment to your wallet. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-to-choose-jolixo"><strong>Why to choose CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p><a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> was found with the vision to create a solid exchange platform that offers everything the customers need. And the platform successfully dealt with all the challenges. Ideally speaking, an online exchange must offer privacy, efficiency and reliability altogether.</p>



<p>Cryptocurrencies are losing the anonymity as more and more institutions continue to sell user data to both regulators and the highest bidders. To prevent your data from getting in the wrong hands, the best method is to not share it with unnecessary platforms. In that regard, CoinCannon platform respects customer privacy by not asking for it at all. No KYC or sign up is mandatory on the website.</p>



<p>Protecting your privacy on the other hand is not a luxury. In that regard, it is not easy to find an exchange that offers both privacy and low exchange rates simultaneously. However, CoinCannon has managed to offer both at the same time. The exchange rates are competitive as you can see for yourself on ranking websites such as BestChange and OkChanger.</p>



<p>Last but not least, reliability is a proof of work that comes with experience. The platform offers 24/7 customer support to ensure all potential problems are immediately dealt with.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-polkadot-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy Polkadot with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-polkadot-with-perfect-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Polkadot with Payeer [Best Rates]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-polkadot-with-payeer/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-polkadot-with-payeer/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 07:19:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5943</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You will need a great exchanger to buy Polkadot with Payeer and CoinCannon is all you need. Thankfully, there are many reasons to invest in Polkadot (DOT) as it is one of the best long-term investments in the crypto sector. The internet of blockchains is connected to multiple different blockchains using various technologies. In that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-polkadot-with-payeer/">How to Buy Polkadot with Payeer [Best Rates]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>You will need a great exchanger to buy Polkadot with Payeer and <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is all you need. Thankfully, there are many reasons to invest in Polkadot (DOT) as it is one of the best long-term investments in the crypto sector. The internet of blockchains is connected to multiple different blockchains using various technologies. In that regard, Polkadot has always been the top of the spear when it comes to innovation. But, considering the intensity of the energy crisis we are facing today, Polkadot has a competitive edge that others don’t have. As of September 2022, <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/polkadot-dot-blockchain/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Polkadot (DOT)</a> is the most energy efficient blockchain In the world. With that, the network will surely stand the test of upcoming regulations concerned with energy consumption. Fortunately, you can buy Polkadot with Payeer on CoinCannon with no added fees in only a matter of minutes.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color"><a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/polkadot-dot-blockchain/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Polkadot to PayPal</a> [No KYC]</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Polkadot with Payeer?</strong></h2>



<p>For this direction, you will need to send Payeer USD and Receive DOT on your wallet. Therefore, you need a verified and active Payeer account with sufficient funds. Make sure that the exchange amount does not exceed your withdrawal limit. To receive DOT, you will need a reliable crypto wallet that supports Polkadot (DOT). As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon. Want a good reason why? How about winning $100 ever month!</p>



<p>Learn more about our <a href="https://hi.exchange/campaign/tether-giveaway">Tet</a><a href="https://hi.exchange/campaign/tether-giveaway" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">h</a><a href="https://hi.exchange/campaign/tether-giveaway">er Giveaway</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Polkadot?</strong></h2>



<p>And here we have yet another third generation blockchain network found by a previous Ethereum member. Initially, Gavin James Wood had a different vision in mind about the (PoS) algorithm. The final goal is to create an infrastructure to create a network of blockchains that are effortlessly communicating with each other.</p>



<p>The multiple blockchain approach provides a better cross-chain interoperability and easier communication. Gavin believes that a single blockchain network can never be complete and a multi-chain architecture will be much more efficient.</p>



<p>The DOT is the token for this multi-chain network. It is currently number 9 by market cap. With the first ICO in 2017, it managed to raise $145 million. Despite being relatively new, it has experienced a huge growth in popularity. DOT has had one of the most successful initial coin offerings in history, raising over 200 million in two ICOs, first one in 2017 and the other in 2020.</p>



<p>To learn everything about the network, continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-polkadot/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Polkadot</a>“</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Use Payeer?</strong></h2>



<p>First and foremost, Payeer is considered an online digital wallet for better asset management. Be it crypto of fiat, the payment processor is quick, reliable and cheap. In that regard, in a short lifespan of almost 8 years, Payeer is now recognized as one of the very best amongst</p>



<p>competitors. Payeer utilizes built-in payment services with giant financial services such as Mastercard, VISA and PayPal.</p>



<p>As of 2022, the Payeer has approximately 7 million users which can transfer funds to each other with extremely low fees. The strength however, lies in diversity. Payeer is far ahead of any similar platform in terms of scale of operation and diversity in supported payment methods. With more than 50 payment approaches, the Payeer wallet offers users various services in one place.</p>



<p>To learn more about Payeer, continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-payeer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Payeer?</a>”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>CoinCannon is an online exchange platform that offers three critical factors for customers. Privacy, Efficiency and Reliability are not an easy combination to find on the internet.</p>



<p>For privacy, the ultimate way to protect your personal information is to not disclose them at all. Unfortunately, a vast majority exchanges are now legally obliged to hand over user data to governments for tax purposes. CoinCannon does not require customers to go through KYC or a sign up process as a sign of respect for anonymity.</p>



<p>Efficiency for an exchange platform calls for competitive exchange rates and quick processing time for orders. To maximize results and minimize efforts, the platform utilizes an automated consensus algorithm to determine the best exchange rates.</p>



<p>Lastly, for reliability and customer satisfaction, CoinCannon offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Buy Polkadot with Payeer?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Enter the homepage first, then select Payeer USD and Polkadot (DOT) from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of DOT you will receive will automatically calculate.</li><li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Polkadot wallet details, email, and phone number.</li><li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li><li>Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the Payeer gateway and make the payment to our Payeer account. Having transferred your Payeer USD to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Success!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Polkadot to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-polkadot-with-payeer/">How to Buy Polkadot with Payeer [Best Rates]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-polkadot-with-payeer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polkadot (DOT) is the Greenest Blockchain</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/polkadot-dot-blockchain/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/polkadot-dot-blockchain/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 07:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5933</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Polkadot (DOT) clearly knows one or two things about the future of blockchain. In a world when a huge energy crisis is terrifyingly the governments, it’s time to put catalytic convertors on mining rigs. Arguably, a storm of regulatory actions is about to hit gas guzzling cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin. With that, the leading altcoin by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/polkadot-dot-blockchain/">Polkadot (DOT) is the Greenest Blockchain</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Polkadot (DOT) clearly knows one or two things about the future of blockchain. In a world when a huge energy crisis is terrifyingly the governments, it’s time to put catalytic convertors on mining rigs. Arguably, a storm of regulatory actions is about to hit gas guzzling cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin. With that, the leading altcoin by market cap is moving on to Proof of Stake mostly out of necessity. Considering the scale of Ethereum and its energy consumption, they simply can’t risk getting hurt by any new laws that will potentially limit their activities. Now, While Vitalik and his team are days away from the <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/ethereum-2-0-upgrade-date/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Ethereum merge</a>, they will have to pull a miracle to stay relevant. In the meantime, Polkadot (DOT) has remained the most <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/top-energy-efficient-blockhains/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">energy efficient blockchain</a>. Once again, proving that blockchain does not necessarily need to brutally consume our electricity to make the whales rich!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color"><a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a> on CoinCannon</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Get Ready for Winter</strong></h2>



<p>But Satoshi isn’t ready for winter. In fact, the best part about Nakamoto is all the conspiracy theories about him. With him gone, Bitcoin is left in the hands of modern day philosophers like <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/michael-saylor-steps-down/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Michael Saylor</a> who pathetically lost $1 billion and respectfully lost his CEO position in MicroStrategy. Another Bitcoin proponent is Jack Dorsey who is busy with Elon’s lawsuit and the great disaster of Twitter bots. To be honest, Bitcoin maximalists have no charismatic leader and of course no tendency to show flexibility. And perhaps, flexibility is all that gets crypto through these times of crisis.</p>



<p>Speaking of crisis, there’s a big one on the horizon as the European union is bracing for a heck ton of cold showers. Once laughing out loud at warnings of their overdependence to Russian gas, EU leaders are now facing the biggest energy shortage in the history of modern Europe. Talk about shooting yourself in the foot! With extreme measures to cut energy consumption, it’s hard to imagine EU letting BTC miners operate. But, the energy shortage and drought is happening all over the world. While this may be speculation, there is overwhelming amount of evidence signaling rocky roads ahead. A winter, to be exact. And in this period where politicians are promising swift action, he who is efficient, shall be pumping and smiling.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Polkadot (DOT)</strong></h2>



<p>Once again, Polkadot (DOT) network has come out on top as the greenest blockchain. This will surely please her majesty Greta Thunberg who knows everything about everything. Sarcasm aside, Polkadot has done an impressive job staying ahead of the curve.</p>



<p>According to new research by <a href="https://twitter.com/PolkadotInsider" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Polkadot Insider</a>, the DOT network consumes only 0.1 GWH. To put that in perspective, this is roughly about six US households on average. Impressively, this low fuel consumption is also accompanied by great scalability. In fact, the Tezos network consumes the same amount of energy but lags behind in scalability.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="1024" height="576" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Polkadot-DOT-1024x576.jpeg" alt="" class="wp-image-5935" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Polkadot-DOT-1024x576.jpeg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Polkadot-DOT-300x169.jpeg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Polkadot-DOT-768x432.jpeg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Polkadot-DOT-1536x864.jpeg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Polkadot-DOT.jpeg 1920w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>As for other networks, Algorand takes the third spot with 0.5 GWH while Cardano and Avalanche are next. At the moment, Bitcoin still remains as the tree killing, bird murdering diesel sipping king of all pollution with 89000 GWH consumption. And Ethereum, is supposed to reinvent itself by the end of September. We will keep you updated on how that goes.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/polkadot-dot-blockchain/">Polkadot (DOT) is the Greenest Blockchain</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/polkadot-dot-blockchain/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polkadot Network is the Most Energy Efficient Blockchain</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/polkadot-network-most-energy-efficient/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/polkadot-network-most-energy-efficient/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 08:38:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy Polkadot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Polkadot to PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4814</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Here is a statistic, the Bitcoin blockchain network consumes as much as 8.6 million times what the US average household uses in electricity. Now, nobody in their right mind can believe that this will go on without hard hitting regulations. To be honest, considering the power outages in so many countries due to Bitcoin mining, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/polkadot-network-most-energy-efficient/">Polkadot Network is the Most Energy Efficient Blockchain</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Here is a statistic, the Bitcoin blockchain network consumes as much as 8.6 million times what the US average household uses in electricity. Now, nobody in their right mind can believe that this will go on without hard hitting regulations. To be honest, considering the power outages in so many countries due to Bitcoin mining, people are turning against cryptocurrencies. Thankfully, altcoins are doing much better in terms of power consumption. On the other hand, Bitcoin maintains a massive dominance over the market. Hence, here is the conflict in our crypto story, Bitcoin is the old drunken king while altcoins are reaching for the crown. Amongst the gallant altcoins, the Polkadot network turns out to be the most energy efficient. In fact, the Polkadot network only consumes 6.6 times an average US household.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><span class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Buy Polkadot on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> to save the Planet!</span></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Polkadot Network Leads the Pack</strong></h2>



<p>According to a new <a href="https://www.carbon-ratings.com/dl/pos-report-2022" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">study</a> by Crypto Carbon Ratings Institute (CCRI), the Polkadot network consumes the least amount of electricity. In the meantime, Bitcoin remains the polluting champion while Ethereum is as always in the second position.</p>



<p>Based on the data, DOT consumes only 6.6 times as much as an average household in electricity. Clearly, the sophisticated twist on the proof-of-stake blockchain network is the reason why, Nonetheless, it turns out not all blockchain networks are made equal.</p>



<p>As for the next best options, Tezos, Avalanche, Algorand, Cardano and Solana are following DOT’s lead.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="557" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Power-1024x557.jpg" alt="Polkadot Network" class="wp-image-4816" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Power-1024x557.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Power-300x163.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Power-768x418.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Power.jpg 1208w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p><em>“An average US household consumes about 10,600 kWh per year and therefore, the least electricity consuming network Polkadot consumes about 6.6 times the electricity and the most electricity consuming network Solana about 200 times the electricity (U.S. Energy Information Administration, 2021. Bitcoin consumes much more electricity than any Proof of Stake system due to its Proof of Work consensus mechanism, resulting in the deployment of energy-intensive hardware.”</em></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Winter is Coming</strong></h2>



<p>Forget about what Cathie Wood and Michael Saylor and Pomp say about Bitcoin. Today, as of early 2022, the world is facing a huge energy crisis, environmental crisis, greenflation, record high gas and oil prices, historical supply-chain issues as well as multiple other lurking in the dark. Bitcoin mining goes against every effort to deal with all the above-mentioned issues. As Bitcoin grows in value, the volatility remains higher than ever. In that sense, a new wave of regulatory actions against BTC mining can seriously harm Bitcoin. Subsequently, a sharp plunge caused by regulations can also wipe out numerous innocent altcoins because of Bitcoin dominance.</p>



<p>The only remedy for the crypto market is in fact the highly efficient proof of stake algorithm. The Polkadot network maintains a good reputation in terms of reliability and scalability and now it is the most energy efficient. This news may not have a strong positive effect on DOT price but it is a significant achievement for the whole blockchain industry.</p>



<p>You can learn everything about Polkadot and its native token DOT on “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-polkadot/">What is Polkadot?</a>”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.okchanger.com/exchangers/jolixo" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">OkChanger</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. We are on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bestchange</a> and are always amongst the top exchanges.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/polkadot-network-most-energy-efficient/">Polkadot Network is the Most Energy Efficient Blockchain</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/polkadot-network-most-energy-efficient/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Polkadot to PayPal [Full Guide]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/how-to-exchange-polkadot-to-paypal-full-guide/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/how-to-exchange-polkadot-to-paypal-full-guide/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 06:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Polkadot to PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4230</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking to exchange Polkadot to PayPal on an online platform? This article provides a step-by-step guide on how to complete the process on the best exchange platform. Polkadot has been amongst the best performing cryptocurrencies in 2021. For all the fans out there, CoinCannon provides an amazing platform to exchange all your crypto and E-currencies. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/how-to-exchange-polkadot-to-paypal-full-guide/">How to Exchange Polkadot to PayPal [Full Guide]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking to exchange Polkadot to PayPal on an online platform? This article provides a step-by-step guide on how to complete the process on the best exchange platform. Polkadot has been amongst the best performing cryptocurrencies in 2021. For all the fans out there, CoinCannon provides an amazing platform to exchange all your crypto and E-currencies.</p>



<p>Jump right in the platform to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">exchange Polkadot to PayPal</a> or buy DOT.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Polkadot?</strong></h2>



<p>Polkadot is a unique blockchain network that allows the users to create their own blockchains.&nbsp; Essentially, it is trying to create a network of blockchains that are connected and interoperable. The goal is to create interoperability among blockchain networks. The network utilizes proof of stake algorithm and has been very successful.</p>



<p>To learn everything about <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-polkadot/">Polkadot network</a>, read our extensive review.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Exchange Polkadot to PayPal on CoinCannon</strong></h2>



<p>We all know how difficult it is to find a suitable exchange platform that meets all our demands. Truthfully, considering the bad publicity regarding cryptocurrencies, it is also hard to trust online platforms.</p>



<p>Furthermore, a vast majority of exchanges require KYC which is the opposite of why cryptocurrencies exist. Your personal information is your property and you should not have to disclose your private data to anyone. In that regard, no KYC is some sort of luxury at this point. A kind of luxury that will cost you in transaction fees.</p>



<p>Luckily, CoinCannon offers everything altogether. No KYC, no sign up process, yet the platform offers the most competitive exchange rates. You can monitor the best rates on websites such as <a href="http://www.bestchange.com/">BestChange</a> and <a href="http://www.okchanger.com/">OkChanger</a> to see it for yourselves.</p>



<p>And for the utmost convenience, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange to PayPal?</strong></h2>



<p>PayPal is at this point the number one financial platform for digital currencies. In terms of security of your assets, they provide great services. As compared with a bank, keeping money in PayPal account can save you some tax payments in the future. It is widely accepted as a payment method and simply makes a lot of sense. Having enjoyed incredible returns on your DOT investment, you can easily transfer the asset to your PayPal account.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Exchange Polkadot to PayPal Step-by-Step Guide</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>As you enter the Homepage on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a>. Select Polkadot on the left field and PayPal on the right one. Enter the exchange amount. You can see the exchange rate being applied to the amount and the USD amount you will receive.</li><li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your PayPal account details, email, and phone number.</li><li>Click on “Exchange one more time and you will be directed to a page to review your order.</li><li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li><li>On this step, please dedicate some time to read our terms and services and follow the instructions.</li><li>Transfer your DOT to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you.</li><li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li></ol>



<p>Having finished the steps, out team will make the exchange and send the PayPal USD to your account. The process does not take long. You can also read some of our exclusive news, opinion and analysis articles on <a href="http://www.blog.hi.exchange/">CoinCannon Blog</a> while your exchange is being processed.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/how-to-exchange-polkadot-to-paypal-full-guide/">How to Exchange Polkadot to PayPal [Full Guide]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/how-to-exchange-polkadot-to-paypal-full-guide/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polkadot Continues on Building Hype</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/polkadot-continues-on-building-hype/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/polkadot-continues-on-building-hype/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 07:53:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Parachain Auction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4163</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Polkadot reached an all-time high on November 3rd as anticipation for the parachain auctions grows. DOT climbed the ladder all the way up to $53 before going for a price correction at the time of writing this article. The parachain auctions allow developers to acquire funds for their projects within the community. Learn all about [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/polkadot-continues-on-building-hype/">Polkadot Continues on Building Hype</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Polkadot reached an all-time high on November 3<sup>rd</sup> as anticipation for the parachain auctions grows. DOT climbed the ladder all the way up to $53 before going for a price correction at the time of writing this article. The parachain auctions allow developers to acquire funds for their projects within the community. Learn all about the network is “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-polkadot/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Polkadot</a>”.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Polkadot Rising</strong></h2>



<p>Although DOT has not been having strong rallies lately, the gradual and persistent growth continues on. The upcoming parachain auctions have the investors excited as it is an industry-first technology that can be beneficial for both users and developers. We have previously called DOT as one of the best <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/top-5-altcoins-for-a-low-risk-investment/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">low-risk altcoin</a> candidates for investment.</p>



<p>Learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange Polkadot to PayPal</a> anonymously with the best possible exchange rate at any moment on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>.</p>



<p>DOT is up 30% in 7 days with a price of $52.8 at the time of writing this article. With a market cap of over $55 billion, DOT is currently ranked as 7<sup>th</sup> cryptocurrency. Data Provided by <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/polkadot" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinGecko</a>.</p>



<p>The growth is primarily caused by the possibility of implementing parachain auctions on the network. At this stage, a governing council must first approve the upgrade. However, by the looks of it, investors are rushing to join the party.</p>



<p>Renowned crypto analyst Michaël van de Poppe states that the hype and momentum revolving around DOT is a bullish sign for the price.</p>



<p>“There’s parachains coming up. There’s hype around Polkadot. Lots of momentum here. So where should you be buying Polkadot at this instance? And we have been discussing that in the updates previously, too. The entire green zone [$35 -$37] was the critical level that you preferably want to see Polkadot sustain.” Said Poppe on YouTube. &nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<p>Initially, Poppe is expecting the next target zones to be at $75 and then $115. These potential target areas are determined by the Fibonacci extension tool. An apparatus that the CoinCannon <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/category/altcoin-price-analysis/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">technical analysis</a> team uses regularly.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Parachain Auctions</strong></h2>



<p> The unique architecture allows the users to create their own blockchains. The secondary blockchains are called parachains. For a complete guide, read <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-polkadot/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">“What is Polkadot”</a>.</p>



<p>The parachain auctions allow DOT developers to simply select a parachain, register their projects on it and receive crowd loan funding for the project.</p>



<p>Essentially, if approved, the auctions can potentially fund useful projects that will benefit both sides of the fence.</p>



<p>In terms of utility, it is too early to comment on how the apparatus will perform. However, it is essentially the hype and momentum around a certain cryptocurrency that can cause rallies in short-term.</p>



<p>The auctions will go live with a total of 11. There will be one auction per week.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><a href="http://hi.exchange">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.okchanger.com/exchangers/jolixo">OkChanger</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. We are on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/">Bestchange</a> and are always amongst the top exchanges.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/polkadot-continues-on-building-hype/">Polkadot Continues on Building Hype</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/polkadot-continues-on-building-hype/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin, Cardano, Polkadot gain massive inflows</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/bitcoin-cardano-polkadot-gain-massive-inflows/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/bitcoin-cardano-polkadot-gain-massive-inflows/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 08:47:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4046</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin, Cardano and Polkadot have had massive institutional money inflows as top cryptocurrencies. The three managed to outperform all the rest in the third consecutive bullish weeks of October. This is all happening in a time when a vast majority of cryptocurrencies are approaching their ATH. You can learn more about ADA and Polkadot from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/bitcoin-cardano-polkadot-gain-massive-inflows/">Bitcoin, Cardano, Polkadot gain massive inflows</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Bitcoin, Cardano and Polkadot have had massive institutional money inflows as top cryptocurrencies. The three managed to outperform all the rest in the third consecutive bullish weeks of October. This is all happening in a time when a vast majority of cryptocurrencies are approaching their ATH.</p>



<p>You can learn more about <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-ada-a-guide-to-the-cardano-project/">ADA</a> and <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-polkadot/">Polkadot</a> from our articles.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Bitcoin, Cardano and Polkadot</strong></h2>



<p>The digital asset manager CoinShares revealed in their <a href="https://medium.com/coinshares/volume-51-digital-asset-fund-flows-weekly-c22873895a0b">weekly report</a>. As a surprise to no one, Bitcoin stood out on top. However, as bloggers would say, the second and third place might surprise you.</p>



<p>With a staggering total inflow of $80 million, about $70 million went into Bitcoin. It is exactly the 5<sup>th</sup> consecutive week of inflows for the lucky BTC.</p>



<p>On the other hand, Cardano (ADA) and Polkadot (DOT) were the ones amongst altcoins to stand behind Bitcoin. In the meantime, Ethereum had minor outflows which we will later discuss.</p>



<p>Cardano (ADA) had $2.7 million inflows as Polkadot performed better with $3.6 million inflows.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="872" height="731" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1-EHaTXGN1itvId9dc8FEcrA.png" alt="" class="wp-image-4047" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1-EHaTXGN1itvId9dc8FEcrA.png 872w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1-EHaTXGN1itvId9dc8FEcrA-300x251.png 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1-EHaTXGN1itvId9dc8FEcrA-768x644.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 872px) 100vw, 872px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Reason for This</strong></h2>



<p>Primarily, as the market remains bullish, it is only natural for top performers to gain more capital. Just this past week, CoinShares hit a record of assets under management thanks to the price appreciation and the inflows.</p>



<p>“<em>These inflows, combined with positive price action over the week, have pushed total assets under management (AuM) to US$72.3bn, their highest level on record, surpassing the previous record of US$71.6bn set in May this year.”</em> Says CoinShares.</p>



<p>However, as inflation keeps looming ahead, institutions are hedging against it with Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies. Read more about <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/as-inflation-grows-institutions-buy-bitcoin/">inflation and Bitcoin</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why not Ethereum</strong></h2>



<p>Simply speaking, Ethereum is not doing so well right now. High transaction fees and slower network as compared with the competition is primarily what is causing outflows.</p>



<p>There is an ironic story here somewhere as both Charles Hoskinson and Gavin Woods were Ethereum co-founders. To give you the daily dose of gossip here is what happened. They broke up with Ethereum (Vitalik Buterin) due to ideological differences. And now, both their projects are outperforming Ethereum.</p>



<p>On the other hand, Ethereum has promised us a total reformation. Ethereum 2.0 is expected to happen very soon. Until then, the network’s poor performance will likely cause minor outflows.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Buy and Sell Bitcoin, Cardano and Polkadot on CoinCannon</strong></h2>



<p><a href="http://hi.exchange">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.okchanger.com/exchangers/jolixo">OkChanger</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. We are on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/">Bestchange</a> and are always amongst the top exchanges.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/bitcoin-cardano-polkadot-gain-massive-inflows/">Bitcoin, Cardano, Polkadot gain massive inflows</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/bitcoin-cardano-polkadot-gain-massive-inflows/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is Polkadot?</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-polkadot/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-polkadot/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 08:11:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4030</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Polkadot is a unique blockchain network that allows the users to create their own blockchains.  Essentially, it is trying to create a network of blockchains that are connected and interoperable. The goal is to create interoperability among blockchain networks. The network utilizes proof of stake algorithm and has been very successful. If you are looking [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-polkadot/">What is Polkadot?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Polkadot is a unique blockchain network that allows the users to create their own blockchains.  Essentially, it is trying to create a network of blockchains that are connected and interoperable. The goal is to create interoperability among blockchain networks. The network utilizes proof of stake algorithm and has been very successful.</p>



<p>If you are looking to buy or sell DOT coin, you can <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/">learn how</a> to exchange DOT or other digital currencies with complete anonymity on <a href="http://hi.exchange">jolixo</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Content</strong></h2>



<ul class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Polkadot the Young</strong></li><li><strong>How the Polkadot Network Functions</strong></li><li><strong>Blocks and Chains Everywhere</strong></li><li><strong>Polkadot CoinCannon</strong></li><li><strong>The Blockchain Trilemma</strong></li><li><strong>DOT Coin</strong></li><li><strong>Buy and Sell Polkadot on CoinCannon</strong></li></ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Polkadot the Young</strong></h2>



<p>Initially found in 2016 and launched in 2020, Polkadot is another one of those cases where an Ethereum co-founder decided to walk down the road not taken. And much like <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-ada-a-guide-to-the-cardano-project/">ADA</a>, Gavin Wood was able to make waves in the industry with a revolutionary innovation. As of October 2021, Polkadot Coin is the 7<sup>th</sup> cryptocurrency by market cap, priced at $42. Considering the very young age, Polkadot has deep roots in the industry as a serious blockchain network. In a time period of less than two years, the network has fulfilled all of the advertised promises and is delivering astonishing results.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How the Polkadot Network Functions</strong></h2>



<p>Blockchain networks such as Ethereum allow the users to create their decentralized applications. Polkadot however, takes it a step further by allowing users to create their own blockchain network on the main network. This allows for the new blockchain to take advantage of the already existing security measures of the Polkadot blockchain. DApps on the other hand, require newly created security since they cannot have access to the main network’s security protocols.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Blocks and Chains Everywhere</strong></h2>



<p>The Polkadot network or in other terms the internet of blockchain networks contains two different blockchain types. The primary blockchains, or the main networks are called relay chain. The transactions are relay chains are permanent and they are limited in nature. They act as foundation for the user created blockchains to be built upon them. The second type or the user created blockchains are called parachains</p>



<p>Utilizing this smart design,parachains can be heavily customized, they have the benefit of having security protocols of the main network since day one. This witty structure allows for lower gas fees since there is far less need for computational horsepower .</p>



<p>On the other hand, the efficiency in design allows for more privacy as the user data is not on public networks.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Polkadot CoinCannon</strong></h2>



<p>Relays and parachains aside, the Polkadot network is certainly not shy. The relay can make CoinCannons into other networks such as Bitcoin and Ethereum using parachains. In that regard, they are able to interact and gain access to almost any blockchain they want. This design allows for a future of interoperability for blockchain networks. Certainly, it would be much appreciated in the future where the technology expands. In that case the need for communication and interoperability will surely increase. Furthermore, other blockchain networks can also benefit from these connecting CoinCannons.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Blockchain Trilemma</strong></h2>



<p>The blockchain trilemma suggest that creators must compromise by choosing two out of three essential qualities of decentralization, speed and security. We can see the Ethereum network dealing with high transaction fees and lower transaction speed. Or as of late, it turned out that despite the low fees and high transaction speed, the Solana network was very much centralized.</p>



<p>The interoperability strategy that the Polkadot proposes, can potentially deal with all the aforementioned issues. After all, if all blockchains networks unite, no one can defeat them.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>DOT Coin</strong></h2>



<p>As no blockchain network is complete without a native token, the DOT coin is the running blood in the veins. With a market cap of $42 billion, DOT is 7<sup>th</sup> in the ranks with a price of $42 according to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/polkadot-new/">CoinMarketCap</a>.</p>



<p>In terms of fundamental analysis, considering the utility of the network, it is a safe assumption to have a long position on DOT.</p>



<p>Think 1 million transactions per second, or transaction fees much lower than any other network. On top of that, you have a network that connects all other networks. The team behind the network has demonstrated that they can deliver. And with the fast pace developments of blockchain technology, Polkadot network is a great medium for both development and communication.</p>



<p>In that scenario, we are bullish on DOT.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Buy and Sell Polkadot on CoinCannon</strong></h2>



<p><a href="http://hi.exchange">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.okchanger.com/exchangers/jolixo">OkChanger</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. We are on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/">Bestchange</a> and are always amongst the top exchanges.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-polkadot/">What is Polkadot?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-polkadot/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
