<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Ripple Lawsuit Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/ripple-lawsuit/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 12:30:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Ripple Ordered to Disclose Financial Information Amid SEC Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/ripple-ordered-to-disclose-financial-information-amid-sec-lawsuit/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/ripple-ordered-to-disclose-financial-information-amid-sec-lawsuit/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Leyli Mamikhani]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 06:19:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple Lawsuit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=8202</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In response to a recent court order, Ripple faces the obligation to disclose further insights into the financial standing and transactions involving its native cryptocurrency, XRP. This mandate follows a request from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), with Judge Analiza Torres previously ruling that the dissemination of XRP tokens to organizations constituted an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ripple-ordered-to-disclose-financial-information-amid-sec-lawsuit/">Ripple Ordered to Disclose Financial Information Amid SEC Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="wp-block-jet-engine-section jet-section wp-block-jet-engine-section jet-section--layout-fullwidth"><div class="jet-section__content">
<p><strong>Key Points:</strong></p>



<ul style="background-color:#d3d5e9" class="has-background wp-block-list">
<li>Ripple ordered to disclose financial details and XRP sales following SEC request.</li>



<li>Judge ruled distribution of XRP tokens to organizations as &#8220;unlawful sale of securities.&#8221;</li>



<li>Ripple must submit 2022-2023 financial reports and XRP sales contracts.</li>



<li>Court approved SEC motion to compel Ripple&#8217;s compliance.</li>



<li>Ripple contested ruling, citing objections as &#8220;untimely&#8221; and &#8220;unnecessary.&#8221;</li>



<li>John Deaton proposed $10 million fine for Ripple.</li>



<li>Lawsuit&#8217;s outcome crucial for Ripple and XRP token, impacting market value.</li>



<li>XRP price declined from $3.40 to $0.41 in response to developments.</li>
</ul>
</div></div>



<p>In response to a recent court order, Ripple faces the obligation to disclose further insights into the financial standing and transactions involving its native cryptocurrency, XRP.</p>



<p> This mandate follows a request from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), with Judge Analiza Torres previously ruling that the dissemination of XRP tokens to organizations constituted an &#8220;unlawful sale of securities.&#8221; However, transactions involving XRP on exchanges and among retail traders were excluded from this classification.</p>



<p>Under the court order, Ripple is now required to furnish its financial reports spanning the years 2022-2023, alongside contracts pertaining to organizational sales of XRP. These disclosures aim to illuminate critical details such as revenue generated from token sales. </p>



<p>Ripple&#8217;s opposition to this ruling signals the onset of a legal confrontation.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full is-resized"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="977" height="397" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/xrp.png" alt="" class="wp-image-8206" style="width:812px;height:auto" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/xrp.png 977w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/xrp-300x122.png 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/xrp-768x312.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 977px) 100vw, 977px" /></figure>



<p>In a significant development within the ongoing lawsuit, U.S. District Judge Annalisa Torres has granted approval to the SEC&#8217;s motion, compelling Ripple to furnish additional financial statements covering the period from 2022 to 2023, along with agreements concerning &#8220;institutional sales&#8221; of XRP. </p>



<p>The SEC contends that this supplementary financial data is indispensable in determining suitable penalties and compensatory measures.</p>



<p>Despite Ripple&#8217;s objections, deeming the SEC&#8217;s requests as &#8220;untimely&#8221; and &#8220;unnecessary,&#8221; the court emphasizes the importance of this information for the litigation process. Notably, John Deaton, representing Pro-XRP holders, has recommended a fine of approximately $10 million for Ripple.</p>



<p> As the SEC gains access to further financial insights from Ripple, the lawsuit enters a pivotal juncture, carrying significant implications for both Ripple and the XRP token. Consequently, the XRP price has witnessed a notable decline, plummeting from its recent high of $3.40 to $0.41.</p>



<p><strong>Source:</strong> <a href="https://coinpedia.org/news/will-judge-torres-go-easy-on-ripple-experts-say-ripple-to-reaches-a-settlement-of-over-10-million/">coinpedia</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ripple-ordered-to-disclose-financial-information-amid-sec-lawsuit/">Ripple Ordered to Disclose Financial Information Amid SEC Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/ripple-ordered-to-disclose-financial-information-amid-sec-lawsuit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Update: Ripple Lawsuit Turns the Tide Against SEC</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/ripple-lawsuit-continues-as-sec-tries-to-cheat/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/ripple-lawsuit-continues-as-sec-tries-to-cheat/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 05:09:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple Lawsuit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4059</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Ripple lawsuit has been going on since 2020! The SEC has been doing their best to fight Ripple but Ripple Inc is a completely different entity than your average hedge fund bro. Honestly, SEC has a pretty extraordinary track record on winning legal cases. There are rumors flying around that SEC has only lost [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ripple-lawsuit-continues-as-sec-tries-to-cheat/">Update: Ripple Lawsuit Turns the Tide Against SEC</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Ripple lawsuit has been going on since 2020! The SEC has been doing their best to fight Ripple but Ripple Inc is a completely different entity than your average hedge fund bro. Honestly, SEC has a pretty extraordinary track record on winning legal cases. There are rumors flying around that SEC has only lost a handful of cases but it&#8217;s not true. Statistics aside, this time may be different for the commission. DeFi is definitely new territory for making legal cases and Ripple Inc is no ordinary DeFi platform. A new interview with Ripple CEO has shed light on the current situation. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">You can learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-ripple-xrp-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your Ripple to PayPal</a> on CoinCannon.</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Federal Judge Says No to SEC! (April 15)</h2>



<p>Recently, SEC made a request to withhold specific information in the form of internal email conversations regarding the Ripple lawsuit. However, a federal judge has turned down the request from U.S Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). </p>



<p>Judge Sarah Netburn made an order to SEC to surrender the relevant drafts and messages related to the case. More specifically, information concerning a 2018 speech from the former director of Corporate Finance Division William Hinman.</p>



<p>Why is it so important? Well, Hinman has apparently said in the speech that Ethereum (ETH) is not a security. And of course, SEC has alleged Ripple Inc for selling XRP as an unregistered security. And it seems that the almighty regulators has failed to stay on the same page on an internal level when it comes to cryptocurrencies. </p>



<p>Initially, Judge Netburn made the order in January but the SEC made an objection. Subsequently, Netburn denied the regulator&#8217;s motion to reconsider the order. But, she did provide a legal clarification. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">The Clarification (April 15)</h2>



<p>&#8220;<em>As discussed above, the question is whether any of the communications about, edits to, or comments on drafts of the Speech were not just related to specific deliberations facing the agency but comprised an ‘essential link’ in those deliberations. Having reviewed the documents, I find that, in general, agency staff communications about edits to the Speech—and the edits themselves—were not part of deliberations about how to communicate agency policy.</em></p>



<p><em>However, to the extent that there exist communications between staff discussing the Speech in the context of how it implicates other, separate agency deliberations—not deliberations about the content of the speech—the SEC may seek leave to redact those communications from its production. To give the SEC some guidance, comment 12 on page 6 of the Speech draft in Document J, which was submitted for in camera review, is the type of communication contemplated.”</em></p>



<p>At this point, SEC may appeal this decision which is of course a very likely decision. And of course, depending on which judge they get, this crucial piece of evidence can choose the fate of the Ripple Lawsuit. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Ripple lawsuit</strong> Delayed</h2>



<p>The SEC filed a lawsuit against Ripple Labs in December 2020 in an effort to prove XRP being an unregistered security. On the other side of the spectrum, many believe that the Ripple is a threat to the international banking system. With that in mind, the SEC is doing what they always did, protect the banking industry.</p>



<p>To make your life easier, you can read our unbiased guide into “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-ripple/">What is Ripple</a>”.</p>



<p>All the drama aside, the SEC <a href="https://www.crypto-law.us/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/SEC-Letter-Request-to-Extend-Discovery-and-Exhibits-10152021.pdf">requested</a> for an extra two months in order to gather evidence. The pre-trial discovery phase allows both parties to gather information and evidence to present in the court.</p>



<p>The SEC demanded the discovery phase to be extended until January 14<sup>th</sup> 2021 for “sufficient time to prepare rebuttal reports and depose a minimum of 14 expert witnesses.”</p>



<p>The Ripple Labs on the other hand called it an unfair request that prolongs the trial for Ripple Lawsuit.</p>



<p>“The SEC’s proposed deadline of January 14… would needlessly prolong discovery, despite both parties’ stated intention to resolve this litigation on an expedited timeline.” Says Ripple.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Ripple Army Be Mad!</strong></h2>



<p>Naturally, the latest request from SEC had the crypto supporters angry as it is interpreted as cheating. The SEC does not exactly have a great track record. Back in 2008, the SEC was the primary agency that could prevent the market crash by paying closer attention to the mortgage industry and the ridiculous CDOs (collateralized debt obligations).</p>



<p>We have previously <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/xrp-coin-predictions-where-is-ripple-headed/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">discussed</a> the details of the lawsuit and possible tactics the SEC could utilize.</p>



<p>The outspoken Attorney and crypto supporter Jeremy Hogan responded to the request on Twitter. He stated that granting this request would postpone the Ripple lawsuit to March or May of 2022. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">What&#39;s clear from this motion to extend discovery out 2 more months is that the SEC filed this $1.4 Billion dollar lawsuit without setting aside the resources to prosecute it.<br><br>IF the judge grants it, the main parts of the case won&#39;t be decided until March-May of &#39;22!<br><br>Thoughts? <a href="https://t.co/AKlwcup5YO">https://t.co/AKlwcup5YO</a> <a href="https://t.co/G7gU3R1vLo">pic.twitter.com/G7gU3R1vLo</a></p>&mdash; Jeremy Hogan (@attorneyjeremy1) <a href="https://twitter.com/attorneyjeremy1/status/1449352112064843777?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">October 16, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Update on Ripple Lawsuit (March 7, 2022)</h2>



<p>In a recent interview, Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse stated the the securities and exchange commission has a bumpy road ahead. Furthermore, Garlinghouse told Fox Business that the SEC essentially tricked them by changing their mind on XRP.</p>



<p> <em>“The irony there is like we were in the SEC’s office. I met with Chairman Clayton. I was meeting with commissioners. No one ever once said, ‘Hey we think XRP is a security.’ They looked backward and say, ‘Now we think it’s all security.’ That’s a hard argument.”</em></p>



<p>Interestingly, Garlinghouse mentioned a point that may very well be the case for SEC. He argued that the SEC really does not know how &#8220;<em>Crypto Really Works</em>&#8221; and basically they are in uncharted territory. This lack of understanding has lawmakers baffled and of course caused platforms quite a bit of damage. </p>



<p><em>“I think it does a disservice to responsible actors like Ripple who are working with governments, with sanctions. Everything that is enforced from a sanction point of view through fiat currency, anything that Ripple does is enforced from the state in the exact same way. There’s no different level playing field. And in some ways, I heard Senator Warren saying things that felt like its holding crypto to a different standard, for example, expecting a blanket ban of all crypto in some of these countries… Well, you can still use PayPal. You can still use some of these other things, and I don’t think we should treat them differently.”</em></p>



<p>According to garlinghouse, Gary Gensler is still against crypto and seeing it as wild west. At this point, it is difficult to predict how much longer the case could take. Having said that, despite SEC&#8217;s resilience, Ripple may have a solid chance of winning their case. Primarily, the nature of this lawsuit is unfamiliar to both lawmakers and the SEC. In that regard, the odds are against SEC.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Buy and Sell XRP Coin on <strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><a href="http://hi.exchange">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.okchanger.com/exchangers/jolixo">OkChanger</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. We are on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/">Bestchange</a> and are always amongst the top exchanges.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ripple-lawsuit-continues-as-sec-tries-to-cheat/">Update: Ripple Lawsuit Turns the Tide Against SEC</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/ripple-lawsuit-continues-as-sec-tries-to-cheat/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
