<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Visa Card Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/visa-card/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 13:22:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Instant Credit Card for Online Shopping [No KYC]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/credit-card-for-online-shopping/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/credit-card-for-online-shopping/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 08:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[credit card]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Master Card]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prepaid Mastercard]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prepaid paypal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prepiad visa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Visa Card]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=8708</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What if I told you that you don&#8217;t need a credit card for online shopping? All you need is someone with a credit card to pay for you right? then, CoinCannon does the work for you!At this point, you might think that you want a virtual prepaid credit card for online shopping but that&#8217;s complicated [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/credit-card-for-online-shopping/">Instant Credit Card for Online Shopping [No KYC]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>What if I told you that you don&#8217;t need a credit card for online shopping? All you need is someone with a credit card to pay for you right? then, CoinCannon does the work for you!<br>At this point, you might think that you want a virtual prepaid credit card for online shopping but that&#8217;s complicated too. <strong>The alternative we offer is instant, anonymous and comes with much lower rates than a prepaid card</strong>. Here&#8217;s how it works.</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>You want to buy something online that requires a credit card for online shopping.</li>



<li>You come to CoinCannon, send whatever currency you have like Tether USDT, Bitcoin or 100+ different currencies. Then you send us the link for your online shopping.</li>



<li>CoinCannon will go to the link and make the payment for you and send you the payment confirmation.</li>
</ul>



<p>Oh and by the way, it&#8217;s instant, with no KYC and comes with 24/7 support!</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-1 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button"><a class="wp-block-button__link wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/En/solutions/online-payment?cur_from=USDTTRC20&amp;cur_to=PPUSDI">Start Now!</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-limitless-virtual-credit-card">The Limitless Virtual Credit Card </h2>



<p>It&#8217;s a pain in the bottom I tell ya! having to buy virtual credit card, going through all the different websites to find the best one, filling out the forms, paying all the extra money for a card you can only use once. Not to mention all the time you waste on purchasing a card for purchasing another thing on the internet! ain&#8217;t nobody got time for that! </p>



<p>Here&#8217;s what we do instead, we can be your cool friend who already has a credit card. All you gotta do is pay your buddy CoinCannon however you like and we&#8217;ll handle the payment stuff like a champ! </p>



<p>That way, you don&#8217;t have to waste time or money and the capitalism gods will be happy! </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-not-to-apply-for-an-online-credit-card-for-shopping">How not to Apply for an Online Credit Card for Shopping</h2>



<p>Honestly, purchasing a virtual credit card is a big hassle for all of us. If you live in a country where payments processors like PayPal, Visa or MasterCard do not provide services, then the trouble gets bigger! </p>



<p>But thanks to our frightening genius, your online purchases will have no limits and shall remain liberated from all the bounds of regulatory nightmare that consumes our ever-expanding financial limbo scattered around the vast expanse of the interweb! (the author has studied literature and wanted to showcase his poetic abilities with this paragraph!) </p>



<p>Whether you&#8217;re a freelancer or representing a business, having an quick and easy alternative for the expensive online credit card for shopping will give you a boost in performance. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-credit-card-fees-vs-jolixo-fees">Credit Card Fees Vs. CoinCannon Fees</h2>



<p>Here&#8217;s a quick look at the associated fees for a prepaid visa card:</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Activation Fee</strong> – Typically $3 to $10.</li>



<li><strong>Purchase Fee</strong> – Some retailers charge an extra fee, usually around $5 to $15.</li>



<li><strong>Exchange Rate Fees</strong> – If you&#8217;re buying it with crypto or a foreign currency, you might pay an extra 1-5%.</li>



<li><strong>Third-Party Markup</strong> – If you’re buying from a reseller, they may charge an additional percentage.</li>
</ol>



<p>If you’re buying from an official provider like Vanilla Visa or a bank, you might just pay the face value ($1,000) plus a small fee. If you&#8217;re getting it from a crypto exchange or P2P seller, expect to pay more, sometimes up to <strong>5-15% extra</strong>.</p>



<p>Considering the fees mentioned above, when utilizing CoinCannon, you will ONLY pay a 1% to 5% exchange fee and there will be <strong>no extra charge at all</strong>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-do-i-need-to-purchase-a-prepaid-card">What do I Need to Purchase a Prepaid Card?</h2>



<p>When purchasing a credit card for online shopping, you will have to sign up on the retailer&#8217;s website and disclose lots and lots of your personal information. mind you, the process can take days! As mentioned before, there are many countries in which online credit cards or even prepaid cards do not provide services. Other than that, paying for the credit card does also require a specific currency. In that regard, you might have to exchange what you already have beforehand and pay for yet another exchange fee.</p>



<p>By using CoinCannon, you will not share any personal information and basically do not need anything to make the purchase. CoinCannon supports 100+ currencies for payment and will instantly make your purchase. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-24-7-online-support">24/7 Online Support</h2>



<p>In order to make sure everything goes as planned, CoinCannon provides online support available all day, everyday. So get started now and Enjoy Online Payments like never before!</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/credit-card-for-online-shopping/">Instant Credit Card for Online Shopping [No KYC]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/credit-card-for-online-shopping/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
