<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Buy USDT Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/buy-usdt/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 08:16:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Buy Tether USDT with Lowest Possible Fees on CoinCannon</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-usdt/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-usdt/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 08:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy USDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5640</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Whether you’re a trader or an avid investor, there are solid reasons to buy Tether USDT. As of 2023, USDT has a lot more utility than what it had only a few years ago. Basically, the dollar-pegged cryptocurrency is accepted in a wide variety of online platforms for shopping and services. Today, you can pay [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-usdt/">Buy Tether USDT with Lowest Possible Fees on CoinCannon</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Whether you’re a trader or an avid investor, there are solid reasons to buy Tether USDT. As of 2023, USDT has a lot more utility than what it had only a few years ago. Basically, the dollar-pegged cryptocurrency is accepted in a wide variety of online platforms for shopping and services. Today, you can pay for almost anything from flight bookings to a Cappuccino with Tether. On the other hand, Forex traders have also been using Tether as a medium on their traders. However, if you are looking to Buy Tether USDT, not all exchanges are equal! For that, you will need an exchange platform that offers the best exchange rates. And more importantly, a platform who doesn’t sell you private data to the highest bidder! Fortunately, <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is the ultimate OTC platform to buy Tether USDT from and this article will tell you why.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Learn <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-crypto-to-tether/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Crypto to Tether</a> on CoinCannon</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-tether-usdt"><strong>What is Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to buy Tether USDT, let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>Learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/how-exchange-tether-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange Tether USDT to PayPal</a></p>
</blockquote>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-should-i-buy-tether-usdt"><strong>Why Should I Buy Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>Owning Tether is basically like having digital dollars in your pocket, only without needing a bank. Recently, there has been lots of talk about how we do not actually own our money when they are in the banks. Digital money means that banks and governments can freeze our access to our funds for whatever reason they seem justifiable. In 2022, Canada denied protestor’s access to their bank accounts and cut out their rightful ownership of their capital. Such incidents are not rare and should be treated seriously. But, political motivation aside, banks are not always available. For example, we saw how the Ukrainians lost all their capital within the banks as soon as the war started. Once again, the decentralized nature of cryptocurrencies meant that the bankless were the lucky ones in that incident.</p>



<p>Thankfully, the list of online merchants and service providers who accept Tether USDT is sufficiently long. With Tether, you can make purchases online and in person almost anywhere. Be it through a direct wallet address or a payment gateway, USDT is as good as cash these days.</p>



<p>Lastly, USDT offers an extra layer of protection for the user with blockchain technology. As a cryptocurrency, it is anonymous and secure. On top of that, the transaction fees for Tether are very low, as long as you use the TRC20 variant based on the Tron network.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-where-do-i-buy-usdt"><strong>Where Do I Buy USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>Every exchange platform must maintain three important characteristics. Anonymity, affordability and reliability. We pride ourselves as a professional platform that offers all three.</p>



<p>For anonymity, <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> requires no KYC or even a sign up process. The best way to protect your information is to not share them with anyone. And for that, we respect our customers and do not ask for their personal info.</p>



<p>As for affordability, CoinCannon utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. By doing so, we have managed to stay on top of the ranks on websites such as Bestchange and OkChanger.</p>



<p>Lastly, reliability is ensured for our customers with 24/7 online support. In case anything goes wrong, you will have our immediate support until the issue is resolved.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-is-tether-a-safe-investment"><strong>Is Tether a Safe Investment?</strong></h2>



<p>Generally speaking, Tether has remained reliable and solid since the initial introduction. While there are numerous controversies, USDT has been consistently stern as an investment option. Most of the controversies come from a lack of transparency regarding Tether’s funds. Basically, there is not much information about what funds are actually held by Tether to back their stablecoin. However, Tether has assured investors that they hold the majority of their funds in the form of cash and investors have no reason to worry.</p>



<p>Regardless, there is still some risk associated with stablecoins, especially after the Terra USD collapse. With that, while there is no clear and imminent risk, make sure to thread carefully and keep some of the risks in mind before you buy Tether USDT.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-usdt/">Buy Tether USDT with Lowest Possible Fees on CoinCannon</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-usdt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Tether with Payeer USD [No KYC]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-payeer/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-payeer/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 11:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy USDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5774</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you already have a Payeer account, you can buy Tether with Payeer USD on CoinCannon. On CoinCannon platform, you will pay the lowest exchange fees on your transaction and don’t have to compromise your personal information. On top of that, all transactions will have 24/7 online support to ensure the utmost quality of service. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-payeer/">How to Buy Tether with Payeer USD [No KYC]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you already have a Payeer account, you can buy Tether with Payeer USD on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>. On CoinCannon platform, you will pay the lowest exchange fees on your transaction and don’t have to compromise your personal information. On top of that, all transactions will have 24/7 online support to ensure the utmost quality of service. Since the early days of crypto, Tether (USDT) has been so inevitably utilitarian that all of us have to use it. Basically, it is a stablecoin that we buy and sell to hedge against the market volatility. In this article, we will go over everything you need to buy Tether with Payeer USD on our platform.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/buy-cryptocurrencies-with-payeer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Buy Cryptocurrencies with Payeer</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Tether with Payeer?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange direction, you will need a verified and active Payeer account to make the payments. Plus, you will also need to have a secure crypto wallet that supports Tether (USDT). As for the CoinCannon, all you need is an email address since no KYC (know your customer) is mandatory. Having said that, there are many advantages for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. By signing up, you will take part in our monthly airdrops with multiple $100 gifts!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Tether (USDT)?</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to buy Tether USDT, let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/how-exchange-tether-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Tether to PayPal</a></p>
</blockquote>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Buy Tether with Payeer?</strong></h2>



<p>First and foremost, Payeer is considered an online digital wallet for better asset management. Be it crypto of fiat, the payment processor is quick, reliable and cheap. In that regard, in a short lifespan of almost 8 years, Payeer is now recognized as one of the very best amongst competitors. Payeer utilizes built-in payment services with giant financial services such as Mastercard, VISA and PayPal.</p>



<p>As of 2021, the Payeer has approximately 7 million users which can transfer funds to each other with extremely low fees. The strength however, lies in diversity. Payeer is far ahead of any similar platform in terms of scale of operation and diversity in supported payment methods. With more than 50 payment approaches, the Payeer wallet offers users various services in one place.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>To learn more about Payeer, continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-payeer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Payeer</a>?”.</p>
</blockquote>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Number One!</strong></h2>



<p>Here’s the deal, exchange platforms are plenty, but the good ones are hard to find. Essentially, what you should be looking for is good exchange rates, anonymity and of course reliability. While these three qualities sound obvious, it’s actually not that easy to find a platform that offers them all at once. With that, platforms often tend to compromise on one of these above-mentioned factors.</p>



<p>Here at CoinCannon, our goal is to provide the ultimate exchange experience. Subsequently, the platform offers all the three important characteristics together.</p>



<p>We respect our customer’s privacy by not asking for their personal information. The best way for anyone to protect their information is to not disclose them at all. In that regard, not having KYC or sign up is the best method.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the platform utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at all times. Our words sound too good? Just pay a visit to ranking websites such as BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>Lastly, according to Murphy’s law “anything that can go wrong will go wrong”. To stay ahead of any problems, we offer 24/7 customer support.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Buy Tether with Payeer USD?</strong></h2>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Step 1</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Select Payeer USD on the “I Give” field on the left and Tether (USDT) on the “I Get” field on the right.</li>



<li>Enter the desired amount for the exchange and wait for the site to calculate the amazing exchange rates!</li>



<li>Click “Exchange”</li>
</ol>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Step 2</strong></h3>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter your Tether Wallet address and E-mail address</li>



<li>Click “Exchange”</li>
</ol>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Step 3</h3>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Read the Information</li>



<li>Complete the CAPTCHA</li>



<li>Click “Exchange”</li>
</ol>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Step 4</h3>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>At this point, please check the transaction information and terms and conditions carefully.</li>



<li>You will be able to see the track id and CoinCannon Payeer account</li>



<li>Open your Payeer account, click on the account menu and copy the account number that begins by the letter “p” and paste it in the required field.</li>



<li>Go back to your Payeer account and send the exchange amount to CoinCannon Payeer account.</li>



<li>Once you have sent the exchange amount, go to the history menu on your Payeer account and copy the operation id for the payment. Then paste the operation id in the required field.</li>



<li>Kindly agree to the terms and conditions and click on “Pay Order.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the USDT to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-payeer/">How to Buy Tether with Payeer USD [No KYC]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-payeer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
