<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Perfect Money Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/perfect-money/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 08:49:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>How to Create Perfect Money E-Voucher [Including Video]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/create-perfect-money-e-voucher/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/create-perfect-money-e-voucher/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 11:36:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[e-currency to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Videos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Payment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-Voucher]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perfect Money]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[voucher]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4954</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Boomer terms, a Perfect Money E-Voucher is basically like a bank check but digital. Basically, users can create a Perfect Money E-Voucher with a certain value and use it as a redeemable transaction for a variety of purposes. Thankfully, these vouchers are instantly redeemable via a code and a pin which could easily be [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/create-perfect-money-e-voucher/">How to Create Perfect Money E-Voucher [Including Video]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In Boomer terms, a Perfect Money E-Voucher is basically like a bank check but digital. Basically, users can create a Perfect Money E-Voucher with a certain value and use it as a redeemable transaction for a variety of purposes. Thankfully, these vouchers are instantly redeemable via a code and a pin which could easily be sent via SMS, E-mail or any form of online messaging. In terms of use cases, the applications are endless since it is an accessible form of payment for both the sender and the receiver. In this article, we will go through everything you need to know about the Perfect Money E-Voucher and how to make one instantly.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="How to Create Perfect Money Voucher on CoinCannon [No KYC]" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/iDN2gUZgupw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<div class="wp-block-buttons alignwide is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-1 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-text-align-center wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/En/solutions/buy-sell-perfectmoney-voucher?cur_from=USDTTRC20&amp;cur_to=PPUSD">Buy Perfect Money Voucher Now!</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-perfect-money-e-voucher"><strong>Perfect Money E-Voucher</strong></h2>



<p>it is easy, it is affordable and it is anonymous a lot like the CoinCannon Platform! The E-Voucher is the solution to some of our biggest payment problems. The electronic voucher is a method of payment that is redeemable instantly. The user pays a specific amount of funds and creates a voucher. Then, the information for the voucher can easily be delivered to the receiver and they will have the choice to redeem the payment anytime they want. Much like a gift card or a bank check, the voucher will hold the value permanently since the payment has already been made.</p>



<p>Although there are numerous applications for this, here are some of the common utilities:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>You can create a voucher to make payments when you don’t have access to your Perfect Money account.</li>



<li>Perfect Money E-Voucher is a good method of payment when you don’t carry cash or traveling abroad.</li>



<li>As a service provider, users can receive vouchers if they don’t wish to reveal their account address.</li>



<li>Send your loved ones a voucher instead of a gift card</li>
</ul>



<p>Perfect Money E-Voucher does not cost users a lot of money to make! You can simply go to CoinCannon and create your voucher immediately with the lowest fees. On top of that, unlike a majority of exchanges, CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or even a sign up process. It is truly fast and truly anonymous.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-perfect-money"><strong>What is Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>Perfect Money is an e-currency for making payments on the internet. It is widely accepted as payment option by countless platforms. With Perfect Money, you can do a lot! Be it transferring funds to others or pay for goods and services. Or how about buying cryptocurrencies or even buying fiat currencies. It is a seriously popular payment method for online users. An additional capability is to loan and receipt issuance throughout the system.</p>



<p>The biggest downside of Perfect Money, however, is that you cannot cash Perfect money to your bank account on its website directly. For that, you will need a platform like CoinCannon to exchange your Perfect Money to PayPal and other e-currencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-jolixo-does-it-better"><strong>CoinCannon Does It Better!</strong></h2>



<p>Essentially, you need three primary qualities in an ideal exchange platform. Anonymity, good rates and reliability. The CoinCannon team consists of traders and professionals who have felt the need for an ideal exchange and pursued their vision.</p>



<p>First and foremost, all users need to protect their personal information especially when it comes down to financial transactions. Unfortunately, a vast majority of exchange apps and platforms make massive profits off of selling user data. Best case scenario, they are legally bound to disclose user information with national authorities for any reason. In that regard, the best method to protect your privacy is to not disclose them with anyone at all. CoinCannon does not require customers to go through KYC (know your customer) or even a mandatory sign up. In that regard, it is simply as safe as one can get making an exchange.</p>



<p>On the other hand, privacy is not a reason to pay more on your exchange. With that in mind, the platform offers some of the most competitive exchange rates you can find anywhere. Don’t take our word for it. You can simply pay a visit to ranking websites such as BestChange or OkChanger and see compare our rates with others.</p>



<p>Last but not least, not everything goes as planned in the digital world. Subsequently, the platform provides true online 24/7 customer support for the users.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-create-perfect-money-e-voucher"><strong>How to Create Perfect Money E-Voucher?</strong></h2>



<ol style="list-style-type:1" class="wp-block-list">
<li>Enter the homepage first, then select Perfect Money and Perfect Money E-Voucher from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, you will see how much USD will be in your E-Voucher</li>



<li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your E-mail address and phone number (it’s optional).</li>



<li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li>Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the Perfect Money gateway and make the payment to our Perfect Money account. Having transferred your Perfect Money to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>



<li>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will create your e-voucher and send the details to you via E-mail.</li>
</ol>



<p>Keep in mind, you can also see your E-Voucher information in Admin description section after that your order completed by using your Track ID. Also, if your Perfect Money account <strong>isn&#8217;t</strong> <strong>verified</strong>, your <strong>send fee will be 1.99</strong> %</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done"><strong>Done</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will immediately process your order and create your e-voucher. The process will take between 3 to 20 minutes. In the meantime, you can spend some time reading some of the latest crypto news on CoinCannon Blog. Remember that our support team is online 24/7 to answer all your questions.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/create-perfect-money-e-voucher/">How to Create Perfect Money E-Voucher [Including Video]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/create-perfect-money-e-voucher/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Polkadot with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-polkadot-with-perfect-money/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-polkadot-with-perfect-money/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 11:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy Polkadot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perfect Money]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4387</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you’re looking to know how to buy Polkadot with Perfect Money look no further as we will provide a full 2024 guide and the best platform to make the exchange. DOT has been amongst the very best altcoins in the past two years. Utilizing a revolutionary idea as well as great leadership by Gavin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-polkadot-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy Polkadot with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you’re looking to know how to buy Polkadot with Perfect Money look no further as we will provide a full 2024 guide and the best platform to make the exchange. </p>



<p>DOT has been amongst the very best altcoins in the past two years. Utilizing a revolutionary idea as well as great leadership by Gavin Wood, the network is reaching new heights. </p>



<p>In this article, we will guide you on how to buy Polkadot with Perfect Money and to avoid sky-high exchange rates. Furthermore, you don’t have to share your personal information with the platform unlike big trading apps.</p>



<p>Get started right now, head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> to buy DOT.</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-2 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button is-style-outline is-style-outline--1"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-black-color has-text-color has-background has-link-color wp-element-button" href="http://www.hi.exchange/" style="background-color:#f49d3f">Buy <strong>DOT</strong> with <strong>Perfect Money</strong> Right Now!</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-buy-polkadot-with-perfect-money"><strong>Why Buy Polkadot with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>Perfect Money is an e-currency used for making payments on the internet. It is widely accepted as payment option by countless platforms. With Perfect Money, you can do a lot! Be it transferring funds to others or pay for goods and services. Or how about buying cryptocurrencies or even buying fiat currencies. It is a seriously popular payment method for online users. An additional capability is to loan and receipt issuance throughout the system.</p>



<p>The biggest downside of Perfect Money, however, is that you cannot cash Perfect money to your bank account on its website directly. For that, you will need a platform like CoinCannon to exchange your Perfect Money to PayPal and other e-currencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-buy-polkadot-with-perfect-money"><strong>How to Buy Polkadot with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>Here are the five easy steps to make the purchase:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 1 : </strong>Enter the homepage first, then select Perfect Money and Polkadot from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of DOT you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>



<li><strong>Step 2 : </strong>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Polkadot wallet details, email, and phone number.</li>



<li><strong>Step 3 : </strong>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li><strong>Step 4 : </strong>Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the Perfect Money gateway and make the payment to our Perfect Money account. Having transferred your Perfect Money to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>



<li><strong>Step 5 : </strong>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the Polkadot to your wallet ASAP.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-that-was-easy"><strong>That Was Easy!</strong></h2>



<p>The sales team will immediately process the exchange and make the DOT payment to your wallet. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-to-choose-jolixo"><strong>Why to choose CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p><a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> was found with the vision to create a solid exchange platform that offers everything the customers need. And the platform successfully dealt with all the challenges. Ideally speaking, an online exchange must offer privacy, efficiency and reliability altogether.</p>



<p>Cryptocurrencies are losing the anonymity as more and more institutions continue to sell user data to both regulators and the highest bidders. To prevent your data from getting in the wrong hands, the best method is to not share it with unnecessary platforms. In that regard, CoinCannon platform respects customer privacy by not asking for it at all. No KYC or sign up is mandatory on the website.</p>



<p>Protecting your privacy on the other hand is not a luxury. In that regard, it is not easy to find an exchange that offers both privacy and low exchange rates simultaneously. However, CoinCannon has managed to offer both at the same time. The exchange rates are competitive as you can see for yourself on ranking websites such as BestChange and OkChanger.</p>



<p>Last but not least, reliability is a proof of work that comes with experience. The platform offers 24/7 customer support to ensure all potential problems are immediately dealt with.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-polkadot-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy Polkadot with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-polkadot-with-perfect-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy DOGE with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-doge-with-perfect-money/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-doge-with-perfect-money/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 08:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy DOGE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perfect Money]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4340</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If your favorite breed of dog is Shiba Inu, then Dogecoin is right up your alley. In this article, we will provide a step-by-step guide on how to buy DOGE with Perfect Money without having to go through KYC or sign up. DOGE is the king of all meme coins but in terms of scalability [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-doge-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy DOGE with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If your favorite breed of dog is Shiba Inu, then Dogecoin is right up your alley.</p>



<p>In this article, we will provide a step-by-step guide on<strong> how to buy DOGE with Perfect Money</strong> without having to go through KYC or sign up.</p>



<p> DOGE is the king of all meme coins but in terms of scalability and transaction fees, it is just as good as the others.</p>



<p>If you’re thinking of buying Dogecoin, CoinCannon is one of the best platforms you can find.</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-3 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button is-style-outline is-style-outline--2"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-black-color has-text-color has-background has-link-color wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/" style="background-color:#f49d3f">Buy <strong>DOGE</strong> with <strong>Perfect Money</strong> Right Now!</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-buy-doge-with-perfect-money"><strong>Why Buy DOGE with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>Perfect Money is an e-currency used for making payments on the internet. It is widely accepted as payment option by countless platforms. With Perfect Money, you can do a lot! Be it transferring funds to others or pay for goods and services. Or how about buying cryptocurrencies or even buying fiat currencies. It is a seriously popular payment method for online users. An additional capability is to loan and receipt issuance throughout the system.</p>



<p>The biggest shortcoming of Perfect Money is that you cannot cash Perfect money to your bank account on its website directly. For that, you will need a platform like CoinCannon to exchange your Perfect Money to PayPal and other e-currencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-buy-doge-with-perfect-money"><strong>How to Buy DOGE with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>All you have to do is go through five simple steps.</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 1:</strong> Enter the homepage first, then select Perfect Money and DOGE from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of DOGE you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-1-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Buy DOGE with Perfect Money - Step 1" class="wp-image-8645" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-1-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-1-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-1-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-1-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-1.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 2:</strong> Press Next and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your DOGE wallet details, email, and phone number.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-2-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Buy DOGE with Perfect Money - step 2" class="wp-image-8644" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-2-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-2-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-2-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-2-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-2.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 3:</strong> One more time, click on the “Next” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-3-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Buy DOGE with Perfect Money - step 3" class="wp-image-8643" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-3-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-3-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-3-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-3-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-3.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 4:</strong> Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Confirm” button to go to the Perfect Money gateway and make the payment to our Perfect Money account. Having transferred your Perfect Money to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-4-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Buy DOGE with Perfect Money - step 4" class="wp-image-8642" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-4-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-4-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-4-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-4-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-4.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 5:</strong> By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the Dogecoin to your wallet ASAP.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-5-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Buy DOGE with Perfect Money - step 5" class="wp-image-8641" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-5-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-5-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-5-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-5-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-5.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done-and-done"><strong>Done and Done!</strong></h2>



<p>Having completed the steps above, our sales team will immediately process your order and make the payment. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-jolixo"><strong>Why CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p>Three reasons: Privacy, efficiency and reliability. <a href="https://hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> offers everything you need from an online exchange platform.</p>



<p>The primary reason for the cryptocurrencies’ success was the cryptic nature. The blockchain platform allows the users to protect their privacy and personal information. However, more and more exchanges are now making it mandatory for users to disclose their information. CoinCannon does not ask for any personal information and it is not mandatory to sign up to use the services.</p>



<p>As for efficiency, CoinCannon offers some of the most competitive exchange rates. The platform utilizes an automated system to determine the best rates and stay ahead of the competition. You can check out ranking websites such as BestChange and OkChanger to see the platform’s rank for yourself.</p>



<p>Lastly, the website offers true 24/7 customer support to be in touch with customers at all times.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-doge-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy DOGE with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-doge-with-perfect-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange USD Coin to Perfect Money [ 2024 Update]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/how-to-exchange-usd-coin-to-perfect-money/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/how-to-exchange-usd-coin-to-perfect-money/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 07:51:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perfect Money]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USD Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6195</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking to exchange USD Coin to Perfect Money? CoinCannon is all you need! Our platform offers a wide variety of stablecoins and the ability to exchange them into multiple payment methods. In this article, we will go over everything you need to know on how to turn USDC to PM USD. The good news is; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/how-to-exchange-usd-coin-to-perfect-money/">How to Exchange USD Coin to Perfect Money [ 2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking to exchange USD Coin to Perfect Money?</p>



<p><a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is all you need! Our platform offers a wide variety of stablecoins and the ability to exchange them into multiple payment methods. In this article, we will go over everything you need to know on how to turn USDC to PM USD. The good news is; you do not have to pay any additional fees or even go through the hassle of KYC. On top of that, CoinCannon offers 24/7 online support to ensure the highest quality of service.</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-4 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button is-style-outline is-style-outline--3"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-black-color has-text-color has-background has-link-color wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/" style="background-color:#f49d3f">Exchange USD Coin to Perfect Money</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-do-i-need-to-exchange-usd-coin-to-perfect-money"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange USD Coin to Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>For this transaction, you will need a verified Perfect Money account. Make sure that the transaction amount does not exceed your deposit limit. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon. Want a good reason why? How about winning $100 ever month!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-usd-coin-usdc"><strong>What is USD Coin (USDC)?</strong></h2>



<p>USD Coin owns the world’s largest stablecoin industry ecosystem in the world. It is a cryptocurrency that is pegged to US dollar in terms of value. That means that each USCD will always be worth $1. Stablecoins are used as a hedge against inflation and volatility in the crypto market. However, they can also be used as an alternative way to hold assets on the blockchain network.</p>



<p>As good as stablecoins might sound, there has always been concern about the companies not being honest about their dollar reserve. Basically, for every 1 USDC the company issues, they must hold $1 in their accounts. </p>



<p>As a matter of fact, there are rumors regarding some large companies not having the dollar equivalent of their stablecoin. If a solid reserve does not back a stablecoin, the currency will lose value and seriously damage the investor’s funds. In that regard, USD Coin aims to provide full transparency about their reserves.</p>



<p>USDC is managed by a consortium called Centre which is a part of the payment technology company Circle. Much like TrueUSD, they offer monthly attestation reports by Grant Thornton to ensure investors regarding their reserves. Where they differ from TrueUSD, is that TrueUSD only holds dollar in different accounts but USD Coin also holds other assets such as gold.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-exchange-to-perfect-money"><strong>Why Exchange to Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>Perfect Money is an e-currency used for making payments on the internet. It is widely accepted as payment option by countless platforms. With Perfect Money, you can do a lot! Be it transferring funds to others or pay for goods and services. Or how about buying cryptocurrencies or even buying fiat currencies. It is a seriously popular payment method for online users. An additional capability is to loan and receipt issuance throughout the system.</p>



<p>The biggest downside of Perfect Money, however, is that you cannot cash Perfect money to your bank account on its website directly. For that, you will need a platform like CoinCannon to exchange your Perfect Money to PayPal and other e-currencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-exchange-usd-coin-to-perfect-money"><strong>How to Exchange USD Coin to Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 1: </strong>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select USD Coin on the left field and Perfect Money on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-1-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange USD to Perfect Money step 1" class="wp-image-8588" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-1-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-1-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-1-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-1-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-1.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 2: </strong>Click on Next and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your Perfect Money account details, USDC wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-2-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange USD to Perfect Money step 2" class="wp-image-8587" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-2-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-2-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-2-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-2-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-2.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 3: </strong>Click on “Next” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-3-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange USD to Perfect Money step 3" class="wp-image-8586" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-3-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-3-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-3-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-3-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-3.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 4: </strong>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL. <br>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-4-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange USD to Perfect Money step 4" class="wp-image-8585" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-4-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-4-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-4-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-4-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-4.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 5: </strong>Transfer your USD Coin to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you.<br></li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-5-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange USD to Perfect Money step 5" class="wp-image-8584" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-5-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-5-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-5-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-5-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/USD-PerfectMoney-5.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the PM USD to your wallet address. Just like that, you have exchanged USD Coin to Perfect Money. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-this-is-jolixo"><strong>This is CoinCannon!</strong></h2>



<p>Cryptocurrencies are a financial apparatus to maximize privacy and efficiency. Sadly, regulations have been severely disrupting the market as they compromise both.</p>



<p>CoinCannon seeks to be a platform that offers privacy and efficiency simultaneously while offering some of the most aggressive exchange rates in the market.</p>



<p>To make this happen, the platform does not require KYC or a sign up process. This way, all customers can easily make transactions without a possible compromise on their personal information.</p>



<p>However, privacy is a crucial element and not a luxury. In that regard, the platform offers some of the most competitive rates amongst all online exchanges. The rates are automatically determined utilizing an automated system and are updated as soon as change in value is detected.</p>



<p>Last but not least, by offering true 24/7 support, all customers will be in touch with the team in case anything goes unplanned.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/how-to-exchange-usd-coin-to-perfect-money/">How to Exchange USD Coin to Perfect Money [ 2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/how-to-exchange-usd-coin-to-perfect-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Solana with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-perfect-money/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-perfect-money/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 09:29:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perfect Money]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5919</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the ever-evolving world of cryptocurrency, knowing how to buy Solana with Perfect Money is essential for savvy investors. With Solana (SOL) emerging as a formidable player in the blockchain space, acquiring this digital asset has become a priority for many. As we step into 2024, one of the most convenient and secure ways to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy Solana with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In the ever-evolving world of cryptocurrency, knowing how to <strong>buy Solana with Perfect Money</strong> is essential for savvy investors. With Solana (SOL) emerging as a formidable player in the blockchain space, acquiring this digital asset has become a priority for many.</p>



<p> As we step into 2024, one of the most convenient and secure ways to buy Solana is through Perfect Money. This article, <strong>&#8220;How to Buy Solana with Perfect Money [2024 Update]&#8221;</strong> will guide you through the latest methods and strategies to seamlessly buy Solana using Perfect Money.</p>



<p> Whether you&#8217;re a seasoned crypto enthusiast or a newcomer looking to diversify your portfolio, this comprehensive guide will provide you with the insights and tools needed to make informed decisions in the dynamic crypto market.</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-5 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button is-style-outline is-style-outline--4"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-black-color has-text-color has-background has-link-color wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/" style="background-color:#f49d3f">Buy <strong>Solana with Perfect Money</strong> Right Now!</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-do-i-need-to-buy-solana-with-perfect-money"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Solana with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will be sending PM USD and receiving Solana (SOL). Subsequently, you will need a verified and active Perfect Money account with sufficient funds. Make sure that the exchange amount does not exceed your withdrawal limit. On the other hand, you will have to have a reliable crypto wallet that supports Solana (SOL). As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-buy-solana-with-perfect-money"><strong>Why Buy Solana with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>It’s fast, it’s cheap and super easy to use. Basically, PM is one of the most popular payment systems that offers a lot of convenience.</p>



<p>Perfect Money is an e-currency used for making payments on the internet. It is widely accepted as payment option by countless platforms. With Perfect Money, you can do a lot! Be it transferring funds to others or pay for goods and services. Or how about buying cryptocurrencies or even buying fiat currencies. It is a seriously popular payment method for online users. An additional capability is to loan and receipt issuance throughout the system.</p>



<p>The biggest downside of Perfect Money, however, is that you cannot cash Perfect money to your bank account on its website directly. For that, you will need a platform like CoinCannon to exchange your Perfect Money to PayPal and other e-currencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-buy-solana-with-perfect-money"><strong>How to Buy Solana with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>Here are the five easy steps to make the purchase:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 1 : </strong>Enter the homepage first, then select Perfect Money and Solana (SOL) from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of SOL you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>



<li><strong>Step 2 : </strong>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Solana wallet details, email, and phone number.</li>



<li><strong>Step 3 : </strong>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li><strong>Step 4 : </strong>Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the Perfect Money gateway and make the payment to our Perfect Money account. Having transferred your Perfect Money to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>



<li><strong>Step 5 : </strong>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the SOL to your wallet ASAP.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done-and-done"><strong>Done and Done!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Solana to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-jolixo-platform"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Cryptocurrencies are a financial apparatus to maximize privacy and efficiency. Sadly, regulations have been severely affecting the market as they compromise both.</p>



<p><a href="https://hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> seeks to be a platform that offers privacy and efficiency simultaneously while offering some of the most aggressive exchange rates in the market.</p>



<p>To make this happen, the platform does not require KYC or a sign up process. This way, all customers can easily make transactions without a possible compromise on their personal information.</p>



<p>However, privacy is a crucial element and not a luxury. In that regard, the platform offers some of the most competitive rates amongst all online exchanges. The rates are automatically determined utilizing an automated system and are updated as soon as change in value is detected.</p>



<p>Last but not least, by offering true 24/7 support, all customers will be in touch with the team in case anything goes unplanned.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy Solana with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-perfect-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy EOS with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-eos-with-perfect-money/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-eos-with-perfect-money/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 07:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perfect Money]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5867</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to the ultimate guide on how to buy EOS with Perfect Money in 2024! In this article, we will walk you through the step-by-step process of acquiring EOS, one of the most popular cryptocurrencies, using the widely used digital payment system, Perfect Money. With the ever-evolving landscape of the cryptocurrency world, it&#8217;s crucial to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-eos-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy EOS with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Welcome to the ultimate guide on how to buy EOS with Perfect Money in 2024!</p>



<p>In this article, we will walk you through the step-by-step process of acquiring EOS, one of the most popular cryptocurrencies, using the widely used digital payment system, Perfect Money. With the ever-evolving landscape of the cryptocurrency world, it&#8217;s crucial to stay up-to-date with the latest methods and platforms to secure your investments. </p>



<p>Whether you&#8217;re a seasoned crypto investor or just starting your journey, we&#8217;ve got you covered. </p>



<p>So, grab your Perfect Money account and let&#8217;s dive into the exciting world of EOS!</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-6 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button is-style-outline is-style-outline--5"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-black-color has-text-color has-background has-link-color wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/" style="background-color:#f49d3f">Buy EOS with Perfect Money Right Now!</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-do-i-need-to-buy-eos-with-perfect-money"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy EOS with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>Basically, you will send Perfect Money USD to CoinCannon and the platform will send EOS to your wallet. For that, you will need a verified and active Perfect Money account with sufficient funds. </p>



<p>To receive EOS, you need a reliable crypto wallet that supports EOS. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-use-perfect-money"><strong>Why Use Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>Perfect Money is an e-currency for making payments on the internet. It is widely accepted as payment option by countless platforms. With Perfect Money, you can do a lot! Be it transferring funds to others or pay for goods and services. Or how about buying cryptocurrencies or even buying fiat currencies. It is a seriously popular payment method for online users. An additional capability is to loan and receipt issuance throughout the system.</p>



<p>The biggest downside of Perfect Money, however, is that you cannot cash Perfect money to your bank account on its website directly. For that, you will need a platform like CoinCannon to exchange your Perfect Money to PayPal and other e-currencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-buy-eos-with-perfect-money"><strong>How to Buy EOS with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>All it takes is 5 easy steps:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 1 : </strong>Enter the homepage first, then select Perfect Money and EOS from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of EOS Coin you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-1-1024x423.jpg" alt="Buy EOS with Perfect Money step by step -step 1" class="wp-image-8624" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-1-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-1-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-1-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-1-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-1.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 2 : </strong>Press Next and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your EOS wallet details, email, and phone number.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-2-1024x423.jpg" alt="Buy EOS with Perfect Money step by step -step 2" class="wp-image-8626" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-2-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-2-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-2-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-2-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-2.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 3 : </strong>One more time, click on the “Next” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-3-1024x423.jpg" alt="Buy EOS with Perfect Money step by step -step 3" class="wp-image-8627" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-3-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-3-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-3-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-3-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-3.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 4 : </strong>Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the Perfect Money gateway and make the payment to our Perfect Money account. Having transferred your Perfect Money to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-4-1024x423.jpg" alt="Buy EOS with Perfect Money step by step -step 4" class="wp-image-8628" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-4-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-4-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-4-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-4-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-4.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 5 : </strong>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the EOS to your wallet as soon as possible</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-5-1024x423.jpg" alt="Buy EOS with Perfect Money step by step -step 5" class="wp-image-8629" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-5-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-5-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-5-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-5-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Perfect-EOS-5.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-status-done"><strong>Status: Done</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the EOS Coin to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. </p>



<p>In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. </p>



<p class="has-text-align-center has-background" style="background-color:#ff6a0029">⚠ Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-this-is-jolixo"><strong>This is CoinCannon!</strong></h2>



<p>Essentially, you need three primary qualities in an ideal exchange platform. Anonymity, good rates and reliability. The CoinCannon team consists of traders and professionals who have felt the need for an ideal exchange and pursued their vision.</p>



<p>First and foremost, all users need to protect their personal information especially when it comes down to financial transactions. Unfortunately, a vast majority of exchange apps and platforms make massive profits off of selling user data. Best case scenario, they are legally bound to disclose user information with national authorities for any reason. In that regard, the best method to protect your privacy is to not disclose them with anyone at all. CoinCannon does not require customers to go through KYC (know your customer) or even a mandatory sign up. In that regard, it is simply as safe as one can get making an exchange.</p>



<p>On the other hand, privacy is not a reason to pay more on your exchange. With that in mind, the platform offers some of the most competitive exchange rates you can find anywhere. Don’t take our word for it. You can simply pay a visit to ranking websites such as BestChange or OkChanger and see compare our rates with others.</p>



<p>Last but not least, not everything goes as planned in the digital world. Subsequently, the platform provides true online 24/7 customer support for the users.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-eos-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy EOS with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-eos-with-perfect-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Polygon to Perfect Money [ 2024 Update]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-polygon-to-perfect-money/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-polygon-to-perfect-money/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 08:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATIC Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perfect Money]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6121</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you interested in learning how to exchange Polygon to Perfect Money? In this article we will guide you through the process of converting your Polygon cryptocurrency to Perfect Money, a popular online payment system. Stay up-to-date with the latest methods for seamlessly exchanging digital currencies to facilitate online transactions. Join us as we explore [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-polygon-to-perfect-money/">How to Exchange Polygon to Perfect Money [ 2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Are you interested in learning how to <strong>exchange Polygon to Perfect Money</strong>?</p>



<p>In this article we will guide you through the process of converting your Polygon cryptocurrency to Perfect Money, a popular online payment system. </p>



<p>Stay up-to-date with the latest methods for seamlessly exchanging digital currencies to facilitate online transactions. Join us as we explore the steps, possibilities, and benefits of this exchange. </p>



<p>Get ready to discover how the world of cryptocurrencies meets the convenience of Perfect Money. </p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons alignwide is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-7 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button is-style-outline is-style-outline--6"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-black-color has-text-color has-background has-link-color wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/" style="background-color:#f49d3f">Exchange Polygon to Perfect Money</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-do-i-need-to-exchange-polygon-to-perfect-money"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Polygon to Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>For this transaction, you will need a verified and active Perfect Money account to receive the funds. Make sure that the transaction does not exceed your deposit limit on PM. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon. Want a good reason why? How about winning $100 every month!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-perfect-money"><strong>Why Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>Perfect Money is simply a digital currency that can be used as a payment system for non-cash payments. A vast majority of the transaction are payments on the internet for online services. In terms of what you can do with Perfect Money, the sky is the limit.</p>



<p>You can use PM to:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Transference of money between users</li>



<li>Accepting payments on your website</li>



<li>Payment for goods and services on the Internet</li>



<li>Purchases of Bitcoins, gold, US dollars, and Euros</li>



<li>Loan and receipt issuance throughout the system</li>



<li>Earn additional revenue by participating in a partnership plan</li>
</ul>



<p>The biggest downside of Perfect Money, however, is that you cannot cash Perfect money to your bank account on its website directly. For that, you will need a platform like CoinCannon to exchange your Perfect Money to PayPal and other e-currencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-exchange-polygon-to-perfect-money"><strong>How to Exchange Polygon to Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 1:</strong> Enter the homepage first, then select Polygon (MATIC) and Perfect Money from the currency pairs in the first step. enter the amount you want to exchange, after that the amount of PM USD you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-1-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange Polygon to Perfect Money on CoinCannon step 1" class="wp-image-8474" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-1-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-1-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-1-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-1-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-1.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 2:</strong> Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your PerfectMoney wallet details, email, and phone number (Optional).</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-2-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange Polygon to Perfect Money on CoinCannon step 2" class="wp-image-8476" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-2-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-2-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-2-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-2-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-2.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 3:</strong> One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-3-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange Polygon to Perfect Money on CoinCannon step 3" class="wp-image-8477" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-3-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-3-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-3-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-3-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-3.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 4:</strong> Pass the captcha test and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. When you have transferred MATIC, attach the screen shot and press and pay order. After you have transferred your MATIC to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-4-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange Polygon to Perfect Money on CoinCannon step 4" class="wp-image-8478" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-4-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-4-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-4-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-4-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-4.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 5:</strong> By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the PM USD to your wallet ASAP.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-5-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange Polygon to Perfect Money on CoinCannon step 5" class="wp-image-8479" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-5-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-5-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-5-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-5-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Polygon-to-PerfectMoney-5.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done"><strong>Done</strong>!</h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Perfect Money USD to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. </p>



<p>In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. </p>



<p>Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-jolixo-platform"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>To exchange any cryptocurrency, you will need to find a good platform first. However, despite the diversity, it is quite a difficult task to find a good online exchange. The problem begins by compromising on your standards. You will want good exchange rates, privacy and reliability altogether. And that is hard to find!</p>



<p>Harsh regulations are pushing exchanges to disclose customer data to governments. This goes against the initial purpose of crypto which is absolute anonymity. Even worse, user data is a commodity, large institutions buy your information at a certain price. The best way to make sure your data is safe, is to not share them at all.</p>



<p>However, it is a luxury to offer no KYC, hence many exchanges charge customers with ridiculous exchange rates to compensate for the anonymity.</p>



<p>CoinCannon on the other hand gives you everything all at once. Want privacy? We have no KYC. Want the best exchange rates? Well, simply visit Bestchange or OkChanger and see for yourself how we are always on top of their lists.</p>



<p>And to make sure everything goes right, we offer 24/7 customer support</p>



<p></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-polygon-to-perfect-money/">How to Exchange Polygon to Perfect Money [ 2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-polygon-to-perfect-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Tether with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-perfect-money/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-perfect-money/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 05:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perfect Money]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6105</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The allure of stable coins like Tether (USDT) continues to grow in the ever-volatile cryptocurrency market. For those looking to enter the world of stable coins or diversify their digital assets, using Perfect Money offers a unique and often overlooked pathway. This updated 2024 guide is your one-stop resource for navigating the process of buying [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy Tether with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The allure of stable coins like Tether (USDT) continues to grow in the ever-volatile cryptocurrency market. For those looking to enter the world of stable coins or diversify their digital assets, using Perfect Money offers a unique and often overlooked pathway. </p>



<p>This updated 2024 guide is your one-stop resource for navigating the process of buying Tether with Perfect Money smoothly and securely.</p>



<p>We&#8217;ll demystify the steps involved, highlighting the most reputable exchanges and platforms facilitating this specific exchange. </p>



<p>Whether you&#8217;re a seasoned crypto enthusiast familiar with Perfect Money&#8217;s features or a newcomer intrigued by its potential, this article provides the insights and practical tips you need. Let&#8217;s dive in and explore how to acquire Tether using Perfect Money in 2024.</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-8 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button is-style-outline is-style-outline--7"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-black-color has-text-color has-background has-link-color wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/?step=1" style="background-color:#f7954f">Buy Tether with Perfect Money Right Now!</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-do-i-need-to-buy-tether-with-perfect-money"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Tether with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>For this transaction, you will need a verified and active PM account. </p>



<p>Furthermore, you will have to have a reliable crypto wallet. </p>



<p>Make sure that the transaction amount does not exceed your withdrawal limit on Perfect Money. </p>



<p>As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on <a href="https://hi.exchange/">jolixo</a>. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-exchange-perfect-money-to-tether-usdt"><strong>Why Exchange Perfect Money to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>Tether USDT is currently the most popular stablecoin in the world. The value of USDT is pegged to the US dollar which means that it will always be worth $1. What it does is a cryptocurrency with a stable value to store investor’s funds. In that case, the investors can hold their capital in form of Tether USDT without worrying about the volatility.</p>



<p>However, volatility is not the only reason to buy Tether USDT. It is very quick and cheap to buy cryptocurrencies with Tether USDT. The transaction fees are next to nothing and it basically takes a few seconds to buy crypto with Tether. In general, Tether USDT has lots of utility whether you’re a crypto trader, Forex trader or a long-term holder.</p>



<p>Furthermore, numerous merchants have started accepting Tether payments in the past few years. Whether in online stores or physical shops, you can use Tether USDT payments. In that regard, having Tether in your crypto wallet is basically as good as cash in 2022.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-buy-tether-with-perfect-money"><strong>How to Buy Tether with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 1:</strong> Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Perfect Money USD on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange PM to Tether on CoinCannon step 1" class="wp-image-8457" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 2:</strong> Click on Next button and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your email.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfecMoney-Tether-2-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange PM to Tether step 2" class="wp-image-8459" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfecMoney-Tether-2-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfecMoney-Tether-2-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfecMoney-Tether-2-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfecMoney-Tether-2-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfecMoney-Tether-2.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 3:</strong> Click on “Next” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-3-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange PM to Tether on CoinCannon step 3" class="wp-image-8460" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-3-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-3-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-3-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-3-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-3.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 4:</strong> At this point, after clicking &#8221; View and Check&#8221; you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-4-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange PM to Tether on CoinCannon step 4" class="wp-image-8461" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-4-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-4-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-4-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-4-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-4.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 5: </strong>On this step, Confirm the transaction and please spend the time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-5-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange Perfect Money to Tether step 5" class="wp-image-8462" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-5-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-5-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-5-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-5-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-5.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 6:</strong> Done! You can track your order now.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-all-good"><strong>All Good!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether USDT to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-2024-updates-and-rules-about-how-to-buy-tether-with-perfect-money">2024 updates and rules about How to Buy Tether with Perfect Money</h2>



<p>While specific regulations surrounding cryptocurrency can vary by jurisdiction, some 2024 updates and general rules apply when buying Tether with Perfect Money:</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Know Your Customer (KYC) and Anti-Money Laundering (AML) Regulations:</h3>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Expect stricter KYC and AML compliance when using platforms for buying Tether with Perfect Money.#### Stablecoin Regulations:</li>



<li>The regulatory landscape for stablecoins is evolving rapidly. informed about any new rules or guidelines issued by governing bodies in your region. and fees. wallet to store your purchased USDT.<strong>In summary, while buying Tether with Perfect Money remains possible in 2024, it&#8217;s crucial to stay informed about evolving regulations, prioritize security, and choose reputable platforms for a smooth and compliant experience.</strong></li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-jolixo-platform"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Every exchange platform must maintain three important characteristics. Anonymity, affordability and reliability. We pride ourselves as a professional platform that offers all three.</p>



<p>For anonymity, <a href="https://hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> requires no KYC or even a sign up process. The best way to protect your information is to not share them with anyone. And for that, we respect our customers and do not ask for their personal info.</p>



<p>As for affordability, CoinCannon utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. By doing so, we have managed to stay on top of the ranks on websites such as Bestchange and OkChanger.</p>



<p>Lastly, reliability is ensured for our customers with 24/7 online support. In case anything goes wrong, you will have our immediate support until the issue is resolved.</p>



<p></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy Tether with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-perfect-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money [2024 Update]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-perfect-money/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-perfect-money/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 10:03:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perfect Money]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5825</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As of October 2022, Ethereum is one of the hottest cryptocurrencies. If you are looking for a platform to exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money and not compromise on anything, you are in luck. CoinCannon platform is the best place to exchange cryptocurrencies with multiple advantages which we will go over later in this article. In [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-perfect-money/">How to Exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>As of October 2022, Ethereum is one of the hottest cryptocurrencies. If you are looking for a platform to exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money and not compromise on anything, you are in luck. </p>



<p><a href="http://www.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> platform is the best place to exchange cryptocurrencies with multiple advantages which we will go over later in this article. In the meantime, Perfect Money users may not find it easy to find platforms who support them. </p>



<p>Thankfully, CoinCannon is an official Perfect Money partner that is also verified. In this article, we will go over everything you need to know to exchange Ethereum to PM.</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-9 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button is-style-outline is-style-outline--8"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-black-color has-text-color has-background has-link-color wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/" style="background-color:#f49d3f">Exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-do-i-need-to-exchange-ethereum-to-perfect-money"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>For this transaction, you will need a crypto wallet to send ETH. In order to receive Perfect Money USD, you need to have a verified and active PM account. </p>



<p>As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-should-i-exchange-ethereum-to-pm"><strong>Should I Exchange Ethereum to PM?</strong></h2>



<p>Perfect Money is simply a digital currency that can be used as a payment system for non-cash payments. A vast majority of the transaction are payments on the internet for online services. In terms of what you can do with Perfect Money, the sky is the limit.</p>



<p>You can use PM to:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Transference of money between users</li>



<li>Accepting payments on your website</li>



<li>Payment for goods and services on the Internet</li>



<li>Purchases of Bitcoins, gold, US dollars, and Euros</li>



<li>Loan and receipt issuance throughout the system</li>



<li>Earn additional revenue by participating in a partnership plan</li>
</ul>



<p>The biggest downside of Perfect Money, however, is that you cannot cash Perfect money to your bank account on its website directly. For that, you will need a platform like CoinCannon to exchange your Perfect Money to PayPal and other e-currencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-exchange-ethereum-to-perfect-money"><strong>How to Exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money</strong>?</h2>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 1: </strong>Enter the homepage first, then select Ethereum and Perfect Money from the currency pairs in the first step. enter the amount you want to exchange, after that the amount of PM USD you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-1-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money step by step - step 1" class="wp-image-8596" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-1-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-1-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-1-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-1-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-1.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 2: </strong>Press Next and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Perfect Money wallet details, email, and phone number (Optional).</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-2-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money step by step - step 2" class="wp-image-8595" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-2-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-2-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-2-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-2-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-2.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 3: </strong>One more time, click on the “Next” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-3-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money step by step - step 3" class="wp-image-8594" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-3-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-3-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-3-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-3-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-3.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 4: </strong>Pass the captcha test and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the PM gateway and pay online. After you have transferred your ETH to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-4-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money step by step - step 4" class="wp-image-8593" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-4-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-4-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-4-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-4-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-4.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 5: </strong>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the PM USD to your wallet ASAP.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-5-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money step by step - step 5" class="wp-image-8592" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-5-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-5-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-5-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-5-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-5.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Perfect Money USD to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. </p>



<p>In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-jolixo-platform"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>To exchange any cryptocurrency, you will need to find a good platform first. However, despite the diversity, it is quite a difficult task to find a good online exchange. The problem begins by compromising on your standards. You will want good exchange rates, privacy and reliability altogether. And that is hard to find!</p>



<p>Harsh regulations are pushing exchanges to disclose customer data to governments. This goes against the initial purpose of crypto which is absolute anonymity. Even worse, user data is a commodity, large institutions buy your information at a certain price. The best way to make sure your data is safe, is to not share them at all.</p>



<p>However, it is a luxury to offer no KYC, hence many exchanges charge customers with ridiculous exchange rates to compensate for the anonymity.</p>



<p><a href="https://hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> on the other hand gives you everything all at once. Want privacy? We have no KYC. Want the best exchange rates? Well, simply visit Bestchange or OkChanger and see for yourself how we are always on top of their lists.</p>



<p>And to make sure everything goes right, we offer 24/7 customer support</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-perfect-money/">How to Exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-perfect-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Bitcoin (BTC) [Video Guide]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-btc-perfect-money/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-btc-perfect-money/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 07:36:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Videos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perfect Money]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6031</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you’re Looking to Buy Bitcoin (BTC), CoinCannon is the best platform for the job. Buying BTC has no time and limit as it is the top cryptocurrency just like it has always been. So, if you want to invest on the top digital asset in the crypto market, Bitcoin is the king of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-btc-perfect-money/">How to Buy Bitcoin (BTC) [Video Guide]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you’re Looking to Buy Bitcoin (BTC), <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is the best platform for the job. Buying BTC has no time and limit as it is the top cryptocurrency just like it has always been. So, if you want to invest on the top digital asset in the crypto market, Bitcoin is the king of the hill. With that, CoinCannon platform provides all the benefits and qualities your need from an exchanger. Without further ado, here is our guide on How to Buy Bitcoin (BTC) with Perfect Money on CoinCannon in only 4 easy steps.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="Buy Bitcoin (BTC) with Perfect Money on CoinCannon" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/l-jUo6jivoc?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Bitcoin (BTC) with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>Essentially, you will be sending Perfect Money USD to CoinCannon and Receive Bitcoin. For that, you will need a verified and active PerfectMoney account. Make sure that the transaction amount does not exceed your withdrawal limit. Then, you will need a reliable crypto wallet. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon. Want a good reason why? How about winning $100 ever month!</p>



<p>Learn more about our <a href="https://hi.exchange/campaign/tether-giveaway">Tether Giveaway</a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Bitcoin (BTC)?</strong></h2>



<p>Well, there is hardly anyone these days who is not familiar with the definition of Bitcoin and what the cryptocurrency is capable of carrying out. However, let’s briefly go through what bitcoin is and where it comes from, then we can focus on the benefits of using this cryptocurrency and explain why to buy Bitcoin with Perfect Money.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a Cryptocurrency that was created after the housing market collapse in January 2009. It follows the ideas set out by the enigmatic and pseudonymous Satoshi Nakamoto in a whitepaper. The identity of the individual or individuals who developed this cryptocurrency is still under wraps. Unlike government-issued currencies, Bitcoin provides the guarantee of lower transaction costs than conventional online payment systems and is regulated by a decentralized authority.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a tempting opportunity for investment and great tool for doing financial transactions. Everything is in favor of exchanging your Perfect Money for some BTC when possible.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Use Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>Perfect Money is an e-currency for making payments on the internet. It is widely accepted as payment option by countless platforms. With Perfect Money, you can do a lot! Be it transferring funds to others or pay for goods and services. Or how about buying cryptocurrencies or even buying fiat currencies. It is a seriously popular payment method for online users. An additional capability is to loan and receipt issuance throughout the system.</p>



<p>The biggest downside of Perfect Money, however, is that you cannot cash Perfect money to your bank account on its website directly. For that, you will need a platform like CoinCannon to exchange your Perfect Money to PayPal and other e-currencies.</p>



<p>To learn all about Perfect money continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/guide-to-exchange-perfect-money/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Perfect Money</a>”.</p>



<p>That Being said, you can buy Bitcoin (BTC) using other digital currencies such as Payeer USD.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>To exchange any cryptocurrency, you will need to find a good platform first. However, despite the diversity, it is quite a difficult task to find a good online exchange. The problem begins by compromising on your standards. You will want good exchange rates, privacy and reliability altogether. And that is hard to find!</p>



<p>Brutal regulations are pushing exchanges to disclose customer data to governments. This goes against the initial purpose of crypto which is absolute anonymity. Even worse, user data is a commodity, large institutions buy your information at a certain price. The best way to make sure your data is safe, is to not share them at all.</p>



<p>However, it is a luxury to offer no KYC, hence many exchanges charge customers with ridiculous exchange rates to compensate for the anonymity.</p>



<p>CoinCannon on the other hand gives you everything all at once. Want privacy? We have no KYC. Want the best exchange rates? Well, simply visit Bestchange or OkChanger and see for yourself how we are always on top of their lists.</p>



<p>And to make sure everything goes right, we offer 24/7 customer support.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Buy Bitcoin (BTC) with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Enter the homepage first, then select Perfect Money and Bitcoin (BTC) from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of BTC you will receive will automatically calculate.</li><li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your BTC wallet address, email, and phone number.</li><li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li><li>Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the Perfect Money gateway and make the payment to our Perfect Money account. Having transferred your Perfect Money to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li><li>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the BTC to your wallet as soon as possible</li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Bitcoin to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-btc-perfect-money/">How to Buy Bitcoin (BTC) [Video Guide]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-btc-perfect-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Zcash with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-zcash-with-perfect-money/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-zcash-with-perfect-money/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 06:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[buy Zcash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perfect Money]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ZCash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5996</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the ever-evolving world of cryptocurrency, knowing how to buy Zcash with Perfect Money is becoming increasingly essential for savvy investors. As privacy-focused digital currencies like Zcash (ZEC) gain prominence, acquiring this asset securely and conveniently has become a priority. As we step into 2024, using Perfect Money to buy Zcash offers a seamless and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-zcash-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy Zcash with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In the ever-evolving world of cryptocurrency, knowing how to <strong><a href="https://hi.exchange/">buy Zcash with Perfect Money</a></strong> is becoming increasingly essential for savvy investors.</p>



<p>As privacy-focused digital currencies like Zcash (ZEC) gain prominence, acquiring this asset securely and conveniently has become a priority. As we step into 2024, using Perfect Money to buy Zcash offers a seamless and efficient way to add this crypto to your portfolio. </p>



<p>This article, <strong>&#8220;How to Buy Zcash with Perfect Money [2024 Update],&#8221;</strong> will guide you through the latest methods and strategies to effortlessly purchase Zcash with Perfect Money.</p>



<p>Whether you&#8217;re a seasoned crypto enthusiast or a newcomer eager to explore privacy coins, this comprehensive guide will equip you with the knowledge and tools needed to make informed decisions in the dynamic world of digital currencies.</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-10 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button is-style-outline is-style-outline--9"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-black-color has-text-color has-background has-link-color wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/" style="background-color:#f49d3f">Buy Zcash with Perfect Money Right Now!</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-do-i-need-to-buy-zcash-with-perfect-money"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Zcash with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>For this transaction, you will be sending PerfectMoney USD and receive Zcash (ZEC) in your wallet. Naturally, you will need to have a verified and active Perfect Money account with sufficient funds. Make sure that the exchange amount does not exceed your withdrawal limit. </p>



<p>On the other hand, you will need a reliable crypto wallet that supports Zcash (ZEC) to receive the funds. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-perfect-money"><strong>Why Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>Perfect Money is an e-currency for making payments on the internet. It is widely accepted as payment option by countless platforms. With Perfect Money, you can do a lot! </p>



<p>Be it transferring funds to others or pay for goods and services. Or how about buying cryptocurrencies or even buying fiat currencies. It is a seriously popular payment method for online users. An additional capability is to loan and receipt issuance throughout the system.</p>



<p>The biggest downside of Perfect Money, however, is that you cannot cash Perfect money to your bank account on its website directly. For that, you will need a platform like CoinCannon to exchange your Perfect Money to PayPal and other e-currencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-buy-zcash-with-perfect-money"><strong>How to Buy Zcash with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 1 : </strong>Enter the homepage first, then select Perfect Money and Zcash (ZEC) from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of ZEC you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>



<li><strong>Step 2 :</strong> Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Zcash wallet address, email, and phone number.</li>



<li><strong>Step 3 :</strong> One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li><strong>Step 4 :</strong> Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the Perfect Money gateway and make the payment to our Perfect Money account. Having transferred your Perfect Money to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>



<li><strong>Step 5 :</strong> By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the Zcash to your wallet as soon as possible</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Zcash to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. </p>



<p>Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-to-choose-jolixo"><strong>Why to Choose CoinCannon!</strong></h2>



<p>To exchange any cryptocurrency, you will need to find a good platform first. However, despite the diversity, it is quite a difficult task to find a good online exchange. The problem begins by compromising on your standards. You will want good exchange rates, privacy and reliability altogether. And that is hard to find!</p>



<p>Brutal regulations are pushing exchanges to disclose customer data to governments. This goes against the initial purpose of crypto which is absolute anonymity. Even worse, user data is a commodity, large institutions buy your information at a certain price. The best way to make sure your data is safe, is to not share them at all.</p>



<p>However, it is a luxury to offer no KYC, hence many exchanges charge customers with ridiculous exchange rates to compensate for the anonymity.</p>



<p><a href="https://hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> on the other hand gives you everything all at once. Want privacy? We have no KYC. Want the best exchange rates? Well, simply visit Bestchange or OkChanger and see for yourself how we are always on top of their lists.</p>



<p>And to make sure everything goes right, we offer 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-zcash-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy Zcash with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-zcash-with-perfect-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Perfect Money to Webmoney [2024 Update]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-perfect-money-to-webmoney/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-perfect-money-to-webmoney/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 06:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perfect Money]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Weboney]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wmz]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5963</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The world of online payment systems is in constant flux, with new players emerging and established platforms evolving to meet the demands of digital commerce. Navigating this landscape can be tricky, especially when you need to move funds between different systems. Perfect Money and WebMoney remain two of the most popular choices for savvy online [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-perfect-money-to-webmoney/">How to Exchange Perfect Money to Webmoney [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The world of online payment systems is in constant flux, with new players emerging and established platforms evolving to meet the demands of digital commerce. Navigating this landscape can be tricky, especially when you need to move funds between different systems.</p>



<p> Perfect Money and WebMoney remain two of the most popular choices for savvy online users, each with its own strengths and features. But what happens when you need to convert your Perfect Money balance to WebMoney?</p>



<p>This updated 2024 guide is your key to unlocking seamless exchanges between Perfect Money and WebMoney. We&#8217;ll cut through the noise and provide a clear, concise roadmap for transferring your funds quickly and securely. </p>



<p>Whether you&#8217;re a seasoned digital investor, an online entrepreneur, or simply looking for the most efficient way to manage your money online, this article will equip you with the knowledge and resources you need to make informed decisions. </p>



<p>Let&#8217;s dive in and explore the optimal strategies for exchanging Perfect Money to WebMoney in 2024.</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-11 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button is-style-outline is-style-outline--10"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-black-color has-text-color has-background has-link-color has-text-align-center wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/?step=1" style="background-color:#f49d3f" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Perfect Money to Webmoney </a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-do-i-need-to-exchange-perfect-money-to-webmoney"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Perfect Money to Webmoney?</strong></h2>



<p>For this direction, you need both PerfectMoney and Webmoney verified and active accounts. Please make sure that the exchange amount does not exceed your deposit and withdrawal limits. </p>



<p>As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon. Want a good reason why? How about winning $100 ever month!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-exchange-perfect-money-to-webmoney"><strong>Why Exchange Perfect Money to Webmoney?</strong></h2>



<p>WebMoney provides digital currency purses that can hold popular national currencies. The payment platform provides a P2P credit purse, global payment solutions, retail services, local payment products, online billing, and direct integration with other global financial service providers. </p>



<p>On top of that, a number of countries worldwide are currently working on WebMoney and consumers pay WebMoney for the services of different companies from Spain, Poland, and Belgium.</p>



<p>Essentially, you can trace back a lot of the crypto and DeFi ideas back to WM. In that regard, it is more of an effort to circumvent unnecessary banking regulations. A decade before Bitcoin, WM was one of the few payment systems independent of banking.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-exchange-perfect-money-to-webmoney"><strong>How to Exchange Perfect Money to Webmoney?</strong></h2>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 1: </strong>Enter the homepage first, then select Perfect Money and Webmoney (WMZ) from the options in the first step. <br>Enter the amount you want to exchange. <br>Following that, the amount of WMZ you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-1-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Exchange Perfect Money to Webmoney- Step 1" class="wp-image-8421" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-1-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-1-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-1-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-1-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-1.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 2: </strong>Press Next and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Webmoney address, email, and phone number.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-2-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Exchange Perfect Money to Webmoney- Step 2" class="wp-image-8422" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-2-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-2-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-2-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-2-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-2.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 3:</strong> One more time, click on the “Next” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-3-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Exchange Perfect Money to Webmoney- Step 3" class="wp-image-8423" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-3-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-3-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-3-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-3-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-3.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 4:</strong> Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. <br>Press the “Confirm” button to go to the Perfect Money gateway and make the payment to our Perfect Money account. Having transferred your Perfect Money to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-4-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Exchange Perfect Money to Webmoney- Step 4" class="wp-image-8424" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-4-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-4-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-4-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-4-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-4.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong><strong>Step 5:</strong></strong> By finishing all the steps above and press &#8220;Confirm Payment&#8221; button, our team of professionals will send the Webmoney to your wallet as soon as possible</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-5-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Exchange Perfect Money to Webmoney- Step 5" class="wp-image-8425" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-5-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-5-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-5-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-5-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/PerfectMoney-WebMoney-5.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-jolixo-is-all-you-need"><strong>CoinCannon is All You Need!</strong></h2>



<p><a href="https://hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> is an online exchange platform that offers three critical factors for customers. Privacy, Efficiency and Reliability are not an easy combination to find on the internet.</p>



<p>For privacy, the ultimate way to protect your personal information is to not disclose them at all. Unfortunately, a vast majority exchanges are now legally obliged to hand over user data to governments for tax purposes. CoinCannon does not require customers to go through KYC or a sign up process as a sign of respect for anonymity.</p>



<p>Efficiency for an exchange platform calls for competitive exchange rates and quick processing time for orders. To maximize results and minimize efforts, the platform utilizes an automated consensus algorithm to determine the best exchange rates.</p>



<p>Lastly, for reliability and customer satisfaction, <a href="https://hi.exchange/">CoinCannon </a>offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-perfect-money-to-webmoney/">How to Exchange Perfect Money to Webmoney [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-perfect-money-to-webmoney/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
