<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Tron (TRX) Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/tron-trx/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 08:42:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>How to Buy Tron with Tether USDT [Instant]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tron-with-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tron-with-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 08:42:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tron (TRX)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6373</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking to buy Tron with Tether? Look no further than CoinCannon. Generally speaking, buying cryptocurrencies and exchanging them into one another is an easy task. However, most exchange platforms tend to compromise on security or offer high exchange rates. With that, it can be difficult to find an online exchange platform that offers everything you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tron-with-tether/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Buy Tron with Tether USDT [Instant]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking to buy Tron with Tether? Look no further than CoinCannon. Generally speaking, buying cryptocurrencies and exchanging them into one another is an easy task. However, most exchange platforms tend to compromise on security or offer high exchange rates. With that, it can be difficult to find an online exchange platform that offers everything you need. Subsequently, CoinCannon provides unparalleled anonymity all while charging no hidden fees on your transaction. With all that, you can easily Buy Tron with Tether (USD) in only a matter of minutes. So head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Tether USDT on the left field, and Tron on the right and start the action!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Tron with Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive Tron (TRX). In case your USDT wallet supports Tether, you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Tron (TRX)?</strong></h2>



<p>Tron is a decentralized, blockchain-based platform that aims to build a free, global entertainment system for digital content with distributed storage technology and enables digital content to be shared easily and cost-effectively.</p>



<p>The TRON ecosystem basically acts as a platform for content-sharing. In this platform, TRX is the payment for users who create or post content, resulting in a fairer and more open monetization mechanism than those that control conventional social media networks. It also allows users to share their content without having to go through a middleman, such as the Google Play Store or Apple Store. This means that TRON is helping to push the decentralized application market (dApps).</p>



<p>Tron was founded by a non-profit organization based in Singapore called the Tron Foundation in September 2017. This foundation is led by Justin Sun, CEO, and benefits from a dedicated in-house development team that includes distinguished stalwarts in technology.</p>



<p>Tron attempts to CoinCannon the gap between content creators and content consumers by eliminating the middleman by using the features of the blockchain and peer-to-peer (P2P) network technology. The result is an overall cost reduction for the consumer and better collection for the content producer through direct receipts, which offers a win-win situation.</p>



<p>To learn everything about Tron (TRX) continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-tron-trx/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Tron?</a>”</p>



<p>If you are interested in investing in Tron (TRX), you can easily and instantly buy Tron with Tether (USDT) or a variety of other digital currencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Buy Tron with Tether (USDT)?</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to buy Tron (TRX) with Tether (USDT), let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon is the Best Exchange!</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Buy Tron with Tether (USDT)?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">Homepage</a> on CoinCannon. Select Tether USDT on the left field and Tron (TRX) on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your TRX wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your USDT to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-that-s-it"><strong>That’s It!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tron (TRX) to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tron-with-tether/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Buy Tron with Tether USDT [Instant]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tron-with-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tron (TRX) Surpassed $6 Billion in TVL</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/tron-trx-tvl/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/tron-trx-tvl/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 05:54:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tron (TRX)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5511</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Always under the radar, the humble altcoin Tron (TRX) been a leading asset in decentralized storage platforms. So far, TRX has been one of the less volatile digital assets but that might change very soon. With a new stablecoin, Tron (TRX) is now holding the third largest TVL in its reserves. Because, at this point [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tron-trx-tvl/">Tron (TRX) Surpassed $6 Billion in TVL</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Always under the radar, the humble altcoin Tron (TRX) been a leading asset in decentralized storage platforms. So far, TRX has been one of the less volatile digital assets but that might change very soon. With a new stablecoin, Tron (TRX) is now holding the third largest TVL in its reserves. Because, at this point and time, the world is in dire need of another algorithmic stablecoin. Nonetheless, investors are now rushing to put capital into Tron’s smart contracts for those juicy returns.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Buy and Sell Tron (TRX) Anonymously on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Tron (TRX) Total Value Locked</strong></h2>



<p>TRON is a decentralized, blockchain-based network that aims to create an open, global entertainment infrastructure for digital content with distributed storage technology and enables digital content to be exchanged quickly and cost-effectively. Continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-tron-trx/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Tron (TRX)</a>”.</p>



<p>However, much like all crypto projects, the initial purpose becomes irrelevant and they have to start an algorithmic stablecoin.</p>



<p>Recently, the Tron network introduced Decentralized USD (USDD), an algorithmic stablecoin. Apparently, USDD has had a massive role in increasing the total value locked in Tron smart contracts.</p>



<p>According to analytics platform DeFi Llama, Tron is now the third largest blockchain in terms of TVL at $6.03 billion.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="999" height="390" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tron-TRX-TVL.webp" alt="" class="wp-image-5512" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tron-TRX-TVL.webp 999w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tron-TRX-TVL-300x117.webp 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tron-TRX-TVL-768x300.webp 768w" sizes="(max-width: 999px) 100vw, 999px" /><figcaption>Source: DeFi Llama</figcaption></figure>



<p>Basically, TVL of a blockchain represents the total money held within the smart contracts. Of course, it comes with interest rates as rewards. To calculate TVL, we multiply the amount of collateral locked into the network by the current value of assets.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How Did Tron Attract This Much Capital?</strong></h2>



<p>Short answer is, 23% annual returns! DeFi Llama noticed that over half of the capital within the smart contracts comes from JustLend (JST). JustLend is a decentralized finance lending and borrowing protocol. With a closer look, we see the platform offers an annual percentage yield of over 23% for USDD holders. To put that in perspective, Russian banks currently offer 20% annual percentage yields. No this comes from a country that is at war and enduring the largest amount of sanctions ever.</p>



<p>According to data, it is clear that the growth in TVL for Tron (TRX) is caused by a quick increase in USDD market cap. Since May, Tron’s total value has almost doubled from $3.73 billion to $6 billion. Within the same period, USDD market cap moved from $269 million to $603 million with a 123% increase.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="857" height="537" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tron-TRX-TVL-1.webp" alt="" class="wp-image-5513" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tron-TRX-TVL-1.webp 857w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tron-TRX-TVL-1-300x188.webp 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Tron-TRX-TVL-1-768x481.webp 768w" sizes="(max-width: 857px) 100vw, 857px" /><figcaption>Source: DeFi Llama</figcaption></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tron-trx-tvl/">Tron (TRX) Surpassed $6 Billion in TVL</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/tron-trx-tvl/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
