<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Altcoins Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/category/altcoins/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/category/altcoins/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 12:43:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Revealing Arthur Hayes&#8217; Top Altcoin Picks for 2024</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/revealing-arthur-hayes-top-altcoin-picks-for-2024/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/revealing-arthur-hayes-top-altcoin-picks-for-2024/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Leyli Mamikhani]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 12:43:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=8188</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As the bearish trend of 2024 unfolds, Arthur Hayes, the former CEO of Bitmax, has shared insights into his chosen altcoins for the year. Departing from his Bitcoin focus, Hayes is now eyeing strategic investments in Solana and Bonk, signaling a shift in his cryptocurrency portfolio. In a recent press release, Hayes expressed concern about [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/revealing-arthur-hayes-top-altcoin-picks-for-2024/">Revealing Arthur Hayes&#8217; Top Altcoin Picks for 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>As the bearish trend of 2024 unfolds, Arthur Hayes, the former CEO of Bitmax, has shared insights into his chosen altcoins for the year. Departing from his Bitcoin focus, Hayes is now eyeing strategic investments in Solana and Bonk, signaling a shift in his cryptocurrency portfolio.</p>



<p>In a recent press release, Hayes expressed concern about Bitcoin&#8217;s struggle to maintain its position above $40,000, predicting potential further declines in the upcoming weeks. In response to this market sentiment, he has diversified his investments into the promising altcoins Solana and Bonk.</p>



<p>Hayes anticipates a 30% correction from Bitcoin&#8217;s recent high of $48,000 in 2024, especially following the approval of Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs). He identifies potential support levels ranging from $30,000 to $35,000. Taking a proactive stance, Hayes has already exited positions in Solana and Bonk at $35,000, even if it meant a modest loss.</p>



<p>Positioning Bitcoin and cryptocurrencies as the last bastion of global open markets, Hayes asserts their ability to predict better fluctuations in the dollar&#8217;s liquidity compared to traditional financial markets. In the event of Bitcoin falling below $35,000, Hayes plans to invest in Solana (SOL), an innovative contract platform, and Dogwifhat (WIF), a meme asset on Ethereum, employing a &#8220;fishing from the bottom&#8221; strategy.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-text-align-center is-style-default has-medium-font-size is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>&#8220;I would choose Solana and WIF over Bitcoin&#8221;  </p>
<cite>Arthur Hayes</cite></blockquote>



<p>Dogwifhat is trading at $0.343, showing a significant 50% increase in the last 24 hours. In contrast, Solana is priced at $86.16, reflecting a 5.5% uptick from the previous day. While Dogwifhat&#8217;s recent price movements have displayed volatility between $0.330 and $0.355, some experts predict a potential return to around $0.45, similar to mid-January levels. Despite Hayes&#8217; optimism, technical indicators offer mixed signals, introducing an element of uncertainty to Dogwifhat&#8217;s future price.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/revealing-arthur-hayes-top-altcoin-picks-for-2024/">Revealing Arthur Hayes&#8217; Top Altcoin Picks for 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/revealing-arthur-hayes-top-altcoin-picks-for-2024/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is PayPal Stablecoin? Here&#8217;s what we know so far</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-paypal-stablecoin-pyusd/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-paypal-stablecoin-pyusd/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 11:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6461</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>PayPal&#8217;s launch of PayPal USD, a U.S. dollar-pegged stablecoin, is indeed a significant milestone for the company and the broader digital payments industry. This move demonstrates PayPal&#8217;s commitment to staying at the forefront of innovation and meeting the evolving needs of its customers. By offering a stablecoin payment option, PayPal is providing its users with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-paypal-stablecoin-pyusd/">What is PayPal Stablecoin? Here&#8217;s what we know so far</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>PayPal&#8217;s launch of PayPal USD, a U.S. dollar-pegged stablecoin, is indeed a significant milestone for the company and the broader digital payments industry. This move demonstrates PayPal&#8217;s commitment to staying at the forefront of innovation and meeting the evolving needs of its customers.</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-layout-flex wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-text-align-center wp-element-button" href="/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange PYUSD Now!</a></div>
</div>



<p>By offering a stablecoin payment option, PayPal is providing its users with increased convenience, efficiency, and security in their transactions. Stablecoins, backed by traditional currencies like the U.S. dollar, offer stability and eliminate the volatility often associated with cryptocurrencies. This feature makes stablecoins a reliable and attractive option for both individuals and businesses.</p>



<p>Furthermore, PayPal&#8217;s entry into the stablecoin market contributes to the mainstream adoption of digital currencies. PayPal&#8217;s endorsement of stablecoins brings further legitimacy and trust to the cryptocurrency ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>



<p>CoinCannon is constantly committed to delivering the utmost quality to customers.</p>



<p> which is why we promptly incorporated PayPal&nbsp; Stablecoin into our website shortly after its initial release. You can exchange&nbsp; PayPal&nbsp; Stablecoin easily on CoinCannon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-pyusd">What is PYUSD?</h2>



<p>The launch of PayPal USD aligns with the growing demand for digital payments and the increasing popularity of cryptocurrencies. By integrating stablecoins into its platform, PayPal is catering to the needs and preferences of its user base, providing them with more choices and flexibility in managing their finances.<gwmw style="display:none;"></gwmw></p>



<p>Overall, PayPal&#8217;s introduction of PayPal USD is a commendable step towards embracing the future of finance and empowering individuals and businesses with secure and efficient digital payment options.<gwmw style="display:none;"></gwmw></p>



<p>PayPal&#8217;s decision to fully back PayPal USD with U.S. dollar deposits, short-term Treasurys, and cash equivalents is a commendable approach that enhances the stability and reliability of the stablecoin. </p>



<p>This commitment to ensuring a 1-to-1 ratio between the stablecoin and the U.S. dollar.</p>



<p> demonstrates PayPal&#8217;s dedication to maintaining the trust and confidence of its users.</p>



<p>Partnering with Paxos Trust Company, a reputable fintech company specializing in blockchain, further strengthens the credibility and security of PayPal USD. This collaboration brings together the expertise of both companies, ensuring the seamless issuance and management of the stablecoin.<gwmw style="display:none;"></gwmw></p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><a href="/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><strong>You can exchange PayPal USD on CoinCannon Now!</strong><gwmw style="display:none;"></gwmw></a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h1 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-paypal-stablecoin-is-now-available">PayPal Stablecoin is Now Available&nbsp;</h1>



<p>PayPal&#8217;s president and CEO, acknowledges the need for a stable instrument that is digitally native and easily connected to fiat.</p>



<p> By introducing PayPal USD, PayPal is meeting this need and empowering individuals and businesses with a reliable and efficient means of conducting digital transactions.<gwmw style="display:none;"></gwmw><gwmw style="display:none;"></gwmw><gwmw style="display:none;"></gwmw></p>



<p>While it is important to be aware of the risks associated with stablecoins and cryptocurrencies in general, PayPal USD offers consumers increased flexibility and payment options. The decentralized nature of stablecoins provides users with greater control over their finances, and the ability to transfer and exchange the stablecoin easily adds to its appeal.<gwmw style="display:none;"></gwmw></p>



<p>It is crucial for potential investors to carefully consider their risk tolerance and conduct thorough research before investing in any financial asset, including stablecoins. However, PayPal&#8217;s commitment to stability, its partnership with a reputable company, and the benefits of increased flexibility and decentralization make PayPal USD an intriguing option for those looking to explore the world of digital currencies.</p>



<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has been cracking down on crypto companies, including Paxos, the partner of PayPal in issuing the stablecoin. The SEC threatened to sue Paxos in February, claiming that their Binance USD coin was not a registered security. This crackdown is part of the SEC&#8217;s efforts to enforce federal investment laws and address potential risks posed by crypto assets to the financial system. The collapse of Luna and its stablecoin, TerraUSD, last year further accelerated the SEC&#8217;s enforcement actions.</p>



<p>Although the SEC has targeted several crypto firms in recent years, it has yet to establish a clear framework for defining and regulating stablecoins. In the case of Paxos, the SEC argued that Binance USD qualifies as a security due to its profit-earning potential as an investment contract. This differs from the agency&#8217;s classification of Terra as an algorithmic stablecoin without investment backing.</p>



<p>Stablecoins are cryptocurrencies that are pegged to the value of another financial instrument, often a currency or commodity, and can be used for payments. The most prominent U.S. dollar-backed stablecoins include TetherUSD, USD Coin, and Binance USD.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-are-potential-use-cases-and-benefits-of-pyusd">What are potential use cases and benefits of PYUSD <gwmw style="display:none;"></gwmw></h2>



<p>The potential uses and benefits of a truly decentralized U.S. dollar stablecoin are significant for the average consumer. It would provide a borderless and potentially uncensorable version of the world&#8217;s reserve currency, enabling people in countries excluded from traditional U.S. payment rails to transact with ease.&nbsp;<gwmw style="display:none;"></gwmw></p>



<p>However, the introduction of PYUSD by PayPal through Venmo seems to limit its utility to banked Americans who already have access to digital representations of the U.S. dollar through PayPal&#8217;s existing products. Although PYUSD may be sent outside of PayPal&#8217;s ecosystem via the Ethereum network, it is unlikely that PayPal would allow this, as the stablecoin is not truly decentralized.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-benefits-of-pyusd">Benefits of PYUSD</h3>



<p>Nevertheless, if individuals who are banned from using Venmo or PayPal in the United States find a way to withdraw their funds via PYUSD on the Ethereum network, it could potentially benefit both PayPal and the consumers with frozen funds. However, this scenario is speculative, and the actual use cases and benefits of PYUSD are more likely to be exploited and utilized by financial institutions rather than directly impacting the average consumer.</p>



<p>Once the transaction gets confirmed on the blockchain network, Your cryptocurrency to PayPal stablecoin&nbsp; exchange will be completed easily and automatically without any waiting period by fulfilling the easy steps that we explained.<gwmw style="display:none;"></gwmw></p>



<p>You can always count on us. In case of any questions and problems, you can contact our 24/7 support via Email and Live Chat. We always get back to you ASAP!<br></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-paypal-stablecoin-pyusd/">What is PayPal Stablecoin? Here&#8217;s what we know so far</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-paypal-stablecoin-pyusd/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top 5 Altcoins for a low-risk Investment in 2022</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/top-5-altcoins-for-a-low-risk-investment/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/top-5-altcoins-for-a-low-risk-investment/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 06:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Top 5]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=3435</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Currently, Bitcoin is trading around $39,000 which means for your investment to double, the market cap has to increase by hundreds of billions. Obviously, altcoins are not this way. But, it&#8217;s really not easy to choose the right altcoin. In this article, we will go over the the top 5 altcoins to buy in 2022. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/top-5-altcoins-for-a-low-risk-investment/">Top 5 Altcoins for a low-risk Investment in 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Currently, Bitcoin is trading around $39,000 which means for your investment to double, the market cap has to increase by hundreds of billions. Obviously, altcoins are not this way. But, it&#8217;s really not easy to choose the right altcoin. In this article, we will go over the the top 5 altcoins to buy in 2022. Primarily, these top 5 altcoins are chosen for the long haul hence the low-risk nature. </p>



<p>Ask any crypto skeptic about their greatest concerns over the market and they will surely tell you the primary reason for their cynical view is simply the volatility. The meme wars on twitter and the absolute swarm of shitcoins in the market is also not helping. In a decentralized and low-regulated market, Investors need to feel safe about their investments. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><span class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Buy Cryptocurrencies on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a></span></p><p><span class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">No KYC</span></p></blockquote></figure>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Content</strong></h3>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li><strong>What Distinguishes the Top 5 Altcoins?</strong></li><li><strong>Ethereum</strong></li><li><strong>ADA</strong></li><li><strong>Algorand</strong></li><li><strong>Polkadot</strong></li><li><strong>VeChain</strong></li><li><strong>Where to buy the top 5 altcoins</strong></li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Distinguishes the Top 5 Altcoins?</strong></h2>



<p>To begin with, an investor must look for the chief premise behind the cryptocurrency to invest in. There are questions to ask and certain information gaps to fill. In that case, we should look for certain qualities such as the infrastructure, the platform, the function and the possible progress in the future. Fortunately, the top 5 altcoins we are going to introduce are well-known for providing solid platforms with revolutionary technological inventions. Despite moving in different directions, all of them are highly progressive, especially when it comes to adoption of new technology. According to numerous analysts, these 5 altcoins are safe bets for the future:</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong><a href="http://ethereum.org" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Ethereum</a></strong></h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="840" height="400" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/image.jpg" alt="Ethereum - top 5 altcoins
" class="wp-image-3436" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/image.jpg 840w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/image-300x143.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/image-768x366.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 840px) 100vw, 840px" /></figure>



<p>Long and short of it, Ethereum is a decentralized blockchain platform. It is essentially a decentralized public ledger for verifying and recording transactions. However, it is considered as one of the largest and most diverse networks out there. </p>



<p>The open-source platform provides a plethora of services to millions of people without geographical restrictions. On the platform, users can create or share services such as business, financial or even entertainment. Therefore, we have an ecosystem where users can pay fees in form of crypto to use the services.</p>



<p>The native cryptocurrency of the platform is Ether (ETH). In terms of market value, it is second, standing only behind Bitcoin. ETH was a revolutionary currency since it managed to compensate for many of Bitcoin`s shortcomings. Problems such as, high gas fees, scalability and even the high transaction fees. However, day by day we see the Ethereum platform utilize revolutionary methods to make the ecosystem even more efficient. &nbsp;</p>



<p>Considering the progressive outlook and the impressive background, investing on ETH can be considered as a safe bet for the future.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong><a href="http://cardano.org" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ADA</a></strong></h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="840" height="400" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/cardano-2.jpg" alt="ADA - Cardano - top 5 altcoins" class="wp-image-3437" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/cardano-2.jpg 840w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/cardano-2-300x143.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/cardano-2-768x366.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 840px) 100vw, 840px" /></figure>



<p>And here we have a crowd favorite! The third generation of the blockchain platform that has a cult following. It was Founded by Charles Hoskinson, one of the main creators of Ethereum. The Cardano project not only was more efficient than the previous ones, it revolutionized the blockchain technology. The Cardano project is one of the leading pioneers of the proof of stake algorithm. As compared with the proof of work, it is vastly more efficient and eco-friendly. You can read a more extensive introduction in <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-ada-a-guide-to-the-cardano-project/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is ADA</a>.</p>



<p>ADA, the native token of the Cardano platform is currently the number 5 cryptocurrency by market cap. In terms of investments, as of August 3, 2021, there is more than $31 billion in the stake pools. A staggering number that is almost double of what ETH investors have staked.</p>



<p>The distinguishing element for ADA is that Cardano has a huge emphasis on scientific literature. Their progressive methods must be approved by academics all around the world. In a sense, they care equally for both quality and quantity of progress.</p>



<p>The rate at which Cardano is expanding is a testament to their forward thinking methods. With smart contracts, stablecoin  &#8220;Djed&#8221; and many more additions coming to the platform, ADA is looking like a snack!</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Algorand</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="840" height="400" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Exchange-Algorand-ALGO-to-PayPal-lowest-Fees-1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-5095" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Exchange-Algorand-ALGO-to-PayPal-lowest-Fees-1.jpg 840w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Exchange-Algorand-ALGO-to-PayPal-lowest-Fees-1-300x143.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Exchange-Algorand-ALGO-to-PayPal-lowest-Fees-1-768x366.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 840px) 100vw, 840px" /></figure>



<p>Officially launched in 2019, Algorand is a proof of stake blockchain network with great emphasis on scalability and speed. As on open-source and decentralized network, Algorand is not a new idea to begin with. However, where it proves to be different is the unique design that allows for faster consensus. With a two-tiered structure, this payment-focused network achieves amazing scalability.</p>



<p>Currently, Algorand network can process over 1000 transactions per second while transaction finality takes less than five seconds. At this point you might say that there are faster networks out there. Well, yes but actually no!</p>



<p>We’ve previously talked about the blockchain trilemma on this blog. Essentially, it is difficult and rare for a blockchain to offer security, speed and decentralization. For example, Solana network is one of the fastest ones out there but it is not that decentralized. In that regard, Algorand is maintaining all positive aspects of an ideal blockchain at once.</p>



<p>ALGO is currently 29th in the ranks with a market cap of $4.6 billion. You can buy ALGO on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong><a href="http://polkadot.network" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Polkadot</a></strong></h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="840" height="400" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Polkadot_OG.jpg" alt="Polkadot - top 5 altcoins" class="wp-image-3439" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Polkadot_OG.jpg 840w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Polkadot_OG-300x143.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Polkadot_OG-768x366.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 840px) 100vw, 840px" /></figure>



<p>And here we have yet another third generation blockchain network found by a previous Ethereum member. Initially, Gavin James Wood had a different vision in mind about the (PoS) algorithm. The final goal is to create an infrastructure to create a network of blockchains that are effortlessly communicating with each other.</p>



<p>The multiple blockchain approach provides a better cross-chain interoperability and easier communication. Gavin believes that a single blockchain network can never be complete and a multi-chain architecture will be much more efficient.</p>



<p>The DOT is the token for this multi-chain network. It is currently number 9 by market cap. With the first ICO in 2017, it managed to raise $145 million. Despite being relatively new, it has experienced a huge growth in popularity. DOT has had one of the most successful initial coin offerings in history, raising over 200 million in two ICOs, first one in 2017 and the other in 2020.</p>



<p>All in all, DOT is a solid choice for investment for three reasons: first, the infrastructure is solid and forward looking. Second, the tremendous success can be a testament of the potential for growth. Third, the network is in no way limited to one blockchain making the future technology implementations effortless.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">VeChain</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="840" height="400" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Exchange-VeChain-VET-to-PayPal-Best-Rates.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-5094" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Exchange-VeChain-VET-to-PayPal-Best-Rates.jpg 840w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Exchange-VeChain-VET-to-PayPal-Best-Rates-300x143.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Exchange-VeChain-VET-to-PayPal-Best-Rates-768x366.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 840px) 100vw, 840px" /></figure>



<p>At this point, we all know how blockchain technology can go far beyond a platform for cryptocurrencies. VeChain is a perfect example of a pragmatic blockchain network designed to increase efficiency in business.</p>



<p>The network utilizes distributed ledger technology (DLT) to streamline and manage supply chain complexities. Basically, the VeChain platform enhances supply chain management and business related processes and eases the flow of information. As a sophisticated data management network, it provides a mapped out view of an organization by managing all data.</p>



<p>In a conventional supply chain ecosystem, the data for business processes can be distributed in multiple silos. This can negatively affect business flow in the ecosystem which could ultimately decrease efficiency. VeChain network solves this issue by disintermediating information from all data silos.</p>



<p>VET is currently 42 in the ranks with a market cap of almost $3 billion. It is also one of the low risk altcoins with a good track record. You can also Buy VET on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>You can Buy The Top 5 Altcoins on CoinCannon</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>



<p> &nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/top-5-altcoins-for-a-low-risk-investment/">Top 5 Altcoins for a low-risk Investment in 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/top-5-altcoins-for-a-low-risk-investment/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is Solana?</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-solana/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-solana/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 08:41:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[What is Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=3998</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Solana has been a rising main character amongst cryptocurrencies lately. Currently ranked as the 6TH coin by market cap, it quickly managed to rise in the ranks. The swift growth also means that the people onboard the Solana train saw massive profits too. Jumping from $1.50 in January 2021 to $142 as of now October [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-solana/">What is Solana?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Solana has been a rising main character amongst cryptocurrencies lately. Currently ranked as the 6<sup>TH</sup> coin by market cap, it quickly managed to rise in the ranks. The swift growth also means that the people onboard the Solana train saw massive profits too. Jumping from $1.50 in January 2021 to $142 as of now October 12, 2021, the fans are basking in the tears of the haters.</p>



<p>In this article, we take a look at how the Solana network managed to achieve success in such short time. Furthermore, we’ll examine the native token SOL for future applications and capabilities. You can also learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/">exchange Solana on CoinCannon</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Content</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Solana the Ethereum Killer</strong></li><li><strong>The Impressive Background of Solana</strong></li><li><strong>Pioneering Technology</strong></li><li><strong>The SOL Token</strong></li><li><strong>Where can I Exchange Solana</strong></li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Solana the Ethereum Killer</strong></h2>



<p>The king of the hill can only go down. That is where Ethereum stands, on top of the altcoin hill. And the competitors are closing in. And perhaps amongst competitors like <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/luna-price-reaches-all-time-high-at-35/">Luna</a>, <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/avalanche-an-ethereum-competitor-raises-230-million/">Avalanche</a> and <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/cardano-platform-is-being-showered-with-money/">ADA</a>, Solana was the one to outperform the all.</p>



<p>In short, Solana is a blockchain platform for decentralized applications (DApps). The network utilizes Proof of Stake consensus algorithm. However, in a world full of PoS blockchain networks, Solana has managed to achieve some impressive figures. The network can support up to 50,000 transactions per second (TPS) and requires 400 milliseconds to build a block. With the quickly increasing number of validators currently at 1,061, the network is one of the fastest out there.</p>



<p>However, what good is a fast network if expensive? Well, in terms of transaction fees, the Solana network maintains the most competitive fees across the board. With an average of $0.00025 per transaction, it’s no wonder why many of the largest <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/go-solana-sol-dethrones-doge-in-the-ranks/">institutional investors</a> use this network.</p>



<p>This flexible network has smart contract capabilities, DeFi, NFT, Web3 and many more. According to the official website, the ecosystem has currently over 400 running projects.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Impressive Background of Solana</strong></h2>



<p>Found in 2017 by Anatoly Yakovenko, a former Qualcomm member, along with Eric Williams and Greg Fitzgerald, the network aimed to create a more efficient and scalable platform.</p>



<p>The team consists of former members of companies such as Google, Apple, Microsoft, Qualcomm, Dropbox, Intel and more.</p>



<p>In that regard, the network is backed by many years of experience in some of the best companies around the world.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Pioneering Technology</strong></h2>



<p>The network famously utilizes 8 core technologies invented by their teams. Each of the eight is exclusive to Solana and is proven to be highly successful.</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Proof of History (PoH)</strong> acts as a synchronized clock</li><li><strong>Tower BFT</strong> is a consensus algorithm utilizing PoH</li><li><strong>Turbine</strong> is a protocol that divides the data into smaller parts so that they reach the nodes easier and faster</li><li><strong>Gulf Stream </strong>is a protocol that allows the nodes to execute the transactions ahead of time, increasing the speed</li><li><strong>Sealevel </strong>is a processing engine that allows concurrent smart contract running at the same time</li><li><strong>Pipeline </strong>distributes transaction data to different hardware therefore a more efficient data processing is achieved</li><li><strong>Cloudbreak </strong>is an optimized data structure</li><li><strong>Archivers </strong>is the data storage for the network</li></ol>



<p>Generally speaking, the Proof of History, keeps the historical records for all transactions and events. It allows the nodes to go through the records at any time and track them easily. It is a revolutionary step forward for the blockchain technology.</p>



<p>These technologies have proven to be working well together as a cohesive unit. And with that, the network is able to maintain efficiency.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The SOL Token</strong></h2>



<p>The SOL is the native token of the Solana network. Currently ranked as the 6<sup>th</sup> cryptocurrency by market cap, it has skyrocketed in value in very short time.</p>



<p>To justify the massive surge in price, we have to consider two main causes.</p>



<p>First, the institutional investors especially in China utilize the network to cut down the costs. As an Ethereum alternative, the network has much lower transaction fees and much better scalability thanks to the innovative technologies. Hence, massive sums of money flows into the network increasing the value of SOL. Subsequently, the investors see this as an opportunity to make large investments. A win-win case!</p>



<p>Second, the NFT hype has also been responsible for the surge in price. The Solana network has been one of the very first platforms to host NFTs and with the lower gas fees, it is a great platform to build and host NFTs. The network has created <a href="sollet.io">their own marketplace</a>.</p>



<p>And as for the ultimate nod to the platform, the investment giant <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/grayscale-adds-solana-and-uniswap-to-assets/">Grayscale has added Solana</a> in the list of their supported assets.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Where Can I Exchange Solana</strong></h2>



<p>You can exchange Solana on <a href="http://hi.exchange">jolixo</a> with the best rates at any moment. Considering the innovative technologies, the promising capabilities and the proven success, Solana seems to be one of the better investments. It holds so much potential as a flexible and efficient network and the native token SOL looks great in both technical and fundamental analysis.</p>



<p>If you are wondering how to exchange your cryptocurrencies into PayPal, you can visit our <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/">step by step guide</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange">jolixo</a></strong></h2>



<p>CoinCannon is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, <a href="http://hi.exchange">jolixo</a> does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.okchanger.com/exchangers/jolixo">OkChanger</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. We are listed on <a href="http://bestchange.com">Bestchange</a> and are always amongst the top exchanges.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="http://blog.hi.echange">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-solana/">What is Solana?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-solana/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Avalanche, an Ethereum Competitor Raises $230 Million</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/avalanche-an-ethereum-competitor-raises-230-million/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/avalanche-an-ethereum-competitor-raises-230-million/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 06:53:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVA LABS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVALANCHE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=3766</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Avalanche Blockchain, an open, programmable smart contracts platform for decentralized applications has raised $230 Million from selling AVAX. AVAX Token has a 65% Jump The native token of the Avalanche network AVAX experience massive gains in the last week. This is due to a private sale event that took place. An investing group led by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/avalanche-an-ethereum-competitor-raises-230-million/">Avalanche, an Ethereum Competitor Raises $230 Million</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://www.avax.network/">Avalanche Blockchain</a>, an open, programmable smart contracts platform for decentralized applications has raised $230 Million from selling AVAX.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>AVAX Token has a 65% Jump</strong></h2>



<p>The native token of the Avalanche network <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-09-16/avalanche-raises-230-million-from-sale-of-surging-crypto-token">AVAX experience massive gains in the last week</a>. This is due to a private sale event that took place. An investing group led by Polychain and Three Arrows Capital made huge investments buying AVAX causing the price surge and reach all time high. Primarily, this was an effort to amplify the growth of DeFi and other capabilities of the Avalanche network.</p>



<p>The president of AVA Labs said in a statement: “We have been relying on the technology having great organic growth, and now it’s time to supercharge that growth,”</p>



<p>Subsequently, AVAX managed to enter the top 20 cryptocurrency club as it’s currently ranked as the <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/avalanche/">11<sup>th</sup> with a market cap of $16.3 billion</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Ethereum Killers on the Rise</strong></h2>



<p>Unfortunately, Ethereum has had poor performance in the past month as many investors and institutional customers are unhappy. The high transaction fees and scalability have been the primary complaints about the network. Naturally, many institutions have been looking for alternative DeFi networks to continue with their payments process. In that regard some of the foremost Ethereum competitors are now on the rise.</p>



<p>We specifically named <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/go-solana-sol-dethrones-doge-in-the-ranks/">Avalanche as a potential surging Ethereum alternative</a> on September 5, less than two weeks before writing this article.</p>



<p>At this point, Solana, Luna, ADA, Cosmos and Avalanche are <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/solana-luna-and-algorand-remain-bullish-reach-ath/">legitimate contenders looking to flip Ethereum</a>. As they rise in the ranks, not only the inflows but also the exposure to the community grows exponentially.</p>



<p>We’ve said it before and will say it again, Ethereum 2.0 has to be awesome. As the opponents gain the upper hand in claiming institutional investors favor, Ethereum is losing ground in the competitive market. In that regard, the PoS algorithm has to result in great improvements, providing the users with many, if not all of the benefits the rising alternatives can provide.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Avalanche to the Moon?</strong></h2>



<p>Kid you not, the Avalanche network is only 1-year-old. Even more surprising than that, during this one year they have hosted more than 225 DeFi projects like, Tether, SushiSwap, Chainlink, Circle, and The Graph.</p>



<p>Long and short of it, Avalanche has turned up with a bazooka in a gunfight and has a better KDR than the Doom Slayer. The latest price hike for AVAX will definitely put the network on the radar.</p>



<p>In terms of future predictions, we can’t possibly know the outcomes. However, one could safely assume a bullish stance on Avalanche only by looking at the 1-year performance.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Good News!</strong></h2>



<p>We are proud to announce hi.exchange will soon add AVAX to the list of supported cryptocurrencies for <a href="http://hi.exchange">Hi Exchange</a> Make sure you check <a href="http://blog.hi.exchange">our blog</a> on a daily basis as well as on social media to stay up to date with our latest announcements, Opinion articles, news and technical analysis.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/avalanche-an-ethereum-competitor-raises-230-million/">Avalanche, an Ethereum Competitor Raises $230 Million</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/avalanche-an-ethereum-competitor-raises-230-million/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin price Skyrockets Following Fake News</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/litecoin-price-skyrockets-following-fake-news/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/litecoin-price-skyrockets-following-fake-news/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 07:08:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Walmart]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=3739</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin had a main character moment two days ago. credible publications such as Reuters, CNBC and Yahoo Finance made reports of a partnership between Litecoin and Walmart. As part of the collaboration, it was stated that Walmart was ready to accept Litecoin as payment. How did the Litecoin Hoax Begin? Following a fake press release [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/litecoin-price-skyrockets-following-fake-news/">Litecoin price Skyrockets Following Fake News</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Litecoin had a main character moment two days ago. credible publications such as <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/walmart-accept-litecoin-payments-2021-09-13/">Reuters</a>, <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/13/walmart-to-accept-payments-with-cryptocurrencies-using-litecoin.html">CNBC</a> and <a href="https://news.yahoo.com/litecoin-whipsawed-by-walmart-hoax-exposing-extremely-adversarial-environment-of-crypto-163629770.html">Yahoo Finance</a> made reports of a partnership between Litecoin and Walmart. As part of the collaboration, it was stated that Walmart was ready to accept Litecoin as payment.</p>



<p><strong>How did the Litecoin Hoax Begin?</strong></p>



<p>Following a fake press release from Walmart, the quick circulation of the news began to take place. All of a sudden, this extremely bullish news spread everywhere. Naturally, LTChad a <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/litecoin-price-analysis-september-14-2021/">spike in price, jumping from $178 to $235</a>. However, the impact was so powerful that it caused a massive jump for Bitcoin to reach $47,000, an important resistance level from $44,600.</p>



<p>To make the situation worse, the official account of <a href="https://twitter.com/litecoin?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor">Litecoin on Twitter</a> posted “Walmart Announces Major Partnership with Litecoin”.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="840" height="400" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/LTC1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-3741" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/LTC1.jpg 840w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/LTC1-300x143.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/LTC1-768x366.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 840px) 100vw, 840px" /></figure>



<p>This tweet has people angry since the spike has had many traders lost their investments. The Litecoin foundation released a statement about the news saying that the social media marketing team jumped the gun on the news. According to them, “the team members were a little bit too eager” to share the news.<br><a href="https://twitter.com/LTCFoundation/status/1437484869664137221">https://twitter.com/LTCFoundation/status/1437484869664137221?s=20</a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>When the Dust Settled</strong></h2>



<p>Thankfully, The Walmart team was quick to let the publications know about the fraudulent nature of the news (<a href="https://corporate.walmart.com/newsroom/2021/09/13/walmart-statement-in-response-to-fake-litecoin-press-release">read the official press release here</a>). Shortly after, the Litecoin foundation declared on Twitter that the news is false.</p>



<p>And Just like any other story, the falling action manifested in the charts. LTC price fell just as much as it had surged in a matter of hours. Bitcoin was no exception as it quickly fell down to below $45k.</p>



<p>The fake press release was put on <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/">GlobeNewswire</a> and never appeared on Walmart’s official website.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Where can I Cash Out my Litecoin?</strong></h2>



<p>If you are looking to <a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your Litecoin into Webmoney, Perfect money or PayPal</a>, hi.exchange provides excellent exchange services. with 24/7 customer support and the best exchange rates at any moment, our team of professionals will guarantee our customers with a secure, easy and smooth exchange experience. And to follow our latest opinion articles, technical analysis and news, <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">stay right here</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/litecoin-price-skyrockets-following-fake-news/">Litecoin price Skyrockets Following Fake News</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/litecoin-price-skyrockets-following-fake-news/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana, Luna and Algorand Remain Bullish and Reach ATH</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-luna-and-algorand-remain-bullish-reach-ath/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-luna-and-algorand-remain-bullish-reach-ath/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 07:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorand]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Luna]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=3705</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Solana, Luna and Algorand managed to climb high in a bearish week of the crypto market and bring hope to the investors. In the early hours of September 7, 2021, the day El Salvador officially announced Bitcoin as a legal tender, the market had a tragic crash. Bitcoin fell from almost $52,000 to $43,000. Subsequently, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-luna-and-algorand-remain-bullish-reach-ath/">Solana, Luna and Algorand Remain Bullish and Reach ATH</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Solana, Luna and Algorand managed to climb high in a bearish week of the crypto market and bring hope to the investors.</p>



<p>In the early hours of September 7, 2021, the day El Salvador officially announced Bitcoin as a legal tender, <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/over-3-54-billion-liquidated-in-a-shocking-day-for-bitcoin/">the market had a tragic crash</a>. Bitcoin fell from almost $52,000 to $43,000. Subsequently, a vast majority of altcoins had to suffer as well. For the past few days, Bitcoin and the majority of altcoins have been consolidating yet the overall outlook remains bearish.</p>



<p>The Solana, Luna and Algorand however, managed to remain bullish and even reach all-time highs.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Solana Reaches ATH at $190</strong></h2>



<p>Solana has been on a roll lately, skyrocketing from $25 to $180 in less than 7 weeks. With an astonishing <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/solana/">405% growth in 3 months</a>, It has managed to reach #6 in the ranks. We did extensively <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/solana-price-reaches-over-100-sol-8th-in-the-ranks/">introduce the Solana network and the reason for this profound success</a> in a recent article. However, to give you the gist of it, The Solana network is a next-gen DeFi infrastructure that serves as a great alternative for Ethereum. It significantly cuts down on gas and transaction fees. In that regard, they have managed to attract quite a bit of institutional investors.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the Solana network has proven to be a hotspot for the NFTs and they have recently opened their own NFT marketplace <a href="http://www.solsea.io/">Solsea</a>.</p>



<p>All in all, the Solana chart is defying the laws of gravity in a week when altcoins are struggling.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Luna Reaches ATH at $41</strong></h2>



<p>Less than two weeks ago, we reported on the amazing success Luna had flying up to $35. Today, despite the bear market, <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/terra-luna/">Luna is at $41 with an eye-watering 653.50% growth in 3 months</a>.</p>



<p>If you want to know more about Luna and the Terra network, <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/luna-price-reaches-all-time-high-at-35/">you can read our article here</a>. However, the Terra network is pretty much the same in function as the Solana. The terra network was developed as a blockchain network for payments through stablecoins. It was essentially built for the Asian e-commerce market and boy oh boy did Asian billionaires love it. The Terra network radically cuts down on transaction fees and as a results, service providers can save millions of dollars per year.</p>



<p>The Terra network is yet another fierce competitor for Ethereum and looks to have great potential for growth.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Algorand Reaches ATH at $2.14</strong></h2>



<p>Currently ranked as 17<sup>th</sup> cryptocurrency by market cap, Algorand has surged 86% this week and 139% this month according to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/algorand/">CoinMarketCap</a>.</p>



<p>As a blockchain for DeFi applications, <a href="https://algodesk.medium.com/algodesk-io-v-2-0-is-live-on-mainnet-e3aed1aa17a3">Algorand announced an upcoming version of their asset management platform on Thursday</a>. However, the bullish run seems to stem from a recent shoutout by a former Trump administration official Anthony Scaramucci on CNBC.</p>



<p>“There’s a lot of great stuff happening in this space… as more digital applications happen, some of those altcoins, stuff like Algorand or Cardano, or things like Ethereum, will continue to rise because there’s actually great use cases for them.” Said the SkyCoinCannon Capital founder.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Recurring Pattern</strong></h2>



<p>Taking a look at some of the best-performing altcoins, we can see that most of them are blockchain networks for DeFi infrastructures that can be considered as alternatives for Ethereum. The high gas and transaction fees of the Ethereum network has investors and service providers looking for more efficient alternatives. In that regard, we should wait and see how Ethereum 2.0 will turn out. If it fails to make sufficient improvements, competitors might flip it pretty soon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Where can I Buy Solana, Luna and Algorand?</strong></h2>



<p>Good news is that we will very soon have these three altcoins on <a href="hi.exchange">Hi.exchange</a>. Make sure you <a href="blog.hi.exchange">check our blog</a> on a daily basis as well as on social media to stay up to date with our latest announcements, Opinion articles, news and technical analysis.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-luna-and-algorand-remain-bullish-reach-ath/">Solana, Luna and Algorand Remain Bullish and Reach ATH</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-luna-and-algorand-remain-bullish-reach-ath/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Go Solana! SOL Dethrones DOGE in the Ranks</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/go-solana-sol-dethrones-doge-in-the-ranks/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/go-solana-sol-dethrones-doge-in-the-ranks/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 07:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solsea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=3655</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Apparently, Solana isn’t done making headlines. On August 30, we reported on the amazing price hike Solana had and subsequent achievement of being 8th in the ranks. However, it wasn’t your average pump and dump since SOL has kept on growing since then. With an impressive 12% climb to $145, Solana’s market cap reached $42 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/go-solana-sol-dethrones-doge-in-the-ranks/">Go Solana! SOL Dethrones DOGE in the Ranks</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Apparently, Solana isn’t done making headlines. On August 30, <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/solana-price-reaches-over-100-sol-8th-in-the-ranks/">we reported on the amazing price hike Solana had and subsequent achievement of being 8<sup>th</sup> in the ranks</a>.</p>



<p>However, it wasn’t your average pump and dump since SOL has kept on growing since then. With an impressive 12% climb to $145, Solana’s market cap reached $42 billion, overtaking Dogecoin with an inferior $38 billion. Dara provided by <a href="messari.io">Messari</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How does Solana keep on winning?</strong></h2>



<p>To begin with, the <a href="solana.com">Solana network</a> has successfully proven to be an excellent DeFi infrastructure. It has been adopted by institutional investors as an alternative for the Ethereum network. So naturally, there is an enormous amount of money flowing in the network. However, the NFT craze is also responsible for bringing massive inflows into the network.</p>



<p>Since the Launch of the Degenerate Ape Academy on August 15, the extremely bullish run for SOL has begun. Furthermore, another big reason for the jump could also be the launch of <a href="solsea.io">Solsea</a>, the dedicated Solana NFT marketplace.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What do we learn from Solana?</strong></h2>



<p>As Dogecoin is having a decline, we can see legitimate tokens with strong fundamental utility are coming up in the ranks. Tokens such as Luna, Avalanche, Cosmos, ADA, NEO and Solana are getting what they deserve according to their functionality and utility. Pragmatically speaking, the crypto market is in dire need of improved reputation. The pump and dump events (ELON), fraudulent ICO’s and shitcoins have created a negative social image for crypto. Fortunately, as these fundamentally strong projects rise, crypto can recover its constructive image.</p>



<p>By surpassing DOGE, Solana proved that at the end of the day, it is function that determines the value, not twitter accounts of billionaires.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Should I Buy Solana?</strong></h2>



<p>If you are to hodl, SOL seems to be a great investment. Even if the NFT craze miraculously dies out, the network has great potential and billions of invested assets in circulation. For short-term however, considering the 14-day RSI at 70, indicating a possible slowdown in rally, SOL seems to be too volatile for us to suggest buying. Generally speaking, high volatility accompanies by a slowdown in trend could provide a good opportunity to sell. So do your research before any investment.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Good News!</strong></h2>



<p>We are proud to announce <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/solana-price-reaches-over-100-sol-8th-in-the-ranks/hi.exchange">jolixo</a> will soon add Solana to the list of supported cryptocurrencies for exchange. Make sure you <a href="http://blog.hi.exchange">check our blog on a daily basis</a> as well as on social media to stay up to date with our latest announcements, Opinion articles, news and technical analysis.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/go-solana-sol-dethrones-doge-in-the-ranks/">Go Solana! SOL Dethrones DOGE in the Ranks</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/go-solana-sol-dethrones-doge-in-the-ranks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Coin predictions, Where is Ripple Headed?</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/xrp-coin-predictions-where-is-ripple-headed/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/xrp-coin-predictions-where-is-ripple-headed/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 09:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC Lawsuit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=3619</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>XRP coin has always been a cryptocurrency with big ambitions. But daring to dream comes with quite a bit of baggage. RippleNet has proven to have incredible function in DeFi not only for its currency, but a robust payment infrastructure. The provided services for the banks and financial institutions have been successful in cutting costs [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/xrp-coin-predictions-where-is-ripple-headed/">XRP Coin predictions, Where is Ripple Headed?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>XRP coin has always been a cryptocurrency with big ambitions. But daring to dream comes with quite a bit of baggage. RippleNet has proven to have incredible function in DeFi not only for its currency, but a robust payment infrastructure. The provided services for the banks and financial institutions have been successful in cutting costs as well as transaction speed. <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-ripple/">You can read our extensive review of Ripple here</a>.</p>



<p>However, no network is perfect. The Achilles` heel in case of ripple is the not so decentralized aspect of the network. If you have been following the news, we know that the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission has an active lawsuit against ripple. A vast majority of concerns that SEC has expressed are due to the more centralized aspect of Ripple. Essentially, SEC argues that Ripple co-founder Christian Larsen and CEO Bradley Garlinghouse sold XRP Coins in unregistered security offering to investors in order to raise funds while providing very little information about its business, <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2020-338">Read the official press release here</a>.</p>



<p>Unfortunately, the lawsuit did have a negative impact on XRP Coin price. Despite the ongoing investigations, XRP coin has managed to bounce back from the plummet and is now recovering.</p>



<p>As of today, August 31, 2021, XRP Coin price stand at $1.129.</p>



<p>But the question is, considering all the challenges as well as the great potential, how does the future look for XRP coin?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How does the future look for XRP Coin?</strong></h2>



<p>In terms of price targets, <a href="https://digitalcoinprice.com/forecast/xrp/2021">DigitalCoin</a> predicts XRP Coin to reach $1.64 by the same time next year. And as for 2022, they believe Ripple will stand above $2. Meanwhile, <a href="https://longforecast.com/ripple-price-prediction-2018-2019-2020-2021-xrp-to-usd">Long Forecast</a> has a much more bearish stance on XRP Coin. They believe Ripple will trade between $0.76 and 0.96 by next year.</p>



<p>For a long-term outlook, Digital coins expects XRP coin to be around $3.70. However, Long Forecast remains bearish, believing XRP will go down to $0.23.</p>



<p>In that regard, the predictions and targets are convoluting at best. It seems that the SEC lawsuit decides the fate for XRP.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What do the Investors think?</strong></h2>



<p>Amongst the cult following of Ripple hodlers, there are many who believe XRP will come out triumphant. Subsequently, it will be the very first fully regulated cryptocurrency. In that case, it will have huge regulatory advantages leading banks and institutional investors to adopt the RippleNet. For that sweet scenario, XRP might reach above $10.</p>



<p>Speculations aside, we should wait for the lawsuit results in order to make the next move for our XRP investments.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Where can I Buy XRP coin?</strong></h2>



<p>You can buy or cash out you XRP in <a href="http://hi.exchange">jolixo</a> with the best possible rates. We utilize a fully automated system that determines the best rats at any moment. To make it an even better deal, our exchange offers 24/7 customer support. Finally, If you would like to follow our daily technical price analysis for XRP as well as the updates on the ongoing SEC lawsuit, <a href="http://blog.hi.exchange">follow our blog posts</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/xrp-coin-predictions-where-is-ripple-headed/">XRP Coin predictions, Where is Ripple Headed?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/xrp-coin-predictions-where-is-ripple-headed/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana Price Reaches over $100, SOL 8th in the Ranks</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-price-reaches-over-100-sol-8th-in-the-ranks/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-price-reaches-over-100-sol-8th-in-the-ranks/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 09:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=3609</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Solana fans rejoice! Solana Price now stands above $100. The cryptocurrency finally had a massive achievement by dethroning Polkadot of the 8th place in the ranks. Solana Price Hike Considering the impressive 250% growth in only a month, SOL was hot in demands as an Ethereum alternative. And finally, Solana price has entered the +$100 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-price-reaches-over-100-sol-8th-in-the-ranks/">Solana Price Reaches over $100, SOL 8th in the Ranks</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Solana fans rejoice! Solana Price now stands above $100. The cryptocurrency finally had a massive achievement by dethroning Polkadot of the 8<sup>th</sup> place in the ranks. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Solana Price Hike</strong></h2>



<p>Considering the impressive 250% growth in only a month, SOL was hot in demands as an Ethereum alternative. And finally, Solana price has entered the +$100 club. Solana has a market capitalization of approximately 28.5 billion, and an insane 24-hour trading volume of about 2.1 billion in the past 24 hours. In terms of Supply and circulating units, there are 290,944,595 units out of 488,630,611.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="524" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Capture-1024x524.jpg" alt="Solana Price" class="wp-image-3610" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Capture-1024x524.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Capture-300x154.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Capture-768x393.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Capture.jpg 1453w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Did Solana Skyrocket?</strong></h2>



<p><a href="http://Solana.com">The Solana network</a> is a next-gen DeFi infrastructure seeking to cut down on gas and transaction fees. Considering the high transaction fees of the primary altcoin infrastructure that is Ethereum, there are numerous alternative hubs in a fierce competition. Generally speaking, the Solana, Cosmos, Luna and Avalanche are the four primary competitor networks. And in case of Solana, it was essentially the institutional investors who favored the network and caused this huge jump in price. It should also be noted that Luna has had amazing success in the past few weeks too. <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/luna-price-reaches-all-time-high-at-35/">Read more about it here</a>.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the explosive hype for NFT`s and the launch of Degenerate Ape Academy managed to bring massive amounts of money into the network.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What does this mean for Ethereum?</strong></h2>



<p>Considering the powerful competitors on the rise, it is obvious that institutional money is moving out of the Ethereum network. At the end of the day, transaction fees will determine which network stands above the rest. In that regard, we should wait and see how Ethereum 2.0 will perform.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Does the Future Hold for Solana?</strong></h2>



<p>Honestly, at this point, SOL looks to be holding a bright future. First of all, in terms of transaction fees, it is one of the best performing networks out there. Secondly, the scalability and speed is also on par with the best in the world. Lastly, NFT`s are performing better than ever and SOL plays a significant role in that as well. In many regards, Solana price is expected to climb even higher thanks to the solid and efficient ecosystem.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Good News!</strong></h2>



<p>We are proud to announce <a href="hi.exchange">hi.exchange</a> will soon add Solana to the list of supported cryptocurrencies for exchange. Make sure you <a href="blog.hi.exchange">check our blog on a daily basis</a> as well as on social media to stay up to date with our latest announcements, Opinion articles, news and technical analysis.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-price-reaches-over-100-sol-8th-in-the-ranks/">Solana Price Reaches over $100, SOL 8th in the Ranks</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-price-reaches-over-100-sol-8th-in-the-ranks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Luna Price Reaches All-Time high at $35</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/luna-price-reaches-all-time-high-at-35/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/luna-price-reaches-all-time-high-at-35/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 10:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Luna]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra Network]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=3600</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Luna Price is having a main character moment as it has reached the all-time high of $35. This massive growth comes when only 6 weeks ago, Luna price was around $6. However, there are many people wondering about the currently 12th largest cryptocurrency and what it is. The Terra Network success justifies Luna price Terra [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/luna-price-reaches-all-time-high-at-35/">Luna Price Reaches All-Time high at $35</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Luna Price is having a main character moment as it has reached the all-time high of $35. This massive growth comes when only 6 weeks ago, Luna price was around $6. However, there are many people wondering about the currently 12<sup>th</sup> largest cryptocurrency and what it is.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">The Terra Network success justifies Luna price</h2>



<p>Terra is a revolutionary blockchain network for payments through stablecoins. Luna is the native token for this decentralized network. Terra provides quick and reliable cross-border payments using fiat-pegged stablecoins. Other than the utility, the Terra network relies on staking of Luna coin as well as numerous stablecoins pegged to fiat currencies. So the question is, how good is the Terra network?</p>



<p>Well, this next-gen ecosystem was initially built for the expanding Asian e-commerce market. The goal was to create an efficient algorithm that has the capability to quickly evolve. And they had an enormous success in that regard. Utilizing the Terra network, service providers are able to save millions of dollar per year. The main contributing factor for this success is the much lower transaction fees. Whereas a 2.5% to 3% is considered a standard fee in the industry, Terra will only charge you 0.5% to 2%. &nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Where is Luna Headed</h2>



<p>Considering the massive adoption of the Terra network, the skyrocketing of Luna sounds well-justified. However, looking at the huge potential of the Terra ecosystem and the ever-expanding adoption of it, we can only expect Luna to be only getting started.</p>



<p><a href="https://digitalcoinprice.com/forecast/terra-luna">DigitalCoin</a> has predicted Luna price will reach around $48 by the end of this year. <a href="https://gov.capital/crypto/luna/">Gov Capital</a> on the other hand, is of the belief that Luna price will reach $62 by the August of next year.</p>



<p>All in all, despite the big price hike, Luna seems to be on a path to greatness.<br><br>To follow the latest opinion articles, technical analysis and news, <a href="blog.hi.exchange">stay right here</a>.<br><br></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/luna-price-reaches-all-time-high-at-35/">Luna Price Reaches All-Time high at $35</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/luna-price-reaches-all-time-high-at-35/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Exactly Is Shiba Inu?</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-shiba-inu/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-shiba-inu/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 20:48:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=3283</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Perhaps DogeCoin remains undisputed as the foremost of the memecoins, yet the new Ethereum-based token Shiba Inu has been flexing its muscles lately as a successor for the highly controversial Dogecoin. This happened while only a few people knew about what is SHIB and where did it come from? Sharply hitting a peak of 0.73 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-shiba-inu/">What Exactly Is Shiba Inu?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Perhaps <a href="/what-is-dogecoin-how-it-work/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">DogeCoin</a> remains undisputed as the foremost of the memecoins, yet the new Ethereum-based token Shiba Inu has been flexing its muscles lately as a successor for the highly controversial Dogecoin. This happened while only a few people knew about what is SHIB and where did it come from?</p>



<p>Sharply hitting a peak of 0.73 USD last week is a long way from the 0.01 USD since January, DOGE has certainly achieved a tremendous success in 2021. However, a new coin called SHIB has stolen the spotlight in the past few days with an incredible success carried out by an explosive growth in value, one that Binance&#8217;s CEO has called “super high risk” for investment purposes.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">What is the Story behind SHIB?</h2>



<p>The Shiba Inu or as shown in currency codes as SHIB, is a ERC20 token based on the Ethereum network. One might think of it as a shameless copy of the Dogecoin since both refer to the indigenous Japanese breed of dog Shiba Inu, yet SHIB`s achievements must not be taken lightly.</p>



<p>Based on the data provided by CoinGecko, Shiba stands at 0.00002858 USD (prices correct at the time of writing this article) with an approximate increase of 39000 percent, and only 1500 percent for the past week. Despite the lack of placement in the rankings of CoinGecko for SHIB, CoinMarketCap has estimated a staggering value of 11 billion USD, placing it as the 20th cryptocurrency in the world.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">The Explosive Price Hike of SHIB</h3>



<p>Since 31st July 2020, SHIB has had an astonishing 2 million percent growth which comparatively speaking is higher than both Bitcoin and Ethereum.</p>



<p>For a token that appeared out of nowhere, these figures are amazing to say the least. Despite lacking the 64 billion USD worth of Dogecoin, Shina Inu has had relatively more achievements in its short period of existence. Altogether, according to CoinGecko, Doge has had a 687% increase for the last month followed by a rough 14% in the last week. By the looks of it, the investors are seeking the same rapidly profitable experience of Doge in the last year.</p>



<p>Since being listed on the Binance, the high demand has been the primary reason ramping the price much higher than expected causing a shortage for ETH payment request address, according to the tweet put out by Binance`s CEO, an unlikely phenomenon that had never occurred before.</p>



<p>Yet despite Binance taking its fair share of the skyrocketing trade volume, the CEO of the <a href="/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">cryptocurrency exchange</a> has pointed out the volatility of SHIB and the possible high risk in his twitter:</p>



<p>“Some have voiced concerns about the $SHIB listing. We follow users. There is a large number of users demanding it, to the point where we ran out of ETH deposit addresses due to SHIB today. Never happened before for any other ERC20 coin. Not endorsing it. Super high risk. NFA.”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">What is SHIB and how it started</h2>



<p>Besides being an Ethereum-Based memcoin and a direct competitor for Dogecoin, what is Shiba Inu? According to the official website, SHIB is an “experiment in decentralized spontaneous community building,” and is the first of many planned dog-themed coins, as a token, it fuels the fire for the whole ecosystem. Also it is the first enlisted in ShibaSwap, the decentralized exchange for cryptocurrency. Developers state that half of the resources within the Uniswap protocol and the other half has been burned, meaning that there are no whales controlling the market behind the curtains. LEASH is another released token, though in limited quantities, it has experienced great earnings. Also BONES is set to be released as the Dogecoin killer in the decentralized ShibaSwap. There will even be a token by the name of Woofpaper, that the developers will provide details for in the future.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Total Worth of Shiba Inu</h2>



<p>The unknown developers have mined a total of 1 quadrillion SHIBs and have sent more than half to Ethereum founder Vitalik Buterin. The developers view these tokens as burned or off market with the hopes of boosting the trade value, yet Buterin still has access to the tokens and has not burned them yet.</p>



<p>Surely you will not be alone in finding all this ridiculous, but we have to remember how before becoming 2021`s top token and being supported by Elon Musk and Mark Cuban, Dogecoin was also a joke cryptocurrency. Can Shiba follow the same path? At least in the massive gains it has had we could say so.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Shiba Looking to Repeat the History</h3>



<p>Thanks to celebrity support and also numerous redditors predicting the 1-dollar price, Dogecoin has had a sharp growth.</p>



<p>Shiba`s official website states that the ERC20 token as the Dogecoin killer will not take long to move past DOGE in value.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Should You Invest in Shiba Inu</h3>



<p>The tempting attempt to become a millionaire by investing in Shiba will surely grow harder as the price of SHIB goes up. With a current market value of 11 billion USD, to reach a profit of ten folds from the investments of today, the market value must reach 130 billion and subsequently dethrone BinanceCoin (BNB) as the third cryptocurrency in the world. All leading to the conclusion that a fierce battle must be won with powerful competitors.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Why the Rapid Price Hike?</h3>



<p>For the most part, the deceiving hoard of investors looking for the next Dogecoin can be said to be the primary cause for the rise in price.</p>



<p>Even in the last 24 hours Shiba has had a noticeable rise. According to CoinMarketCap, SHIB stands at 0.00002885 USD while being at 0.0000006 in April as compared with Dogecoin standing at 0.51 USD now whilst being at 0.005 in first quarter of the year.</p>



<p>All that said, Elon Musk`s twits have also been highly effective. After jokingly saying he was looking for a Shiba Inu dog on twitter, a massive hoard of investors rushed to buy DOGE with such force that Binance quickly listed the token on Monday leading to a 260% rise. Other Chinese exchanges such as Huobi and OKEx also listed Shiba.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What Does the Future Hold for Shiba</h3>



<p>Shiba proceeded to shock everyone today with the massive 1500% increase in 7 days.</p>



<p>It is too difficult to make any predictions for the future, for all we know, this could be another one of the infamous Pump and Dumps that have happened in the past. According to the charts, we see that having suffered a 35% fall, the price is slowly gaining back. With the continuous trades of low quantities we can expect the continuation of growth, yet falling below 0.000027 could call this prediction null.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Conclusion</h2>



<p>Generally speaking, investing in cryptocurrencies, decentralized financial tokens and finance are high-risk trades since there is no reassurance of absolute success, make sure to be aware of possible hazards and generate tolerance for the possible loss of investments.</p>



<p>Do not forget that fluctuations are an inherent part of the market, therefore your investments can go up and down at any rate. As always, try not to invest in something you do not have sufficient knowledge for. Also, make investments with an amount of money that there is no urgency for.</p>



<p>What do you think about Shiba Inu? Can this memecoin dominate Dogecoin? Share your opinion with us and don’t forget to follow us on twitter for cryptocurrency prices and all the latest news.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-shiba-inu/">What Exactly Is Shiba Inu?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-shiba-inu/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
