<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Webmoney Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/webmoney/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 11:22:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Bitcoin to Webmoney [No Fees]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bitcoin-to-webmoney/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bitcoin-to-webmoney/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 07:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Webmoney]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6108</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you’re looking to exchange Bitcoin to Webmoney, CoinCannon is all you need. Fundamentally, BTC has been the centerpiece of all crypto market and will likely remain as the crowned king. With that, many investors will look to exchange BTC to various e-currencies. However, it is not that easy to find some exchange pairs online. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bitcoin-to-webmoney/">How to Exchange Bitcoin to Webmoney [No Fees]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you’re looking to exchange Bitcoin to Webmoney, <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is all you need. Fundamentally, BTC has been the centerpiece of all crypto market and will likely remain as the crowned king. With that, many investors will look to exchange BTC to various e-currencies. However, it is not that easy to find some exchange pairs online. Even still, you may find a platform that offers your pair but they seldom charge additional fees on the transaction. Luckily, CoinCannon offers a wide variety of exchange pairs all while charging no fees. On top of that, you get to enjoy full anonymity and 24/7 online support. In this article, we will go over how to exchange Bitcoin to Webmoney on CoinCannon.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/how-exchange-bitcoin-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Bitcoin to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Bitcoin to Webmoney?</strong></h2>



<p>For this transaction, you will need a verified and active Webmoney account. Make sure that the exchange amount does not exceed your deposit limit for WMZ. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon. Want a good reason why? How about winning $100 ever month!</p>



<p>Learn more about our <a href="https://hi.exchange/campaign/tether-giveaway" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Tether Giveaway</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Bitcoin?</strong></h2>



<p>This might still be a question to many, before reading about how to exchange, one must know where Bitcoins come from. Bitcoin is a digital currency that was developed following the housing market crash in January 2009. This cryptocurrency follows the ideas started out by the pseudonymous and mysterious Satoshi Nakamoto in a whitepaper. The identity of the individual or individuals that developed the software is still a mystery. Unlike government-issued currencies, Bitcoin is operated by a decentralized authority and offers the promise of lower transaction fees than traditional online payment mechanisms.</p>



<p>There are no physical Bitcoins and the coins you see are novelty coins that do not have any real value without the code inscribed on them. Bitcoin is only balances retained on a public ledger that everyone has transparent access to, and is verified by a massive amount of computing power along with all Bitcoin transactions. Bitcoins are not issued or supported as a commodity by any banks or governments, nor are individual bitcoins valuable. Although it is not legal tender, the popularity of Bitcoin charts is high, and hundreds of other virtual currencies collectively referred to as Altcoins have been launched following this cryptocurrency.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Webmoney?</strong></h2>



<p>WebMoney is an online payment system and a comprehensive tool for online business operations. It was originally developed as a money transfer system for US dollars in Russia in 1998 and since then, nearly 40 million people from all over the globe have joined the program.</p>



<p>WebMoney provides digital currency purses that can hold popular national currencies. The payment platform provides a P2P credit purse, global payment solutions, retail services, local payment products, online billing, and direct integration with other global financial service providers. On top of that, a number of countries worldwide are currently working on WebMoney and consumers pay WebMoney for the services of different companies from Spain, Poland, and Belgium.</p>



<p>Continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-webmoney/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Webmoney</a>”.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon for the Win!</strong></h2>



<p>Every exchange platform must maintain three important characteristics. Anonymity, affordability and reliability. We pride ourselves as a professional platform that offers all three.</p>



<p>For anonymity, CoinCannon requires no KYC or even a sign up process. The best way to protect your information is to not share them with anyone. And for that, we respect our customers and do not ask for their personal info.</p>



<p>As for affordability, CoinCannon utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. By doing so, we have managed to stay on top of the ranks on websites such as Bestchange and OkChanger.</p>



<p>Lastly, reliability is ensured for our customers with 24/7 online support. In case anything goes wrong, you will have our immediate support until the issue is resolved.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Bitcoin to Webmoney (WMZ)?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Enter the homepage first, then select Bitcoin on the left field and Webmoney WMZ on the right. Enter the amount you want to exchange and wait for the exchange rate to apply.</li><li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Webmoney address details and email address.</li><li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li><li>Complete the captcha and click on “exchange” to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. At this point, you will have the CoinCannon wallet address to send the Bitcoin to.&nbsp; After you have transferred your BTC, click on Pay Order button. Don’t forget to attach the screenshot for the BTC payment. your order will process swiftly.</li><li>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the Webmoney to your wallet ASAP.</li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>All Good!</strong></h2>



<p>Just like that, you have now exchanged Bitcoin to Webmoney. In general, Webmoney payments don’t take very long to process. Give it a few minutes and the WMZ will be in your wallet quickly. In the meantime, you can follow up on your order using the Track ID provided for you. Simply enter the track id in the required section on homepage to see at which point your order is. Remember not to share your Track ID with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bitcoin-to-webmoney/">How to Exchange Bitcoin to Webmoney [No Fees]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bitcoin-to-webmoney/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange AdvCash to Webmoney [No KYC]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-webmoney-wmz/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-webmoney-wmz/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 08:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AdvCash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange AdvCash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Webmoney]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6071</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking to exchange AdvCash to Webmoney? CoinCannon is the best platform for the job. With hundreds of payment platforms to choose from, exchanging them can cost you a lot of money. Furthermore, not all exchangers offer the direction you need. Thankfully, CoinCannon does not charge any additional fees on transactions and offers amazing rates. In [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-webmoney-wmz/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange AdvCash to Webmoney [No KYC]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking to exchange AdvCash to Webmoney? <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is the best platform for the job. With hundreds of payment platforms to choose from, exchanging them can cost you a lot of money. Furthermore, not all exchangers offer the direction you need. Thankfully, CoinCannon does not charge any additional fees on transactions and offers amazing rates. In the meantime, you will not have to compromise on your privacy since the platform does not ask for any personal information. With that, you can easily exchange AdvCash to Webmoney in four easy steps. Continue reading to learn more.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/how-exchange-webmoney-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Webmoney to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange AdvCash to Webmoney?</strong></h2>



<p>Naturally, you already have both payment accounts. However, make sure that both accounts are verified and active. On top of that, pay attention to the transaction amount and whether it will exceed your withdrawal limit on AdvCash. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon. Want a good reason why? How about winning $100 ever month!</p>



<p>Learn more about our <a href="https://hi.exchange/campaign/tether-giveaway" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Tether Giveaway</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is AdvCash?</strong></h2>



<p>AdvCash is a currency used for online payments. It is based in Belize which provides immunity from national laws of other countries for it. As an offshore currency, it is also encrypted much like cryptocurrencies and benefits from better anonymity and security. The Advance Cash company provides an account for users that allows for a variety of currencies to operate through it. In many ways, it is a lot like Payeer.</p>



<p>And much like Payeer, AdvCash supports transfers in both fiat and cryptocurrency form. With a virtual wallet, users can transfer funds and make payments with very low commission. What makes it interesting, is that Advance Cash is also compatible with other payment systems such as WebMoney or Perfect Money. With free international transfers, users get to enjoy a wide variety of currencies all in a virtual wallet. Furthermore, there are both physical and virtual bank cards available for quick and cheap international Visa/Mastercard payments.</p>



<p>The company was founded in 2014 as a competitor for PayPal and much like its peers, it has gained notable success in the past few years. As the need for virtual banking grows, online payment processing companies continue to narrow the gap with PayPal. Although, such companies are not as popular as PayPal, they offer a lot more freedom.</p>



<p>Keep in mind that you can also <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-advcash-to-payeer-usd/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange AdvCash to PayPal</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Webmoney?</strong></h2>



<p>WebMoney is an online payment system and a comprehensive tool for online business operations. It was originally developed as a money transfer system for US dollars in Russia in 1998 and since then, nearly 40 million people from all over the globe have joined the program.</p>



<p>WebMoney provides digital currency purses that can hold popular national currencies. The payment platform provides a P2P credit purse, global payment solutions, retail services, local payment products, online billing, and direct integration with other global financial service providers. On top of that, a number of countries worldwide are currently working on WebMoney and consumers pay WebMoney for the services of different companies from Spain, Poland, and Belgium.</p>



<p>Continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-tether-to-webmoney/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Webmoney</a>”.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon to the Moon!</strong></h2>



<p>Every exchange platform must maintain three important characteristics. Anonymity, affordability and reliability. We pride ourselves as a professional platform that offers all three.</p>



<p>For anonymity, CoinCannon requires no KYC or even a sign up process. The best way to protect your information is to not share them with anyone. And for that, we respect our customers and do not ask for their personal info.</p>



<p>As for affordability, CoinCannon utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. By doing so, we have managed to stay on top of the ranks on websites such as Bestchange and OkChanger.</p>



<p>Lastly, reliability is ensured for our customers with 24/7 online support. In case anything goes wrong, you will have our immediate support until the issue is resolved.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange AdvCash to Webmoney?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Enter the homepage first, then select AdvCash USD and Webmoney (WMZ) from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of WMZ you will receive will automatically calculate.</li><li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your AdvCash and Payeer wallet details and email. The phone number is optional.</li><li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li><li>Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the AdvCash gateway and make the payment to our AdvCash account. Having transferred your AdvCash USD to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li><li>By finishing all the steps above, our team will send the Webmoney to your wallet as soon as possible</li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Finished!</strong></h2>



<p>Just like that, you have now exchanged AdvCash to Webmoney. In general, WMZ payments are inconsistent in terms of how long they might take. Give it a few minutes and the Webmoney will be in your account ASAP. In the meantime, you can follow up on your order using the Track ID provided for you. Simply enter the track id in the required section on homepage to see at which point your order is. Remember not to share your Track ID with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-webmoney-wmz/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange AdvCash to Webmoney [No KYC]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-webmoney-wmz/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WebMoney Review 2024, WebMoney Remarkable Achievements</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/webmoney-review/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/webmoney-review/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 06:23:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[e-currency to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Webmoney]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[webmoney pros and cons]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[webmoney review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wmz]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5578</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For this WebMoney review, there will be no need for introduction. Undoubtedly, almost all traders are at least familiar with WM let alone working with the payment system. It is arguably the first anonymity-based payment system with a global success due to its emphasis on privacy. But, so much privacy meant that they had to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/webmoney-review/">WebMoney Review 2024, WebMoney Remarkable Achievements</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>For this WebMoney review, there will be no need for introduction. Undoubtedly, almost all traders are at least familiar with WM let alone working with the payment system. It is arguably the first anonymity-based payment system with a global success due to its emphasis on privacy. But, so much privacy meant that they had to compromise somewhere. Therefore, WM has always been a payment system that works hard yet plays hard too! Considering the overwhelming legal limitations, we’re doing a WebMoney review to see if it can hold up with the competition in the saturated sector.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Exchange WebMoney to PayPal instantly on <a href="https://hi.exchange/directions/popular/exchange-webmoney-paypal" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Webmoney?</strong></h2>



<p>WebMoney is an online payment system and a comprehensive tool for online business operations. It was originally developed as a money transfer system for US dollars in Russia in 1998 and since then, nearly 40 million people from all over the globe have joined the program.</p>



<p>WebMoney provides digital currency purses that can hold popular national currencies. The payment platform provides a P2P credit purse, global payment solutions, retail services, local payment products, online billing, and direct integration with other global financial service providers. On top of that, a number of countries worldwide are currently working on WebMoney and consumers pay WebMoney for the services of different companies from Spain, Poland, and Belgium.</p>



<p>Essentially, you can trace back a lot of the crypto and DeFi ideas back to WM. In that regard, it is more of an effort to circumvent unnecessary banking regulations. A decade before Bitcoin, WM was one of the few payment systems independent of banking.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>WebMoney Transaction Fees</strong></h2>



<p>Primarily, WM offers very low exchange fees hence the popularity with Forex traders. The network charges fees only from sending while the receiver doesn’t pay anything. Sending WM units cost $0.8% per transaction while the minimum fee remains at 0.01. for all the fees an tariffs, you can visit the <a href="https://www.wmtransfer.com/eng/information/rates/index.shtml" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">system fees</a> section on their official website.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>WM Account</strong></h2>



<p>Basically, WebMoney utilizes a “pay-as-you-go” basis which eliminates long-term commitment. With that, users can cancel at any time. But, for this model, you will have to find a reliable exchange platform to deposit and withdraw. This will allow WM to provide an affordable system to replace risky merchant accounts and offshore merchant accounts.</p>



<p>Thankfully, we have just the right exchange platform to introduce in this WebMoney review 2024.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>WebMoney 2024: Remarkable Achievements</strong></h2>



<p>In a milestone year marked by its 25th anniversary, WebMoney has been on an impressive journey of service enhancement and innovation, striving to deliver cutting-edge solutions to its valued users.</p>



<p>One of the notable advancements this year includes the introduction of a Telegram bot to the WebMoney Keeper, accompanied by a host of updates to our applications. Among its many features, the new bot empowers users to create direct donation links easily shared through Telegram, websites, or QR codes.</p>



<p>Throughout the year 2023, WebMoney users have enjoyed the freedom of conducting transfers without geographical limitations, enabling seamless transactions to bank accounts and cards across various currencies, including dollars, euros, and yuan.</p>



<p>In response to user demand, a new WMS wallet in Uzbek sums was introduced, further expanding the platform&#8217;s currency options. Additionally, users can now conveniently transfer funds from their WMT wallet in USDT directly to a bank card, streamlining financial management processes.</p>



<p>With the addition of over 100 new services for payment in WMZ, WMT, and WMS, encompassing mobile operators and popular games, WebMoney continues to evolve to meet diverse user needs. Furthermore, the platform has broadened the range of available currencies in its WebMoney Debt service, providing greater flexibility for financial transactions.</p>



<p>Exciting updates from WebMoney&#8217;s partners further enhance the user experience, with significant improvements to the Paymer digital checks service and the addition of new cryptocurrencies on the INDX exchange.</p>



<p>Looking ahead to the future, WebMoney remains optimistic and committed to delivering innovative solutions that empower users to achieve their financial goals. As we embark on the journey ahead, we invite our users to join us in celebrating our achievements and embracing the possibilities that lie ahead in 2024.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p><a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> platform is an official WebMoney partner with a solid Business Level rating. Using CoinCannon, you can deposit into you WebMoney account or withdraw WM units. CoinCannon does not charge any additional fees for Webmoney transactions therefore it remains as one of the best exchange platforms for this purpose. In fact, <a href="https://hi.exchange/directions/popular?step=1&amp;send=Perfect%20Money%20USD" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Webmoney to PayPal</a> is our most popular exchange direction because of the affordability and reliability.</p>



<p>On top of that, CoinCannon offers multiple benefits for WM users. For one, the platform does not require mandatory KYC or even sign up. This is in fact the best way to protect your private information since you wouldn’t have to disclose them with anyone.</p>



<p>As for reliability, CoinCannon offers 24/7 online customer service to ensure the utmost quality of service.</p>



<p>Learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/how-exchange-webmoney-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange Webmoney to paypal</a> </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>WebMoney Review: Pros and Cons</strong></h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Pros</strong></h3>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Instant Payments</li>



<li>Low exchange fees</li>



<li>Eliminates the need for credit card in Forex</li>



<li>Great for offshore payments</li>
</ul>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Cons</strong></h3>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Customer support in English is subpar</li>



<li>Not available globally</li>



<li>Blocking virtual wallets</li>



<li>Security could be better</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Conclusion</strong></h2>



<p>For this WebMoney review in 2024, we could only say that WebMoney is good as long as you can use it. Meaning that the service is facing sanctions in the US and western Europe. If you have access to WM services, it is an affordable and instant payment system so long as you use a solid exchange platform like CoinCannon.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/webmoney-review/">WebMoney Review 2024, WebMoney Remarkable Achievements</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/webmoney-review/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
