<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Digital Currencies Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/category/digital-currencies/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/category/digital-currencies/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 12:01:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Revolut Money Transfer Guide [No Sign up]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/revolut-money-transfer/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/revolut-money-transfer/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 10:49:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Digital Currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolut]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolut Card]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolut Transfer]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=8748</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s exactly what you&#8217;d expect from a European digital bank, lots of rules, lots of regulations, and a world of bureaucracy! But, making a Revolut money transfer can be easy if you know the right platform. For the most part, this post is a full guide on how to send money to a Revolut account [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/revolut-money-transfer/">Revolut Money Transfer Guide [No Sign up]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>It&#8217;s exactly what you&#8217;d expect from a European digital bank, lots of rules, lots of regulations, and a world of bureaucracy! But, making a Revolut money transfer can be easy if you know the right platform. </p>



<p>For the most part, this post is a full guide on how to send money to a Revolut account instantly without having to sign up anywhere. And believe me, a simple task of sending funds to an account will be difficult without CoinCannon. </p>



<p>It will take a few minutes, so get started now!</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-1 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button has-custom-width wp-block-button__width-100 is-style-outline is-style-outline--1"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-black-color has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-text-color has-background has-link-color wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/En?cur_from=USDTTRC20&amp;cur_to=Revolut"><strong>Transfer Money to Revolut!</strong></a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-revolut-and-why-would-i-need-it">What is Revolut and Why Would I Need it?</h2>



<p>This ain&#8217;t you 2010&#8217;s blog post with 4000 words 🙂 so I will just cut it down to the basics! Basically, Revolut is simply a digital bank based in the UK. They have had a massive success over the past few years as a replacement for physical banks. You can have your own virtual card from Revolut and use it for online payments or use it when you&#8217;re traveling. </p>



<p>Now, since I&#8217;m not on the Revolut marketing team (yo Revolut marketing, hit me up if you&#8217;re interested), my honest opinion about them is that it is at best a mediocre digital banking solution mostly suited for Europeans. What they have to offer is good currency exchange rates. But, there are better options out there. Nonetheless, its popularity and the free subscription (for the basic plan) means that lots of people will sign up for a revolut account and card.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-make-a-revolut-money-transfer">How to Make a Revolut Money Transfer?</h2>



<p>If you don&#8217;t have a Revolut account, making the transfer has to be done via another bank. In such case, you will not be able to transfer cryptocurrencies to your account. However, with CoinCannon, making the Revolut money transfer is instant and easy. Here&#8217;s how it works:</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li>You select Tether USDT and Revolut EUR on the exchange box</li>



<li>Send us the destination Revolut address iBAN, account holder name and email address</li>



<li>You send USDT to CoinCannon&#8217;s wallet</li>



<li>CoinCannon will send funds to the designated Revolut address</li>
</ol>



<p>By using CoinCannon, there is no need for a bank account, or signing up on any platform. The process is instant and regardless of where you live, you can still make Revolut money transfers. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-common-questions-about-revolut">Common Questions about Revolut</h2>



<p><strong>1. How secure is Revolut for online transactions?</strong></p>



<p>Revolut uses advanced security features like biometric authentication, disposable virtual cards, and real-time fraud detection to protect your transactions.</p>



<p><strong>2. Does Revolut support cryptocurrency transactions?</strong></p>



<p>Yes, Revolut allows users to buy, sell, and hold cryptocurrencies, but direct withdrawals to external wallets are limited.</p>



<p><strong>3. How can I add money to my Revolut account?</strong></p>



<p>You can fund your Revolut account via bank transfer, debit/credit card, Apple Pay, Google Pay, or supported e-wallets.</p>



<p><strong>4. Can I exchange USDT to Revolut?</strong></p>



<p>Yes, you can exchange USDT to Revolut using third-party platforms like CoinCannon, as Revolut does not natively support USDT deposits.</p>



<p><strong>5. Are there fees for exchanging USDT to Revolut?</strong></p>



<p>Fees depend on the exchange platform; CoinCannon offers competitive rates with no hidden charges for USDT to Revolut transfers.</p>



<p><strong>6. Do I need a verified Revolut account to receive USDT from CoinCannon?</strong></p>



<p>Yes, your Revolut account must be verified to receive fiat currency after converting USDT through CoinCannon</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/revolut-money-transfer/">Revolut Money Transfer Guide [No Sign up]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/revolut-money-transfer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Free Virtual Debit Card &#124; No KYC</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/virtual-debit-card/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/virtual-debit-card/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 09:13:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Digital Currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[debit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[debit card]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mastercard]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[visa]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=8720</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you&#8217;re reading this blog post, it means that you need to purchase something online or register somewhere but don&#8217;t have a debit card to use. Obviously, a virtual debit card is the answer right? No! a virtual debit card is not necessarily the best solution for your needs simply because you will have to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/virtual-debit-card/">Free Virtual Debit Card | No KYC</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you&#8217;re reading this blog post, it means that you need to purchase something online or register somewhere but don&#8217;t have a debit card to use. Obviously, a virtual debit card is the answer right? No! a virtual debit card is not necessarily the best solution for your needs simply because you will have to pay a lot more fees. let&#8217;s face it, there is no such thing as a free debit card. Instead, you will have have to pay a whole lot of extra fees for a virtual debit card that is a pain in the bottom area! On top of that, you have to fill out forms, wait for confirmation, give out all your personal information and worry about the card declining! </p>



<p>So what if I told you that there&#8217;s a totally better option? With zero extra fees, and it comes instantly with no sign up, how about that? </p>



<p><strong>With CoinCannon Online Payments, you can pay with 100+ currencies including crypto and e-currencies, and CoinCannon will use its own debit card to pay for you! </strong></p>



<p>By doing this, you can instantly pay for your purchase without paying any extra fees. You will have PayPal, Visa card and MasterCard payments anywhere on the vast expanse of web, anytime you need! </p>



<p>Ready to go? Click on the button below and get started!</p>



<p></p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-2 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button has-custom-width wp-block-button__width-100 is-style-outline is-style-outline--2"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-white-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-background-color has-text-color has-background has-link-color wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/En/solutions/online-payment?cur_from=USDTTRC20"><mark style="background-color:#0693e3" class="has-inline-color has-white-color">G</mark>et Your Virtual Debit Card</a></div>
</div>



<p></p>



<p>Need more information? Continue reading!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-use-a-virtual-debit-card">Why use a virtual debit card?</h2>



<p>Depending on where you live and your life choices 🙂  you might not have a debit card! in that case, there comes a time where you need to purchase something online and they only take a handful of debit cards for payment. having a virtual debit card let&#8217;s you bypass all that regulatory shenanigan but at a cost! </p>



<p>there&#8217;s also another scenario in which you find yourself in need of a free debit card! And that&#8217;s when you&#8217;re going to register on a website or application and they ask for your card info! In such cases of presumptuous capitalist demand, do not give them what they ask for! I mean, if a presumably &#8220;free&#8221; website is asking for your debit card information, it will only mean that at some point, their customer journey is designed to bill you and take money (trust me, I&#8217;ve been in marketing for years!).</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="Buy Everything Using Only Crypto! Meet Online Payments" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/XElLN5HP7fg?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-not-use-a-prepaid-debit-card">Why Not Use a Prepaid Debit Card?</h2>



<p>And now, you&#8217;re looking for a virtual debit card to get around the problem. But here&#8217;s a list of new problems that you&#8217;ll have:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Having to pay activation fee, purchase fee, exchange rate fee, third party markup fee!</li>



<li>A long process of purchasing your prepaid debit card</li>



<li>Sharing your personal information for a so called &#8220;free debit card&#8221;</li>



<li>Risking the purchase of a card that might not work! </li>



<li>Having to sign up on a sketchy website and believe me, they will send you promotional emails!</li>
</ul>



<p>After all, a virtual debit card is not exactly legit, is it?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-jolixo-has-to-offer">What CoinCannon has to Offer</h2>



<p>A better solution! here&#8217;s how it works:</p>



<p>You open <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/en">jolixo</a>, choose the currency you want to pay with</p>



<figure class="wp-block-gallery has-nested-images columns-default is-cropped wp-block-gallery-3 is-layout-flex wp-block-gallery-is-layout-flex">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="1024" height="275" data-id="8721" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/virtual-debit-card-Free-Debit-Card-step-1-1024x275.png" alt="virtual debit card - free debit card " class="wp-image-8721" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/virtual-debit-card-Free-Debit-Card-step-1-1024x275.png 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/virtual-debit-card-Free-Debit-Card-step-1-300x81.png 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/virtual-debit-card-Free-Debit-Card-step-1-768x206.png 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/virtual-debit-card-Free-Debit-Card-step-1-1536x413.png 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/virtual-debit-card-Free-Debit-Card-step-1.png 1895w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>
</figure>



<p>Then, select which debit card you need. we have Visa, MasterCard and PayPal. then, click on &#8220;next&#8221; to head to the second step.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><img decoding="async" width="956" height="654" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/Virtual-debit-card-free-dibit-card-step-2.png" alt="virtual debit card - free debit card " class="wp-image-8722" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/Virtual-debit-card-free-dibit-card-step-2.png 956w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/Virtual-debit-card-free-dibit-card-step-2-300x205.png 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/Virtual-debit-card-free-dibit-card-step-2-768x525.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 956px) 100vw, 956px" /></figure></div>


<p>On the second step, share the purchase link, username and password for the account + any additional info. CoinCannon will automatically delete your account information after your transaction is done. However, make sure to change your password later.</p>



<p>click on &#8220;next&#8221; one more time to head to the third step. Here, you get a final chance to review your order. </p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><img decoding="async" width="600" height="792" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/virtual-debit-card-free-debit-card-step-3.png" alt="virtual debit card - free debit card " class="wp-image-8723" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/virtual-debit-card-free-debit-card-step-3.png 600w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/virtual-debit-card-free-debit-card-step-3-227x300.png 227w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></figure></div>


<p>Remember, signing up on CoinCannon is not mandatory. But, CoinCannon offers various rewards for those who sign up! You will have discount codes, cashback and affiliate payments as a CoinCannon member. Ready to finish? head to the final step.</p>



<p>On the final step, you will need to make your payment. as you can see below, the CoinCannon wallet address is available to you. the payment settlement is automatic. As soon as you send your Payment, the transaction status will change to &#8220;processing&#8221;.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="603" height="817" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/virtual-debit-card-free-debit-card-step-4.png" alt="prepaid debit card  " class="wp-image-8724" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/virtual-debit-card-free-debit-card-step-4.png 603w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/virtual-debit-card-free-debit-card-step-4-221x300.png 221w" sizes="(max-width: 603px) 100vw, 603px" /></figure></div>


<p>Send us your chosen currency and our team will make the payment on your behalf Instantly. </p>



<p><strong>With that, you will have your online payment in just a few minutes. No need to sign up, no need to pay ANY extra fees.</strong></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-faq">FAQ</h2>



<p><strong>How much does a virtual debit card cost on CoinCannon?</strong></p>



<p>CoinCannon offers a completely free virtual debit card for all customer.</p>



<p><strong>How do I apply for a virtual debit card?</strong></p>



<p>CoinCannon does not require an application process. All you need for this service is to share an email address.</p>



<p><strong>How can I pay for my virtual debit card?</strong></p>



<p>You will have the ability to pay with USDT, BTC, ETH and 100+ currencies for your virtual debit card.</p>



<p><strong>What can I spend my funds in my virtual debit card?</strong></p>



<p>Absolutely everything! there is no limit at all! you can pay for an invoice, buy stuff off Amazon, charge your accounts online or pay for your kid&#8217;s school! the sky is the limit.</p>



<p><strong>Where can I see the transaction history?</strong></p>



<p>You can always check your user dashboard on CoinCannon or enter your track ID to see the history.</p>



<p><strong>Can I choose Visa or MasterCard as my virtual debit card?</strong></p>



<p>Yes, you will have the option to choose between Visa, MasterCard and also PayPal!</p>



<p><strong>Can I use CoinCannon virtual debit card in another country?</strong></p>



<p>Yes, you can use this service on CoinCannon wherever you are in the world!</p>



<p></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/virtual-debit-card/">Free Virtual Debit Card | No KYC</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/virtual-debit-card/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Global Monetary System is After Crypto (Opinion)</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/global-monetary-system/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/global-monetary-system/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 08:01:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Digital Currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IMF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World Bank]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6334</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>To think about it, a gigantic and inefficient global monetary system is all we’ve got. Lead by unelected individuals who god knows who they are, this system can make or break the fate of the world. To put it simply, policies of this sector can affect pretty much all lives around the world. Now, before [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/global-monetary-system/">&lt;strong&gt;Global Monetary System is After Crypto (Opinion)&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>To think about it, a gigantic and inefficient global monetary system is all we’ve got. Lead by unelected individuals who god knows who they are, this system can make or break the fate of the world. To put it simply, policies of this sector can affect pretty much all lives around the world. Now, before this article starts to turn into a second communist manifesto, there was in fact a second coming of Marxist idealism sometime back in 2008. This time, it was more practical yet the creator that is Satoshi remains anonymous. The seemingly decentralized and revolutionary system was at first true to its nature. Decentralized, anonymous and independent of the global monetary system. In fact, crypto filled a void that pointed out the embarrassing flaws of the conventional boomer banking system of the old days.</p>



<p>However, efficiency and utility will always call for the appeal to expand and to grow. And this isolated system that is crypto, managed to branch out into banks and hedge funds and institutions as the ultimate financial apparatus. More capital flowed into the market and adoption took a rapid momentum. In the meantime, function and utility had some improvement but did not develop as much as it needed.</p>



<p>Subsequently, mass adoption brought out centralized industry titans such as Binance and Coinbase and FTX. Soon, there was a cult forming around crypto thanks to a tremendous boom in popularity. Figures like Michael Saylor and Elon Musk spread the good word of hodl and persuaded retail investors to have faith in computer codes and algorithms which they had no idea how they functioned.</p>



<p>Sadly, the utility of crypto did not keep up with the growing popularity. But worry not, useless functions and marketing schemes like NFTs and shitcoins kept the market afloat for a while. But soon, in this isolated (unregulated) crypt market, Entropy began to turn into chaos. Somewhere, in the drug infused orgies of billionaire crypto entrepreneurs, something went wrong.</p>



<p>And here we are, in the post Luna crash and <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ftx-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">FTX collapse</a> era. Elon is still pumping the market to no avail and Saylor keeps shitposting on Twitter. Yet, retail investors do not believe a word. And finally, the global monetary system seems to be going after crypto. But here’s the catch, they will not try to bring down crypto, but rather swallow and integrate crypto into their own kerfuffle. And there is our bottom line, most, if not all crypto CEOs will gladly accept the overlords’ terms. After all, can’t beat them, join ‘em.</p>



<p>And how will the global monetary system bring crypto into its own corrupt embrace? Regulations!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-undying-global-monetary-system"><strong>The Undying Global Monetary System</strong></h2>



<p>The executive board of the International Monetary Fund (IMF) have <a href="https://www.imf.org/en/News/Articles/2023/02/23/pr2351-imf-executive-board-discusses-elements-of-effective-policies-for-crypto-assets" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">expressed</a> their concerns about crypto assets. According to IMF, the board considers crypto assets and their rising adoption a threat.</p>



<p>For the most part, they all agree that crypto assets will have crucial implications on the UN financial agency’s mandate and policies. With that, what they do demand is providing guidance regarding policy response to crypto assets.</p>



<p>“In particular, the widespread adoption of crypto assets could undermine the effectiveness of monetary policy, circumvent capital flow management measures, and exacerbate fiscal risks. Widespread adoption could also have significant implications for the international monetary system in the longer term.”</p>



<p>To put it simply, IMF directors are calling for countries that are adoption crypto to adopt effective strategies. What that means is that they are fighting to keep their grasp on the financial system of such countries.</p>



<p>“Directors, therefore, emphasized that robust macroeconomic policies, including credible institutions and monetary policy frameworks are first-order requirements and that Fund advice in these areas will remain crucial.”</p>



<p>Now, with all the scandalous <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/pump-and-dump-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">pump and dump crypto</a> schemes, regulators are finding it easy to impose more regulations.</p>



<p>Perhaps, cryptocurrencies may have had their debut as decentralized and independent. Satoshi may have been a revolutionary figure who did not seem to want to compromise and wanted to bring down the global monetary system with a bang. But the reality of the situation is far from what is promised.</p>



<p>When all is said and done, crypto industry is now more centralized than decentralized. And the massive influence that a few individuals have over the market will eventually make the market a lost cause. With that, this article predicts that crypto assets will integrate into the global monetary system. Maybe not today, but sometime in the future cryptocurrencies will be fully and extensively regulated. And then, the global monetary system will finally have its own prodigal son back!</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/global-monetary-system/">&lt;strong&gt;Global Monetary System is After Crypto (Opinion)&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/global-monetary-system/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top Platforms Who Accept ETH Payments</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/platforms-accept-eth-payments/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/platforms-accept-eth-payments/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 08:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Digital Currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Payments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5597</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A few years ago, ETH payments were essentially unicorns in the online business. Even as a crypto journalist, it’s actually hard to keep up with all the updates and news sometimes. Of course, this is mostly because there is so much news coming up every day that you quickly forget some of the bare essentials. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/platforms-accept-eth-payments/">Top Platforms Who Accept ETH Payments</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A few years ago, ETH payments were essentially unicorns in the online business. Even as a crypto journalist, it’s actually hard to keep up with all the updates and news sometimes. Of course, this is mostly because there is so much news coming up every day that you quickly forget some of the bare essentials. Arguably, even more important than the bear market is the rapid crypto adoption that is taking place. And sadly, all this adoption is overshadowed by speculative news and the Twitter drama. Thankfully, we have a spark of joy ready for you crypto lovers and libertarian warriors out there! </p>



<p>Unlike a few years ago, you don’t have to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange cryptocurrency to PayPal</a> in order to buy something online. Today, we will take a look at some of the most significant online platforms be it merchants or retailers and service providers. Hopefully, this is would indicate a positive impression of the big picture for cryptocurrencies. And, if you like this article, tell us down in the comments so that we would write the same for other cryptocurrencies.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-ethereum-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Ethereum to PayPal</a></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Merchants Accepting ETH Payments</strong></h2>



<p>While the list is too long to go through, here are some of the best online merchants who accept ETH payments:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Amazon: </strong>Ethereum holders can spend Ether on the biggest e-commerce platform using Bitpay.</li><li><strong>Travala:</strong> you can pay for trips with ETH on Travala.com application</li><li><strong>Purism:</strong> The privacy-focused company accepts Ethereum payments</li><li><strong>Toro Coffee Co.</strong>: Buy specialty coffee with various crypto payment methods using crypto</li><li><strong>Renjer Wild Jerky:</strong> Beef and Deer Jerky paid by ETH</li><li><strong>Headphones.com: </strong>guess what you can buy on this website with Ether!</li><li><strong>Bitdial:</strong> This is a luxury watch company that offer so many brands and accepts crypto and Ethereum as payments</li><li><strong>Trippki:</strong> Plan your trip, with over 1.5 million hotels to choose from, Trippki accepts ETH payments</li><li><strong>BitPay:</strong> Literally buy real estate using Ethereum on BitPay website</li><li><strong>PayPal:</strong> Spend ETH at any platform that accepts PayPal</li><li><strong>BlockFi:</strong> Spend Ether at any platform that accepts Visa</li><li><strong>Amagi Metals:</strong> Buy and sell precious metals online via ETH</li><li><strong>PizzaForCoins:</strong> Pizza!</li><li><strong>Destinia:</strong> Pay for hotel bookings, flight packages and train tickets.</li><li><strong>Freelanceforcoins.</strong>com: Find freelance jobs and get paid in Ethereum.</li><li><strong>Natural Pet Shop:</strong> Pet products store</li></ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why ETH Payments?</strong></h2>



<p>With all this adoption, the question is, why not? What Ethereum or in fact any other cryptocurrency offers is a straightforward and hassle free payment method. How many times have you wanted to make a purchase and PayPal has for some reason rejected your payment? Perhaps, this takes us back to the fundamental advantages of crypto which is privacy, freedom of choice and affordability. In any case, Ethereum of today is not just an unusable asset in your wallet, it is as good as cash when it comes to payments. However, the only downside is trusting large exchange platforms who sell your data to the illuminati and the lizard people (jk). For that, you need a trustworthy exchanger who is awesome like CoinCannon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/platforms-accept-eth-payments/">Top Platforms Who Accept ETH Payments</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/platforms-accept-eth-payments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Regulatory Actions Against Stablecoins Are Coming</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/regulatory-actions-against-stablecoins-are-coming/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/regulatory-actions-against-stablecoins-are-coming/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 07:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Digital Currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=3786</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Stablecoins have been causing so much controversy lately. The crypto market continues as the longest running bullish market in history. In that regard, the stablecoins are the necessary medium in this market. As of late, recent rumors and statements from Washington are indicating a possible wave of new regulations coming on stablecoins way. Stablecoins [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/regulatory-actions-against-stablecoins-are-coming/">Regulatory Actions Against Stablecoins Are Coming</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Stablecoins have been causing so much controversy lately. The crypto market continues as the longest running bullish market in history. In that regard, the stablecoins are the necessary medium in this market. As of late, recent rumors and statements from Washington are indicating a possible wave of new regulations coming on stablecoins way.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Stablecoins and CBDCs</strong></h2>



<p>Generally speaking, a stablecoin is a type of digital currency that has its value pegged to another asset. Most commonly, fiat pegged stablecoins are used in cryptocurrency trading. However, their superpower is to make quick, cheap and mostly secure transaction on the blockchain network as an alternative for banking services. Considering the impressive <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/view/stablecoin/">$126 billion market cap</a> as of September, 2021, it is no wonder the politicians are worried about it.</p>



<p>To be fair, a valid argument against private sector stablecoins is that regarding the value, many of them are backed by debt. On the other hand, the decentralized nature of these companies can make it difficult to protect the users against possibly malicious policies. Subsequently, the governments are now seeking to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/cbdc-the-ultimate-financial-apparatus-for-governments/">issue Government backed stablecoins or CBDC</a>.</p>



<p>The concern lies in the fact that CBDC can be an over powered apparatus for central banks that initially limits people from owning or having access to their wealth. The money is not in their hands, the money is on a digital network and the bank can block access if they wanted. In a dystopian situation, central banks can impose negative interest rates on bank accounts. Furthermore, it would be entirely possible for policymakers to impose regulations demanding only CBDC is the only legal medium to trade crypto.  <a href="https://www.atlanticcouncil.org/cbdctracker/">Currently 83 countries are looking into CBDC release.</a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Possible Legal Approaches for Stablecoins</strong></h2>



<p>Only a few days ago, a <a href="https://home.treasury.gov/news/press-releases/jy0281">press release from the US Treasury</a> demanded quick actions against stablecoins expressing urgency. This is an indication of the severity of the situation.</p>



<p>Yesterday, a <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2021/09/17/business/economy/federal-reserve-virtual-currency-stablecoin.html">New York Times article</a> discussed six different legal approaches that lawmakers can take against stablecoins. Here are the six approaches:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list"><li>Regarding them as “systematically risky”. This would call for strict and harsh regulatory control can be quite destructive for them.</li><li>Recognizing them as “securities” and putting them under SEC supervision. (oh lawd)</li><li>Regulate them as Banks, putting them under the office of the Comptroller of Currency.</li><li>Engage in an active competition utilizing CBDC (or release the hounds in other terms).</li></ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Bottom line</strong></h2>



<p>Sadly, it would be unrealistic to expect a phenomenon like stablecoin can continue this much unregulated. As it grows in market cap, the realization has hit the politicians that first, they want some if not all the profit and second, it is too liberating to be considered as safe for the political structure. Conversely, the fraudulent activities, lack of vision or in some cases just bad luck has given the crypto market a bad image for politicians to exploit. We must wait and see the regulatory outcome of stablecoin discussions. However, we could be sure that people are losing ground in these regulatory battles.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Our Vision</strong></h2>



<p>We believe in crypto, not only for income but liberation as well. Although we’re not the first decentralized online exchange, we’re looking to be the best.  You can exchange your cryptocurrencies and digital currencies on <a href="hi.exchange">hi.exchange</a>. We Utilize an automated system to determine the best rates. Furthermore, we offer 24/7 customer support. Also, we have technical price analysis for Bitcoin and Altcoins, opinion articles and news on <a href="blog.hi.exchange">our blog</a>. Our vision is to keep our customers up do date with the latest news and professional analysis.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/regulatory-actions-against-stablecoins-are-coming/">Regulatory Actions Against Stablecoins Are Coming</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/regulatory-actions-against-stablecoins-are-coming/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CBDC, the Ultimate Financial Apparatus for Governments</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/cbdc-the-ultimate-financial-apparatus-for-governments/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/cbdc-the-ultimate-financial-apparatus-for-governments/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 10:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Digital Currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[China]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[interest rates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=3695</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It seems that the pursuit of central bank digital currencies (CBDC) has gained so much momentum lately. China, came up with the digital Yuan raising speculations about the possible agenda. Then US and the European union announced their Digital dollar and Euro to be utilized soon. On the surface, this was a development toward the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/cbdc-the-ultimate-financial-apparatus-for-governments/">CBDC, the Ultimate Financial Apparatus for Governments</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>It seems that the pursuit of central bank digital currencies (CBDC) has gained so much momentum lately. China, came up with the digital Yuan raising speculations about the possible agenda. Then US and the European union announced their Digital dollar and Euro to be utilized soon. On the surface, this was a development toward the up and coming financial technology.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">The Threat That is Crypto</h2>



<p>With the rise of the cryptocurrency industry, central banks lost a great deal of dominance over the world’s finance. This was due to the superior profits, anonymity, availability and better exchange rates that crypto provides. On the other hand, a crucial medium for these transactions were the stablecoins. A type of digital currency that has its value pegged to another asset such as fiat currencies.</p>



<p>This emerging market with high inflows is causing great concerns for governments regardless of their political orientations. In a recent opinion article, we discussed how the <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/china-crackdowns-on-bitcoin-why-so-harsh-opinion/">cryptocurrencies were having an impact on the China’s political structure</a>. On the other hand, the massive inflow into crypto currencies has cost gold a great deal of inflows. In that regard, US banks are deeply concerned with this prevailing phenomenon. Only a few days ago, we predicted that due to the recent increase in SCE’s activities, <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/elizabeth-warren-calls-crypto-the-new-shadow-bank/">there could be a wave of destructive crackdowns coming toward crypto-related institutions</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Commence the Trojan Horse</strong></h2>



<p>With all that said, the persistence to create a national CBDC seems to be bit rushed and a bit unnecessary. After all, why not adopt a pre-existing stablecoin? Why must central banks spend billions of dollars to re-invent the wheel?</p>



<p>A CBDC provides so much regulatory potential for a government. To begin with, it could be much easier to trace the transactions utilizing CBDC. However, it’s entirely possible that at some point, governments demand that entry and exit into the crypto market can only be done using CBDC. In that case, it will be much easier to impose taxes on investors as their private activities are compromised.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CBDC and the Negative Interest Rates</strong></h2>



<p>In an eye-opening <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/digital-currencies-pave-way-for-deeply-negative-interest-rates-11631091581">Wall Street Journal article</a>, the famous financial journalist <a href="https://www.wsj.com/news/author/james-mackintosh">James Mackintosh</a> has pointed out a possible use case scenario for CBDC. According to Mackintosh, CBDCs can be an over powered apparatus for central bankers to adjust interest rates. As of now, the interest rates are the lowest in the US at 0.25%. In the worst case scenario, they could only fall to zero. When it comes down to that, people would rather keep cash under their pillows than to have it held in banks.</p>



<p>So long as there is cash, you are the master of your own money. Yet, when speaking of CBDC, banks will have the capability to impose “deeply negative interest rates”. You heard me right, with digital money, central banks can impose negative interest rates or better said “harm rates”.</p>



<p>This strategy is a last effort to fight inflation in a country but nonetheless, people must be in charge of their money. If central banks are responsible for the inflation to begin with, should they harm our life savings in the times of need?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Current State of CBDC Projects</strong></h2>



<p><a href="https://www.atlanticcouncil.org/cbdctracker/">The Atlantic council has a dedicated CBDC tracker</a> on their website. As of now, 5 countries have launched their central bank digital currency projects. The China is currently piloting the project while the US is in the research phase.</p>



<p>As the crypto market grows in value, the oppressive regulations and false interventions rise in numbers. Unchallenged for many years, Central banks are now desperate to defeat their foe. Lobbyist politicians are creating FUDs and spreading fear in order to fight crypto. And finally, CBDCs are being developed fast. In many ways, we are witnessing a financial renaissance. The traditional neoclassical finance is faced with the peril of a pragmatic opponent. The question is, in the escalating tensions between both parties, will the common folk prevail?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Our Vision</strong></h2>



<p>We believe in crypto, not only for income but liberation as well. Although we’re not the first decentralized online exchange, we’re looking to be the best. We believe that the market should be accessible and the customer has the right to maintain as much anonymity as they desire. This goal is now possible thanks to our automated systems and 24/7 customer support to ensure a secure and reliable exchange process. You can exchange your cryptocurrencies and digital currencies on <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/china-crackdowns-on-bitcoin-why-so-harsh-opinion/hi.exchange">hi.exchange</a>. Also, we have technical price analysis for Bitcoin and Altcoins, opinion articles and news <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/china-crackdowns-on-bitcoin-why-so-harsh-opinion/blog.hi.exchange">on our blog</a> to keep our customers up do date with the latest news and professional analysis for their investment journey.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/cbdc-the-ultimate-financial-apparatus-for-governments/">CBDC, the Ultimate Financial Apparatus for Governments</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/cbdc-the-ultimate-financial-apparatus-for-governments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
