<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>what is advcash Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/what-is-advcash/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 10:19:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>What is AdvCash? Underrated E-Wallet!</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-advcash/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-advcash/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 10:19:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[e-currency to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AdvCash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange AdvCash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[what is advcash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5545</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>E-wallets have been a great online service for payment solutions. And of course, there are multiple options to choose from. However, for those in need of hassle-free regulations, the options become very much limited! In this article, we will go over what is AdvCash and how it works. Furthermore, we will touch on how CoinCannon [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-advcash/">What is AdvCash? Underrated E-Wallet!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>E-wallets have been a great online service for payment solutions. And of course, there are multiple options to choose from. However, for those in need of hassle-free regulations, the options become very much limited! In this article, we will go over what is AdvCash and how it works. Furthermore, we will touch on how CoinCannon platform can help customers with its hassle-free KYC requirements for AdvCash transactions. What is AdvCash? A payment system that is compatible with Mastercard.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Buy and Sell AdvCash on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a><br>No KYC!</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is AdvCash?</strong></h2>



<p>AdvCash is a currency used for online payments. It is based in Belize which provides immunity from national laws of other countries for it. As an offshore currency, it is also encrypted much like cryptocurrencies and benefits from better anonymity and security. The Advance Cash company provides an account for users that allows for a variety of currencies to operate through it. In many ways, it is a lot like Payeer.</p>



<p>And much like Payeer, AdvCash supports transfers in both fiat and cryptocurrency form. With a virtual wallet, users can transfer funds and make payments with very low commission. What makes it interesting, is that Advance Cash is also compatible with other payment systems such as WebMoney or Perfect Money. With free international transfers, users get to enjoy a wide variety of currencies all in a virtual wallet. Furthermore, there are both physical and virtual bank cards available for quick and cheap international Visa/Mastercard payments.</p>



<p>The company was founded in 2014 as a competitor for PayPal and much like its peers, it has gained notable success in the past few years. As the need for virtual banking grows, online payment processing companies continue to narrow the gap with PayPal. Although, such companies are not as popular as PayPal, they offer a lot more freedom.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>AdvCash</strong> <strong>Pros and Cons</strong></h2>



<p>Now that we’ve gone over what is AdvCash, let’s take a look at some of the pros and cons.</p>



<p>The platform does offer numerous advantages and here are some of the most noteworthy:</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Pros:</strong></h3>



<ul class="wp-block-list"><li>No Fee for internal operations</li><li>Virtual Cards are a great tool</li><li>Cards that offer free service</li><li>High Security and lots of safety features</li><li>Low Fees</li><li>Crypto Support</li></ul>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Cons:</strong></h3>



<ul class="wp-block-list"><li>No Service in the US</li><li>Anonymous Owner, nobody knows who founded the company</li><li>Irreversible transactions</li><li>No Smartphone application available yet.</li></ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Does CoinCannon Support AdvCash?</strong></h2>



<p>Yes, you can <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/buy-advcash-with-perfect-money/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Buy</a> AdvCash on CoinCannon with Perfect Money or <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-advcash-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange</a> AdvCash to PayPal. CoinCannon offers the best exchange rates as well as 24/7 online support. And to respect anonymity, the platform does not require KYC or Sign Up.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-advcash/">What is AdvCash? Underrated E-Wallet!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-advcash/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
