<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>SEC Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/sec/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 11:22:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Cryptocurrency Regulations: The SEC is Divided!</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrency-regulations/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrency-regulations/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 11:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6409</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency regulations have been a hot topic in recent years, with governments and regulatory agencies around the world grappling with how to approach this rapidly evolving industry. In the United States, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) plays a key role in regulating the cryptocurrency market. For the most part, the SEC has been showing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrency-regulations/">Cryptocurrency Regulations: The SEC is Divided!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Cryptocurrency regulations have been a hot topic in recent years, with governments and regulatory agencies around the world grappling with how to approach this rapidly evolving industry. In the United States, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) plays a key role in regulating the cryptocurrency market. For the most part, the SEC has been showing an anti-crypto attitude. However, Commissioner Hester Peirce, a well-known advocate for innovation in the crypto space, has recently <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/statement/peirce-rendering-inovation-2023-04-12" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">voiced her dissent</a> against Chair Gary Gensler&#8217;s anti-crypto agenda. Of course, we can be sure about an upcoming shock wave of regulatory action coming for crypto. However, recent debates show how there is internal conflict within the SEC regarding crypto assets.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Commissioner Pierce on Cryptocurrency Regulations</strong></h2>



<p>In a recent speech, Commissioner Peirce criticized the SEC&#8217;s proposal to adjust the definition of &#8220;exchange&#8221; to include decentralized finance (DeFi) protocols. According to Peirce, this change would be counterproductive, promoting stagnation and centralization rather than embracing the potential of new technology.</p>



<p>&#8220;Stagnation, centralization, expatriation, and extinction are the watchwords of this release. Rather than embracing the promise of new technology as we have done in the past, here we propose to embrace stagnation, force centralization, urge expatriation, and welcome extinction of new technology. Accordingly, I dissent,&#8221; said Peirce.</p>



<p>Commissioner Peirce further highlighted that the SEC&#8217;s proposal could potentially violate the First Amendment protections by categorizing blockchain ecosystems as a &#8220;group,&#8221; creating ambiguity around their speech rights.</p>



<p>&#8220;The release&#8217;s ambiguity undermines fundamental First Amendment protections. Because the release makes everybody involved in the relevant blockchain ecosystem part of a &#8216;group,&#8217; it creates significant ambiguity around what speech requires government pre-approval, which will unavoidably chill constitutionally-protected speech,&#8221; Peirce explained.</p>



<p>Peirce also emphasized the importance of the SEC remaining open to the idea of tweaking its rules to accommodate new technologies, something she believes the Commission understood in the 1990s.</p>



<p>&#8220;The Commission of the 1990s understood this basic principle and created space for significant innovations in securities trading. This release, on the other hand, takes the view that any business model that cannot meet the specific requirements of our existing regulatory model does not belong in our markets,&#8221; Peirce stated.</p>



<p>In essence, Peirce argues that the SEC&#8217;s current approach to cryptocurrency regulations is hindering innovation and preventing cutting-edge businesses from entering the market. She believes that a Commission serious about regulating, rather than destroying, the cryptocurrency market should reflect on its past regulatory failures and be open to adapting its rules to accommodate the unique characteristics of cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-sec-s-iron-fist"><strong>The SEC’s Iron Fist</strong></h2>



<p>Peirce&#8217;s dissenting voice within the SEC sheds light on the internal conflict within the regulatory agency regarding how to approach cryptocurrency regulations. Chair Gary Gensler has taken a more stringent stance on cryptocurrencies, expressing concerns about investor protection and market integrity. On the other hand, Commissioner Peirce has been a vocal advocate for embracing innovation and allowing the cryptocurrency market to flourish.</p>



<p>The debate over cryptocurrency regulations is not limited to the SEC. Governments and regulatory agencies worldwide are grappling with how to effectively regulate the rapidly growing cryptocurrency market. Some countries have taken a more progressive approach, recognizing the potential of cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology, while others have adopted a more cautious stance, expressing concerns about risks such as money laundering and fraud.</p>



<p>In the United States, the lack of clear and consistent cryptocurrency regulations has created uncertainty for businesses and investors operating in the crypto space. Many argue that a well-regulated cryptocurrency market could provide significant benefits, such as increased investor protection, market transparency, and economic growth. However, excessive regulation could stifle innovation and hinder the development of the cryptocurrency market.</p>



<p>The SEC, as a key regulatory agency in the U.S., plays a crucial role in shaping cryptocurrency regulations. Commissioner Peirce&#8217;s dissenting voice highlights the need for a balanced and pragmatic approach to regulating cryptocurrencies. While it is important to address risks and protect investors, paralyzing a whole industry does not sound like a democratic approach either.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrency-regulations/">Cryptocurrency Regulations: The SEC is Divided!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrency-regulations/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Silvergate Bank Gets Knifed in the Back</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/silvergate-bank/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/silvergate-bank/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 08:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Silvergate Bank]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6349</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Silvergate bank, the innovative and awesome crypto-friendly haven, is now facing a great betrayal. Following a massive plummet of 60% in stocks, crypto firms are abandoning their old friend for cautionary reasons. A term which could also translate into cautionary fear of the SEC coming for you with a flurry of lawsuits. Now, considering the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/silvergate-bank/">&lt;strong&gt;Silvergate Bank Gets Knifed in the Back&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Silvergate bank, the innovative and awesome crypto-friendly haven, is now facing a great betrayal. Following a massive <a href="https://www.google.com/finance/quote/SI:NYSE?window=5D" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">plummet</a> of 60% in stocks, crypto firms are abandoning their old friend for cautionary reasons. A term which could also translate into cautionary fear of the SEC coming for you with a flurry of lawsuits. Now, considering the high profile crypto companies moving away from the wounded bank, we can clearly see regulators raising the stakes for such companies to take risks like they used to. </p>



<p>In the meantime, the <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ripple-lawsuit-continues-as-sec-tries-to-cheat/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Ripple lawsuit</a> is coming to its final verdict and the result could probably have a big impact on the crypto industry as a whole. With all that in mind, as the regulatory grip get tighter, crypto firms are acting a lot more careful. And for crypto, this probably means that the age of maturity is upon us. Perhaps, this could also be a sign of <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/global-monetary-system/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Global Monetary System</a> closing in on crypto assets in order to put a leash on them.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-silvergate-bank-the-fallen-soldier"><strong>Silvergate Bank, The Fallen Soldier</strong></h2>



<p>So far, prominent firms such as Coinbase exchange and Stablecoin issuer Paxos have cut ties with Silvergate bank. Interestingly, a vast majority of these companies are already dealing with their own devastating share of ongoing lawsuits.</p>



<p>Last Month, Silvergate Bank <a href="https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1312109/000110465923027353/tm238251d1_nt10k.htm" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">informed</a> the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) that it will postpone the submission of its annual financial report. According to the company&#8217;s previous year report, they suffered a loss of $1 billion in Q4 of 2022 caused by the ongoing crypto winter. Or simply put, the were not able to recover from the <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ftx-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">FTX collapse</a>.</p>



<p>Following that, Coinbase announced that they will no longer accept or initiate payments to or from Silvergate. This did not go well for Silvergate bank as they endured a huge 45% dip in their stock.</p>



<p>“In light of recent developments and out of an abundance of caution, Coinbase is no longer accepting or initiating payments to or from Silvergate. Coinbase has de minimis corporate exposure to Silvergate.”</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="799" height="542" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Silvergate-Bank-Stock.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-6351" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Silvergate-Bank-Stock.jpg 799w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Silvergate-Bank-Stock-300x204.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Silvergate-Bank-Stock-768x521.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 799px) 100vw, 799px" /></figure>



<p>Similiarly, Paxos, the stablecoin issuer for the troubled <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/busd-stablecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">BUSD</a> made a similar announcement. Paxos announced that they will discontinue all transfers to Silvergate Bank accounts.</p>



<p>&nbsp;“In light of recent developments with Silvergate Bank, Paxos has discontinued all SEN [Silvergate Exchange Network] transfers and wires to our Silvergate account. Paxos will continue to process all outgoing payments.”</p>



<p>The wave of crypto firms jumping ship has continued so far as other industry titans are now cutting ties. So far, investment firm Galaxy Digital, payment platform Circle and crypto exchange Bitstamp and exchange platform Gemini have stopped working with Silvergate.</p>



<p>At the moment, Silvergate stock is trading at $5.77 which is down almost 70% from its monthly high of $22.32.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The SEC Problem</strong></h2>



<p>As predicted, <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-regulations-sec-cftc/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">crypto regulations</a> and the SEC are breathing down the industry’s neck. Frankly, with all the reckless behavior we saw from CEOs such as Sam Bankman-Fried and Do Kwon, regulations were a long time coming. In the meantime, the debate over whether cryptocurrencies are securities or commodities seems to be settling in favor of the SEC.</p>



<p>As the Securities and Exchange Commission insists that crypto assets are securities, industry giants seem unable to prove otherwise. In the meantime, one of the most impactful lawsuits that is the XRP case will soon come to an end. Primarily, the argument behind this frustrating lawsuit is whether a security or a commodity. Now, even with the endless appeal system in the US, the result of this case can determine the future. Essentially, the XRP lawsuits has been going on for two and a half years. During this time, XRP has failed to attract retail investors and experience any stable growth. Basically, Ripple has been like a sick child watching his friends playing outside. And now, the SEC has clearly made an example out of XRP by showing others how they are not afraid to go to court and how detrimental their lawsuits can be for crypto companies.</p>



<p>In a recent interview with Bloomberg, Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse said that their failure will have an impact on the whole industry. Subsequently, Garlinghouse believes that SECs attitude toward crypto assets is simply “not healthy”.</p>



<p>“The SEC bringing the case against Ripple was not really just a case about Ripple or about XRP. It’s really about the industry and how the SEC is kind of playing offense and attacking the whole industry. Two and a half years ago when it started, I’m not sure everyone fully digested that. And now that is widely understood.</p>



<p>This is going to be pivotal for the whole industry because if the SEC is able to prevail, I think there’s a lot of other cases and some of them just in the last four weeks: I think they brought five additional enforcement cases.”</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="Ripple CEO Says SEC Suit Is &#039;Not Healthy&#039; for Industry" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/2YCKG2g7UE0?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<p>Considering the situation, the SEC is making it harder for crypto to get back to its boom and bust days. Simultaneously, retail investors are far more interested in AI stocks than coming back to crypto. Although AI coins are apparently a thing, they haven’t had any tangible utility to prove their worth. And that leaves us with the crypto winter, which is seemingly here to stay a while.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/silvergate-bank/">&lt;strong&gt;Silvergate Bank Gets Knifed in the Back&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/silvergate-bank/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Grayscale Bitcoin Trust in Trouble Thanks to FTX</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/grayscale-bitcoin-trust/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/grayscale-bitcoin-trust/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 08:26:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grayscale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6185</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Grayscale Bitcoin Trust is trading at a huge discount and the outflows are consistent. But before we get into the details, let’s talk about Charles Ponzi, a man who infamously carries the torch for all scams with his last name. Funny enough, the original Ponzi scheme cost investors $20 million in early 20’s and ran [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/grayscale-bitcoin-trust/">Grayscale Bitcoin Trust in Trouble Thanks to FTX</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Grayscale Bitcoin Trust is trading at a huge discount and the outflows are consistent. But before we get into the details, let’s talk about Charles Ponzi, a man who infamously carries the torch for all scams with his last name. Funny enough, the original Ponzi scheme cost investors $20 million in early 20’s and ran for over a year. Since then, the devil has had lots of time to learn and it really shows. While the <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/ftx-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">FTX collapse</a> is behind us, the chaotic state of affairs is here to stay with us for the rest of the year. And in chaos, one might find the most unexpected outcomes previously thought to be impossible. What is this unlikely phenomenon? Well, super-rich people are losing money on Grayscale Bitcoin Trust.</p>



<p>For those who don’t know, Grayscale is the largest cryptocurrency fund in the world. For the most part, their financial services are exclusive to ultra-wealthy clients with very large investments. At this point, Grayscale holds about 3.5% of world’s Bitcoin and their shares are going down. Their largest digital asset holding is Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) which used to be a banger. Unfortunately, the share price for the $10.5 billion GBTC has plummeted 40% as investors rush to exit. Ironically, Michael Sonnenshein, the CEO of the investment giant had said that investors see <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/investors-see-crypto-crash-as-opportunity-grayscale/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">crypto crash</a> as an opportunity!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) Down!</strong></h2>



<p>In total, GBTC investors are down 83% since Bitcoin peaked in November 2021. Now, Bitcoin itself is down 74% in the same timeframe. To sum up, Grayscale Bitcoin Trust investors have endured a massive loss trusting Grayscales’ Bitcoin Trust.</p>



<p>2021 has not been kind to cryptocurrency investors to say the least. However, the bear market has revealed the dark side of crypto startups and investment firms. The recent FTX implosion came not long after the collapse of <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/terra-2-0-launch/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Terra (LUNA)</a>. In The meantime, the upcoming regulations bring too much uncertainty. Now, putting that on top of all the loss in the market, we are left with no hope, at least for short-term.</p>



<p>On top of that, crypto broker Genesis Trading also had a vibe check on Wednesday. Last year, Genesis Trading originated over $50 billion of loans. A few days ago, they suspended redemptions and originations of loans at its lending arm. This was due to contagion from the collapse of <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/crypto-hedge-fund/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Three Arrows Capital</a>.</p>



<p>Both Grayscale and Genesis are subsidiaries of Digital Currency Group which is a venture capital company based in Connecticut.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="682" src="http://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Grayscale-Bitcoin-Trust-1024x682.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-6188" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Grayscale-Bitcoin-Trust-1024x682.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Grayscale-Bitcoin-Trust-300x200.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Grayscale-Bitcoin-Trust-768x512.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Grayscale-Bitcoin-Trust.jpg 1246w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The GBTC Problem</strong></h2>



<p>Grayscale Bitcoin Trust launched back in 2013 as a private placement offering. Back then, it was not as easy to buy and sell Bitcoin. Mind you, many of the reliable crypto exchangers did not exist back then. With that in mind, GBTC was a great vehicle for holding Bitcoin.</p>



<p>However, with the introduction of Bitcoin ETFs and the rise of popular exchange apps, Grayscale does not have any edge in the competition left. Bear in mind that Grayscale charges a premium at 2% a year while ETFs tend to charge less than half.</p>



<p>Pairing that with the Genesis Trading problem ad we can now see why GBTC is down more than Bitcoin itself. Furthermore, Grayscale does not actually have a buyback program. Subsequently, investors cannot redeem GBTC for BTC or cash and will only be able to sell it to another buyer in an over-the-counter market.</p>



<p>Now, the securities and exchange commission has blocked all plans to exchange GBTC into a spot Bitcoin ETF. Grayscale is now suing the SEC to attain the right to convert GBTC.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="705" src="http://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Grayscale-Bitcoin-Trust-2-1024x705.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-6187" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Grayscale-Bitcoin-Trust-2-1024x705.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Grayscale-Bitcoin-Trust-2-300x207.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Grayscale-Bitcoin-Trust-2-768x529.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Grayscale-Bitcoin-Trust-2.jpg 1245w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>At this point, Grayscale is cornered by regulations and the fate of GBTC depends on the ability to convert GBTC. We will post updates in the situation at hand as soon as we have more information.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/grayscale-bitcoin-trust/">Grayscale Bitcoin Trust in Trouble Thanks to FTX</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/grayscale-bitcoin-trust/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lummis Bill Considers Cryptocurrencies as Commodities</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/lummis-bill/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/lummis-bill/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 06:37:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CFTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lummis Bill]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5530</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There has been an argument on whether digital assets are commodities or securities. This simple question could have a serious impact on the future. The Lummis Bill has finally settled the debate stating that most cryptocurrencies are commodities. Basically, securities are regulated by the SEC which has a hostile history towards crypto. On the other [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/lummis-bill/">Lummis Bill Considers Cryptocurrencies as Commodities</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>There has been an argument on whether digital assets are commodities or securities. This simple question could have a serious impact on the future. The Lummis Bill has finally settled the debate stating that most cryptocurrencies are commodities. Basically, securities are regulated by the SEC which has a hostile history towards crypto. On the other hand, the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) will have oversight on commodities. In order to come up with a legal framework, cryptocurrencies must first be categorized. Previously, the CFTC chair Rostin Behnam said that digital assets will be <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/crypto-regulations-sec-cftc/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">divided</a> into two categories. And now, the Lummis Bill is proposing crypto regulations will be handed to CFTC instead of the SEC.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Exchange Cryptocurrencies to PayPal Instantly on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Lummis Bill</strong></h2>



<p>Politically speaking, US regulators are struggling to categorize digital assets. Generally speaking, GOP members used to be against cryptocurrencies. However, there seems to be a shift in policies in the past few years. With that, the democratic members tend to be against cryptocurrencies while republicans have been defending it. As for the latest battle, GOP house members have been doing their best to prevent SEC from gaining jurisdiction over digital assets.</p>



<p>The Lummis bill, sponsored by US Senators Cynthia M. Lummis and Kristen Gillibrand, is the first attempt to push the agenda. The new bipartisan bill will hand over crypto regulations to the Commodity Futures Trading Commission. By categorizing digital assets as commodities, the bill prevents the securities and Exchange commission from regulating the crypto industry.</p>



<p>The SEC head Gary Gensler, a prominent crypto <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/secs-gary-gensler-skeptic-of-crypto-signals-crackdowns/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">critic</a> has argued that digital assets are essentially securities. On the other hand, the Lummis Bill asserts that “most digital assets are much more similar to commodities than securities.”</p>



<p>The CFTC already oversees Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) futures trading in the US. Comparatively, the SEC has six times more budget than the CFTC.</p>



<p>Senator Lummis said in a statement,</p>



<p>“The United States is the global financial leader, and to ensure the next generation of Americans enjoys greater opportunity, it is critical to integrate digital assets into existing law and to harness the efficiency and transparency of this asset class while addressing risk.”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The </strong>Opposition</h2>



<p>On the opposing side, critics still believe that most digital assets are securities. While this goes beyond semantics, it is pretty difficult to simply categorize them. The director if financial regulation and corporate governance Todd Philips <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2022/06/07/crypto-lummis-gillibrand-regulation/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">said</a> at the liberal think tank center for American progress.</p>



<p>“The status quo would be better than this bill. So many of these tokens are securities and need to comply with the regular, usual securities laws, and this bill tries to create a special crypto-specific disclosure regime that I don’t think discloses all the information investors need to fully evaluate whether to purchase a security.”</p>



<p>Much like anything else in the US, the upcoming regulations have become a battleground between the left and the right.</p>



<p>Jeremy Hogan, a crypto legal expert took on Twitter to express his opinion on the Lummis Bill.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Lummis Bill thoughts:<br><br>1. The bill is strikingly broad. Reporting, taxes, brokers, etc. are all under its umbrella.<br><br>2. It&#39;s MUCH better than status quo.<br><br>3. It carves a niche for digital assets that are subject to SEC oversight if they are &quot;investment contracts.&quot;  BUT&#8230;  1/2 <a href="https://t.co/kJotCxFyWY">https://t.co/kJotCxFyWY</a></p>&mdash; Jeremy Hogan (@attorneyjeremy1) <a href="https://twitter.com/attorneyjeremy1/status/1534145506611449859?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 7, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Even IF a digital asset falls under SEC oversight, the reporting requirements aren’t onerous. AT LEAST it’s possible that a crypto company could fulfill the reporting requirements (unlike now). In summary, I like it. It tries and mainly strikes a nice balance. [In my opinion].”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/lummis-bill/">Lummis Bill Considers Cryptocurrencies as Commodities</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/lummis-bill/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Regulations Will Divide Them in Two Categories</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-regulations-sec-cftc/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-regulations-sec-cftc/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CFTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5451</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Recently, the Biden Administration took a serious step toward crypto regulations. To begin with, cryptocurrencies are a matter of national security in The US and multiple agencies are responsible to make reports to the Whitehouse regarding the upcoming crypto regulations. Initially, agencies are to analyze and research the sector and basically find out who’s jurisdiction [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-regulations-sec-cftc/">Crypto Regulations Will Divide Them in Two Categories</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Recently, the Biden Administration took a serious <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/crypto-regulations-national-security/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">step</a> toward crypto regulations. To begin with, cryptocurrencies are a matter of national security in The US and multiple agencies are responsible to make reports to the Whitehouse regarding the upcoming crypto regulations. Initially, agencies are to analyze and research the sector and basically find out who’s jurisdiction it is to regulate these digital assets. The analysis phase will go on until the end of 2022’s third quarter. However, new information coming from CFTC Chief indicates a categorization on the horizon to deal with cryptocurrencies.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Exchange Cryptocurrencies to PayPal Instantly on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Divided Crypto Regulations</strong></h2>



<p>Are they commodities, or are they securities? Tis the question that the regulators are arguing about. The Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) chair Behnam has said in a recent interview that cryptocurrencies may be divided into different categories. In order to come up with a legal framework for crypto regulations, cryptocurrencies must first find their definition.</p>



<p>With a recent interview, on CNBC, Behnam pointed out that the categorization can make a big difference on regulation agencies. In short, if they are commodities, then the CFTC will have oversight. If selected as securities, then the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) will take care of them.</p>



<p>“Within this fear of digital assets and the coins which make up thousands of thousands, they are naturally going to be some commodities and securities. In my view, it makes sense to sort of parse through the two and figure out where we can place each.</p>



<p>It’s going to be difficult because from a legislative standpoint and given the novelties of some of these coins and the technology, we have to figure out what will constitute the security under the traditional securities law and what would constitute more of a commodity so that we can regulate appropriately – given the two different legal structures.”</p>



<p>But, Behnam believes that Bitcoin and Ethereum are in fact commodities which makes sense. Bitcoin and Ethereum are the two largest cryptocurrencies by market cap.</p>



<p>“I can say for sure Bitcoin, which is the largest of the coins and has always been the largest regardless of the total market cap of the entire digital asset market capitalization, is a commodity.</p>



<p>Ethereum as well. I have argued this before, my predecessors said it is a commodity. There may be, in fact, hundreds, if not thousands of security coins, but there are plenty of commodity coins that I think it makes sense, as we’ve done historically, to make sure that each agency has jurisdiction over commodities and securities respectively.”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Will it Make a Difference?</strong></h2>



<p>We know for a fact that the SEC is a sworn enemy of all that is crypto. Although. They have not said it exactly this way, they have made quite a few remarks that supports our theory. Gary Gensler, the head of SEC has <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/secs-gary-gensler-skeptic-of-crypto-signals-crackdowns/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">called</a> cryptocurrencies private money from the wildcat banking era. So, if crypto regulations come from the SEC, then they wouldn’t be pleasant at all.</p>



<p>However, Behnam indicated that they are pretty much on the same page with the SEC on crypto regulations. So, commodities or securities, both agencies are going to be imposing the bejesus out of them crypto regulations.</p>



<p>“We each are trying to do what’s best and right now, and we saw this last week, a lot of people got hurt, a lot of values lost in the market and there really are no customer protections right now. We have a number of state-level regulations and oversights but in terms of market oversight, in terms of disclosures, we don’t really have much right now as it relates to traditional financial markets…</p>



<p>need to put forward a regulatory framework that will protect customers, make appropriate disclosures and ultimately, for those who support the industry, support its growth and maturity over the next couple of years.”</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-regulations-sec-cftc/">Crypto Regulations Will Divide Them in Two Categories</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-regulations-sec-cftc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Update: Ripple Lawsuit Turns the Tide Against SEC</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/ripple-lawsuit-continues-as-sec-tries-to-cheat/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/ripple-lawsuit-continues-as-sec-tries-to-cheat/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 05:09:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple Lawsuit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4059</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Ripple lawsuit has been going on since 2020! The SEC has been doing their best to fight Ripple but Ripple Inc is a completely different entity than your average hedge fund bro. Honestly, SEC has a pretty extraordinary track record on winning legal cases. There are rumors flying around that SEC has only lost [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ripple-lawsuit-continues-as-sec-tries-to-cheat/">Update: Ripple Lawsuit Turns the Tide Against SEC</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Ripple lawsuit has been going on since 2020! The SEC has been doing their best to fight Ripple but Ripple Inc is a completely different entity than your average hedge fund bro. Honestly, SEC has a pretty extraordinary track record on winning legal cases. There are rumors flying around that SEC has only lost a handful of cases but it&#8217;s not true. Statistics aside, this time may be different for the commission. DeFi is definitely new territory for making legal cases and Ripple Inc is no ordinary DeFi platform. A new interview with Ripple CEO has shed light on the current situation. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">You can learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-ripple-xrp-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your Ripple to PayPal</a> on CoinCannon.</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Federal Judge Says No to SEC! (April 15)</h2>



<p>Recently, SEC made a request to withhold specific information in the form of internal email conversations regarding the Ripple lawsuit. However, a federal judge has turned down the request from U.S Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). </p>



<p>Judge Sarah Netburn made an order to SEC to surrender the relevant drafts and messages related to the case. More specifically, information concerning a 2018 speech from the former director of Corporate Finance Division William Hinman.</p>



<p>Why is it so important? Well, Hinman has apparently said in the speech that Ethereum (ETH) is not a security. And of course, SEC has alleged Ripple Inc for selling XRP as an unregistered security. And it seems that the almighty regulators has failed to stay on the same page on an internal level when it comes to cryptocurrencies. </p>



<p>Initially, Judge Netburn made the order in January but the SEC made an objection. Subsequently, Netburn denied the regulator&#8217;s motion to reconsider the order. But, she did provide a legal clarification. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">The Clarification (April 15)</h2>



<p>&#8220;<em>As discussed above, the question is whether any of the communications about, edits to, or comments on drafts of the Speech were not just related to specific deliberations facing the agency but comprised an ‘essential link’ in those deliberations. Having reviewed the documents, I find that, in general, agency staff communications about edits to the Speech—and the edits themselves—were not part of deliberations about how to communicate agency policy.</em></p>



<p><em>However, to the extent that there exist communications between staff discussing the Speech in the context of how it implicates other, separate agency deliberations—not deliberations about the content of the speech—the SEC may seek leave to redact those communications from its production. To give the SEC some guidance, comment 12 on page 6 of the Speech draft in Document J, which was submitted for in camera review, is the type of communication contemplated.”</em></p>



<p>At this point, SEC may appeal this decision which is of course a very likely decision. And of course, depending on which judge they get, this crucial piece of evidence can choose the fate of the Ripple Lawsuit. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Ripple lawsuit</strong> Delayed</h2>



<p>The SEC filed a lawsuit against Ripple Labs in December 2020 in an effort to prove XRP being an unregistered security. On the other side of the spectrum, many believe that the Ripple is a threat to the international banking system. With that in mind, the SEC is doing what they always did, protect the banking industry.</p>



<p>To make your life easier, you can read our unbiased guide into “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-ripple/">What is Ripple</a>”.</p>



<p>All the drama aside, the SEC <a href="https://www.crypto-law.us/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/SEC-Letter-Request-to-Extend-Discovery-and-Exhibits-10152021.pdf">requested</a> for an extra two months in order to gather evidence. The pre-trial discovery phase allows both parties to gather information and evidence to present in the court.</p>



<p>The SEC demanded the discovery phase to be extended until January 14<sup>th</sup> 2021 for “sufficient time to prepare rebuttal reports and depose a minimum of 14 expert witnesses.”</p>



<p>The Ripple Labs on the other hand called it an unfair request that prolongs the trial for Ripple Lawsuit.</p>



<p>“The SEC’s proposed deadline of January 14… would needlessly prolong discovery, despite both parties’ stated intention to resolve this litigation on an expedited timeline.” Says Ripple.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Ripple Army Be Mad!</strong></h2>



<p>Naturally, the latest request from SEC had the crypto supporters angry as it is interpreted as cheating. The SEC does not exactly have a great track record. Back in 2008, the SEC was the primary agency that could prevent the market crash by paying closer attention to the mortgage industry and the ridiculous CDOs (collateralized debt obligations).</p>



<p>We have previously <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/xrp-coin-predictions-where-is-ripple-headed/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">discussed</a> the details of the lawsuit and possible tactics the SEC could utilize.</p>



<p>The outspoken Attorney and crypto supporter Jeremy Hogan responded to the request on Twitter. He stated that granting this request would postpone the Ripple lawsuit to March or May of 2022. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">What&#39;s clear from this motion to extend discovery out 2 more months is that the SEC filed this $1.4 Billion dollar lawsuit without setting aside the resources to prosecute it.<br><br>IF the judge grants it, the main parts of the case won&#39;t be decided until March-May of &#39;22!<br><br>Thoughts? <a href="https://t.co/AKlwcup5YO">https://t.co/AKlwcup5YO</a> <a href="https://t.co/G7gU3R1vLo">pic.twitter.com/G7gU3R1vLo</a></p>&mdash; Jeremy Hogan (@attorneyjeremy1) <a href="https://twitter.com/attorneyjeremy1/status/1449352112064843777?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">October 16, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Update on Ripple Lawsuit (March 7, 2022)</h2>



<p>In a recent interview, Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse stated the the securities and exchange commission has a bumpy road ahead. Furthermore, Garlinghouse told Fox Business that the SEC essentially tricked them by changing their mind on XRP.</p>



<p> <em>“The irony there is like we were in the SEC’s office. I met with Chairman Clayton. I was meeting with commissioners. No one ever once said, ‘Hey we think XRP is a security.’ They looked backward and say, ‘Now we think it’s all security.’ That’s a hard argument.”</em></p>



<p>Interestingly, Garlinghouse mentioned a point that may very well be the case for SEC. He argued that the SEC really does not know how &#8220;<em>Crypto Really Works</em>&#8221; and basically they are in uncharted territory. This lack of understanding has lawmakers baffled and of course caused platforms quite a bit of damage. </p>



<p><em>“I think it does a disservice to responsible actors like Ripple who are working with governments, with sanctions. Everything that is enforced from a sanction point of view through fiat currency, anything that Ripple does is enforced from the state in the exact same way. There’s no different level playing field. And in some ways, I heard Senator Warren saying things that felt like its holding crypto to a different standard, for example, expecting a blanket ban of all crypto in some of these countries… Well, you can still use PayPal. You can still use some of these other things, and I don’t think we should treat them differently.”</em></p>



<p>According to garlinghouse, Gary Gensler is still against crypto and seeing it as wild west. At this point, it is difficult to predict how much longer the case could take. Having said that, despite SEC&#8217;s resilience, Ripple may have a solid chance of winning their case. Primarily, the nature of this lawsuit is unfamiliar to both lawmakers and the SEC. In that regard, the odds are against SEC.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Buy and Sell XRP Coin on <strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><a href="http://hi.exchange">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.okchanger.com/exchangers/jolixo">OkChanger</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. We are on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/">Bestchange</a> and are always amongst the top exchanges.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ripple-lawsuit-continues-as-sec-tries-to-cheat/">Update: Ripple Lawsuit Turns the Tide Against SEC</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/ripple-lawsuit-continues-as-sec-tries-to-cheat/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Financial Regulator, Tales from the Chain IX</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/financial-regulator-tax/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/financial-regulator-tax/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 06:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[CoinCannon Special]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Regulator]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Treasury]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4256</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The financial regulator is there to serve and to protect. To tax the rich and to bring financial stability to the nation. It is a noble quest to supervise and regulate all financial activity in a nation. It is 2021, inflation is insane, people are losing jobs, Biden’s administration is gonna make rich people feel [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/financial-regulator-tax/">Financial Regulator, Tales from the Chain IX</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The financial regulator is there to serve and to protect. To tax the rich and to bring financial stability to the nation. It is a noble quest to supervise and regulate all financial activity in a nation. It is 2021, inflation is insane, people are losing jobs, Biden’s administration is gonna make rich people feel the pain.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Financial Regulator to the Rescue</strong></h2>



<p>The world is unfair, there are those who print money in times of need and cause hyperinflation. There are companies who sell a total of million cars in a couple of years and are worth more than Ford who sells 20 million a year. There are people who impose tax on common people and neglect the rich.</p>



<p>But, the financial regulator does not care about that. He or She is only concerned with the safety of investors assets. And to make the world a better place, they call for more taxes and more regulations right where it hits the common folk.</p>



<p>However, at this point one should not forget that the regulator is not a US native. They are everywhere across the globe.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Smart Regulator</strong></h2>



<p>First and foremost, people need to keep calm. In the event of a sinking ship, what matters is that the people remain on their seats as they sink. Just look back at 2008 financial collapse. A few months before that, everyone was assured that the mortgage section is solid, secure and safe. This is important because if they didn’t keep calm, there would have been an even bigger collapse.</p>



<p>You see, the inflation is growing at record levels in the US. In China, the real estate market which makes up one third of the nation’s income is literally torn to pieces. In Brazil, India and Germany there is an energy crisis going on. Australia is like a high security dystopian prison where the citizens are ordered to limit their commute. Yet, what matters is that cryptocurrencies are taxed.</p>



<p>The passive income which helped save the livelihood of the people should be taxed. This is all because crypto is unsafe. Central bankers and policy makers who print money are good people. Marxist politicians who officially state on the TV that there would be no inflation are good people. Just don’t buy Ethereum because it is volatile.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Financial Regulator Dilemma</strong></h2>



<p>Long story short, ain’t nobody got time to look for the cause. Nobody is interested to imprison those who lie with a straight face about the future. The financial expert does not care about the trillions of dollars spent on war. Instead, they go bald behind their generic office desks looking for solutions. And boy do they come up with them!</p>



<p>Don’t have faith in them? Just take a look at how successful they are in controlling inflation, bubbles and fraudulent ventures.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><a href="http://hi.exchange">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.okchanger.com/exchangers/jolixo">OkChanger</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. We are on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/">Bestchange</a> and are always amongst the top exchanges.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/financial-regulator-tax/">Financial Regulator, Tales from the Chain IX</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/financial-regulator-tax/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Another Bitcoin ETF Set to Roll Out in US</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/another-bitcoin-etf-set-to-roll-out-in-us/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/another-bitcoin-etf-set-to-roll-out-in-us/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4063</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin ETF is now the talk of the town. Following the successful launch of the ProShares’ Bitcoin Strategy ETF (BITO), another similar product will be available. As of October 22, Valkyrie Investments has rolled out the second Bitcoin ETF in the US. The Valkyrie Bitcoin Strategy ETF is now trading on Nasdaq by the symbol [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/another-bitcoin-etf-set-to-roll-out-in-us/">Another Bitcoin ETF Set to Roll Out in US</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Bitcoin ETF is now the talk of the town. Following the successful launch of the ProShares’ Bitcoin Strategy ETF (BITO), another similar product will be available.</p>



<p>As of October 22, Valkyrie Investments has rolled out the second Bitcoin ETF in the US. The Valkyrie Bitcoin Strategy ETF is now trading on Nasdaq by the symbol BTF.</p>



<p>You can Directly buy or sell Bitcoin on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> with the best exchange rates at any moment.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Bitcoin ETF to the Rescue</strong></h2>



<p>Some call it a coincidence, others see it as irrelevant. Nonetheless, Bitcoin managed to reach a new ATH the same day its first ETF was introduced on Nasdaq. The <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/a-bitcoin-rally-could-cause-damage-for-altcoins/">skyrocketing</a> in value has brought attention to the cryptocurrency as an alternative asset to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/as-inflation-grows-institutions-buy-bitcoin/">hedge against the inflation</a>.</p>



<p>It should also be mentioned that BITO is now the second largest ETF launch. It managed to mark almost $1 billion in volume only on first day.</p>



<p>The Exchange-Traded Funds provides exposure to future contracts for Bitcoin and does not directly invest in BTC.</p>



<p>The asset management firm Valkyrie is now following the footsteps of ProShares by launching another ETF.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Surge in Price</strong></h2>



<p>In a recent <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-10-20/jpmorgan-says-bitcoin-s-record-run-is-being-driven-by-inflation">Bloomberg</a> article, A JP Morgan analyst claims that the primary cause for the rapid growth is still the fear of rising inflation.</p>



<p>Furthermore, he stated that the excitement over this launch will soon fade away.</p>



<p>“By itself, the launch of BITO is unlikely to trigger a new phase of significantly more fresh capital entering Bitcoin.” He went on further to say “The initial hype with BITO could fade after a week”.</p>



<p>BTC managed to reach a record high of $66,988 two days ago and has now settled around $61,000 as of writing October 22. Data provided by <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/bitcoin">CoinGecko</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><a href="http://hi.exchange">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.okchanger.com/exchangers/jolixo">OkChanger</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. We are on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/">Bestchange</a> and are always amongst the top exchanges.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/another-bitcoin-etf-set-to-roll-out-in-us/">Another Bitcoin ETF Set to Roll Out in US</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/another-bitcoin-etf-set-to-roll-out-in-us/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Under Attack, 6000 Accounts Hacked</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/coinbase-under-attack-6000-accounts-hacked/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/coinbase-under-attack-6000-accounts-hacked/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 07:35:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Private Information]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=3905</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase says more than 6000 customers have lost their assets. In a letter sent to the California Attorney General, they stated that the hackers took advantage of a flaw in the SMS account recovery process. They were able to receive an SMS two-factor authentication token allowing them to gain access to the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/coinbase-under-attack-6000-accounts-hacked/">Coinbase Under Attack, 6000 Accounts Hacked</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase says more than 6000 customers have lost their assets. In a letter sent to the California Attorney General, they stated that the hackers took advantage of a flaw in the SMS account recovery process. They were able to receive an SMS two-factor authentication token allowing them to gain access to the funds. Then, they quickly sent the funds into their own secure wallet.</p>



<p>As it seems, the hackers were targeting these customers beforehand. They had prepared e-mail accounts, phone numbers and passwords associated with the victim accounts. However, Coinbase strongly rejects the possibility of their private information stolen from their servers.</p>



<p>“In this incident, for customers who use SMS texts for two-factor authentication, the third party took advantage of a flaw in Coinbase’s SMS Account Recovery process in order to receive an SMS two-factor authentication token and gain access to your account.”</p>



<p>These attacks apparently carried out between March and May of 2021.</p>



<p>Coinbase claims that they have updated the account recovery protocol to prevent further attacks. The follow up process to find the bad actors is now officially active in cooperation with the law enforcement.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Coinbase is Important</strong></h2>



<p>It is worth knowing that Coinbase is the primary cryptocurrency exchange of the United States. The US customers certainly have fewer choices for crypto exchanges due to tight regulations regarding these platforms.</p>



<p>Following regulatory crackdowns on <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-binance-coin-bnb-a-beginners-guide-to-bnb/">Binance</a> in the US, cryptocurrency exchanges are being closely watched by the US Treasury and <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/secs-gary-gensler-skeptic-of-crypto-signals-crackdowns/">SEC</a>.</p>



<p>A reoccurring pattern of similar series of attacks can be disastrous for Coinbase and other crypto exchanges active in the US. Furthermore, we stand in a crucial time in history where skepticism toward crypto is strong. Any negligence toward customer service and security can be detrimental to the whole market at this point..</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">jolixo</h2>



<p><a href="http://hi.exchange">Hi.exchange</a> is an online decentralized platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and digital currencies. Our automated systems automatically determine the best exchange rates based on the competition. Furthermore, we provide 24l7 customer support. You can visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange">Hi exchange Blog</a> to stay up to date with our latest opinion articles, technical price analysis and news.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/coinbase-under-attack-6000-accounts-hacked/">Coinbase Under Attack, 6000 Accounts Hacked</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/coinbase-under-attack-6000-accounts-hacked/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC&#8217;s Gary Gensler skeptic of Crypto, Signals Crackdowns</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/secs-gary-gensler-skeptic-of-crypto-signals-crackdowns/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/secs-gary-gensler-skeptic-of-crypto-signals-crackdowns/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 07:37:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gary Gensler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Treasury]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=3804</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SEC’s Gary Gensler has further cleared their stance on Cryptocurrencies and stablecoins in a recent Interview with the Washington Post. And the unsurprising answer is, Skeptic! During this interview, the Securities and Exchange Commission Chairman addresses two primary subjects of cryptocurrencies (private money) and stablecoins. With not so witty dramatic analogies, Gensler regards the crypto [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/secs-gary-gensler-skeptic-of-crypto-signals-crackdowns/">SEC&#8217;s Gary Gensler skeptic of Crypto, Signals Crackdowns</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>SEC’s Gary Gensler has further cleared their stance on Cryptocurrencies and stablecoins in a recent Interview with the <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/washington-post-live/2021/09/21/path-forward-cryptocurrency-with-gary-gensler-us-securities-exchange-commission-chair/">Washington Post</a>. And the unsurprising answer is, Skeptic!</p>



<p>During this interview, the Securities and Exchange Commission Chairman addresses two primary subjects of cryptocurrencies (private money) and stablecoins. With not so witty dramatic analogies, Gensler regards the crypto market as “wild west casino” and the stablecoins the “poker chips” of it.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Gary Gensler on Private Money</strong></h2>



<p>Following a bearish summer for crypto after the <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/china-crackdowns-on-bitcoin-why-so-harsh-opinion/">China Lockdowns</a>, It seems that the United States Federal Government shares the same views as China.</p>



<p>By the looks of it, we <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/elizabeth-warren-calls-crypto-the-new-shadow-bank/">predicted the US treasury and the SEC will take an opposing stance regarding cryptocurrencies</a>. This recent interview was sadly an indication of upcoming crackdowns and harsh regulations. And the news reached us on a rainy day, amidst the bearish market caused by <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/evergrande-and-china-responsible-for-the-dip/">China’s Evergrande possible default</a>.</p>



<p>Gensler expressed his skepticism regarding private money stating that they have proven to unsustainable. In case of cryptocurrencies, having thousands of such project is an even worse according to Gensler.</p>



<p>&#8220;Private monies usually don&#8217;t last that long. So, I don&#8217;t think there&#8217;s a long-term viability for 5,000 or 6,000 private forms of money. History tells us otherwise,&#8221; said Gensler. To address this issue, he stated “So, in the meantime, I think it&#8217;s worthwhile to have an investor protection regime placed around this&#8221;.</p>



<p>Once again, He called the more than $2 trillion crypto market as “wild west”.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>On Stablecoins and Exchanges</strong></h2>



<p><a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/regulatory-actions-against-stablecoins-are-coming/">The stablecoins have been on the spotlight lately</a>. US Treasury Janet Yellen and SEC’s Gary Gensler have both called for regulations on stablecoins. During the interview, Gensler called the stablecoins as “Poker Chips” of the crypto casino.</p>



<p>“The SEC is putting together a report about stable coins under the guidance of Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen” said Gensler. It would be possible that they work with the Congress to maintain a better leverage.</p>



<p>In a senate hearing last week, <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/sec-gary-gensler-crypto-regulation-exchanges-coinbase-securities-lending-2021-9?utm_source=markets&amp;utm_medium=ingest">Gensler told the Banking Committee</a> that the cryptocurrency exchanges need to register with SEC since their products or tokens may be securities.</p>



<p>&#8220;Those platforms should come in, they should figure out how to register, be an investment&#8211;investor protection remit,&#8221; he told the Washington Post.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Regulated future of Cryptocurrency</strong></h2>



<p>It would be impossible to make predictions about the future of cryptocurrencies. However, we should wait and see up to what extent the US is willing to push regulations on crypto. China has set the bar high with crackdowns. Despite that, cryptocurrencies showed great resilience maintaining the $30k support. It would be great to know how far can policymakers affect the market this time.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Our Vision</strong></h2>



<p>We believe in crypto, not only for income but liberation as well. Although we’re not the first decentralized online exchange, we’re looking to be the best. You can exchange your cryptocurrencies and digital currencies on <a href="hi.exchange">hi.exchange</a>. We Utilize an automated system to determine the best rates. Furthermore, we offer 24/7 customer support. Also, we have technical price analysis for Bitcoin and Altcoins, opinion articles and news on <a href="blog.hi.exchange">our blog</a>. Our vision is to keep our customers up do date with the latest news and professional analysis.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/secs-gary-gensler-skeptic-of-crypto-signals-crackdowns/">SEC&#8217;s Gary Gensler skeptic of Crypto, Signals Crackdowns</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/secs-gary-gensler-skeptic-of-crypto-signals-crackdowns/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Regulatory Actions Against Stablecoins Are Coming</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/regulatory-actions-against-stablecoins-are-coming/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/regulatory-actions-against-stablecoins-are-coming/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 07:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Digital Currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=3786</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Stablecoins have been causing so much controversy lately. The crypto market continues as the longest running bullish market in history. In that regard, the stablecoins are the necessary medium in this market. As of late, recent rumors and statements from Washington are indicating a possible wave of new regulations coming on stablecoins way. Stablecoins [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/regulatory-actions-against-stablecoins-are-coming/">Regulatory Actions Against Stablecoins Are Coming</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Stablecoins have been causing so much controversy lately. The crypto market continues as the longest running bullish market in history. In that regard, the stablecoins are the necessary medium in this market. As of late, recent rumors and statements from Washington are indicating a possible wave of new regulations coming on stablecoins way.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Stablecoins and CBDCs</strong></h2>



<p>Generally speaking, a stablecoin is a type of digital currency that has its value pegged to another asset. Most commonly, fiat pegged stablecoins are used in cryptocurrency trading. However, their superpower is to make quick, cheap and mostly secure transaction on the blockchain network as an alternative for banking services. Considering the impressive <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/view/stablecoin/">$126 billion market cap</a> as of September, 2021, it is no wonder the politicians are worried about it.</p>



<p>To be fair, a valid argument against private sector stablecoins is that regarding the value, many of them are backed by debt. On the other hand, the decentralized nature of these companies can make it difficult to protect the users against possibly malicious policies. Subsequently, the governments are now seeking to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/cbdc-the-ultimate-financial-apparatus-for-governments/">issue Government backed stablecoins or CBDC</a>.</p>



<p>The concern lies in the fact that CBDC can be an over powered apparatus for central banks that initially limits people from owning or having access to their wealth. The money is not in their hands, the money is on a digital network and the bank can block access if they wanted. In a dystopian situation, central banks can impose negative interest rates on bank accounts. Furthermore, it would be entirely possible for policymakers to impose regulations demanding only CBDC is the only legal medium to trade crypto.  <a href="https://www.atlanticcouncil.org/cbdctracker/">Currently 83 countries are looking into CBDC release.</a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Possible Legal Approaches for Stablecoins</strong></h2>



<p>Only a few days ago, a <a href="https://home.treasury.gov/news/press-releases/jy0281">press release from the US Treasury</a> demanded quick actions against stablecoins expressing urgency. This is an indication of the severity of the situation.</p>



<p>Yesterday, a <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2021/09/17/business/economy/federal-reserve-virtual-currency-stablecoin.html">New York Times article</a> discussed six different legal approaches that lawmakers can take against stablecoins. Here are the six approaches:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list"><li>Regarding them as “systematically risky”. This would call for strict and harsh regulatory control can be quite destructive for them.</li><li>Recognizing them as “securities” and putting them under SEC supervision. (oh lawd)</li><li>Regulate them as Banks, putting them under the office of the Comptroller of Currency.</li><li>Engage in an active competition utilizing CBDC (or release the hounds in other terms).</li></ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Bottom line</strong></h2>



<p>Sadly, it would be unrealistic to expect a phenomenon like stablecoin can continue this much unregulated. As it grows in market cap, the realization has hit the politicians that first, they want some if not all the profit and second, it is too liberating to be considered as safe for the political structure. Conversely, the fraudulent activities, lack of vision or in some cases just bad luck has given the crypto market a bad image for politicians to exploit. We must wait and see the regulatory outcome of stablecoin discussions. However, we could be sure that people are losing ground in these regulatory battles.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Our Vision</strong></h2>



<p>We believe in crypto, not only for income but liberation as well. Although we’re not the first decentralized online exchange, we’re looking to be the best.  You can exchange your cryptocurrencies and digital currencies on <a href="hi.exchange">hi.exchange</a>. We Utilize an automated system to determine the best rates. Furthermore, we offer 24/7 customer support. Also, we have technical price analysis for Bitcoin and Altcoins, opinion articles and news on <a href="blog.hi.exchange">our blog</a>. Our vision is to keep our customers up do date with the latest news and professional analysis.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/regulatory-actions-against-stablecoins-are-coming/">Regulatory Actions Against Stablecoins Are Coming</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/regulatory-actions-against-stablecoins-are-coming/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CBDC, the Ultimate Financial Apparatus for Governments</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/cbdc-the-ultimate-financial-apparatus-for-governments/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/cbdc-the-ultimate-financial-apparatus-for-governments/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 10:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Digital Currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[China]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[interest rates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=3695</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It seems that the pursuit of central bank digital currencies (CBDC) has gained so much momentum lately. China, came up with the digital Yuan raising speculations about the possible agenda. Then US and the European union announced their Digital dollar and Euro to be utilized soon. On the surface, this was a development toward the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/cbdc-the-ultimate-financial-apparatus-for-governments/">CBDC, the Ultimate Financial Apparatus for Governments</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>It seems that the pursuit of central bank digital currencies (CBDC) has gained so much momentum lately. China, came up with the digital Yuan raising speculations about the possible agenda. Then US and the European union announced their Digital dollar and Euro to be utilized soon. On the surface, this was a development toward the up and coming financial technology.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">The Threat That is Crypto</h2>



<p>With the rise of the cryptocurrency industry, central banks lost a great deal of dominance over the world’s finance. This was due to the superior profits, anonymity, availability and better exchange rates that crypto provides. On the other hand, a crucial medium for these transactions were the stablecoins. A type of digital currency that has its value pegged to another asset such as fiat currencies.</p>



<p>This emerging market with high inflows is causing great concerns for governments regardless of their political orientations. In a recent opinion article, we discussed how the <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/china-crackdowns-on-bitcoin-why-so-harsh-opinion/">cryptocurrencies were having an impact on the China’s political structure</a>. On the other hand, the massive inflow into crypto currencies has cost gold a great deal of inflows. In that regard, US banks are deeply concerned with this prevailing phenomenon. Only a few days ago, we predicted that due to the recent increase in SCE’s activities, <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/elizabeth-warren-calls-crypto-the-new-shadow-bank/">there could be a wave of destructive crackdowns coming toward crypto-related institutions</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Commence the Trojan Horse</strong></h2>



<p>With all that said, the persistence to create a national CBDC seems to be bit rushed and a bit unnecessary. After all, why not adopt a pre-existing stablecoin? Why must central banks spend billions of dollars to re-invent the wheel?</p>



<p>A CBDC provides so much regulatory potential for a government. To begin with, it could be much easier to trace the transactions utilizing CBDC. However, it’s entirely possible that at some point, governments demand that entry and exit into the crypto market can only be done using CBDC. In that case, it will be much easier to impose taxes on investors as their private activities are compromised.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CBDC and the Negative Interest Rates</strong></h2>



<p>In an eye-opening <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/digital-currencies-pave-way-for-deeply-negative-interest-rates-11631091581">Wall Street Journal article</a>, the famous financial journalist <a href="https://www.wsj.com/news/author/james-mackintosh">James Mackintosh</a> has pointed out a possible use case scenario for CBDC. According to Mackintosh, CBDCs can be an over powered apparatus for central bankers to adjust interest rates. As of now, the interest rates are the lowest in the US at 0.25%. In the worst case scenario, they could only fall to zero. When it comes down to that, people would rather keep cash under their pillows than to have it held in banks.</p>



<p>So long as there is cash, you are the master of your own money. Yet, when speaking of CBDC, banks will have the capability to impose “deeply negative interest rates”. You heard me right, with digital money, central banks can impose negative interest rates or better said “harm rates”.</p>



<p>This strategy is a last effort to fight inflation in a country but nonetheless, people must be in charge of their money. If central banks are responsible for the inflation to begin with, should they harm our life savings in the times of need?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Current State of CBDC Projects</strong></h2>



<p><a href="https://www.atlanticcouncil.org/cbdctracker/">The Atlantic council has a dedicated CBDC tracker</a> on their website. As of now, 5 countries have launched their central bank digital currency projects. The China is currently piloting the project while the US is in the research phase.</p>



<p>As the crypto market grows in value, the oppressive regulations and false interventions rise in numbers. Unchallenged for many years, Central banks are now desperate to defeat their foe. Lobbyist politicians are creating FUDs and spreading fear in order to fight crypto. And finally, CBDCs are being developed fast. In many ways, we are witnessing a financial renaissance. The traditional neoclassical finance is faced with the peril of a pragmatic opponent. The question is, in the escalating tensions between both parties, will the common folk prevail?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Our Vision</strong></h2>



<p>We believe in crypto, not only for income but liberation as well. Although we’re not the first decentralized online exchange, we’re looking to be the best. We believe that the market should be accessible and the customer has the right to maintain as much anonymity as they desire. This goal is now possible thanks to our automated systems and 24/7 customer support to ensure a secure and reliable exchange process. You can exchange your cryptocurrencies and digital currencies on <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/china-crackdowns-on-bitcoin-why-so-harsh-opinion/hi.exchange">hi.exchange</a>. Also, we have technical price analysis for Bitcoin and Altcoins, opinion articles and news <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/china-crackdowns-on-bitcoin-why-so-harsh-opinion/blog.hi.exchange">on our blog</a> to keep our customers up do date with the latest news and professional analysis for their investment journey.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/cbdc-the-ultimate-financial-apparatus-for-governments/">CBDC, the Ultimate Financial Apparatus for Governments</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/cbdc-the-ultimate-financial-apparatus-for-governments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
