<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Payeer USD Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/payeer-usd/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 11:35:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Exchange Payeer USD to Other Currencies [Step-by-Step]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-payeer-usd-to-other-currencies-easy-guide/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-payeer-usd-to-other-currencies-easy-guide/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 11:35:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[e-currency to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer USD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4199</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you are looking to exchange Payeer USD to cryptocurrencies or digital currencies, you might want to read how to exchange Payeer to PayPal first. Don&#8217;t forget you can always exchange Payeer to cryptocurrency or other currencies here at CoinCannon. the transaction and requirements might be a bit confusing. Luckily, this post will provide a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-payeer-usd-to-other-currencies-easy-guide/">Exchange Payeer USD to Other Currencies [Step-by-Step]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you are looking to exchange Payeer USD to cryptocurrencies or digital currencies, you might want to read <a href="/blog/how-exchange-payeer-usd-to-paypal/">how to exchange Payeer to PayPal</a> first. Don&#8217;t forget you can always exchange Payeer to cryptocurrency or other currencies here at CoinCannon. the transaction and requirements might be a bit confusing. Luckily, this post will provide a step-by step guide on how to send Payeer USD to another wallet. Furthermore, you will learn how to find your account number and operation id.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color"><a href="/directions/popular/exchange-payeer-paypal">Exchange Payeer to PayPal</a> or other currencies in 4 easy steps </mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-exchange-payeer-usd"><strong>How to Exchange Payeer USD</strong></h2>



<p>To begin with, you must first enter your Payeer account. As you log in, you are directed to the Dashboard. From there, you can navigate to different menus.</p>



<p>For this article, we demonstrate how to make a transaction. In order to make the payment, click on the “Transfer” menu on the left sidebar menu.</p>



<p>On the Transfer page, type the destination account number, remember that if it is a Payeer account, the number will start with the letter “P”. Following that, type the desired amount you want to transfer. To finish the transfer, simply click on “Send” button.</p>



<p>If you are new to Payeer, you can learn all about the platform on “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-payeer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Payeer</a>” article.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="1024" height="562" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Payeer-Transfer-1024x562.jpg" alt="Exchange Payeer USD" class="wp-image-4200" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Payeer-Transfer-1024x562.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Payeer-Transfer-300x165.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Payeer-Transfer-768x422.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Payeer-Transfer.jpg 1069w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-payeer-account-number"><strong>Payeer Account Number</strong></h2>



<p>To exchange Payeer USD, you need to give the exchange platform your account number so that they can transfer funds to your account. To find account number, simply click on the account menu on the top-right. The account number and other information will appear and you can easily copy the number.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="443" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Payeer-Account-Number-1024x443.jpg" alt="Exchange Payeer USD" class="wp-image-4201" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Payeer-Account-Number-1024x443.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Payeer-Account-Number-300x130.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Payeer-Account-Number-768x333.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Payeer-Account-Number.jpg 1365w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-payeer-operation-id"><strong>Payeer Operation ID</strong></h2>



<p>The operation id is a dedicated identification code that holds the transfer information for a transaction. To exchange Payeer USD on any platform, you will need this id to prove your payment firs. The operation id is simple to find. To do so, first click on the “History” on the left sidebar.</p>



<p>In the page that appears, you can see all your previous transaction. For the specific transaction, click on the ID. By clicking on the ID, information about the transaction will appear and you can see the operation id. Simply copy it and use it on the exchange platform.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="467" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Payeer-operation-id-1024x467.jpg" alt="Exchange Payeer USD" class="wp-image-4202" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Payeer-operation-id-1024x467.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Payeer-operation-id-300x137.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Payeer-operation-id-768x350.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Payeer-operation-id.jpg 1309w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-exchange-payeer-usd-on-jolixo"><strong>Exchange Payeer USD on CoinCannon</strong></h2>



<p><a href="http://hi.exchange">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require complex KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/jolixo-exchanger.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Bestchange</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. You can easily <a href="/directions/popular/exchange-payeer-paypal">swap Payeer to PayPal</a> or other Digital currencies or CRyptocurrencies on CoinCannon.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-payeer-usd-to-other-currencies-easy-guide/">Exchange Payeer USD to Other Currencies [Step-by-Step]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-payeer-usd-to-other-currencies-easy-guide/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top Forex Brokers that Accept Payeer</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/forex-brokers-accepting-payeer/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/forex-brokers-accepting-payeer/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:28:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Accept Payeer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Forex Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer USD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5561</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Forex traders are no stranger to Payeer as an efficient payment system. In general, Payeer offers three types of services. First, Payeer Transfers is the most popular one that allows users around the world to transfer funds with low fees. Second, Payeer Merchant is basically a payment solution for e-commerce. And third, Payeer Prepaid which [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/forex-brokers-accepting-payeer/">Top Forex Brokers that Accept Payeer</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Forex traders are no stranger to Payeer as an efficient payment system. In general, Payeer offers three types of services. First, Payeer Transfers is the most popular one that allows users around the world to transfer funds with low fees. Second, Payeer Merchant is basically a payment solution for e-commerce. And third, Payeer Prepaid which is a personal ATM card with zero fees that can be used anywhere. However, if you want to add money to forex, not a lot of platforms accept this payment system. In this article, we will introduce some of the best forex brokers that accept Payeer USD.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color"><a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/buy-cryptocurrencies-with-payeer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Learn how</a> to buy cryptocurrencies with Payeer USD on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a></mark></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Is Payeer a Good Payment System?</strong></h2>



<p>Short answer is yes. As of 2022, the Payeer has over 7 million users which can transfer funds to each other for free. The strength however, lies in diversity. Payeer is far ahead of any similar platform in terms of scale of operation and diversity in supported payment methods. With more than 50 payment approaches, the Payeer wallet offers users various services in one place.</p>



<p>You can read our 2022 <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/payeer-review/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Payeer review</a> to see how it stacks up against the competition in 2022.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Forex.com</strong></h2>



<p>Fortunately, this is one of the few platforms that is operational in the United States. In terms of user experience, Forex.com pretty much maintains the highest scores across the board. The minimum deposit is at $50 which allows for competitive spreads with an average of 1.3 pips on EUR/USD. However, users can enjoy better spreads with Direct Market Account (DMA) by paying more commission. Lastly, the maximum leverage on the platform is 1:50 across all accounts.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>FXTM</strong></h2>



<p>This platform is one of the most popular brokers in the world. With a minimum deposit of only $10 and no commission for basic accounts, it is very much hassle-free. But, hassle free does not mean basic in this case. They offer, micro, advantage and advantage plus accounts with spreads starting from 1.5 pips which is pretty good. As for the commission, the micro and advantage plus have no added commission. The Advantage account however will charge between $0.4 and $2 per side per lot. As for the best part, depending on the account and location, FXTM will offer a maximum of 1:2000 leverage.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Grand Capital</strong></h2>



<p>Based in Saint Vincent and the Grenadines Seychelles Grand Capital is a STP | ECN type broker. They offer a $10 minimum deposit while the average spread for EUR/USD is 17 pips on standard, the spreads for other instruments are variable. As for leverage, they offer up to 1:500 on Standard, Swap Free, and Micro accounts. However, the best part about Grand Capital is the competitive trading fees. For stocks, the platform charges 0.1% for all accounts while for crypto it is 0.5%.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>AZAForex</strong></h2>



<p>AZAforex is a legally registered forex broker located in Saint Vincent and the Grenadines, but not regulated by any government agency. It is a STP | ECN type broker that offers an impressive $1 minimum deposit. AZAforex is a broker that offers ultra-high leverage of up to 1:1,000, low spreads. But, the range of instruments can be a bit limiting for traders as compared to the competition. As of now, they only offer 6 crypto pairs. Another benefit for this platform is the simple registration and verification process.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Best Exchange Platform for Payeer</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p><a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-payeer-usd-to-paypal-no-kyc-or-sign-up/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Learn</a> how to exchange Payeer USD to PayPal [Video Guide]</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/forex-brokers-accepting-payeer/">Top Forex Brokers that Accept Payeer</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/forex-brokers-accepting-payeer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Payeer Review 2022: How Good is it?</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/payeer-review/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/payeer-review/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[e-currency to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer Review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer USD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5537</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Online digital wallets are multiplying in numbers like crazy! In a fierce competition between payment gateways, the consumers are the real winners. Right now, the transaction fees are the lowest they have ever been, not to mention the global availability of such services. And today, it is time for a Payeer review to find out [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/payeer-review/">Payeer Review 2022: How Good is it?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Online digital wallets are multiplying in numbers like crazy! In a fierce competition between payment gateways, the consumers are the real winners. Right now, the transaction fees are the lowest they have ever been, not to mention the global availability of such services. And today, it is time for a Payeer review to find out if the service is still on top of its competition. To begin with, before reading this year’s Payeer review, make sure you know all the basics about the digital wallet by reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-payeer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Payeer</a>”. Having done that, let’s take a look at the Estonian digital wallet.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color"><a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/buy-cryptocurrencies-with-payeer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Learn how</a> to buy cryptocurrencies with Payeer USD on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Payeer Review</strong></h2>



<p>First and foremost, Payeer is considered an online digital wallet for better asset management. Be it crypto of fiat, the payment processor is quick, reliable and cheap. In that regard, in a short lifespan of almost 8 years, Payeer is now recognized as one of the very best amongst competitors. Payeer utilizes built-in payment services with giant financial services such as Mastercard, VISA and PayPal.</p>



<p>As of 2022, the Payeer has over 7 million users which can transfer funds to each other for free. The strength however, lies in diversity. Payeer is far ahead of any similar platform in terms of scale of operation and diversity in supported payment methods. With more than 50 payment approaches, the Payeer wallet offers users various services in one place.</p>



<p>All transactions made on Payeer are irreversible. A feature that minimizes the possibility of malicious attacks or unwanted third party interference. Furthermore, they offer great customer support for users.</p>



<p>There is always room for improvement. And in this economy, if a company does not make constructive improvement, they could quickly look irrelevant. Already, Payeer services have been top-notch considering pretty much everything. But, for this Payeer review, we’re looking at how does Payeer stack up against the competition in 2022.</p>



<p>Basically, there is no perfect digital wallet and users will have to choose their service based on their needs. With that, we should first consider the pros and cons and then decide if it’s right for us.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Pros</strong></h2>



<ul class="wp-block-list"><li>Payeer is also an online cryptocurrency exchange. They used to offer limited number of cryptocurrencies but have noticeably expanded the list</li><li>Users can easily withdraw from Payeer account from ATM machines which is simply awesome!</li><li>The affiliate program is extensive and better than the competition.</li><li>Payeer is always up to date with the latest features</li><li>The transaction fees are very low and transactions are very quick.</li><li>The mobile app is intuitive and easy to use</li></ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Cons</strong></h2>



<ul class="wp-block-list"><li>Despite providing services in over 100 countries, Payeer is not active in the US.</li><li>Privacy and anonymity are not anywhere close to cryptocurrencies.</li><li>Having a limit on transactions can deter institutions.</li><li>The minimum amount for trading cryptocurrencies is a bit high</li></ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Conclusion</strong></h2>



<p>Essentially, the diversity policy was the big bread winner for Payeer. In this Payeer review, it is important to mention that Payeer hit a jackpot with cryptocurrencies. They were one of the first digital wallets to accept both fiat and crypto and that was a big success. Similarly, we see other competitors rushing to diversify their list of digital assets.</p>



<p>For 2022, it seems like Payeer has put a lot more emphasis on cryptocurrencies. The digital wallet services were already good, but now they want to expand their online crypto exchange. However, the regulations and KYC requirements are still a bummer. Users can potentially use Payeer services without verification but will face strong limitations. Yet, overall, Payeer is still right there with the best of online digital wallets and payment settlement services.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p><a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-payeer-usd-to-paypal-no-kyc-or-sign-up/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Learn</a> how to exchange Payeer USD to PayPal [Video Guide]</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/payeer-review/">Payeer Review 2022: How Good is it?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/payeer-review/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Buy Cryptocurrencies with Payeer USD on CoinCannon</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-cryptocurrencies-with-payeer/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-cryptocurrencies-with-payeer/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 07:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer USD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4804</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Digital payments are now a predominant method of transactions. Subsequently, there are numerous payment giants such as PayPal and Perfect Money who offer a variety of benefits. However, Payeer is now a great option for making transactions as it is a strong alternative for PayPal. You can buy cryptocurrencies with Payeer USD on CoinCannon without [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-cryptocurrencies-with-payeer/">Buy Cryptocurrencies with Payeer USD on CoinCannon</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Digital payments are now a predominant method of transactions. Subsequently, there are numerous payment giants such as PayPal and Perfect Money who offer a variety of benefits. However, Payeer is now a great option for making transactions as it is a strong alternative for PayPal. You can buy cryptocurrencies with Payeer USD on CoinCannon without paying high exchange fees. In this article, we will provide a brief introduction to Payeer and give you some good reasons to buy cryptocurrencies with Payeer USD for your next exchange.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><span style="background-color:rgba(0, 0, 0, 0)" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Head over to <a href="http://www.hi.excahnge/">jolixo</a> to buy cryptocurrencies anonymously.</span></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-payeer"><strong>What is Payeer?</strong></h2>



<p>First and foremost, Payeer is considered an online digital wallet for better asset management. Be it crypto of fiat, the payment processor is quick, reliable and cheap. In that regard, in a short lifespan of almost 8 years, Payeer is now recognized as one of the very best amongst competitors. Payeer utilizes built-in payment services with giant financial services such as Mastercard, VISA and PayPal.</p>



<p>As of 2021, the Payeer has approximately 7 million users which can transfer funds to each other with extremely low fees. The strength however, lies in diversity. Payeer is far ahead of any similar platform in terms of scale of operation and diversity in supported payment methods. With more than 50 payment approaches, the Payeer wallet offers users various services in one place.</p>



<p>To learn more about Payeer, continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-payeer/">What is Payeer</a>?”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-buy-cryptocurrencies-with-payeer-usd"><strong>Why Buy Cryptocurrencies with Payeer USD?</strong></h2>



<p>As a payment platform, Payeer hold many advantages over PayPal and competitors in general. To begin with, the primary reason to actually use a platform is the low exchange fees. After all, nobody like paying huge fees for their transactions. On the other hand, saving money is not everything we need in a platform.</p>



<p>What makes Payeer stand out is perhaps the diversity. The digital wallet offers an impressively diverse group of digital currencies including cryptocurrencies on demand. In that regard, you can easily exchange Payeer USD to other assets immediately with low fees.</p>



<p>On top of that, Payeer also provides payment services with large financial services such as PayPal, MasterCard and VISA so customers can easily make their payments without being limited to a single platform. One thing to note is that internal Payeer payments have extremely low transaction fees as compared to payments headed or from outside the network.</p>



<p>Considering both the diversity and accessibility, Payeer can be a good alternative to store your assets as compared with giants such as PayPal. Furthermore, it can also provide excellent payment solutions for institutions.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-buy-cryptocurrencies-with-payeer-usd-on-jolixo"><strong>Why Buy Cryptocurrencies with Payeer USD on CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p>Well, CoinCannon does offer very low exchange fees but so does the Payeer wallet. You might ask yourself why not directly buy cryptocurrencies in the Payeer platform?</p>



<p>The answer is short and simple, <strong>Anonymity!</strong></p>



<p>On CoinCannon, you do not have to share personal information with the website and that is a sure way to protect your privacy. Luckily, CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or a sign up process. That being said, there are benefits for the registered users but nonetheless it is not mandatory.</p>



<p>With that in mind, the exchange fees on the CoinCannon platform are also very competitive and low. In that sense, there will be no major difference in your transaction fees.</p>



<p>Last but not least, CoinCannon offers online 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>If you need help with transferring Payeer USD, continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-payeer-usd-to-other-currencies-easy-guide/">Exchange Payeer USD to Other Currencies [Easy Guide]</a>”</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-cryptocurrencies-with-payeer/">Buy Cryptocurrencies with Payeer USD on CoinCannon</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-cryptocurrencies-with-payeer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is Payeer?</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-payeer/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-payeer/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 09:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4072</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Payeer has been on a steady rise recently as a platform that doesn’t discriminate! In a world of ever growing demand for digital assets, those who offer services for both crypto and fiat are extremely convenient. Payeer is such platform that offers diverse financial services with competitive fees. These services include both cryptocurrencies and fiat [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-payeer/">What is Payeer?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Payeer has been on a steady rise recently as a platform that doesn’t discriminate!</p>



<p>In a world of ever growing demand for digital assets, those who offer services for both crypto and fiat are extremely convenient. Payeer is such platform that offers diverse financial services with competitive fees. These services include both cryptocurrencies and fiat currencies.</p>



<p>Here at <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a>, we offer exchange services for Payeer USD so that our users can anonymously exchange their assets.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Payeer the Estonian<strong> Warrior</strong></h2>



<p>First and foremost, Payeer is considered an online digital wallet for better asset management. Be it crypto of fiat, the payment processor is quick, reliable and cheap. In that regard, in a short lifespan of almost 8 years, Payeer is now recognized as one of the very best amongst competitors. Payeer utilizes built-in payment services with giant financial services such as Mastercard, VISA and PayPal.</p>



<p>As of 2021, the Payeer has approximately 7 million users which can transfer funds to each other with extremely low fees. The strength however, lies in diversity. Payeer is far ahead of any similar platform in terms of scale of operation and diversity in supported payment methods. With more than 50 payment approaches, the Payeer wallet offers users various services in one place.</p>



<p>All transactions made on Payeer are irreversible. A feature that minimizes the possibility of malicious attacks or unwanted third party interference. Furthermore, they offer 24/7 support for users.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Functions and Utility</strong></h2>



<p>On top of being a wallet, Payeer is also a registered cryptocurrency exchange. Users can buy, sell and trade the supported cryptocurrencies on Payeer without the need for a third-party. When they are finished making those stonks, they can simply withdraw and receive cash from an ATM machine.</p>



<p>They offer a 6-step affiliate program that is practical and has the potential to bring noticeable income for the user. It can reward the user with up to 25% of the charged fees by the platform to the affiliate user. Learn about our own <a href="https://hi.exchange/jolixo-affiliate">affiliate program</a>.</p>



<p>Utilizing the diversity in services, Payeer can offer financial solutions for both individuals and institutions. An advantage that is considered as the primary cause for the rapid growth.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Payeer Fees</strong></h2>



<p>To begin with, transferring funds into another Payeer account is free of charge. To transfer outside the platform however, the receiver pays a 0.95% transaction fee. For currency conversion, for example, USD to EUR, there is a 2% fee which is very competitive. In terms of bank transfer deposits, there will be between 0% to 3% fee and for withdrawals, the fee is between 3-5%. As for credit card payments, there is a designated 3% fee. password recovery service could cost you $50.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Payeer Shortcomings</strong></h2>



<p>We pointed out many of the advantages and benefits of the platform. However, there are some cons that the users might want to consider.</p>



<p>First of all, Payeer is regulated by VFSC and the MEAC which are responsible to oversee financial services in Estonia. In that case, the platform does not offer as much anonymity as cryptocurrency services. A solution for this flaw can be using <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> services.</p>



<p>The regulations and policies can potentially cause problems for financial operations on large scales. There are certain limits in transactions.</p>



<p>Perhaps the most common criticism of Payeer is the limited list of supported cryptocurrencies on the platform. This is an issue that the company has stated to be following closely. We can expect the list to expand in the future but as of now, the supported cryptocurrencies are limited.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Conclusion</strong></h2>



<p>As a diverse and affordable platform, Payeer has managed to prove utility and CoinCannon the gap between cryptocurrencies and fiat currencies. The platform offers a vast number of financial services and is also a crypto exchange. Considering the variety of services as well as the low fees, one could safely assume a bright future for the platform. In terms of cons, the supported cryptocurrencies on the platform will surely grow in number. For strict regulations and policies, there are third-party methods to overcome some of the challenges.</p>



<p>All in all, Payeer is a great digital financial platform that is trustable, affordable and highly practical.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><a href="http://hi.exchange">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.okchanger.com/exchangers/jolixo">OkChanger</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. We are on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/">Bestchange</a> and are always amongst the top exchanges.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-payeer/">What is Payeer?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-payeer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
