<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Bitcoin Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/bitcoin/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 09:03:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Could Surge to $112,000, Predicts CryptoQuant CEO</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/bitcoin-price-could-surge-to-112000-predicts-cryptoquant-ceo/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/bitcoin-price-could-surge-to-112000-predicts-cryptoquant-ceo/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Leyli Mamikhani]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 12:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=8209</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Key Points: In an insightful analysis shared by CryptoQuant CEO Ki Young Ju, Bitcoin is poised for a remarkable ascent to $112,000 in 2024, primarily fueled by the anticipated influx of funds from exchange-traded funds (ETFs). Highlighting the pivotal role of ETF cash inflows, Ju predicts a monthly surge of $9.5 billion, augmenting Bitcoin&#8217;s actual [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/bitcoin-price-could-surge-to-112000-predicts-cryptoquant-ceo/">Bitcoin Price Could Surge to $112,000, Predicts CryptoQuant CEO</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Key Points:</strong></h2>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>CEO of CryptoQuant, Ki Young Ju, forecasts Bitcoin&#8217;s price to soar up to $112,000 by the end of 2024, driven by anticipated inflows from Spot ETFs.</li>



<li>A potential monthly inflow of $9.5 billion from ETFs could augment Bitcoin&#8217;s actual value by $114 billion, potentially propelling the price to $112,000.</li>



<li>Ju presents an optimistic projection ranging from $104,000 to $112,000, with a more conservative estimate between $55,000 and $59,000.</li>
</ul>



<p class="has-black-color has-text-color has-link-color wp-elements-e6322d0116284c915cf7bc8d3aee3c30">In an insightful analysis shared by CryptoQuant CEO Ki Young Ju, Bitcoin is poised for a remarkable ascent to $112,000 in 2024, primarily fueled by the anticipated influx of funds from exchange-traded funds (ETFs). Highlighting the pivotal role of ETF cash inflows, Ju predicts a monthly surge of $9.5 billion, augmenting Bitcoin&#8217;s actual capitalization by a staggering $114 billion annually.</p>



<p>Ju&#8217;s forecast paints a bullish picture of Bitcoin&#8217;s trajectory, envisioning a potential surge to $112,000 by the year&#8217;s end. Despite speculation regarding possible exits from Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC), Ju remains optimistic about Bitcoin&#8217;s price rally, projecting a substantial increase of $76 billion in accurate capitalization. This could elevate Bitcoin&#8217;s current capitalization from $451 billion to between $527 billion and $565 billion.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image is-style-default">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="655" height="789" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/فاببتع-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-8212" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/فاببتع-1.png 655w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/فاببتع-1-249x300.png 249w" sizes="(max-width: 655px) 100vw, 655px" /></figure></div>


<p>Ju remains confident in Bitcoin&#8217;s resilience despite potential fluctuations, foreseeing a price range between $104,000 and $112,000 fueled by ETF inflows. Even in a more conservative scenario, Bitcoin could still maintain a strong position, trading between $55,000 and $59,000.</p>



<p>Amidst this anticipation, Bitcoin is already displaying signs of momentum, with its current weekly candle reflecting a gain of 12.58%. Trading above $48,000, Bitcoin&#8217;s volume in the last 24 hours has surged to $20.65 billion, hinting at growing investor interest and market activity.</p>



<p></p>



<p>Source: <a href="https://coinpedia.org/news/bitcoin-could-hit-112k-cryptoquant-ceo-drops-insider-info-on-etfs-history-making-trends/">coinpedia</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/bitcoin-price-could-surge-to-112000-predicts-cryptoquant-ceo/">Bitcoin Price Could Surge to $112,000, Predicts CryptoQuant CEO</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/bitcoin-price-could-surge-to-112000-predicts-cryptoquant-ceo/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Analysis of Bitcoin&#8217;s Continued Drop Amid ETF Approval Expectations</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/analysis-of-bitcoins-continued-drop-amid-etf-approval-expectations/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/analysis-of-bitcoins-continued-drop-amid-etf-approval-expectations/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Leyli Mamikhani]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 06:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=8056</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Despite the most recent changes regarding the Bitcoin ETF, the landscape of virtual currencies is once more in the midst of a profound shift. The most valuable cryptocurrency in the world of digital assets, Bitcoin, has recently declined, losing more than 2.4% of its value. This year has witnessed a stunning 156% acquisition in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/analysis-of-bitcoins-continued-drop-amid-etf-approval-expectations/">Analysis of Bitcoin&#8217;s Continued Drop Amid ETF Approval Expectations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Despite the most recent changes regarding the Bitcoin ETF, the landscape of virtual currencies is once more in the midst of a profound shift. The most valuable cryptocurrency in the world of digital assets, Bitcoin, has recently declined, losing more than 2.4% of its value.</p>



<p>This year has witnessed a stunning <strong>156% acquisition</strong> in the value of the most popular digital currency, Bitcoin. The primary cause for these changes is the conjecture that the launch of ETFs could generate a new wave of demand. Undoubtedly, not all of this can be considered entirely beneficial because there is a lot of speculation in the market on whether or not the approval of these ETFs would lead to profit-taking strategies. Such speculation can potentially negatively impact the shifts in the value of bitcoin.</p>



<p><strong>CryptoQuant</strong> described what happened as a possible<em> <strong>&#8220;sell the news&#8221;</strong></em> incident, referring to the wave that formed upon the news.</p>



<p>The term used above refers to a well-known phenomenon in the capital markets: the rising sentiment, leverage, and asset prices before a positive event, followed by a sharp decline in prices.</p>



<p>This is because smart traders take advantage of overloaded long deals, ensnaring leveraged traders and pressuring them to sell out or liquidate during drops.</p>



<p>The announcement that an ETF for Bitcoin is being approved can be seen as beneficial since it allows institutions to start investing in the cryptocurrency, increasing buying pressure.</p>



<p>The memo stated that &#8220;Bitcoin short holders are experiencing an unrealistic 30% profit margin, which has historically been before price corrections (areas marked with red circles).&#8221; Furthermore, short-term holders keep spending Bitcoin profitably, and returns typically materialize once short-term losses are realized.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Conclusion</h2>



<h1 class="wp-block-heading">ETF Approval: What to Expect from Bitcoin?</h1>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Bitcoin has recently declined, losing 2.4% of its value, and is currently trading at $42,400</li>



<li>2023 has witnessed a stunning 156% acquisition in Bitcoin&#8217;s value</li>



<li>The main cause of this decline can be the conjecture of the launch of ETFs and the newly generated wave of demand.</li>



<li>Bitcoin short holders are experiencing an unrealistic 30% profit margin.</li>



<li>CryptoQuant described what happened as a possible &#8220;sell the news&#8221; incident, referring to the wave that formed upon the news.</li>



<li>Lots of speculation in the market on whether or not the approval of these ETFs would lead to profit-taking strategies that can potentially negatively impact the shifts in the value of bitcoin.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/analysis-of-bitcoins-continued-drop-amid-etf-approval-expectations/">Analysis of Bitcoin&#8217;s Continued Drop Amid ETF Approval Expectations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/analysis-of-bitcoins-continued-drop-amid-etf-approval-expectations/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin [Instant]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin-2/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin-2/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 07:36:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AdvCash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6435</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking to exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin? CoinCannon offers everything you need! Digital currencies have been a quintessential asset for online payments. On top of that, cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin (BTC) are gaining momentum as popular payment methods. In that regard, users will find themselves in the need to exchange their assets into one another. And [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin-2/">How to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin [Instant]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking to exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin? CoinCannon offers everything you need! Digital currencies have been a quintessential asset for online payments. On top of that, cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin (BTC) are gaining momentum as popular payment methods. In that regard, users will find themselves in the need to exchange their assets into one another. And by doing so, the exchange fees can quickly put a dent in their pockets. Fortunately, you can easily exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin with the lowest fees, full anonymity and 24/7 online support. Want to know how?</p>



<p>Head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select AdvCash and Bitcoin in the exchange box and you’re good to go!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a verified and active Advanced Cash (AdvCash) account. Make sure that the transaction amount does not exceed your withdrawal limit. To receive Bitcoin (BTC), you will need a reliable and secure crypto wallet. Primarily, we suggest you use Trust Wallet. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon provides a hassle-free KYC process and no sign up to speed up your work flow. Despite that, there are benefits for those who sign up on CoinCannon. For example, you can take advantage of <a href="https://hi.exchange/jolixo-affiliate" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon affiliate</a> program and earn money online.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Advanced Cash (AdvCash)?</strong></h2>



<p>Before we go on to talk about how to convert AdvCash to Bitcoin, let’s take a quick look at what this digital currency is. AdvCash is a currency used for online payments. It is based in Belize which provides immunity from national laws of other countries for it. As an offshore currency, it is also encrypted much like cryptocurrencies and benefits from better anonymity and security. The Advance Cash company provides an account for users that allows for a variety of currencies to operate through it. In many ways, it is a lot like Payeer.</p>



<p>And much like Payeer, AdvCash supports transfers in both fiat and cryptocurrency form. With a virtual wallet, users can transfer funds and make payments with very low commission. What makes it interesting, is that Advance Cash is also compatible with other payment systems such as WebMoney or Perfect Money. With free international transfers, users get to enjoy a wide variety of currencies all in a virtual wallet. Furthermore, there are both physical and virtual bank cards available for quick and cheap international Visa/Mastercard payments.</p>



<p>The company was founded in 2014 as a competitor for PayPal and much like its peers, it has gained notable success in the past few years. As the need for virtual banking grows, online payment processing companies continue to narrow the gap with PayPal. Although, such companies are not as popular as PayPal, they offer a lot more freedom.</p>



<p>Keep in mind that you can also <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-advcash-to-payeer-usd/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange AdvCash to PayPal</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin?</strong></h2>



<p>Bitcoin is a digital currency that was developed following the housing market crash in January 2009. This cryptocurrency follows the ideas started out by the pseudonymous and mysterious Satoshi Nakamoto in a whitepaper. The identity of the individual or individuals that developed the software is still a mystery. Unlike government-issued currencies, Bitcoin is operated by a decentralized authority and offers the promise of lower transaction fees than traditional online payment mechanisms.</p>



<p>There are no physical Bitcoins and the coins you see are novelty coins that do not have any real value without the code inscribed on them. Bitcoin is only balances retained on a public ledger that everyone has transparent access to, and is verified by a massive amount of computing power along with all Bitcoin transactions. Bitcoins are not issued or supported as a commodity by any banks or governments, nor are individual bitcoins valuable. Although it is not legal tender, the popularity of Bitcoin charts is high, and hundreds of other virtual currencies collectively referred to as Altcoins have been launched following this cryptocurrency.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the homepage first, then select AdvCash USD and Bitcoin from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of BTC you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>



<li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your AdvCash and Payeer wallet details and email. The phone number is optional.</li>



<li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li>Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the AdvCash gateway and make the payment to our AdvCash account. Having transferred your AdvCash USD to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>



<li>By finishing all the steps above, our team will send the Bitcoin to your wallet as soon as possible</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>Just like that, you have now converted AdvCash to BTC. In general, WMZ payments are inconsistent in terms of how long they might take. Give it a few minutes and the AdvCash USD will be in your account ASAP. In the meantime, you can follow up on your order using the Track ID provided for you. Simply enter the track id in the required section on homepage to see at which point your order is. Remember not to share your Track ID with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin-2/">How to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin [Instant]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The US Banking Crisis: The Role of Crypto</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/us-banking-crisis/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/us-banking-crisis/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 08:47:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Money]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6429</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The role of cryptocurrency in the failures of banks Silvergate, Silicon Valley, and Signature has been highlighted in a recent report by the Congressional Research Service (CRS). The report examines the impact of crypto on the US banking crisis and reveals that the banks&#8217; exposure to crypto was minimal, but the perception of risk &#8220;may [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/us-banking-crisis/">The US Banking Crisis: The Role of Crypto</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The role of cryptocurrency in the failures of banks Silvergate, Silicon Valley, and Signature has been highlighted in a recent <a href="https://crsreports.congress.gov/product/pdf/IN/IN12148" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">report</a> by the Congressional Research Service (CRS). The report examines the impact of crypto on the US banking crisis and reveals that the banks&#8217; exposure to crypto was minimal, but the perception of risk &#8220;may have driven non-crypto firms/individuals to make significant withdrawals.&#8221; Interestingly, the statement sheds light on a critical issue regarding crypto assets. Despite all the bullish predictions, the failure of crypto-friendly banks outlines the severe lack of trust in crypto still dominant among retail investors.</p>



<p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Limited Exposure to Crypto</strong></h2>



<p>According to analyst Paul Tierno from CRS, the banks&#8217; exposure to crypto &#8220;was somewhat limited.&#8221; Tierno noted that &#8220;volatility in crypto markets may expose banks to liquidity risks that could ultimately lead to fatal losses.&#8221; However, it was the dwindling deposits from crypto firms that led banks to sell securities at a loss, exacerbating liquidity issues and solvency.</p>



<p>In November 2021, the crypto market reached an all-time high of around $3 trillion. However, by December 2022, the market lost more than two-thirds of its market capitalization. The report highlighted that the fall in digital asset prices led to centralized crypto platforms and stablecoin issuers experiencing redemptions, causing them to draw down deposits held at these banks.</p>



<p>To meet the withdrawal demand, banks sold securities for losses, affecting their liquidity and, in some cases, solvency. For instance, Silvergate&#8217;s deposits fell by over half, while Signature&#8217;s deposits dropped by 15% in Q4 2022. The CRS report emphasized that the losses were not realized on crypto-related assets but were caused by crypto deposit withdrawals.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="703" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/US-Banking-Crisis.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-6431" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/US-Banking-Crisis.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/US-Banking-Crisis-300x206.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/US-Banking-Crisis-768x527.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-crypto-s-impact-on-us-banking-crisis"><strong>Crypto’s Impact on US Banking Crisis</strong></h2>



<p>The CRS report reminds us that the crypto market chaos affected US bank stocks. SVB, Silvergate, and Signature were pushed over the edge by fear, uncertainty, and doubt. The report concluded that &#8220;banks must be prepared for the potential of rapid withdrawal of deposits. This can exacerbate liquidity issues and, ultimately, threaten solvency.&#8221;</p>



<p>In conclusion, the CRS report serves as a reminder that the crypto market&#8217;s volatility can impact US banks. Although the banks&#8217; exposure to crypto was limited, the perception of risk was enough to drive non-crypto firms/individuals to make significant withdrawals, leading to the banks selling securities at a loss. This affected their liquidity and, in some cases, their solvency. </p>



<p>However, it’s also important to analyze the fear and the lack of trust in crypto. Perhaps, the volatility is the key factor here. Yet, the <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ftx-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">FTX collapse</a>, may have been a big wake up call for investors. Portraying how easy it is to run a multi-billion dollar scam, Sam Bankman-Fried may have permanently stained the face of crypto. considering this congressional report, we can see how limited exposure to crypto can have negative effects on their business. With all that in mind, we can see how banks may be hesitant to integrate crypto asset into their systems.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/us-banking-crisis/">The US Banking Crisis: The Role of Crypto</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/us-banking-crisis/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cryptocurrency Regulations: The SEC is Divided!</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrency-regulations/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrency-regulations/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 11:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6409</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency regulations have been a hot topic in recent years, with governments and regulatory agencies around the world grappling with how to approach this rapidly evolving industry. In the United States, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) plays a key role in regulating the cryptocurrency market. For the most part, the SEC has been showing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrency-regulations/">Cryptocurrency Regulations: The SEC is Divided!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Cryptocurrency regulations have been a hot topic in recent years, with governments and regulatory agencies around the world grappling with how to approach this rapidly evolving industry. In the United States, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) plays a key role in regulating the cryptocurrency market. For the most part, the SEC has been showing an anti-crypto attitude. However, Commissioner Hester Peirce, a well-known advocate for innovation in the crypto space, has recently <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/statement/peirce-rendering-inovation-2023-04-12" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">voiced her dissent</a> against Chair Gary Gensler&#8217;s anti-crypto agenda. Of course, we can be sure about an upcoming shock wave of regulatory action coming for crypto. However, recent debates show how there is internal conflict within the SEC regarding crypto assets.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Commissioner Pierce on Cryptocurrency Regulations</strong></h2>



<p>In a recent speech, Commissioner Peirce criticized the SEC&#8217;s proposal to adjust the definition of &#8220;exchange&#8221; to include decentralized finance (DeFi) protocols. According to Peirce, this change would be counterproductive, promoting stagnation and centralization rather than embracing the potential of new technology.</p>



<p>&#8220;Stagnation, centralization, expatriation, and extinction are the watchwords of this release. Rather than embracing the promise of new technology as we have done in the past, here we propose to embrace stagnation, force centralization, urge expatriation, and welcome extinction of new technology. Accordingly, I dissent,&#8221; said Peirce.</p>



<p>Commissioner Peirce further highlighted that the SEC&#8217;s proposal could potentially violate the First Amendment protections by categorizing blockchain ecosystems as a &#8220;group,&#8221; creating ambiguity around their speech rights.</p>



<p>&#8220;The release&#8217;s ambiguity undermines fundamental First Amendment protections. Because the release makes everybody involved in the relevant blockchain ecosystem part of a &#8216;group,&#8217; it creates significant ambiguity around what speech requires government pre-approval, which will unavoidably chill constitutionally-protected speech,&#8221; Peirce explained.</p>



<p>Peirce also emphasized the importance of the SEC remaining open to the idea of tweaking its rules to accommodate new technologies, something she believes the Commission understood in the 1990s.</p>



<p>&#8220;The Commission of the 1990s understood this basic principle and created space for significant innovations in securities trading. This release, on the other hand, takes the view that any business model that cannot meet the specific requirements of our existing regulatory model does not belong in our markets,&#8221; Peirce stated.</p>



<p>In essence, Peirce argues that the SEC&#8217;s current approach to cryptocurrency regulations is hindering innovation and preventing cutting-edge businesses from entering the market. She believes that a Commission serious about regulating, rather than destroying, the cryptocurrency market should reflect on its past regulatory failures and be open to adapting its rules to accommodate the unique characteristics of cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-sec-s-iron-fist"><strong>The SEC’s Iron Fist</strong></h2>



<p>Peirce&#8217;s dissenting voice within the SEC sheds light on the internal conflict within the regulatory agency regarding how to approach cryptocurrency regulations. Chair Gary Gensler has taken a more stringent stance on cryptocurrencies, expressing concerns about investor protection and market integrity. On the other hand, Commissioner Peirce has been a vocal advocate for embracing innovation and allowing the cryptocurrency market to flourish.</p>



<p>The debate over cryptocurrency regulations is not limited to the SEC. Governments and regulatory agencies worldwide are grappling with how to effectively regulate the rapidly growing cryptocurrency market. Some countries have taken a more progressive approach, recognizing the potential of cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology, while others have adopted a more cautious stance, expressing concerns about risks such as money laundering and fraud.</p>



<p>In the United States, the lack of clear and consistent cryptocurrency regulations has created uncertainty for businesses and investors operating in the crypto space. Many argue that a well-regulated cryptocurrency market could provide significant benefits, such as increased investor protection, market transparency, and economic growth. However, excessive regulation could stifle innovation and hinder the development of the cryptocurrency market.</p>



<p>The SEC, as a key regulatory agency in the U.S., plays a crucial role in shaping cryptocurrency regulations. Commissioner Peirce&#8217;s dissenting voice highlights the need for a balanced and pragmatic approach to regulating cryptocurrencies. While it is important to address risks and protect investors, paralyzing a whole industry does not sound like a democratic approach either.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrency-regulations/">Cryptocurrency Regulations: The SEC is Divided!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrency-regulations/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The US Dollar Collapse is a Political Hoax!</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/us-dollar-collapse/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/us-dollar-collapse/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 08:58:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[CoinCannon Special]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[China]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Money]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US DOLLAR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Yuan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6400</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Here’s our keyword for the day: US dollar collapse! This bold statement seems to be flying around the media like an imminent threat. It’s currently “the” topic of conversation in every podcast, every tweet and every Substack article censored by Elon. On the opposite side, China and Russia and their allies are embracing this US [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/us-dollar-collapse/">The US Dollar Collapse is a Political Hoax!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Here’s our keyword for the day: US dollar collapse! This bold statement seems to be flying around the media like an imminent threat. It’s currently “the” topic of conversation in every podcast, every tweet and every Substack article <a href="https://reason.com/2023/04/10/elon-musk-matt-taibbi-twitter-substack/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">censored by Elon</a>. On the opposite side, China and Russia and their allies are embracing this US dollar collapse conversation with wide open arms. Now, while the BRICS countries are supposedly developing their own currency, this unborn currency has a long road ahead. In this article, we will go over some of the big reasons why the US dollar will not bow down to Chinese Yuan or even Bitcoin. At least not as easy as the media says!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>World Superpower by 2032 (Probably)</strong></h2>



<p>Ironically, you can find thousands of podcast clips on YouTube where you see <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XzhRWfim8ZE" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">former CIA spies</a> explain how and why China will be the top superpower by a decade or something. Of course, they’re very careful with their words and use a lot of “if” and “possibly” and “probably” in their discourse. Of course, we are assuming that this former CIA agent used to be a geopolitical expert in CIA and not just a field agent (sarcasm). Regardless, everyone is talking about how the US economy is about to collapse. Subsequently, the ruthless wave of suggested posts and videos about this topic made me angry last week. So here we are, swimming against the current mostly because it tickles my ego to be the opposing side in every conversation.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Bitcoin Will Kill Fiat (Probably Not) </h3>



<p>On top of that, it’s also critical to talk about cryptocurrencies and whether they will be replacing the US dollar. This one has been a long time coming! Thousands of crypto bros talking about the upcoming US dollar collapse and how Bitcoin will be the next world reserve currency. Once again, all the video suggestions on YouTube where you have a random guy telling me that Bitcoin will be $1,000,000 by 2024 annoyed me beyond belief.  </p>



<p>Ironically, the <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tales-from-the-chain-chapter-v-bitcoin-maximalist/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bitcoin maximalist</a> community isn’t concerned at all with their terminology. They are certain about their predictions and value their vision just like the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Manson_Family" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Manson family</a> did! Of course, this article will address Bitcoin and its future implications in detail. But before we do that, let’s just say that altcoins will always be alternative coins to Bitcoin and that’s just what they are forever! So no! I am not interested in your upcoming altcoin airdrop!</p>



<p>At this point, it is worth mentioning that the sole purpose of this article is to address the US dollar collapse topic which does not include a defense for US foreign or domestic policies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The US Dollar Collapse (Unlikely)</strong></h2>



<p>To address this topic, there are countless factors to consider and thousands of unexpected event that can (possibly) happen. However, there are five primary points to consider before making the final judgement.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>China’s Bond Market </strong></h3>



<p>When it comes to China, although the Chinese economy has grown significantly in recent years, its bond market is still relatively smaller and less developed compared to established reserve currencies like the US dollar, euro, and Japanese yen. According to data from the Bank for International Settlements (BIS), as of 2021, the Chinese yuan (CNY) accounted for only around 2% of global foreign exchange reserves, while the US dollar (USD) remained the dominant reserve currency with a share of around 59%. <strong>The Chinese bond market also lacks liquidity and transparency</strong> compared to more mature markets, which can affect its attractiveness as a reserve currency.</p>



<p>Additionally, various factors such as government intervention, capital controls, and regulatory restrictions in China&#8217;s financial markets may also impact the development and internationalization of its bond market, which in turn can affect its potential as a reserve currency. Ultimately, the Chinese bond market does not bring about a lot of investor confidence.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Capital Controls in China</strong></h3>



<p>Capital controls refer to restrictions imposed by a government on the movement of funds in and out of a country. In the case of a currency aspiring to be a reserve currency, it is important to have minimal or no capital controls to facilitate free movement of capital across borders. Capital controls can limit the liquidity and flexibility of a currency in international transactions, which can impact its attractiveness as a reserve currency.</p>



<p>China has been known for implementing capital controls to manage its economy and financial system. These controls can include limits on the amount of capital that can be transferred out of the country, requirements for approval or documentation for cross-border transactions, and other measures to restrict capital flows. Such capital controls can hinder the free movement of funds and limit the liquidity of the Chinese yuan (CNY) in international markets, potentially affecting its suitability as a reserve currency.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The U.S. dollar (USD) Trade and Investment </strong></h3>



<p>Many countries and international companies hold substantial amounts of USD-denominated debts, including government bonds, corporate bonds, and loans. These debts are typically denominated in USD due to the historical dominance of the USD in global financial markets, and the stability and liquidity of the U.S. bond market.</p>



<p>According to data from the Bank for International Settlements (BIS), as of 2021, the USD continues to dominate global foreign exchange markets, accounting for around 88% of daily forex trading volume. Additionally, the BIS also reports that the USD remains the most widely used currency for international debt securities, with a significant portion of global debt issued in USD.</p>



<p>As a result, countries and international companies that have accumulated trillions of dollars in USD-denominated debts will likely need USD for the foreseeable future to service and repay these debts. This ongoing demand for USD to settle international debts is one of the factors that support the continued use and demand for the USD in global financial markets.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>BRICS is </strong>Not Robust<strong>! </strong></h3>



<p>Trust is a crucial factor in the international monetary system, particularly for a currency to become a reserve currency. A reserve currency is a currency that is held by central banks and other international institutions as part of their foreign exchange reserves and is widely used in global trade and finance.</p>



<p>The BRICS (Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa) are a group of emerging economies that pose as potential challengers to the dominance of traditional reserve currencies like the U.S. dollar. However, despite their economic potential, the BRICS countries face challenges in establishing mutual trust among themselves. These challenges may include geopolitical tensions, economic disparities, and differences in monetary policies and regulations, which could affect their ability to fully trust and rely on each other&#8217;s currencies.</p>



<p>While the BRICS countries have made efforts to promote intra-BRICS trade and investment, the use of their currencies in international trade and finance remains relatively limited compared to traditional reserve currencies. According to data from the International Monetary Fund (IMF), as of 2021, the share of BRICS currencies in global foreign exchange reserves remains relatively small, with the U.S. dollar and the euro continuing to dominate as reserve currencies.</p>



<p>On the other hand, Russia, that is a critical member of the BRICS is currently facing serious challenges in Ukraine. Consequently, this has deeply affected Russia in terms of economy. As they are growing desperate, countries like China are taking advantage of the sanctions imposed on Russia. For instance, <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/chinas-march-imports-russian-oil-may-hit-record-shiptracking-data-2023-03-02/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">China’s import of Russian crude oil</a> is now hitting historical levels. Simultaneously, reports indicated that Russia is selling their oil. Petrol and natural gas at huge discounts to China solely out of desperation for money. Now, you can’t necessarily consider China a proper ally if you were Putin would you?</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>US Dollar Collapse Will Damage Chinese Economy </strong></h3>



<p>China is in fact the biggest customer for the US dollar. As the world&#8217;s second-largest economy, China has a significant presence in global trade and is a major exporter. It is true that a significant portion of China&#8217;s exports is denominated in U.S. dollars. According to data from the U.S. Census Bureau, in 2020, China&#8217;s total exports to the United States amounted to over $450 billion, making the U.S. one of China&#8217;s largest export markets.</p>



<p>In order to facilitate international trade, many countries, including China, conduct their trade transactions in U.S. dollars. This is because the U.S. dollar is a dominant global medium of exchange and serves as the dominant currency for international trade and finance. The use of the U.S. dollar in global trade allows countries to access international markets, facilitate cross-border transactions, and conduct business with other countries.</p>



<p>However, it&#8217;s worth noting that while the U.S. dollar plays a significant role in China&#8217;s export-driven economy, China has also been taking steps to diversify its trade and reduce its reliance on the U.S. dollar. China has been actively promoting the use of its own currency, the Chinese yuan (CNY), in international trade and investment, and has established currency swap agreements with various countries to promote direct bilateral trade in their respective currencies. Additionally, China has been working to develop alternative payment systems and financial infrastructure to reduce its dependence on the U.S. dollar in international trade and finance.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Will Bitcoin Trigger the US Dollar Collapse?</strong></h2>



<p>Cryptocurrencies, including the most well-known one, Bitcoin, have gained attention as a digital form of currency that operates outside the traditional financial system and is not tied to any particular country&#8217;s currency, including the U.S. dollar. While cryptocurrencies have gained popularity and acceptance in some circles, they currently do not pose a significant threat as a direct replacement for the U.S. dollar or any other global reserve currency for several reasons.</p>



<p>First, cryptocurrencies are relatively new and still face significant challenges in terms of regulatory and legal frameworks, scalability, stability, and acceptance by mainstream financial institutions and governments.</p>



<p>Second, cryptocurrencies are volatile and price fluctuations, which can impact their suitability as a stable medium of exchange and store of value. The lack of stability and the speculative nature of cryptocurrencies pose risks for businesses and governments in terms of pricing, risk management, and financial stability.</p>



<p>Third, while cryptocurrencies offer certain advantages such as faster and cheaper cross-border transactions, they also come with risks, including potential for money laundering, fraud, and lack of consumer protection.</p>



<p>Ultimately, while cryptocurrencies have gained attention and acceptance in some circles, they currently do not pose a significant threat as a direct replacement for the U.S. dollar or any other global reserve currency. The challenges of regulatory frameworks, volatility, stability, acceptance, and risks associated with cryptocurrencies limit their potential to replace traditional currencies in global trade and finance.</p>



<p>On the other hand, if cryptocurrencies were to replace the US dollar, the whales and industry CEOs will have an unprecedented influence on the world’s economy and it’s really terrifying to say the least!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-will-the-us-dollar-collapse"><strong>Will the US Dollar Collapse?</strong></h2>



<p>According to Murphy’s law, anything that can go wrong will go wrong. Personally speaking, I saw the murphy’s law manifest to reality last month since anything that could go wrong with a motorcycle went wrong with my motorcycle and it was in the shop for two weeks and it was really annoying and that’s probably why I got mad consuming all the content about the US dollar collapse content! The point is, unless something radical occurs, no Yuan or Bitcoin can replace the US dollar anytime soon.</p>



<p>Can we all agree that the United States is politically divided? If so, then we can clearly see how both sides of the political spectrum could use a strong dose of fear mongering to promote their own campaign. While it’s impossible to call the trending of “US dollar collapse” an orchestrated political hoax, most of the content out there seems to be following an unsubstantiated discourse. &nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/us-dollar-collapse/">The US Dollar Collapse is a Political Hoax!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/us-dollar-collapse/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Bitcoin with Dai [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 10:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6379</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you are looking to buy Bitcoin with Dai, CoinCannon is the ultimate platform for the job. Bitcoin has finally managed to bounce back and move above the critical resistance level at $25k. Subsequently, investors are once again eager to invest in the top crypto asset by market cap. On top of that, the mass [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Buy Bitcoin with Dai [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you are looking to buy Bitcoin with Dai, CoinCannon is the ultimate platform for the job. Bitcoin has finally managed to bounce back and move above the critical resistance level at $25k. Subsequently, investors are once again eager to invest in the top crypto asset by market cap. On top of that, the mass adoption of BTC has turned it into a utilitarian digital asset. Today, thousands of credible online stores accept Bitcoin as payment. Fortunately, you can now pay for goods and services via BTC and there’s lots of stuff you can <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-with-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">buy with Bitcoin</a>. However, if you’re holding DAI, you can instantly exchange Dai into Bitcoin in only a matter of minutes. Want to get started? Head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Dai on the left box and Bitcoin on the right and you’re good to go!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/">How to exchange cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Bitcoin with Dai?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive Bitcoin (BTC). In case your Dai wallet supports BTC, you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is DAI?</strong></h2>



<p>Before we go over how to buy Bitcoin with Dai, let’s take a brief look at Dai as a stablecoin.</p>



<p>DAI is an Ethereum-based stablecoin. A stablecoin is a cryptocurrency with a pegged value to another currency. In case of DAI, it is pegged to the US dollar and much like Tether and USDC, Dai will always be worth $1. Stablecoins are a crucial part of the crypto market as they offer very little volatility. In that regard, investors use stablecoins to save their funds in the form of a reliable and stable asset.</p>



<p>What makes DAI unique is a clever design that eliminates the biggest concerns for stablecoins. Generally speaking, conventional stablecoins require a massive reserve by the company. For example, for every Tether USD, the Tether company must hold $1 USD in their reserve. This is a huge issue for companies as it is difficult to provide liquidity and keep it consistent.</p>



<p>DAI offers a new solution for this problem. By using an automated system of smart contracts on Ethereum blockchain, DAI does now need a reserve. Using collateralized debt denominated in ETH allows DAI to maintain the 1:1 ration with USD. Simply speaking, users can deposit Ethereum or other cryptocurrencies can borrow against the value of their deposit and generate new DAI. The currency is this case is known as collateral.</p>



<p>You can <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange Dai to PayPal</a> on CoinCannon with the lowest exchange fees ever!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Invest in Bitcoin?</strong></h2>



<p>Well, there is hardly anyone these days who is not familiar with the definition of Bitcoin and what the cryptocurrency is capable of carrying out. However, let’s briefly go through what bitcoin is and where it comes from, then we can focus on the benefits of using this cryptocurrency and explain why to buy Bitcoin with Perfect Money.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a Cryptocurrency that was created after the housing market collapse in January 2009. It follows the ideas set out by the enigmatic and pseudonymous Satoshi Nakamoto in a whitepaper. The identity of the individual or individuals who developed this cryptocurrency is still under wraps. Unlike government-issued currencies, Bitcoin provides the guarantee of lower transaction costs than conventional online payment systems and is regulated by a decentralized authority.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a tempting opportunity for investment and great tool for doing financial transactions. In that regard, it has been a solid choice for investment as an asset that is truly decentralized. On top of that, there are countless online platform that accept Bitcoin as payment which makes BTC a utilitarian option for online payments.</p>



<p>So, if You’ve decided to invest in BTC, you can buy Bitcoin with Dai in only a matter of minutes on CoinCannon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-buy-bitcoin-with-dai"><strong>How to Buy Bitcoin with DAI?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Dai (DAI) on the left field and Bitcoin (BTC) on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your BTC wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your DAI to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>You’re All Set!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Bitcoin (BTC) to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Buy Bitcoin with Dai [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aiden Pleterski; Canada’s “Crypto King” Kidnapped</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/aiden-pleterski/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/aiden-pleterski/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 09:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Canada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6376</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What goes up, must come down, and in case of Aiden Pleterski, he came down hard. In fact, his fell from grace is something you can see in a crime thriller. And a lot like a crime thriller, his story is as typical as it gets. A young man who became a millionaire overnight, then [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/aiden-pleterski/">&lt;strong&gt;Aiden Pleterski; Canada’s “Crypto King” Kidnapped&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>What goes up, must come down, and in case of Aiden Pleterski, he came down hard. In fact, his fell from grace is something you can see in a crime thriller. And a lot like a crime thriller, his story is as typical as it gets. A young man who became a millionaire overnight, then took a lot of money from a lot of people and scammed them. That would be the first chapter, but then he loses the money as the movie goes on. </p>



<p>And here comes the climax, the self-proclaimed &#8220;Crypto King&#8221; Aiden Pleterski was kidnapped, tortured, and held for ransom after allegedly exploiting investors out of millions. Funny enough, Aiden owned a neon green Lamborghini Urus which is officially the stereotypical vehicle of choice for all social media scammers. Not that we’re pointing fingers but Aiden’s case does not look good for all Lamborghini Urus owners.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Aiden Pleterski; A Classic Tale</strong></h2>



<p>Last August, Pleterski declared bankruptcy after being accused of running a fraudulent investment scheme. The 23-year-old allegedly convinced investors that he would pool their funds and invest them in cryptocurrency and foreign exchange positions. However, since bankruptcy proceedings began, $25 million Canadian worth of claims have been filed against him. This is according to the official <a href="https://docs.grantthornton.ca/document-folder/viewer/docul8LWsxcWho7J/155791662019177193?_gl=1*cbjbqk*_ga*MTczODA4NTY0NS4xNjc5ODY3MjA2*_ga_JLRBBJ6PTP*MTY3OTg2NzIwNi4xLjAuMTY3OTg2NzIwOS41Ny4wLjA.&amp;_ga=2.75019794.1613509646.1679867206-1738085645.1679867206" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">court documents</a> file against him.</p>



<p>Pleterski&#8217;s alleged deceitful behavior was revealed as it was discovered that he only invested less than 2% of the total amount he received, which amounted to $670,000. This is in stark contrast to what he promised investors, leaving many with significant financial losses. The alleged investment scheme has brought into question the regulation and security of the cryptocurrency market, which has become increasingly popular in recent years, as investors look to capitalize on its high returns.</p>



<p>In the meantime, Aiden Pleterski did what every 23-year-old dreams to do one day. Allegedly, Aiden spent around 16 million on his “personal lifestyle” which is all part of the plan. After all, he had to convince investors on social media by flexing hard. His extravagant lifestyle included renting private jets and going on awesome vacations. But, the hallmark of all crypto millionaires is perhaps their car collection. Other than the mandatory neon green Lamborghini Urus, his exotic vehicle collection consisted of “​​a Ferrari, four Audis, three Lamborghinis, three McLarens, a Land Rover, and a BMW.” Now, Maybe the author is jealous, but honestly why three McLarens? McLarens tend to lose value very quickly overtime due to their poor reliability.</p>



<p>All that said, using cheat codes in real life can have devastating consequences.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-kidnapped-tortured-and-held-for-ransom"><strong>Kidnapped, Tortured and Held for Ransom</strong></h2>



<p>In a shocking turn of events, Pleterski&#8217;s troubles seemed to have escalated beyond his financial mismanagement. Pleterski&#8217;s father testified that his son had been kidnapped, held captive for three days, tortured, and beaten by unknown assailants in December 2021. He was only released on the condition that he quickly find money to pay his kidnappers and refrain from contacting law enforcement.</p>



<p>Pleterski reportedly reached out to his landlord, Sandeep Gupta, while in captivity, asking for $3 million to pay his kidnappers. According to Pleterski&#8217;s father, his son was eventually released with the threat that he needed to come up with some money fast and not involve law enforcement.</p>



<p>The kidnapping has further complicated the ongoing bankruptcy proceedings against Pleterski. The case has already seen $25 million Canadian worth of claims filed against Pleterski. Now, with the added layer of criminality, the situation has become even more complex. It remains to be seen what impact the kidnapping will have on the bankruptcy case and how it will affect the investors who have lost their money due to Pleterski&#8217;s alleged fraudulent investment scheme.</p>



<p>Perhaps, the downturn in his situation began with the <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ftx-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">FTX Collapse</a> back in November 2021. As the crypto market started to deteriorate, Aiden claimed that he has lost all his crypto investments. Obviously, the self-proclaimed crypto king of Canada assured his investors that he was taking aggressive measures to give people back their money.</p>



<p>“I essentially tried to redeem myself [&#8230;] but obviously in doing so, I guess you could say greed took over,” he testified. “I was trying to make returns that obviously weren&#8217;t feasible or weren&#8217;t necessarily possible at the time, and it just caused more losses.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">How to Prevent Future Aiden Pleterski!</h2>



<p>Now that he’s sorry, his regret is not helping anyone get their money back. Unfortunately, one of the biggest stains in the face of crypto is fraudulent social media personalities. Young people with flashy lifestyles, green Lamborghini Urus selling a false promise of success is a big problem for the longevity of cryptocurrencies. Now, while governments are obsessively imposing <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-regulations-sec-cftc/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">crypto regulations</a>, nobody is doing anything about false social media marketing. It’s always sad to see hopeful investors with less technical knowledge losing their life savings. And in case of crypto, nine times out of ten the money will go missing in the oblivion and never recovered. We’ve seen similar cases on a larger scale with FTX and Terra.</p>



<p>On one hand, crypto personalities emphasis on the need for the lack of regulatory supervision on the market. However, People like Aiden Pleterski prove that unregulated markets need more regulation.</p>



<p>But, here is the best financial advice you will ever get. Don’t trust people who own a green Lamborghini Urus!</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/aiden-pleterski/">&lt;strong&gt;Aiden Pleterski; Canada’s “Crypto King” Kidnapped&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/aiden-pleterski/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 06:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AdvCash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6369</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking to exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin? CoinCannon is the ultimate platform for the job. These days, online platform accept a confusing variety of digital assets including cryptocurrencies. With that, comes to need to exchange these assets into one another on a regular basis. Yet, it could be difficult to find an exchange platform that offers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking to exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin? <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is the ultimate platform for the job. These days, online platform accept a confusing variety of digital assets including cryptocurrencies. With that, comes to need to exchange these assets into one another on a regular basis. Yet, it could be difficult to find an exchange platform that offers great exchange rates and anonymity at the same time. Fortunately, CoinCannon offers the most competitive exchange fees all while providing a hassle-free KYC process for the customers. Today, we will go over how to exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin with no hidden fees, no KYC and 24/7 online support.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange AdvCash to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange direction, you will need a verified AdvCash account. Make sure that the transaction amount does not exceed your withdrawal limit. Furthermore, you will need a reliable crypto wallet to hold Bitcoin. There are multiple options out there, but we do suggest Trust Wallet as a suitable wallet.  As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email address and there is no KYC (know your customer) required. However, there are numerous benefits for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. Want a good reason why? You can win $100 gifts on CoinCannon every single month!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is AdvCash?</strong></h2>



<p>AdvCash is a currency used for online payments. It is based in Belize which provides immunity from national laws of other countries for it. As an offshore currency, it is also encrypted much like cryptocurrencies and benefits from better anonymity and security. The Advance Cash company provides an account for users that allows for a variety of currencies to operate through it. In many ways, it is a lot like Payeer.</p>



<p>And much like Payeer, AdvCash supports transfers in both fiat and cryptocurrency form. With a virtual wallet, users can transfer funds and make payments with very low commission. What makes it interesting, is that Advance Cash is also compatible with other payment systems such as WebMoney or Perfect Money. With free international transfers, users get to enjoy a wide variety of currencies all in a virtual wallet. Furthermore, there are both physical and virtual bank cards available for quick and cheap international Visa/Mastercard payments.</p>



<p>The company was founded in 2014 as a competitor for PayPal and much like its peers, it has gained notable success in the past few years. As the need for virtual banking grows, online payment processing companies continue to narrow the gap with PayPal. Although, such companies are not as popular as PayPal, they offer a lot more freedom.</p>



<p>Continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-advcash/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is AdvCash</a>” to learn everything about Advanced Cash.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Is Bitcoin a Good Investment?</strong></h2>



<p>Well, there is hardly anyone these days who is not familiar with the definition of Bitcoin and what the cryptocurrency is capable of carrying out. However, let’s briefly go through what bitcoin is and where it comes from, then we can focus on the benefits of using this cryptocurrency and explain why to buy Bitcoin with Perfect Money.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a Cryptocurrency that was created after the housing market collapse in January 2009. It follows the ideas set out by the enigmatic and pseudonymous Satoshi Nakamoto in a whitepaper. The identity of the individual or individuals who developed this cryptocurrency is still under wraps. Unlike government-issued currencies, Bitcoin provides the guarantee of lower transaction costs than conventional online payment systems and is regulated by a decentralized authority.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a tempting opportunity for investment and great tool for doing financial transactions. In that regard, it has been a solid choice for investment as an asset that is truly decentralized. On top of that, there are countless online platform that accept Bitcoin as payment which makes BTC a utilitarian option for online payments.</p>



<p>So, if You&#8217;ve decided to invest in BTC, you can exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin in only a matter of minutes on CoinCannon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon to the Moon!</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon homepage</a> first, then select AdvCash USD and Bitcoin from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of BTC you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>



<li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your AdvCash and BTC wallet details and email. The phone number is optional.</li>



<li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li>Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the AdvCash gateway and make the payment to our AdvCash account. Having transferred your AdvCash USD to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>



<li>By finishing all the steps above, our team will send the Bitcoin to your wallet as soon as possible.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-you-re-all-set"><strong>You’re All Set!</strong></h2>



<p>Just like that, you have now exchanged AdvCash to Binance Coin. Give it a few minutes and the BNB will be in your account ASAP. In the meantime, you can follow up on your order using the Track ID provided for you. Simply enter the track id in the required section on homepage to see at which point your order is. Remember not to share your Track ID with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Silvergate Bank Gets Knifed in the Back</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/silvergate-bank/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/silvergate-bank/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 08:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Silvergate Bank]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6349</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Silvergate bank, the innovative and awesome crypto-friendly haven, is now facing a great betrayal. Following a massive plummet of 60% in stocks, crypto firms are abandoning their old friend for cautionary reasons. A term which could also translate into cautionary fear of the SEC coming for you with a flurry of lawsuits. Now, considering the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/silvergate-bank/">&lt;strong&gt;Silvergate Bank Gets Knifed in the Back&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Silvergate bank, the innovative and awesome crypto-friendly haven, is now facing a great betrayal. Following a massive <a href="https://www.google.com/finance/quote/SI:NYSE?window=5D" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">plummet</a> of 60% in stocks, crypto firms are abandoning their old friend for cautionary reasons. A term which could also translate into cautionary fear of the SEC coming for you with a flurry of lawsuits. Now, considering the high profile crypto companies moving away from the wounded bank, we can clearly see regulators raising the stakes for such companies to take risks like they used to. </p>



<p>In the meantime, the <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ripple-lawsuit-continues-as-sec-tries-to-cheat/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Ripple lawsuit</a> is coming to its final verdict and the result could probably have a big impact on the crypto industry as a whole. With all that in mind, as the regulatory grip get tighter, crypto firms are acting a lot more careful. And for crypto, this probably means that the age of maturity is upon us. Perhaps, this could also be a sign of <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/global-monetary-system/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Global Monetary System</a> closing in on crypto assets in order to put a leash on them.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-silvergate-bank-the-fallen-soldier"><strong>Silvergate Bank, The Fallen Soldier</strong></h2>



<p>So far, prominent firms such as Coinbase exchange and Stablecoin issuer Paxos have cut ties with Silvergate bank. Interestingly, a vast majority of these companies are already dealing with their own devastating share of ongoing lawsuits.</p>



<p>Last Month, Silvergate Bank <a href="https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1312109/000110465923027353/tm238251d1_nt10k.htm" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">informed</a> the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) that it will postpone the submission of its annual financial report. According to the company&#8217;s previous year report, they suffered a loss of $1 billion in Q4 of 2022 caused by the ongoing crypto winter. Or simply put, the were not able to recover from the <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ftx-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">FTX collapse</a>.</p>



<p>Following that, Coinbase announced that they will no longer accept or initiate payments to or from Silvergate. This did not go well for Silvergate bank as they endured a huge 45% dip in their stock.</p>



<p>“In light of recent developments and out of an abundance of caution, Coinbase is no longer accepting or initiating payments to or from Silvergate. Coinbase has de minimis corporate exposure to Silvergate.”</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="799" height="542" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Silvergate-Bank-Stock.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-6351" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Silvergate-Bank-Stock.jpg 799w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Silvergate-Bank-Stock-300x204.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Silvergate-Bank-Stock-768x521.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 799px) 100vw, 799px" /></figure>



<p>Similiarly, Paxos, the stablecoin issuer for the troubled <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/busd-stablecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">BUSD</a> made a similar announcement. Paxos announced that they will discontinue all transfers to Silvergate Bank accounts.</p>



<p>&nbsp;“In light of recent developments with Silvergate Bank, Paxos has discontinued all SEN [Silvergate Exchange Network] transfers and wires to our Silvergate account. Paxos will continue to process all outgoing payments.”</p>



<p>The wave of crypto firms jumping ship has continued so far as other industry titans are now cutting ties. So far, investment firm Galaxy Digital, payment platform Circle and crypto exchange Bitstamp and exchange platform Gemini have stopped working with Silvergate.</p>



<p>At the moment, Silvergate stock is trading at $5.77 which is down almost 70% from its monthly high of $22.32.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The SEC Problem</strong></h2>



<p>As predicted, <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-regulations-sec-cftc/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">crypto regulations</a> and the SEC are breathing down the industry’s neck. Frankly, with all the reckless behavior we saw from CEOs such as Sam Bankman-Fried and Do Kwon, regulations were a long time coming. In the meantime, the debate over whether cryptocurrencies are securities or commodities seems to be settling in favor of the SEC.</p>



<p>As the Securities and Exchange Commission insists that crypto assets are securities, industry giants seem unable to prove otherwise. In the meantime, one of the most impactful lawsuits that is the XRP case will soon come to an end. Primarily, the argument behind this frustrating lawsuit is whether a security or a commodity. Now, even with the endless appeal system in the US, the result of this case can determine the future. Essentially, the XRP lawsuits has been going on for two and a half years. During this time, XRP has failed to attract retail investors and experience any stable growth. Basically, Ripple has been like a sick child watching his friends playing outside. And now, the SEC has clearly made an example out of XRP by showing others how they are not afraid to go to court and how detrimental their lawsuits can be for crypto companies.</p>



<p>In a recent interview with Bloomberg, Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse said that their failure will have an impact on the whole industry. Subsequently, Garlinghouse believes that SECs attitude toward crypto assets is simply “not healthy”.</p>



<p>“The SEC bringing the case against Ripple was not really just a case about Ripple or about XRP. It’s really about the industry and how the SEC is kind of playing offense and attacking the whole industry. Two and a half years ago when it started, I’m not sure everyone fully digested that. And now that is widely understood.</p>



<p>This is going to be pivotal for the whole industry because if the SEC is able to prevail, I think there’s a lot of other cases and some of them just in the last four weeks: I think they brought five additional enforcement cases.”</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="Ripple CEO Says SEC Suit Is &#039;Not Healthy&#039; for Industry" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/2YCKG2g7UE0?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<p>Considering the situation, the SEC is making it harder for crypto to get back to its boom and bust days. Simultaneously, retail investors are far more interested in AI stocks than coming back to crypto. Although AI coins are apparently a thing, they haven’t had any tangible utility to prove their worth. And that leaves us with the crypto winter, which is seemingly here to stay a while.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/silvergate-bank/">&lt;strong&gt;Silvergate Bank Gets Knifed in the Back&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/silvergate-bank/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Bitcoin with Tether (USDT) [Video]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 08:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Videos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6332</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Here is a full guide on how to buy Bitcoin with Tether on CoinCannon platform with a whole slew of unique benefits. Perhaps, to exchange Tether to Bitcoin can be the most popular exchange direction in crypto market. Both being the first of their kind, both BTC and USDT remain the king of the category. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-tether/">How to Buy Bitcoin with Tether (USDT) [Video]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Here is a full guide on how to buy Bitcoin with Tether on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">HiEx</a><a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">c</a><a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">hange</a> platform with a whole slew of unique benefits. Perhaps, to exchange Tether to Bitcoin can be the most popular exchange direction in crypto market. Both being the first of their kind, both BTC and USDT remain the king of the category. With that, everyone will need a great platform like CoinCannon to buy Bitcoin with Tether without any compromise. Subsequently, we will go over how easy it is to do that in only a matter of few minutes.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/how-exchange-bitcoin-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Bitcoin to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="Exchange Tether to Bitcoin   Buy BTC with USDT" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xh0FlrOrGnw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Bitcoin with Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive Bitcoin that is reliable and secure. Although there are thousands of options at this moment, we advise you to pay extra attention when choosing a Bitcoin wallet. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon. Want a good reason why? How about winning $100 ever month!</p>



<p>Learn more about our <a href="https://hi.exchange/campaign/tether-giveaway" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Tether Giveaway</a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Bitcoin (BTC)?</strong></h2>



<p>Well, there is hardly anyone these days who is not familiar with the definition of Bitcoin and what the cryptocurrency is capable of carrying out. However, let’s briefly go through what bitcoin is and where it comes from, then we can focus on the benefits of using this cryptocurrency and explain why to buy Bitcoin with Perfect Money.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a Cryptocurrency that was created after the housing market collapse in January 2009. It follows the ideas set out by the enigmatic and pseudonymous Satoshi Nakamoto in a whitepaper. The identity of the individual or individuals who developed this cryptocurrency is still under wraps. Unlike government-issued currencies, Bitcoin provides the guarantee of lower transaction costs than conventional online payment systems and is regulated by a decentralized authority.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a tempting opportunity for investment and great tool for doing financial transactions. Everything is in favor of exchanging your Perfect Money for some BTC when possible.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Pay with Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>Owning Tether is basically like having digital dollars in your pocket, only without needing a bank. Recently, there has been lots of talk about how we do not actually own our money when they are in the banks. Digital money means that banks and governments can freeze our access to our funds for whatever reason they seem justifiable. In 2022, Canada denied protestor’s access to their bank accounts and cut out their rightful ownership of their capital. Such incidents are not rare and should be treated seriously. But, political motivation aside, banks are not always available. For example, we saw how the Ukrainians lost all their capital within the banks as soon as the war started. Once again, the decentralized nature of cryptocurrencies meant that the bankless were the lucky ones in that incident.</p>



<p>Thankfully, the list of online merchants and service providers who accept Tether USDT is sufficiently long. With Tether, you can make purchases online and in person almost anywhere. Be it through a direct wallet address or a payment gateway, USDT is as good as cash these days.</p>



<p>Lastly, USDT offers an extra layer of protection for the user with blockchain technology. As a cryptocurrency, it is anonymous and secure. On top of that, the transaction fees for Tether are very low, as long as you use the TRC20 variant based on the Tron network.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon FTW!</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Buy Bitcoin with Tether?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Tether on the left field and Bitcoin on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your Bitcoin wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your Tether (USDT) to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-easy-as-that"><strong>Easy as That!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the BTC to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-tether/">How to Buy Bitcoin with Tether (USDT) [Video]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Recent Crypto Market Rally: Divisive and Hopeful</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-market-rally/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-market-rally/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 06:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6293</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Finally, we all lived the day to see a crypto market rally pulling underwater investors out of a year-long slump. Subsequently, BTC moved up from the $17k channel and is currently trading at $23k. with that, altcoins did what altcoins do best that is to follow Bitcoin without any sort of autonomy. However, recent statistics [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-market-rally/">&lt;strong&gt;Recent Crypto Market Rally: Divisive and Hopeful&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Finally, we all lived the day to see a crypto market rally pulling underwater investors out of a year-long slump. Subsequently, BTC moved up from the $17k channel and is currently trading at $23k. with that, altcoins did what altcoins do best that is to follow Bitcoin without any sort of autonomy. However, recent statistics from CoinShares have revealed a fascinating insight as to what is going on behind the crypto market rally. From a conflict in opinion in different regions to high amount of weekly inflows used to short crypto assets, circumstances in crypto market have divided the investor sentiment. Let’s take a closer look.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Not Your Average Crypto Market Rally</strong></h2>



<p>Essentially, the wild rallies back in 2020 and 2021 had a pretty straightforward structure. The overall outlook toward crypto was bullish while institutional investors made huge purchases for the long run. In the meantime, retail investors were more inclined toward hodling.</p>



<p>Following the embarrassing collapse of <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/terra-2-0-launch/v" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">terra (LUNA)</a> and the horrible annihilation of <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ftx-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">FTX</a>, both the institutional and retail investors have lost faith in the crypto. With that, it seems that the majority of bullish investors at the moment are traders who aren’t necessarily committing to long-term ventures.</p>



<p>In the latest Digital Asset Fund Flows Weekly Report, <a href="https://blog.coinshares.com/volume-115-digital-asset-fund-flows-weekly-report-c7cd25f806ea" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinShares</a> finds that trading activity is suspiciously higher than usual.</p>



<p>“Trading activity for the week was high at US$1.6bn, above the 90-day average of US$990m, with 80% of the trading focused on Bitcoin.”</p>



<p>Despite that gargantuan number, most of the weekly inflow went on to back short BTC products. Fundamentally, these products profit on downward moves of Bitcoin. In total short BTC products had over $25.5 million in inflows last week which is almost five times higher than what traditional BTC products had in inflows that is $5.7 million.</p>



<p>&nbsp;“Digital asset investment products saw US$37m inflows last week, although this was predominantly into short investment products (68%).”</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Recent-Crypto-Market-Rally-Divisive-and-Hopeful-1024x725.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-6295" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-regionally-divided"><strong>Regionally Divided</strong></h2>



<p>Basically, CoinShare data reveals that North American institutions are predominantly making the short moves on BTC. At the moment, the sentiment on Bitcoin and other crypto assets are radically different on both sides of the Atlantis.</p>



<p>“Regionally, opinion is very polarised. Inflows were seen in Europe, most notably Germany and Switzerland with US$14m and US$10m respectively. Outflows were seen in European short investment products too, suggesting sentiment is positive. In contrast, Hong Kong saw outflows from long investment products (US$11m), while the 95% of the inflows into the US were into short-Bitcoin products.”</p>



<p>At this point, there’s still not enough evidence to prove that the recent crypto market rally is a bull trap. Regardless, the data is consistently indicating a massive divide in sentiment and of course a huge amount of interest in trading rather than holding. With all that, it would be safe to assume that the crypto market will likely become highly volatile for at least the first quarter of 2023. So hang in tight, and get onboard the emotional roller coaster of crypto investment!</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-market-rally/">&lt;strong&gt;Recent Crypto Market Rally: Divisive and Hopeful&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-market-rally/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
