<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>DAI Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/dai/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 10:08:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>How to Buy Bitcoin with Dai [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 10:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6379</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you are looking to buy Bitcoin with Dai, CoinCannon is the ultimate platform for the job. Bitcoin has finally managed to bounce back and move above the critical resistance level at $25k. Subsequently, investors are once again eager to invest in the top crypto asset by market cap. On top of that, the mass [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Buy Bitcoin with Dai [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you are looking to buy Bitcoin with Dai, CoinCannon is the ultimate platform for the job. Bitcoin has finally managed to bounce back and move above the critical resistance level at $25k. Subsequently, investors are once again eager to invest in the top crypto asset by market cap. On top of that, the mass adoption of BTC has turned it into a utilitarian digital asset. Today, thousands of credible online stores accept Bitcoin as payment. Fortunately, you can now pay for goods and services via BTC and there’s lots of stuff you can <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-with-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">buy with Bitcoin</a>. However, if you’re holding DAI, you can instantly exchange Dai into Bitcoin in only a matter of minutes. Want to get started? Head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Dai on the left box and Bitcoin on the right and you’re good to go!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/">How to exchange cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Bitcoin with Dai?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive Bitcoin (BTC). In case your Dai wallet supports BTC, you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is DAI?</strong></h2>



<p>Before we go over how to buy Bitcoin with Dai, let’s take a brief look at Dai as a stablecoin.</p>



<p>DAI is an Ethereum-based stablecoin. A stablecoin is a cryptocurrency with a pegged value to another currency. In case of DAI, it is pegged to the US dollar and much like Tether and USDC, Dai will always be worth $1. Stablecoins are a crucial part of the crypto market as they offer very little volatility. In that regard, investors use stablecoins to save their funds in the form of a reliable and stable asset.</p>



<p>What makes DAI unique is a clever design that eliminates the biggest concerns for stablecoins. Generally speaking, conventional stablecoins require a massive reserve by the company. For example, for every Tether USD, the Tether company must hold $1 USD in their reserve. This is a huge issue for companies as it is difficult to provide liquidity and keep it consistent.</p>



<p>DAI offers a new solution for this problem. By using an automated system of smart contracts on Ethereum blockchain, DAI does now need a reserve. Using collateralized debt denominated in ETH allows DAI to maintain the 1:1 ration with USD. Simply speaking, users can deposit Ethereum or other cryptocurrencies can borrow against the value of their deposit and generate new DAI. The currency is this case is known as collateral.</p>



<p>You can <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange Dai to PayPal</a> on CoinCannon with the lowest exchange fees ever!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Invest in Bitcoin?</strong></h2>



<p>Well, there is hardly anyone these days who is not familiar with the definition of Bitcoin and what the cryptocurrency is capable of carrying out. However, let’s briefly go through what bitcoin is and where it comes from, then we can focus on the benefits of using this cryptocurrency and explain why to buy Bitcoin with Perfect Money.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a Cryptocurrency that was created after the housing market collapse in January 2009. It follows the ideas set out by the enigmatic and pseudonymous Satoshi Nakamoto in a whitepaper. The identity of the individual or individuals who developed this cryptocurrency is still under wraps. Unlike government-issued currencies, Bitcoin provides the guarantee of lower transaction costs than conventional online payment systems and is regulated by a decentralized authority.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a tempting opportunity for investment and great tool for doing financial transactions. In that regard, it has been a solid choice for investment as an asset that is truly decentralized. On top of that, there are countless online platform that accept Bitcoin as payment which makes BTC a utilitarian option for online payments.</p>



<p>So, if You’ve decided to invest in BTC, you can buy Bitcoin with Dai in only a matter of minutes on CoinCannon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-buy-bitcoin-with-dai"><strong>How to Buy Bitcoin with DAI?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Dai (DAI) on the left field and Bitcoin (BTC) on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your BTC wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your DAI to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>You’re All Set!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Bitcoin (BTC) to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Buy Bitcoin with Dai [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Ethereum to DAI [No Fees]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-dai/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-dai/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 07:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6315</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you’re looking to exchange Ethereum to DAI, CoinCannon is all you need! Volatile assets such as ETH and BTC will definitely have some risks associated with them. However, investors can easily convert them into stablecoins to stop the loss at a certain period of time. Thankfully, exchanging crypto assets into one another does not [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-dai/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange Ethereum to DAI [No Fees]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you’re looking to exchange Ethereum to DAI, <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is all you need! Volatile assets such as ETH and BTC will definitely have some risks associated with them. However, investors can easily convert them into stablecoins to stop the loss at a certain period of time. Thankfully, exchanging crypto assets into one another does not have massive fees so it’s a pretty safe bet. As far as stablecoins go, DAI has been a top choice for crypto enthusiasts as it is perhaps very different than the others. In this article, we will go over everything you need to know on how to exchange Ethereum to DAI on CoinCannon platform.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Ethereum to DAI?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive DAI. In case your Ether wallet supports DAI, you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Ethereum?</strong></h2>



<p>As an open-source decentralized blockchain platform, Ethereum is perhaps the most diverse and innovative one out there. In its essence, it is a decentralized public ledger for verifying and recording transactions. The Ethereum is considered as a second-gen blockchain platform, improving upon the high gas fees, scalability issues and high transactions fees of previous platforms. This open-source platform has no geographical restrictions and has always been the tip of the spear as far as innovation goes. Essential services such as Smart contracts, NFT`s and decentralized apps were first introduced on the Ethereum platform. As for the cherry on top, the native token of the Ethereum platform called Ether or ETH is second in terms of market value standing only behind Bitcoin.</p>



<p>With the <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/ethereum-2-0-upgrade-date/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Ethereum 2.0</a> launch in August 2022, the network totally switched to proof of stake. With that, Ethereum network will have much better scalability and very low gas fees. On top of that, all the criticism regarding energy consumption will go away. Many consider the 2.0 upgrade as a great investment opportunity since ETH is very much likely to have a rally. Nonetheless, Ethereum is the second most popular cryptocurrency in the world for good reason. Their team has always been on the forefront of innovation which could potentially attract capital and provide great returns.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Ethereum to DAI?</strong></h2>



<p>DAI is an Ethereum-based stablecoin. A stablecoin is a cryptocurrency with a pegged value to another currency. In case of DAI, it is pegged to the US dollar and much like Tether and USDC, Dai will always be worth $1. Stablecoins are a crucial part of the crypto market as they offer very little volatility. In that regard, investors use stablecoins to save their funds in the form of a reliable and stable asset.</p>



<p>What makes DAI unique is a clever design that eliminates the biggest concerns for stablecoins. Generally speaking, conventional stablecoins require a massive reserve by the company. For example, for every Tether USD, the Tether company must hold $1 USD in their reserve. This is a huge issue for companies as it is difficult to provide liquidity and keep it consistent.</p>



<p>DAI offers a new solution for this problem. By using an automated system of smart contracts on Ethereum blockchain, DAI does now need a reserve. Using collateralized debt denominated in ETH allows DAI to maintain the 1:1 ration with USD. Simply speaking, users can deposit Ethereum or other cryptocurrencies can borrow against the value of their deposit and generate new DAI. The currency is this case is known as collateral.</p>



<p>Currently, DAI has a market cap of over $5 billion and is ranked as 17th cryptocurrency.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Ethereum to DAI</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Ethereum on the left field and DAI on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your DAI wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your Ethereum to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-that-s-it"><strong>That’s it!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the DAI to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-dai/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange Ethereum to DAI [No Fees]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-dai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange DAI to PayPal [lowest commission]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 09:45:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange DAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Maker DAO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4432</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>if you&#8217;re Looking to cash out your stablecoins, you can exchange DAI to PayPal on CoinCannon with the lowest exchange fees. DAI is the latest stablecoin added to CoinCannon platform along with, USDC and TUSD. Created with a unique architecture, DAI is a different kind of stable coin that offers better reliability compared with others. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/">How to Exchange DAI to PayPal [lowest commission]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>if you&#8217;re Looking to cash out your stablecoins, you can <strong>exchange DAI to PayPal on CoinCannon</strong> with the lowest exchange fees. DAI is the latest stablecoin added to CoinCannon platform along with, USDC and TUSD. Created with a unique architecture, DAI is a different kind of stable coin that offers better reliability compared with others. In this article, we will go through everything you need to exchange DAI to PayPal on CoinCannon website. You can also exchange DAI to other currencies on the platform.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-dai"><strong>What is DAI?</strong></h2>



<p>DAI is an Ethereum-based stablecoin. A stablecoin is a cryptocurrency with a pegged value to another currency. In case of DAI, it is pegged to the US dollar and much like Tether and USDC, Dai will always be worth $1. Stablecoins are a crucial part of the crypto market as they offer very little volatility. In that regard, investors use stablecoins to save their funds in the form of a reliable and stable asset.</p>



<p>What makes DAI unique is a clever design that eliminates the biggest concerns for stablecoins. Generally speaking, conventional stablecoins require a massive reserve by the company. For example, for every Tether USD, the Tether company must hold $1 USD in their reserve. This is a huge issue for companies as it is difficult to provide liquidity and keep it consistent.</p>



<p>DAI offers a new solution for this problem. By using an automated system of smart contracts on Ethereum blockchain, DAI does now need a reserve. Using collateralized debt denominated in ETH allows DAI to maintain the 1:1 ration with USD. Simply speaking, users can deposit Ethereum or other cryptocurrencies can borrow against the value of their deposit and generate new DAI. The currency is this case is known as collateral.</p>



<p>Currently, DAI has a market cap of over $9 billion and is ranked as 19<sup>th</sup> cryptocurrency.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-exchange-dai-to-paypal"><strong>Why Exchange DAI to PayPal?</strong></h2>



<p>PayPal is an online trade company that, through online transfers, facilitates payments between parties. Its system allows clients to set up an account on its platform that is linked to the user’s credit card or checking account. Upon confirmation of identification and proof of funds, through the website or application of the company, users can begin sending or receiving payments online to and from other PayPal accounts.</p>



<p>As mentioned above, in order to transfer money to others using the receiver’s email address or mobile phone number, PayPal account holders can use the website or mobile application of the company. Within only a matter of minutes, transactions go through and the company promises that transfers are immediately available for payment or withdrawal to a bank account.</p>



<p>The ease of use and the wide acceptance makes the exchange cryptocurrencies to PayPal one of the best options when you need some cash to spend online.</p>



<p>All that said, you also have the ability to exchange DAI to Perfect Money USD, Payeer USD or Webmoney USD.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-jolixo"><strong>Why CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p><strong>CoinCannon is an online exchange that offers everything you need from a platform.</strong></p>



<p>Truthfully, it is a rare combination for an online exchange to offer anonymity, lowest exchange rates and unparalleled reliability altogether.</p>



<p>We respect our customer’s privacy by not asking for their personal information. The best way for anyone to protect their information is to not disclose them at all. In that regard, not having KYC or sign up is the best method.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the platform utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at all times. Our words sound too good? Just pay a visit to ranking websites such as BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>Lastly, according to Murphy’s law “anything that can go wrong will go wrong”. To stay ahead of any problems, we offer 24/7 customer support.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-exchange-dai-to-paypal"><strong>How to Exchange DAI to PayPal?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select DAI on the left field and PayPal on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your PayPal account details, email, and phone number.</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your DAI to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>At this point, our team will process the order and make the payment to your account. PayPal payments might take some time. We suggest you read some of the articles on <a href="blog.hi.exchange">CoinCannon Blog</a> as you wait for the transaction.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/">How to Exchange DAI to PayPal [lowest commission]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top Stablecoins to Buy [Ranked by Security]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/top-stablecoins-to-buy/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/top-stablecoins-to-buy/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 06:23:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TrueUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USD Coin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4892</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>“Anything that can go wrong, will go wrong”. This is called Murphy’s law and it has been consistently true all throughout history. Why is it important for stablecoins? Well, potentially any stablecoin can lose value due to a multitude of reasons. Be it network issues or simply a lack of sufficient dollar reserve, stablecoins can [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/top-stablecoins-to-buy/">Top Stablecoins to Buy [Ranked by Security]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>“Anything that can go wrong, will go wrong”. This is called Murphy’s law and it has been consistently true all throughout history. Why is it important for stablecoins? Well, potentially any stablecoin can lose value due to a multitude of reasons. Be it network issues or simply a lack of sufficient dollar reserve, stablecoins can drop in value as we have seen with IRON stablecoin. In that regard, security is the utmost priority when it comes to stablecoins. At this point, Tether is still the predominant stablecoin but there are rumors about its connection with Chinese real estate giants that are making investors uncomfortable. And here we are with a list of top stablecoins to buy with solid reputations to introduce as Tether alternatives.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><span class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Looking for top stablecoins to buy? Head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>.</span></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Security Comes First</strong></h2>



<p>Considering the pegged value, the only reason to choose a stablecoin over another is the security. Primarily, a secure stablecoin is one that holds just as much US dollar reserve as the issued coins. However, there are tricks that some issuers can resort to for hiding their lack of reserve.</p>



<p>Generally speaking, an ideal stablecoin issuer must be fully transparent about how much dollar they are holding and in what form. And form, is what brings us to the second trick. Issuers can potentially hold different forms of assets for their reserve. Sometimes, these assets are in form of bonds or security papers issued from questionable companies. For example, the fallen real estate giant Evergrande used security papers to pay off or loan other companies. Subsequently, if you have security papers from Evergrande, good luck turning it into cash as it is exactly worth zero in 2022.</p>



<p>Bear in mind, these two tricks are just the tip of the iceberg as there are thousands of ways an stablecoin issuer can conceal their true dollar reserve. With that in mind, our top picks for stablecoins to buy are ranked by transparency and low diversity in assets. However, there is one outlier that utilizes a different method to hold a pegged value which we will talk about later in this article.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Top Stablecoins to Buy Available on CoinCannon</strong></h2>



<p>You can invest on stablecoins or exchange your cryptocurrencies to stablecoins on CoinCannon platform. CoinCannon gives you three good reasons to join in:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Anonymity: The platform does not require KYC (know your customer)</li><li>Efficiency: Very, very, low exchange fees. Our rates are seriously competitive</li><li>24/7 online Support: That’s right, we’re available to talk all day every day!</li></ul>



<p>On top of that, you can find guide articles for every exchange direction on <a href="//blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a>. CoinCannon blog is an all-in-one crypto blog where you can follow the latest <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/category/news/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">news</a>, <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/category/exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">guide articles</a>, <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/category/cryptocurrency/price-analysis/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">price analysis</a> and much more!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>TrueUSD</strong></h2>



<p>TrueUSD (TUSD) is a stablecoin based on the Ethereum (ERC20) network. Stablecoins are cryptocurrencies that have their value pegged to another currency. In this case, as you might have guessed it, TUSD is backed by US dollar. However, the question is, why would someone create another stablecoin in this highly saturated market? The answer is, no one offers better transparency and security as much as TrueUSD.</p>



<p>Time and time again, we have heard concerns about Tether not being honest about their dollar reserve. Essentially, a stablecoin issuer must hold as much USD as they have their stablecoin in circulation. Sadly, these companies do not provide full clarity regarding their reserve. Subsequently, in case things get out of hand, the value of the stablecoin can drop in a matter of minutes.</p>



<p>TrueUSD has an emphasis on honesty and transparency to fight the bad reputation about stablecoins. They offer legal protections and real-time audits for users. All of the circulating supply of the token is fully collateralized by USD. The crypto exchange TrustToken issued TUSD in 2018. The TrustToken exchange has mandated a monthly audit for TUSD which means that the users are assured about the state of the reserve. Despite being based on the Ethereum network, TUSD has extremely low transaction fees. This is due to the fact that TrustToken generates revenue from their US dollar based holdings in different accounts. Here on CoinCannon, we will exchange your TrueUSD with astonishingly low exchange fees!</p>



<p>TrueUSD is Certainly on top of our Stablecoins to Buy list!</p>



<div class="wp-block-columns is-layout-flex wp-container-core-columns-is-layout-1 wp-block-columns-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-column is-layout-flow wp-block-column-is-layout-flow" style="flex-basis:100%">
<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"><p>Buy and Sell TrueUSD on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a>.</p></blockquote>
</div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>USD Coin</strong></h2>



<p>USD Coin owns the world’s largest stablecoin industry ecosystem in the world. It is a cryptocurrency that is pegged to US dollar in terms of value. That means that each USCD will always be worth $1. Stablecoins are used as a hedge against inflation and volatility in the crypto market. However, they can also be used as an alternative way to hold assets on the blockchain network.</p>



<p>As good as stablecoins might sound, there has always been concern about the companies not being honest about their dollar reserve. Basically, for every 1 USDC the company issues, they must hold $1 in their accounts. As a matter of fact, there are rumors regarding some large companies not having the dollar equivalent of their stablecoin. If a solid reserve does not back a stablecoin, the currency will lose value and seriously damage the investor’s funds. In that regard, USD Coin aims to provide full transparency about their reserves.</p>



<p>USDC is managed by a consortium called Centre which is a part of the payment technology company Circle. Much like TrueUSD, they offer monthly attestation reports by Grant Thornton to ensure investors regarding their reserves. Where they differ from TrueUSD, is that TrueUSD only holds dollar in different accounts but USD Coin also holds other assets such as gold.</p>



<div class="wp-block-columns is-layout-flex wp-container-core-columns-is-layout-2 wp-block-columns-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-column is-layout-flow wp-block-column-is-layout-flow" style="flex-basis:100%">
<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"><p>Buy and Sell USD Coin on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a>.</p></blockquote>
</div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>DAI</strong></h2>



<p>DAI is an Ethereum-based stablecoin. A stablecoin is a cryptocurrency with a pegged value to another currency. In case of DAI, it is pegged to the US dollar and much like Tether and USDC, Dai will always be worth $1. Stablecoins are a crucial part of the crypto market as they offer very little volatility. In that regard, investors use stablecoins to save their funds in the form of a reliable and stable asset.</p>



<p>What makes DAI unique is a clever design that eliminates the biggest concerns for stablecoins. Generally speaking, conventional stablecoins require a massive reserve by the company. For example, for every Tether USD, the Tether company must hold $1 USD in their reserve. This is a huge issue for companies as it is difficult to provide liquidity and keep it consistent.</p>



<p>DAI offers a new solution for this problem. By using an automated system of smart contracts on Ethereum blockchain, DAI does now need a reserve. Using collateralized debt denominated in ETH allows DAI to maintain the 1:1 ration with USD. Simply speaking, users can deposit Ethereum or other cryptocurrencies can borrow against the value of their deposit and generate new DAI. The currency is this case is known as collateral.</p>



<div class="wp-block-columns is-layout-flex wp-container-core-columns-is-layout-3 wp-block-columns-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-column is-layout-flow wp-block-column-is-layout-flow" style="flex-basis:100%">
<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"><p>Buy and Sell DAI on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a>.</p></blockquote>
</div>
</div>



<p></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/top-stablecoins-to-buy/">Top Stablecoins to Buy [Ranked by Security]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/top-stablecoins-to-buy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DeFi Coins to Buy in 2022</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/defi-coins-to-buy-in-2022/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/defi-coins-to-buy-in-2022/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 09:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Decentealized Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi Coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTM]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra LUNA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4873</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Undoubtedly, the greatest innovation in financial technology (Fintech) is Decentralized Finance (DeFi) utilizing the blockchain technology. Love or hate cryptocurrencies, Defi is a bigger deal than even Bitcoin at this point. In fact, numerous countries are now adopting Defi for their national stablecoins and many other applications outside finance. Clearly, DeFi has a heck ton [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/defi-coins-to-buy-in-2022/">DeFi Coins to Buy in 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Undoubtedly, the greatest innovation in financial technology (Fintech) is Decentralized Finance (DeFi) utilizing the blockchain technology. Love or hate cryptocurrencies, Defi is a bigger deal than even Bitcoin at this point. In fact, numerous countries are now adopting Defi for their national stablecoins and many other applications outside finance. Clearly, DeFi has a heck ton of demand right now and those who are leading this market now, will surely have big fat share of the future markets. However, when it comes down to which DeFi coins to buy, we really had to think twice since there are quite a few good options. But, here we are with a short list of top DeFi Coins to buy in 2022.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><span style="background-color:rgba(0, 0, 0, 0)" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Don’t go through KYC, buy DeFi coins on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> anonymously with the lowest fees.</span></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-defi-coins-to-buy-for-freedom"><strong>DeFi Coins to Buy for Freedom!</strong></h2>



<p>Decentralized finance cuts out the middle man. Transaction times are reduced and the gas fees are much lower. How does it work? The Blockchain technology.</p>



<p>DeFi utilizes blockchain to record and verify transactions in blocks. Also, all the information available on the blocks is encrypted. By decentralizing this network of data and transactions much like cryptocurrencies, DeFi manages to provide a much more efficient network and a quicker consensus mechanism.</p>



<p>On the other hand, DeFi is accessible anywhere in the world that has a connection to the internet. So, gone are the days of waiting for bank transfers.</p>



<p>For the time being, the only downside for DeFi is the unclear regulatory status. Each country has its own set of rules concerning DeFi and the technology is in early stages. However, considering the scope of this technology, DeFi is definitely here to last. Without further ado, here are DeFi Coin to Buy.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-terra-luna"><strong>Terra (LUNA)</strong></h2>



<p>The Terra network is an open-source blockchain protocol that works as a payment platform for stablecoins. Essentially, the network creates stablecoins pegged to fiat currencies. These stablecoins constantly track the price of these fiat currencies. Within the network, users can buy, hold, trade or simply exchange all stablecoins.</p>



<p>Perhaps the biggest challenge for any stablecoin is to keep the value pegged and stable. To overcome this challenge, Terra network balances the supply and demand by their governance token LUNA. Used for both governance and mining, LUNA ensures that all stablecoins remain stable. In that regard, LUNA acts as a counterweight in the network. Users can either burn LUNA to mint Terra or simple stake LUNA.</p>



<p>As of December 2021, LUNA is in the top 10 cryptocurrencies with a market cap of over $21 billion USD. Considering the inevitable demand for stablecoins and the clever design of Terra, it is safe to assume LUNA a highly successful future.</p>



<div class="wp-block-columns is-layout-flex wp-container-core-columns-is-layout-4 wp-block-columns-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-column is-layout-flow wp-block-column-is-layout-flow" style="flex-basis:100%">
<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>Buy Luna instantly with the lowest exchange fees on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a>.</p>
</blockquote>
</div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-avalanche-avax"><strong>Avalanche (AVAX)</strong></h2>



<p>Avalanche is a blockchain platform launched in 2020 by Ava Labs. It is essentially a smart contracts platform that aims to dethrone Ethereum. To make this happen, the network offers incredibly fast transaction speed, low transaction fees and eco-friendly attitude.</p>



<p>If you know about the blockchain trilemma, you will know how at least no one has been able to solve this issue. However, Avalanche promises to deliver impressive scalability while at the same time remains decentralized and secure. So far, it has been able to fulfill almost all promises as a worthy Ethereum killer on the rise.</p>



<p>AVAX is the native token of the network and is currently 10<sup>TH</sup> in the ranks. With an impressive $20 billion market cap, it is continuing to close the gap with Ethereum.</p>



<div class="wp-block-columns is-layout-flex wp-container-core-columns-is-layout-5 wp-block-columns-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-column is-layout-flow wp-block-column-is-layout-flow" style="flex-basis:100%">
<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>You can easily buy AVAX on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> with no KYC or Sign Up required.</p>
</blockquote>
</div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-dai"><strong>DAI</strong></h2>



<p>Why would you invest on a stablecoin? There answer is despite the stable price, Dai is an excellent alternative for Tether. Considering all the rumors about Tether, Dai is the safer alternative as a stablecoin.</p>



<p>DAI is an Ethereum-based stablecoin. A stablecoin is a cryptocurrency with a pegged value to another currency. In case of DAI, it is pegged to the US dollar and much like Tether and USDC, Dai will always be worth $1. Stablecoins are a crucial part of the crypto market as they offer very little volatility. In that regard, investors use stablecoins to save their funds in the form of a reliable and stable asset.</p>



<p>What makes DAI unique is a clever design that eliminates the biggest concerns for stablecoins. Generally speaking, conventional stablecoins require a massive reserve by the company. For example, for every Tether USD, the Tether company must hold $1 USD in their reserve. This is a huge issue for companies as it is difficult to provide liquidity and keep it consistent.</p>



<p>DAI offers a new solution for this problem. By using an automated system of smart contracts on Ethereum blockchain, DAI does now need a reserve. Using collateralized debt denominated in ETH allows DAI to maintain the 1:1 ration with USD. Simply speaking, users can deposit Ethereum or other cryptocurrencies can borrow against the value of their deposit and generate new DAI. The currency is this case is known as collateral.</p>



<p>Currently, DAI has a market cap of over $10 billion and is ranked as 19th cryptocurrency.</p>



<div class="wp-block-columns is-layout-flex wp-container-core-columns-is-layout-6 wp-block-columns-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-column is-layout-flow wp-block-column-is-layout-flow" style="flex-basis:100%">
<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>Buy Dai instantly on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>.</p>
</blockquote>
</div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-fantom-ftm"><strong>Fantom (FTM)</strong></h2>



<p>Fantom is an open-source decentralized smart contract platform for DApps and digital assets. It is made to be an alternative to Ethereum. Fantom is looking to overcome the primary limitations of previous blockchains and balancing three components (blockchain trilemma): scalability, security and decentralization. The project offers a series of apparatus to simplify the process of integrating existing DApps, as well as an extensive staking reward system and built-in DeFi instruments.</p>



<p>Fantom is basically a Layer-1 blockchain that uses a scratch-built consensus mechanism and independent consensus layer, “Lachesis”, to facilitate DeFi and related services on the basis of smart contracts. Lachesis also provide security for other layers, including Opera, Fantom&#8217;s EVM-compatible smart contract chain. The goal of the project is to “grant compatibility between all transaction bodies around the world.”</p>



<p>The Fantom network is fast and furious! thousands of transactions per second, where transactions are finished in 1-2 seconds, and the cost is fractions of a cent per transaction. Hence, Fantom provides better scalability at a lower cost.</p>



<p>Currently, FTM is 32<sup>nd</sup> in the ranks with a market cap of over $6 billion USD. It is a relatively new player in the game but has so much potential for the future.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-jolixo"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.okchanger.com/exchangers/jolixo" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">OkChanger</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. We are on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bestchange</a> and are always amongst the top exchanges.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/defi-coins-to-buy-in-2022/">DeFi Coins to Buy in 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/defi-coins-to-buy-in-2022/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Regulatory Actions Against Stablecoins Are Coming</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/regulatory-actions-against-stablecoins-are-coming/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/regulatory-actions-against-stablecoins-are-coming/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 07:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Digital Currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=3786</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Stablecoins have been causing so much controversy lately. The crypto market continues as the longest running bullish market in history. In that regard, the stablecoins are the necessary medium in this market. As of late, recent rumors and statements from Washington are indicating a possible wave of new regulations coming on stablecoins way. Stablecoins [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/regulatory-actions-against-stablecoins-are-coming/">Regulatory Actions Against Stablecoins Are Coming</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Stablecoins have been causing so much controversy lately. The crypto market continues as the longest running bullish market in history. In that regard, the stablecoins are the necessary medium in this market. As of late, recent rumors and statements from Washington are indicating a possible wave of new regulations coming on stablecoins way.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Stablecoins and CBDCs</strong></h2>



<p>Generally speaking, a stablecoin is a type of digital currency that has its value pegged to another asset. Most commonly, fiat pegged stablecoins are used in cryptocurrency trading. However, their superpower is to make quick, cheap and mostly secure transaction on the blockchain network as an alternative for banking services. Considering the impressive <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/view/stablecoin/">$126 billion market cap</a> as of September, 2021, it is no wonder the politicians are worried about it.</p>



<p>To be fair, a valid argument against private sector stablecoins is that regarding the value, many of them are backed by debt. On the other hand, the decentralized nature of these companies can make it difficult to protect the users against possibly malicious policies. Subsequently, the governments are now seeking to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/cbdc-the-ultimate-financial-apparatus-for-governments/">issue Government backed stablecoins or CBDC</a>.</p>



<p>The concern lies in the fact that CBDC can be an over powered apparatus for central banks that initially limits people from owning or having access to their wealth. The money is not in their hands, the money is on a digital network and the bank can block access if they wanted. In a dystopian situation, central banks can impose negative interest rates on bank accounts. Furthermore, it would be entirely possible for policymakers to impose regulations demanding only CBDC is the only legal medium to trade crypto.  <a href="https://www.atlanticcouncil.org/cbdctracker/">Currently 83 countries are looking into CBDC release.</a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Possible Legal Approaches for Stablecoins</strong></h2>



<p>Only a few days ago, a <a href="https://home.treasury.gov/news/press-releases/jy0281">press release from the US Treasury</a> demanded quick actions against stablecoins expressing urgency. This is an indication of the severity of the situation.</p>



<p>Yesterday, a <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2021/09/17/business/economy/federal-reserve-virtual-currency-stablecoin.html">New York Times article</a> discussed six different legal approaches that lawmakers can take against stablecoins. Here are the six approaches:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list"><li>Regarding them as “systematically risky”. This would call for strict and harsh regulatory control can be quite destructive for them.</li><li>Recognizing them as “securities” and putting them under SEC supervision. (oh lawd)</li><li>Regulate them as Banks, putting them under the office of the Comptroller of Currency.</li><li>Engage in an active competition utilizing CBDC (or release the hounds in other terms).</li></ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Bottom line</strong></h2>



<p>Sadly, it would be unrealistic to expect a phenomenon like stablecoin can continue this much unregulated. As it grows in market cap, the realization has hit the politicians that first, they want some if not all the profit and second, it is too liberating to be considered as safe for the political structure. Conversely, the fraudulent activities, lack of vision or in some cases just bad luck has given the crypto market a bad image for politicians to exploit. We must wait and see the regulatory outcome of stablecoin discussions. However, we could be sure that people are losing ground in these regulatory battles.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Our Vision</strong></h2>



<p>We believe in crypto, not only for income but liberation as well. Although we’re not the first decentralized online exchange, we’re looking to be the best.  You can exchange your cryptocurrencies and digital currencies on <a href="hi.exchange">hi.exchange</a>. We Utilize an automated system to determine the best rates. Furthermore, we offer 24/7 customer support. Also, we have technical price analysis for Bitcoin and Altcoins, opinion articles and news on <a href="blog.hi.exchange">our blog</a>. Our vision is to keep our customers up do date with the latest news and professional analysis.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/regulatory-actions-against-stablecoins-are-coming/">Regulatory Actions Against Stablecoins Are Coming</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/regulatory-actions-against-stablecoins-are-coming/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
