<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>crypto to crypto Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/category/crypto-to-crypto-articles/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/category/crypto-to-crypto-articles/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 09:03:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Litecoin to Tether USDT [Instant]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-litecoin-to-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-litecoin-to-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 08:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6424</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking for an easy way to exchange Litecoin to Tether with full anonymity? CoinCannon is all you need. Litecoin is one of the oldest altcoins in the crypto space and has strong group of loyal investors. In terms of utility, a vast number of online platforms support LTC transactions as payment. With that, investors can [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-litecoin-to-tether/">How to Exchange Litecoin to Tether USDT [Instant]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking for an easy way to exchange Litecoin to Tether with full anonymity? CoinCannon is all you need. Litecoin is one of the oldest altcoins in the crypto space and has strong group of loyal investors. In terms of utility, a vast number of online platforms support LTC transactions as payment. With that, investors can not only hold LTC for investment, but they can also use it for payments. However, if you want to stay safe from volatility, you will need to exchange LTC. For that, it’s not easy to find an exchange platform that offers low exchange fees and privacy simultaneously. Fortunately, we will introduce the ultimate OTC exchange platform in this article and provide a step-by-step guide on how to exchange Litecoin to Tether.</p>



<p>So get started, head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Litecoin and Tether and you’re good to go.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-do-i-need-to-exchange-litecoin-to-tether"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Litecoin to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive USDT. Most likely, your Litecoin wallet supports USDT, so you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Litecoin (LTC)?</strong></h2>



<p>Litecoin was one of the earliest Bitcoin spinoffs back in 2011. Generally speaking, Litecoin bears resemblance to Bitcoin in many ways. It is essentially a global payment network that is autonomous and open-source. The decentralized network does not allow a central authority to take control over the payments. LTC is the native currency of this network which is the medium for all transactions within the network. Litecoin utilizes a proof of work (POW) blockchain network meaning that there are active miners working for it.</p>



<p>So far, it looks to be Another Bitcoin impersonator. However, the LTC network uses a different cryptographic algorithm called scrypt. Furthermore, it provides much faster block generation speeds and subsequently much better scalability.</p>



<p>As of April 2023, LTC is 12<sup>th</sup> cryptocurrency in the ranks with a market cap of over $6.5 billion. To learn everything about the network and its cryptocurrency continue reading “<a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-litecoin/">What is Litecoin?”</a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Litecoin to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>At this point, it’s good to briefly introduce Tether. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Litecoin to Tether?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Litecoin (LTC) on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your LTC to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>You’re all Set!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether USDT to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-litecoin-to-tether/">How to Exchange Litecoin to Tether USDT [Instant]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-litecoin-to-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Ripple to Tether USDT [Instant]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ripple-to-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ripple-to-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 08:44:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6418</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking for an easy way to exchange Ripple to Tether with anonymity? CoinCannon is all you need. Ripple (XRP) has been one of the most popular investment options for crypto enthusiasts. The blockchain network offers great utility for cross border transactions and an alternative payment system for traditional banking. On top of that, XRP has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ripple-to-tether/">How to Exchange Ripple to Tether USDT [Instant]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking for an easy way to exchange Ripple to Tether with anonymity? CoinCannon is all you need. Ripple (XRP) has been one of the most popular investment options for crypto enthusiasts. The blockchain network offers great utility for cross border transactions and an alternative payment system for traditional banking. On top of that, XRP has had great returns for investors as a native token for this innovative network. In this article, we will go over how to exchange Ripple to Tether without compromising on exchange rates or privacy.</p>



<p>So get started, head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Ripple (XRP) on the left box and Tether (USDT) on the right one and you’re good to go!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Ripple to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p> For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive USDT. Most likely, your Cardano wallet supports USDT, so you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Ripple (XRP)?</strong></h2>



<p>To put it simply, Ripple is a payment protocol designed to operate as a digital bank. However, by utilizing a decentralized blockchain network as the financial platform it can operate much more efficiently. As compared with a bank, Ripple network has significantly lower transaction fees and god-like scalability! This allows for seamless digital money transfers that are inexpensive and quick. This is especially important since institutions can save millions of dollars and long hours on their large transactions.</p>



<p>As the native token of the network, XRP basically acts as a mediator. All the funds deposited on the network will automatically convert to XRP and then converted back to the target currency. This clever design provides massive circulation for the cryptocurrency. To make it an even better deal, all XRP coins are pre-mined. Meaning that it is environmentally friendly and maintains very low gas fees.</p>



<p>As of April 2023, XRP is the 6th cryptocurrency with a market cap of almost $23.7 billion.</p>



<p>To learn everything about Ripple XRP continue reading “<a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-ripple/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Ripple and How it Works?</a>”.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Ripple to Tether (USDT)?</strong></h2>



<p>At this point, it’s good to briefly introduce Tether. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon to the Moon!</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Ripple to Tether (USDT)</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Ripple (XRP) on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your XRP to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-finished"><strong>Finished!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether USDT to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ripple-to-tether/">How to Exchange Ripple to Tether USDT [Instant]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ripple-to-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange BNB to USDT [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bnb-to-usdt/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bnb-to-usdt/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 08:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6412</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Here’s the easiest way to exchange BNB to USDT instantly with full anonymity! Binance Coin (BNB) is one of the top crypto assets by market cap. For the most part, this popularity stem’s from Binance’s massive scale as an exchange platform. Now, while users can easily exchange BNB to USDT on Binance platform, they will [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bnb-to-usdt/">How to Exchange BNB to USDT [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Here’s the easiest way to exchange BNB to USDT instantly with full anonymity! Binance Coin (BNB) is one of the top crypto assets by market cap. For the most part, this popularity stem’s from Binance’s massive scale as an exchange platform. Now, while users can easily exchange BNB to USDT on Binance platform, they will have to compromise on their privacy to do the job. Primarily, Binance requires a much stricter KYC process to authenticate users. On top of that, they will have to comply with multiple governments and share user data with the authorities. Fortunately, CoinCannon cuts down all complications by offering a truly hassle-free KYC process. Furthermore, privacy will not come as a luxury sine CoinCannon offer the lowest exchange fees. With all that, here is a full guide on how to exchange Binance Coin to Tether USDT in only a matter of minutes.</p>



<p>So, head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, choose Binance Coin (BNB) on the left field and Tether (USDT) on the right one and start your exchange.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange BNB to USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive USDT. Most likely, your Cardano wallet supports USDT, so you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Binance Coin (BNB)?</strong></h2>



<p>Before we go over how to exchange BNB to USDT, let’s go over a brief introduction on Binance Coin. Initially found in China, Binance began as an online cryptocurrency exchange with a strong emphasis on altcoin trading. It didn’t take long for Binance to be crowned as the number one exchange in the world. Amongst the numerous motivating factors and reasons for this profound success, the primary one was high liquidity, low transaction fees and additional discounts for users who made payments by its native coin, BNB. The massive platform has a staggering capacity to process approximately 1.4 million orders per second, offering trading for more than 500 cryptocurrencies and virtual tokens.</p>



<p>As for trading, Binance offers seven trade orders of Limit order, Market order, stop limit order, stop market order, Trailing stop order, Post only order and Limit TP/SL order. Despite the varying transaction fees for withdrawal based on the currency and its amount, there is no transaction fee for deposits.</p>



<p>Initially introduced as an ERC20 Ethereum based cryptocurrency in 2017, BNB has now moved on to Binance’s own blockchain named Binance chain. As the native coin for Binance exchange, BNB was primarily a utility token to motivate users for transaction fee discounts. However, the applications for Binance coin have now expanded dramatically since you can now use Binance Coin for financial services, entertainment, online services and many more.</p>



<p>With all this development happening in a short time period, the 26,500% overall price increase (correct as of January 2022) since being introduced in 2017 is well justified. As of June 4th 2021 BNB has a market cap of $53.7 billion dollars and is only ranked behind Bitcoin and Ethereum.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange BNB to USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>At this point, it’s good to briefly introduce Tether. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange BNB to USDT</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Cardano on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your ADA to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-and-you-re-all-set"><strong>And You’re All Set!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bnb-to-usdt/">How to Exchange BNB to USDT [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bnb-to-usdt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Solana to Tether [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-solana-to-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-solana-to-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 07:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6403</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sure, you can exchange Solana to Tether on so many platforms, but CoinCannon is better! Solana (SOL) is one of the fastest blockchain networks out there. It offers lightning speed transaction speeds and super cheap transaction costs. With all that in mind, SOL has a loyal group of institutions using it for their global transactions. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-solana-to-tether/">How to Exchange Solana to Tether [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Sure, you can exchange Solana to Tether on so many platforms, but CoinCannon is better! Solana (SOL) is one of the fastest blockchain networks out there. It offers lightning speed transaction speeds and super cheap transaction costs. With all that in mind, SOL has a loyal group of institutions using it for their global transactions. Subsequently, Solana is one of the top cryptocurrencies by market cap. In this article, we will go over how to exchange Solana to Tether on CoinCannon platform. At CoinCannon, you can have the lowest exchange rates, full anonymity and 24/7 online support all together.</p>



<p>So head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Solana on the left box and Tether on the right and get started!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Solana to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive USDT. Most likely, your Solana wallet supports USDT, so you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Solana?</strong></h2>



<p>In short, Solana is a blockchain platform for decentralized applications (DApps). The network utilizes Proof of Stake consensus algorithm. However, in a world full of PoS blockchain networks, Solana has managed to achieve some impressive figures. The network can support up to 50,000 transactions per second (TPS) and requires 400 milliseconds to build a block. With the quickly increasing number of validators currently at 1,061, the network is one of the fastest out there.</p>



<p>Found in 2017 by Anatoly Yakovenko, a former Qualcomm member, along with Eric Williams and Greg Fitzgerald, the network aimed to create a more efficient and scalable platform.</p>



<p>The team consists of former members of companies such as Google, Apple, Microsoft, Qualcomm, Dropbox, Intel and more.</p>



<p>In that regard, the network is backed by many years of experience in some of the best companies around the world.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>    Continue reading “<a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-solana/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Solana</a>” to learn everything about the network.</p>
</blockquote>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Solana to Tether</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to exchange Solana to Tether USDT, let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Solana to Tether?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Solana on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your SOL to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-you-re-all-set"><strong>You’re All Set!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-solana-to-tether/">How to Exchange Solana to Tether [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-solana-to-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cardano-ada-to-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cardano-ada-to-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 08:39:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6393</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking for the best platform to exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether? CoinCannon is all you need. Cardano is one of the top cryptocurrencies by market cap and has a pretty strong community of investors. Today, it’s hard to find an online exchanger that doesn’t have ADA on their supported currency list. Despite that, it is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cardano-ada-to-tether/">Exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking for the best platform to exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether? CoinCannon is all you need. Cardano is one of the top cryptocurrencies by market cap and has a pretty strong community of investors. Today, it’s hard to find an online exchanger that doesn’t have ADA on their supported currency list. Despite that, it is still difficult to find a platform that offers the lowest exchange rates and full anonymity. Fortunately, you can instantly exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether without compromising on anything! In this article, we will go over everything you need to know on how to convert ADA to USDT.</p>



<p>So, head over to <strong><a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a></strong>, choose Cardano (ADA) on the left field and Tether (USDT) on the right one and start your exchange.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive USDT. Most likely, your Cardano wallet supports USDT, so you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Cardano (ADA)?</strong></h2>



<p>The Cardano project launched in 2017. It was the third generation of blockchain networks. One that successfully dealt with some of the greatest challenges of previous generations. Issues such as high gas fees and scalability by introducing the Ouroboros, a proof of stake algorithm to mine blocks which will be further explained in the article.</p>



<p>In 2017, the Cardano project started as a third-gen open-source and public blockchain platform. ADA is the native token of the platform. It is Led by Charles Hoskinson, one of the co-founders of Ethereum. Cardano had a great emphasis on being future-proof by being peer-reviewed and methodically developed by academic experts in the field. Cardano views itself as the updated version of Ethereum. Moving towards building a connected and decentralized system and providing banking services to the unbanked.</p>



<p>ADA is the native token of the network. Currently, ADA stands in 7th place in the ranks with a market cap of 13.5 billion USD.</p>



<p>To learn everything about Cardano and ADA continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-ada-a-guide-to-the-cardano-project/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is ADA?</a>”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether (USDT)?</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT, let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon for the Win!</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Cardano on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your ADA to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-all-good"><strong>All Good!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cardano-ada-to-tether/">Exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cardano-ada-to-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT Instantly</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether-usdt/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether-usdt/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 07:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6386</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>CoinCannon is the ultimate platform to exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT instantly! Exchanging crypto assets into one another is a seemingly simple task. However, finding a platform that offers the best exchange rates and anonymity at the same time is no easy feat. With all the strict user verification out there, user privacy is slowly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether-usdt/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT Instantly&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>CoinCannon is the ultimate platform to exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT instantly! Exchanging crypto assets into one another is a seemingly simple task. However, finding a platform that offers the best exchange rates and anonymity at the same time is no easy feat. With all the strict user verification out there, user privacy is slowly losing its value. Fortunately, our platform provides a hassle-free KYC process that speeds up your exchange process and massively improves security. On top of that, we offer 24/7 online support to ensure the utmost reliability for our customers. In this article, we will go over everything you need to know on how to exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT on CoinCannon.</p>



<p>So get started, head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Ethereum ETH on the left box, and Tether USDT on the right one and you’re good to go!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-paypal-2/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Ethereum to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-do-i-need-to-exchange-ethereum-to-tether-usdt"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive USDT. In case your Ether wallet supports ETH, you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-dai/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Ethereum (ETH)?</strong></h2>



<p>As an open-source decentralized blockchain platform, Ethereum is perhaps the most diverse and innovative one out there. In its essence, it is a decentralized public ledger for verifying and recording transactions. The Ethereum is considered as a second-gen blockchain platform, improving upon the high gas fees, scalability issues and high transactions fees of previous platforms. This open-source platform has no geographical restrictions and has always been the tip of the spear as far as innovation goes. Essential services such as Smart contracts, NFT`s and decentralized apps were first introduced on the Ethereum platform. As for the cherry on top, the native token of the Ethereum platform called Ether or ETH is second in terms of market value standing only behind Bitcoin.</p>



<p>With the Ethereum 2.0 launch in August 2022, the network totally switched to proof of stake. With that, Ethereum network will have much better scalability and very low gas fees. On top of that, all the criticism regarding energy consumption will go away. Many consider the 2.0 upgrade as a great investment opportunity since ETH is very much likely to have a rally. Nonetheless, Ethereum is the second most popular cryptocurrency in the world for good reason. Their team has always been on the forefront of innovation which could potentially attract capital and provide great returns.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT, let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Ethereum on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your Ethereum to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether-usdt/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT Instantly&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether-usdt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Bitcoin with Dai [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 10:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6379</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you are looking to buy Bitcoin with Dai, CoinCannon is the ultimate platform for the job. Bitcoin has finally managed to bounce back and move above the critical resistance level at $25k. Subsequently, investors are once again eager to invest in the top crypto asset by market cap. On top of that, the mass [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Buy Bitcoin with Dai [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you are looking to buy Bitcoin with Dai, CoinCannon is the ultimate platform for the job. Bitcoin has finally managed to bounce back and move above the critical resistance level at $25k. Subsequently, investors are once again eager to invest in the top crypto asset by market cap. On top of that, the mass adoption of BTC has turned it into a utilitarian digital asset. Today, thousands of credible online stores accept Bitcoin as payment. Fortunately, you can now pay for goods and services via BTC and there’s lots of stuff you can <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-with-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">buy with Bitcoin</a>. However, if you’re holding DAI, you can instantly exchange Dai into Bitcoin in only a matter of minutes. Want to get started? Head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Dai on the left box and Bitcoin on the right and you’re good to go!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/">How to exchange cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Bitcoin with Dai?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive Bitcoin (BTC). In case your Dai wallet supports BTC, you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is DAI?</strong></h2>



<p>Before we go over how to buy Bitcoin with Dai, let’s take a brief look at Dai as a stablecoin.</p>



<p>DAI is an Ethereum-based stablecoin. A stablecoin is a cryptocurrency with a pegged value to another currency. In case of DAI, it is pegged to the US dollar and much like Tether and USDC, Dai will always be worth $1. Stablecoins are a crucial part of the crypto market as they offer very little volatility. In that regard, investors use stablecoins to save their funds in the form of a reliable and stable asset.</p>



<p>What makes DAI unique is a clever design that eliminates the biggest concerns for stablecoins. Generally speaking, conventional stablecoins require a massive reserve by the company. For example, for every Tether USD, the Tether company must hold $1 USD in their reserve. This is a huge issue for companies as it is difficult to provide liquidity and keep it consistent.</p>



<p>DAI offers a new solution for this problem. By using an automated system of smart contracts on Ethereum blockchain, DAI does now need a reserve. Using collateralized debt denominated in ETH allows DAI to maintain the 1:1 ration with USD. Simply speaking, users can deposit Ethereum or other cryptocurrencies can borrow against the value of their deposit and generate new DAI. The currency is this case is known as collateral.</p>



<p>You can <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange Dai to PayPal</a> on CoinCannon with the lowest exchange fees ever!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Invest in Bitcoin?</strong></h2>



<p>Well, there is hardly anyone these days who is not familiar with the definition of Bitcoin and what the cryptocurrency is capable of carrying out. However, let’s briefly go through what bitcoin is and where it comes from, then we can focus on the benefits of using this cryptocurrency and explain why to buy Bitcoin with Perfect Money.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a Cryptocurrency that was created after the housing market collapse in January 2009. It follows the ideas set out by the enigmatic and pseudonymous Satoshi Nakamoto in a whitepaper. The identity of the individual or individuals who developed this cryptocurrency is still under wraps. Unlike government-issued currencies, Bitcoin provides the guarantee of lower transaction costs than conventional online payment systems and is regulated by a decentralized authority.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a tempting opportunity for investment and great tool for doing financial transactions. In that regard, it has been a solid choice for investment as an asset that is truly decentralized. On top of that, there are countless online platform that accept Bitcoin as payment which makes BTC a utilitarian option for online payments.</p>



<p>So, if You’ve decided to invest in BTC, you can buy Bitcoin with Dai in only a matter of minutes on CoinCannon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-buy-bitcoin-with-dai"><strong>How to Buy Bitcoin with DAI?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Dai (DAI) on the left field and Bitcoin (BTC) on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your BTC wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your DAI to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>You’re All Set!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Bitcoin (BTC) to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Buy Bitcoin with Dai [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Tron with Tether USDT [Instant]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tron-with-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tron-with-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 08:42:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tron (TRX)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6373</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking to buy Tron with Tether? Look no further than CoinCannon. Generally speaking, buying cryptocurrencies and exchanging them into one another is an easy task. However, most exchange platforms tend to compromise on security or offer high exchange rates. With that, it can be difficult to find an online exchange platform that offers everything you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tron-with-tether/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Buy Tron with Tether USDT [Instant]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking to buy Tron with Tether? Look no further than CoinCannon. Generally speaking, buying cryptocurrencies and exchanging them into one another is an easy task. However, most exchange platforms tend to compromise on security or offer high exchange rates. With that, it can be difficult to find an online exchange platform that offers everything you need. Subsequently, CoinCannon provides unparalleled anonymity all while charging no hidden fees on your transaction. With all that, you can easily Buy Tron with Tether (USD) in only a matter of minutes. So head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Tether USDT on the left field, and Tron on the right and start the action!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Tron with Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive Tron (TRX). In case your USDT wallet supports Tether, you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Tron (TRX)?</strong></h2>



<p>Tron is a decentralized, blockchain-based platform that aims to build a free, global entertainment system for digital content with distributed storage technology and enables digital content to be shared easily and cost-effectively.</p>



<p>The TRON ecosystem basically acts as a platform for content-sharing. In this platform, TRX is the payment for users who create or post content, resulting in a fairer and more open monetization mechanism than those that control conventional social media networks. It also allows users to share their content without having to go through a middleman, such as the Google Play Store or Apple Store. This means that TRON is helping to push the decentralized application market (dApps).</p>



<p>Tron was founded by a non-profit organization based in Singapore called the Tron Foundation in September 2017. This foundation is led by Justin Sun, CEO, and benefits from a dedicated in-house development team that includes distinguished stalwarts in technology.</p>



<p>Tron attempts to CoinCannon the gap between content creators and content consumers by eliminating the middleman by using the features of the blockchain and peer-to-peer (P2P) network technology. The result is an overall cost reduction for the consumer and better collection for the content producer through direct receipts, which offers a win-win situation.</p>



<p>To learn everything about Tron (TRX) continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-tron-trx/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Tron?</a>”</p>



<p>If you are interested in investing in Tron (TRX), you can easily and instantly buy Tron with Tether (USDT) or a variety of other digital currencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Buy Tron with Tether (USDT)?</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to buy Tron (TRX) with Tether (USDT), let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon is the Best Exchange!</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Buy Tron with Tether (USDT)?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">Homepage</a> on CoinCannon. Select Tether USDT on the left field and Tron (TRX) on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your TRX wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your USDT to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-that-s-it"><strong>That’s It!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tron (TRX) to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tron-with-tether/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Buy Tron with Tether USDT [Instant]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tron-with-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Crypto to Tether USDT [Lowest Fees]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-to-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-to-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 07:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange crypto to tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5617</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Very often, you will have to exchange crypto to Tether USDT in order to avoid market volatility. As of 2022, Tether USDT is still the dominant stablecoin in the market and the top US dollar crypto equivalent. Whether you trade or hodl, Tether USDT is the ultimate mediator apparatus for everyone. However, although making the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-to-tether/">How to Exchange Crypto to Tether USDT [Lowest Fees]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Very often, you will have to exchange crypto to Tether USDT in order to avoid market volatility. As of 2022, Tether USDT is still the dominant stablecoin in the market and the top US dollar crypto equivalent. Whether you trade or hodl, Tether USDT is the ultimate mediator apparatus for everyone. However, although making the exchange is easy, it matters a lot which platform you choose to exchange crypto to Tether. For one, not all platforms offer the same exchange rates and you may have to pay more for the order. More importantly, anonymity is also a key feature user should keep in mind. For that, a reliable exchange platform like <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is absolutely necessary. In this article, we will go over how to exchange crypto to Tether and why CoinCannon is the best platform to do the job.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/how-exchange-tether-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How To Exchange Tether USDT To PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Crypto to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>Generally speaking, exchanging assets to Tether is for times when you want to pay less commission and be ready for the next purchase. When you <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange cryptocurrency to PayPal</a>, the cost for the exchange is considerably higher and it takes a longer time to have the assets in your account. On top of that, the next time you want to buy cryptocurrencies, you will once again have to pay high commission and wait longer. With Tether, the transactions are almost immediate and have a very low cost of transaction.</p>



<p>Comparatively, Tether is good for those who are actively monitoring the market to make their next move. Thankfully, numerous Forex platforms also accept Tether as payment so it has even more utility. On the other hand, PayPal is generally a safer method to store assets with much more regulations. Naturally, it is good for those looking for better security and purchasing options.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Tether (USDT)?</strong></h2>



<p>&nbsp;Before reading about how to exchange crypto to Tether (USDT), let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Crypto to Tether on CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p>very exchange platform must maintain three important characteristics. Anonymity, affordability and reliability. We pride ourselves as a professional platform that offers all three.</p>



<p>For anonymity, CoinCannon requires no KYC or even a sign up process. The best way to protect your information is to not share them with anyone. And for that, we respect our customers and do not ask for their personal info.</p>



<p>As for affordability, CoinCannon utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. By doing so, we have managed to stay on top of the ranks on websites such as Bestchange and OkChanger.</p>



<p>Lastly, reliability is ensured for our customers with 24/7 online support. In case anything goes wrong, you will have our immediate support until the issue is resolved.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Crypto to Tether (USDT) on CoinCannon</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the homepage first, then select the cryptocurrency you want on the left field and Tether TRC20 or ERC20 on the right. Enter the amount you want to exchange and wait for the exchange rate to apply.</li>



<li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Tether wallet details, email, and phone number.</li>



<li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li>Complete the captcha and click on “exchange” to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. At this point, you will have the CoinCannon wallet address to send the cryptocurrency to. &nbsp;After you have transferred your cryptocurrency, click on Pay Order button. Don’t forget to attach the screenshot for the payment. your order will process swiftly.</li>



<li>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the Tether to your wallet ASAP.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>And Done!</strong></h2>



<p>Usually, Tether payments are very quick to go through. For that, give it a few minutes and you will have the USDT in your wallet. In the meantime, you can follow up on your order using the Track ID provided for you. Simply enter the track id in the required section on homepage to see at which point your order is. Remember not to share your Track ID with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-to-tether/">How to Exchange Crypto to Tether USDT [Lowest Fees]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-to-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Bitcoin with Tether (USDT) [Video]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 08:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Videos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6332</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Here is a full guide on how to buy Bitcoin with Tether on CoinCannon platform with a whole slew of unique benefits. Perhaps, to exchange Tether to Bitcoin can be the most popular exchange direction in crypto market. Both being the first of their kind, both BTC and USDT remain the king of the category. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-tether/">How to Buy Bitcoin with Tether (USDT) [Video]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Here is a full guide on how to buy Bitcoin with Tether on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">HiEx</a><a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">c</a><a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">hange</a> platform with a whole slew of unique benefits. Perhaps, to exchange Tether to Bitcoin can be the most popular exchange direction in crypto market. Both being the first of their kind, both BTC and USDT remain the king of the category. With that, everyone will need a great platform like CoinCannon to buy Bitcoin with Tether without any compromise. Subsequently, we will go over how easy it is to do that in only a matter of few minutes.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/how-exchange-bitcoin-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Bitcoin to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="Exchange Tether to Bitcoin   Buy BTC with USDT" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xh0FlrOrGnw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Bitcoin with Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive Bitcoin that is reliable and secure. Although there are thousands of options at this moment, we advise you to pay extra attention when choosing a Bitcoin wallet. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon. Want a good reason why? How about winning $100 ever month!</p>



<p>Learn more about our <a href="https://hi.exchange/campaign/tether-giveaway" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Tether Giveaway</a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Bitcoin (BTC)?</strong></h2>



<p>Well, there is hardly anyone these days who is not familiar with the definition of Bitcoin and what the cryptocurrency is capable of carrying out. However, let’s briefly go through what bitcoin is and where it comes from, then we can focus on the benefits of using this cryptocurrency and explain why to buy Bitcoin with Perfect Money.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a Cryptocurrency that was created after the housing market collapse in January 2009. It follows the ideas set out by the enigmatic and pseudonymous Satoshi Nakamoto in a whitepaper. The identity of the individual or individuals who developed this cryptocurrency is still under wraps. Unlike government-issued currencies, Bitcoin provides the guarantee of lower transaction costs than conventional online payment systems and is regulated by a decentralized authority.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a tempting opportunity for investment and great tool for doing financial transactions. Everything is in favor of exchanging your Perfect Money for some BTC when possible.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Pay with Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>Owning Tether is basically like having digital dollars in your pocket, only without needing a bank. Recently, there has been lots of talk about how we do not actually own our money when they are in the banks. Digital money means that banks and governments can freeze our access to our funds for whatever reason they seem justifiable. In 2022, Canada denied protestor’s access to their bank accounts and cut out their rightful ownership of their capital. Such incidents are not rare and should be treated seriously. But, political motivation aside, banks are not always available. For example, we saw how the Ukrainians lost all their capital within the banks as soon as the war started. Once again, the decentralized nature of cryptocurrencies meant that the bankless were the lucky ones in that incident.</p>



<p>Thankfully, the list of online merchants and service providers who accept Tether USDT is sufficiently long. With Tether, you can make purchases online and in person almost anywhere. Be it through a direct wallet address or a payment gateway, USDT is as good as cash these days.</p>



<p>Lastly, USDT offers an extra layer of protection for the user with blockchain technology. As a cryptocurrency, it is anonymous and secure. On top of that, the transaction fees for Tether are very low, as long as you use the TRC20 variant based on the Tron network.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon FTW!</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Buy Bitcoin with Tether?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Tether on the left field and Bitcoin on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your Bitcoin wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your Tether (USDT) to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-easy-as-that"><strong>Easy as That!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the BTC to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-tether/">How to Buy Bitcoin with Tether (USDT) [Video]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Buy Tether USDT with Lowest Possible Fees on CoinCannon</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-usdt/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-usdt/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 08:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy USDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5640</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Whether you’re a trader or an avid investor, there are solid reasons to buy Tether USDT. As of 2023, USDT has a lot more utility than what it had only a few years ago. Basically, the dollar-pegged cryptocurrency is accepted in a wide variety of online platforms for shopping and services. Today, you can pay [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-usdt/">Buy Tether USDT with Lowest Possible Fees on CoinCannon</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Whether you’re a trader or an avid investor, there are solid reasons to buy Tether USDT. As of 2023, USDT has a lot more utility than what it had only a few years ago. Basically, the dollar-pegged cryptocurrency is accepted in a wide variety of online platforms for shopping and services. Today, you can pay for almost anything from flight bookings to a Cappuccino with Tether. On the other hand, Forex traders have also been using Tether as a medium on their traders. However, if you are looking to Buy Tether USDT, not all exchanges are equal! For that, you will need an exchange platform that offers the best exchange rates. And more importantly, a platform who doesn’t sell you private data to the highest bidder! Fortunately, <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is the ultimate OTC platform to buy Tether USDT from and this article will tell you why.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Learn <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-crypto-to-tether/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Crypto to Tether</a> on CoinCannon</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-tether-usdt"><strong>What is Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to buy Tether USDT, let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>Learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/how-exchange-tether-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange Tether USDT to PayPal</a></p>
</blockquote>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-should-i-buy-tether-usdt"><strong>Why Should I Buy Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>Owning Tether is basically like having digital dollars in your pocket, only without needing a bank. Recently, there has been lots of talk about how we do not actually own our money when they are in the banks. Digital money means that banks and governments can freeze our access to our funds for whatever reason they seem justifiable. In 2022, Canada denied protestor’s access to their bank accounts and cut out their rightful ownership of their capital. Such incidents are not rare and should be treated seriously. But, political motivation aside, banks are not always available. For example, we saw how the Ukrainians lost all their capital within the banks as soon as the war started. Once again, the decentralized nature of cryptocurrencies meant that the bankless were the lucky ones in that incident.</p>



<p>Thankfully, the list of online merchants and service providers who accept Tether USDT is sufficiently long. With Tether, you can make purchases online and in person almost anywhere. Be it through a direct wallet address or a payment gateway, USDT is as good as cash these days.</p>



<p>Lastly, USDT offers an extra layer of protection for the user with blockchain technology. As a cryptocurrency, it is anonymous and secure. On top of that, the transaction fees for Tether are very low, as long as you use the TRC20 variant based on the Tron network.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-where-do-i-buy-usdt"><strong>Where Do I Buy USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>Every exchange platform must maintain three important characteristics. Anonymity, affordability and reliability. We pride ourselves as a professional platform that offers all three.</p>



<p>For anonymity, <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> requires no KYC or even a sign up process. The best way to protect your information is to not share them with anyone. And for that, we respect our customers and do not ask for their personal info.</p>



<p>As for affordability, CoinCannon utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. By doing so, we have managed to stay on top of the ranks on websites such as Bestchange and OkChanger.</p>



<p>Lastly, reliability is ensured for our customers with 24/7 online support. In case anything goes wrong, you will have our immediate support until the issue is resolved.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-is-tether-a-safe-investment"><strong>Is Tether a Safe Investment?</strong></h2>



<p>Generally speaking, Tether has remained reliable and solid since the initial introduction. While there are numerous controversies, USDT has been consistently stern as an investment option. Most of the controversies come from a lack of transparency regarding Tether’s funds. Basically, there is not much information about what funds are actually held by Tether to back their stablecoin. However, Tether has assured investors that they hold the majority of their funds in the form of cash and investors have no reason to worry.</p>



<p>Regardless, there is still some risk associated with stablecoins, especially after the Terra USD collapse. With that, while there is no clear and imminent risk, make sure to thread carefully and keep some of the risks in mind before you buy Tether USDT.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-usdt/">Buy Tether USDT with Lowest Possible Fees on CoinCannon</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-usdt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Ethereum to DAI [No Fees]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-dai/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-dai/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 07:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6315</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you’re looking to exchange Ethereum to DAI, CoinCannon is all you need! Volatile assets such as ETH and BTC will definitely have some risks associated with them. However, investors can easily convert them into stablecoins to stop the loss at a certain period of time. Thankfully, exchanging crypto assets into one another does not [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-dai/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange Ethereum to DAI [No Fees]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you’re looking to exchange Ethereum to DAI, <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is all you need! Volatile assets such as ETH and BTC will definitely have some risks associated with them. However, investors can easily convert them into stablecoins to stop the loss at a certain period of time. Thankfully, exchanging crypto assets into one another does not have massive fees so it’s a pretty safe bet. As far as stablecoins go, DAI has been a top choice for crypto enthusiasts as it is perhaps very different than the others. In this article, we will go over everything you need to know on how to exchange Ethereum to DAI on CoinCannon platform.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Ethereum to DAI?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive DAI. In case your Ether wallet supports DAI, you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Ethereum?</strong></h2>



<p>As an open-source decentralized blockchain platform, Ethereum is perhaps the most diverse and innovative one out there. In its essence, it is a decentralized public ledger for verifying and recording transactions. The Ethereum is considered as a second-gen blockchain platform, improving upon the high gas fees, scalability issues and high transactions fees of previous platforms. This open-source platform has no geographical restrictions and has always been the tip of the spear as far as innovation goes. Essential services such as Smart contracts, NFT`s and decentralized apps were first introduced on the Ethereum platform. As for the cherry on top, the native token of the Ethereum platform called Ether or ETH is second in terms of market value standing only behind Bitcoin.</p>



<p>With the <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/ethereum-2-0-upgrade-date/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Ethereum 2.0</a> launch in August 2022, the network totally switched to proof of stake. With that, Ethereum network will have much better scalability and very low gas fees. On top of that, all the criticism regarding energy consumption will go away. Many consider the 2.0 upgrade as a great investment opportunity since ETH is very much likely to have a rally. Nonetheless, Ethereum is the second most popular cryptocurrency in the world for good reason. Their team has always been on the forefront of innovation which could potentially attract capital and provide great returns.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Ethereum to DAI?</strong></h2>



<p>DAI is an Ethereum-based stablecoin. A stablecoin is a cryptocurrency with a pegged value to another currency. In case of DAI, it is pegged to the US dollar and much like Tether and USDC, Dai will always be worth $1. Stablecoins are a crucial part of the crypto market as they offer very little volatility. In that regard, investors use stablecoins to save their funds in the form of a reliable and stable asset.</p>



<p>What makes DAI unique is a clever design that eliminates the biggest concerns for stablecoins. Generally speaking, conventional stablecoins require a massive reserve by the company. For example, for every Tether USD, the Tether company must hold $1 USD in their reserve. This is a huge issue for companies as it is difficult to provide liquidity and keep it consistent.</p>



<p>DAI offers a new solution for this problem. By using an automated system of smart contracts on Ethereum blockchain, DAI does now need a reserve. Using collateralized debt denominated in ETH allows DAI to maintain the 1:1 ration with USD. Simply speaking, users can deposit Ethereum or other cryptocurrencies can borrow against the value of their deposit and generate new DAI. The currency is this case is known as collateral.</p>



<p>Currently, DAI has a market cap of over $5 billion and is ranked as 17th cryptocurrency.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Ethereum to DAI</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Ethereum on the left field and DAI on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your DAI wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your Ethereum to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-that-s-it"><strong>That’s it!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the DAI to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-dai/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange Ethereum to DAI [No Fees]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-dai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
