<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>exchange crypto Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/exchange-crypto/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 09:05:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Crypto to Tether USDT [Lowest Fees]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-to-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-to-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 07:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange crypto to tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5617</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Very often, you will have to exchange crypto to Tether USDT in order to avoid market volatility. As of 2022, Tether USDT is still the dominant stablecoin in the market and the top US dollar crypto equivalent. Whether you trade or hodl, Tether USDT is the ultimate mediator apparatus for everyone. However, although making the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-to-tether/">How to Exchange Crypto to Tether USDT [Lowest Fees]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Very often, you will have to exchange crypto to Tether USDT in order to avoid market volatility. As of 2022, Tether USDT is still the dominant stablecoin in the market and the top US dollar crypto equivalent. Whether you trade or hodl, Tether USDT is the ultimate mediator apparatus for everyone. However, although making the exchange is easy, it matters a lot which platform you choose to exchange crypto to Tether. For one, not all platforms offer the same exchange rates and you may have to pay more for the order. More importantly, anonymity is also a key feature user should keep in mind. For that, a reliable exchange platform like <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is absolutely necessary. In this article, we will go over how to exchange crypto to Tether and why CoinCannon is the best platform to do the job.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/how-exchange-tether-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How To Exchange Tether USDT To PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Crypto to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>Generally speaking, exchanging assets to Tether is for times when you want to pay less commission and be ready for the next purchase. When you <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange cryptocurrency to PayPal</a>, the cost for the exchange is considerably higher and it takes a longer time to have the assets in your account. On top of that, the next time you want to buy cryptocurrencies, you will once again have to pay high commission and wait longer. With Tether, the transactions are almost immediate and have a very low cost of transaction.</p>



<p>Comparatively, Tether is good for those who are actively monitoring the market to make their next move. Thankfully, numerous Forex platforms also accept Tether as payment so it has even more utility. On the other hand, PayPal is generally a safer method to store assets with much more regulations. Naturally, it is good for those looking for better security and purchasing options.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Tether (USDT)?</strong></h2>



<p>&nbsp;Before reading about how to exchange crypto to Tether (USDT), let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Crypto to Tether on CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p>very exchange platform must maintain three important characteristics. Anonymity, affordability and reliability. We pride ourselves as a professional platform that offers all three.</p>



<p>For anonymity, CoinCannon requires no KYC or even a sign up process. The best way to protect your information is to not share them with anyone. And for that, we respect our customers and do not ask for their personal info.</p>



<p>As for affordability, CoinCannon utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. By doing so, we have managed to stay on top of the ranks on websites such as Bestchange and OkChanger.</p>



<p>Lastly, reliability is ensured for our customers with 24/7 online support. In case anything goes wrong, you will have our immediate support until the issue is resolved.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Crypto to Tether (USDT) on CoinCannon</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the homepage first, then select the cryptocurrency you want on the left field and Tether TRC20 or ERC20 on the right. Enter the amount you want to exchange and wait for the exchange rate to apply.</li>



<li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Tether wallet details, email, and phone number.</li>



<li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li>Complete the captcha and click on “exchange” to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. At this point, you will have the CoinCannon wallet address to send the cryptocurrency to. &nbsp;After you have transferred your cryptocurrency, click on Pay Order button. Don’t forget to attach the screenshot for the payment. your order will process swiftly.</li>



<li>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the Tether to your wallet ASAP.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>And Done!</strong></h2>



<p>Usually, Tether payments are very quick to go through. For that, give it a few minutes and you will have the USDT in your wallet. In the meantime, you can follow up on your order using the Track ID provided for you. Simply enter the track id in the required section on homepage to see at which point your order is. Remember not to share your Track ID with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-to-tether/">How to Exchange Crypto to Tether USDT [Lowest Fees]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-to-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Ethereum to PayPal [Video Guide]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-paypal-2/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-paypal-2/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 05:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Videos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6003</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>On CoinCannon platform, you can exchange Ethereum to PayPal with ultimate anonymity. Finally, as of September 2022, Ethereum has officially moved on to Proof of Stake. Generally speaking, we saw no massive movement in price and one could call it anticlimactic. However, the Ethereum merge will payoff big time in the future when upcoming regulations [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-paypal-2/">How to Exchange Ethereum to PayPal [Video Guide]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>On <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> platform, you can exchange Ethereum to PayPal with ultimate anonymity. Finally, as of September 2022, Ethereum has officially moved on to Proof of Stake. Generally speaking, we saw no massive movement in price and one could call it anticlimactic. However, the <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/ethereum-merge/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Ethereum merge</a> will payoff big time in the future when upcoming regulations arrive. With that, ETH will be on the winning side of cryptocurrencies with a green and Eco-friendly smile. Until then, you can exchange Ethereum to PayPal on CoinCannon platform with no added fees. On top of that, all transaction will have 24/7 online support. Here is everything you need to know on how to cash out Ethereum.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="How to Exchange Ethereum to PayPal on CoinCannon [No KYC]" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/l5ykmDjJFOY?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Ethereum to PayPal?</strong></h2>



<p>For this transaction, you send Ethereum from your wallet and receive PayPal USD on your account. Naturally, you will need a verified and active PayPal account to receive the funds. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon. Want a good reason why? How about winning $100 ever month!</p>



<p>Learn more about our <a href="https://hi.exchange/campaign/tether-giveaway" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Tether Giveaway</a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Ethereum?</strong></h2>



<p>Ethereum, launched in 2015, is a blockchain-based, decentralized, and open-source software platform that is employed for Ether, its own dedicated cryptocurrency. Ethereum allows Smart Contracts and Distributed Applications to be developed and operate without any downtime, fraud, control, or intrusion from a third party.</p>



<p>Ethereum is not only a platform but also a programming language (Turing complete) operating on a blockchain, assisting developers in developing and publishing distributed applications.</p>



<p>Ethereum (ETH), the Ethereum network’s cryptocurrency, is probably the second most popular digital token after Bitcoin (BTC). Indeed, as the second largest cryptocurrency by market cap, comparison between Ether and BTC is only natural.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>PayPal is King for a Reason!</strong></h2>



<p>PayPal is an online trade company that, through online transfers, facilitates payments between parties. Its system allows clients to set up an account on its platform that is linked to the user’s credit card or checking account. Upon confirmation of identification and proof of funds, through the website or application of the company, users can begin sending or receiving payments online to and from other PayPal accounts.</p>



<p>As mentioned above, in order to transfer money to others using the receiver’s email address or mobile phone number, PayPal account holders can use the website or mobile application of the company. Within only a matter of minutes, transactions go through and the company promises that transfers are immediately available for payment or withdrawal to a bank account.</p>



<p>The ease of use and the wide acceptance makes the exchange cryptocurrencies to PayPal one of the best options when you need some cash to spend online.</p>



<p>All that said, you also have the ability to exchange ETH to Perfect Money USD or Tether USD.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Of course, in order to exchange Ethereum to PayPal, you will first need a reliable exchange platform. For that, CoinCannon is one of the best options out there.</p>



<p>Every exchange platform must maintain three important characteristics. Anonymity, affordability and reliability. We pride ourselves as a professional platform that offers all three.</p>



<p>For anonymity, CoinCannon requires no KYC or even a sign up process. The best way to protect your information is to not share them with anyone. And for that, we respect our customers and do not ask for their personal info.</p>



<p>As for affordability, CoinCannon utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. By doing so, we have managed to stay on top of the ranks on websites such as Bestchange and OkChanger.</p>



<p>Lastly, reliability is ensured for our customers with 24/7 online support. In case anything goes wrong, you will have our immediate support until the issue is resolved.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Ethereum to PayPal</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Ethereum (ETH) on the left field and PayPal on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li><li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your PayPal account details, email, and phone number.</li><li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li><li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li><li>On this step, please spend the time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li><li>Transfer your ETH to the CoinCannon Skrill address that is provided for you.</li><li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>Just like that, you have now exchanged Ethereum (ETH) to PayPal. In general, PayPal payments are inconsistent in terms of how long they might take. Give it a few minutes and the PayPal USD will be in your account ASAP. In the meantime, you can follow up on your order using the Track ID provided for you. Simply enter the track id in the required section on homepage to see at which point your order is. Remember not to share your Track ID with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-paypal-2/">How to Exchange Ethereum to PayPal [Video Guide]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-paypal-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PayPal Vs. Perfect Money, Exchange Crypto the Right Way</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-the-right-way/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-the-right-way/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 08:19:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perfect Money]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5585</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When you are done hodling, comes the time to exchange crypto and cash out your profit. But, with so many options around, users may face some confusion as to what they should do. Essentially, both PayPal and Perfect Money are very practical payment systems but depending on the use case, they have some fundamental differences. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-the-right-way/">PayPal Vs. Perfect Money, Exchange Crypto the Right Way</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>When you are done hodling, comes the time to exchange crypto and cash out your profit. But, with so many options around, users may face some confusion as to what they should do. Essentially, both PayPal and Perfect Money are very practical payment systems but depending on the use case, they have some fundamental differences. As an exchange platform, we offer both solutions but here is our guide as to which one is better for you to exchange crypto.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Crypto to PayPal</strong></h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="840" height="400" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Make-PayPal-Payments-in-Russia-No-Commission.jpg" alt="exchange crypto" class="wp-image-5104" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Make-PayPal-Payments-in-Russia-No-Commission.jpg 840w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Make-PayPal-Payments-in-Russia-No-Commission-300x143.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Make-PayPal-Payments-in-Russia-No-Commission-768x366.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 840px) 100vw, 840px" /></figure>



<p>PayPal is a digital payment service that can be used by customers while they shop online. The platform stores payment information, such as bank account or credit card numbers, so that every time they buy something, customers do not have to type the numbers out. Also, it hides from companies this financial information, adding a layer of security to online shopping. PayPal payments can be incorporated into online checkout process by small companies and similarly by large corporations.</p>



<p>Now, while PayPal does not offer lots of anonymity, they are the top secure payment system by a mile. Considering the huge amount of regulations as well as the largest user base in the world, PayPal keeps it safe. Thankfully, transactions are reversible and the quality of service remains the benchmark in the industry.</p>



<p>Distinguishably, PayPal has so many hassles and requirements, but your assets are very safe. For that, you will face many restrictions on buying cryptocurrencies the next time yet the security is worth it.</p>



<p>So, if you want to cash out for a long time and want your assets available on various platforms, PayPal is the way to go.</p>



<p>Learn how you can <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/how-exchange-bitcoin-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Bitcoin to PayPal</a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Crypto to Perfect Money</strong></h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="840" height="400" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/How-to-Exchange-Perfect-Money-to-PayPal-Lowest-Fees.jpg" alt="exchange crypto" class="wp-image-4698" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/How-to-Exchange-Perfect-Money-to-PayPal-Lowest-Fees.jpg 840w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/How-to-Exchange-Perfect-Money-to-PayPal-Lowest-Fees-300x143.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/How-to-Exchange-Perfect-Money-to-PayPal-Lowest-Fees-768x366.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 840px) 100vw, 840px" /></figure>



<p>On the other hand, Perfect Money is all about lesser regulations and lesser hassle. With PM, what you get is a lot more financial freedom and privacy all while your assets are available to you as the owner at all times. Unfortunately, most people think of Perfect Money as a gray area for payment systems that is sketchy. However, PM has been around for years and for what is worth, it is actually very much reliable.</p>



<p>Sadly, in this day and age, we do not actually own our money since it’s not in our pockets. Instead, we have to trust digital networks to hold them for us and hopefully let us have it when we want them. While we praise PayPal for the security, they tend to passive-aggressively restrict our financial activities with thousands of regulations and requirements. For example, there are numerous constraints on buying cryptocurrencies with PayPal all in the name of regulations.</p>



<p>And this, is where Perfect Money shines. PM allows the user to buy and exchange crypto on platforms like <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> in full privacy.</p>



<p>Continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/guide-to-exchange-perfect-money/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Perfect Money</a>”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Verdict</strong></h2>



<p>In this case, it’s actually very simple to pick one. If you’re looking to store your assets for a long time, go with PayPal. PayPal offers the highest security of funds but also suffers from a vast variety of regulations. In that regard, it would be more difficult to buy cryptocurrencies the next time with PayPal. Conversely, if you want to get back in the market quick, exchange crypto to Perfect Money. Despite the reputation, PM has consistently remained as a reliable payment system. On top of that, the financial liberty is a rare gem these days and Perfect Money knows it!</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-the-right-way/">PayPal Vs. Perfect Money, Exchange Crypto the Right Way</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-the-right-way/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
