<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>PayPal Invoice Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/paypal-invoice/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 09:05:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Make PayPal Payment Without a PayPal Account [Video]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-payment/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-payment/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 06:42:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Essentials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Videos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payment Service]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal Invoice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal Payment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5123</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>These days, PayPal Payment is a dominant method of transaction on the internet. A vast majority of online platforms support PayPal as payment method for their goods and services. However, that doesn’t mean that everyone gets equal access to PayPal payment services. Unfortunately, many countries do not have access to PayPal services and subsequently face [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-payment/">Make PayPal Payment Without a PayPal Account [Video]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>These days, PayPal Payment is a dominant method of transaction on the internet. A vast majority of online platforms support PayPal as payment method for their goods and services. However, that doesn’t mean that everyone gets equal access to PayPal payment services. Unfortunately, many countries do not have access to PayPal services and subsequently face payment issues. Furthermore, there are those who rarely need PayPal services and just don’t feel compelled to create an account. But, when the time comes, they might need to make a PayPal payment instantly. Fortunately, CoinCannon PayPal Invoice service is the perfect solution to all problems stated above. It offers multiple benefits and does not cost extra commission. Stay with us as we go over everything to know about our PayPal invoice service.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="How to Make PayPal Payments without a PayPal Account" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Yy3JjVEEHHI?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Make PayPal Payment Without a PayPal Account on<br><a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Can I Make PayPal Payment Without an Account?</strong></h2>



<p>Yes, you don’t necessarily need an official PayPal account in order to make a payment. In order to do this, you will need an exchange platform to make the payment for you. This service is specifically designed for those who do not have access to a PayPal account at the moment. This could be caused by a suspended account for short-term or sanctions imposed on a country which would suspend all PayPal services indefinitely. In any case, you can use the PayPal invoice service to make the PayPal payment instantly.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Does It Better</strong></h2>



<p>However, using the PayPal invoice service is only a good solution as long as you utilize a good exchange platform. Since this is a unique service, the exchangers might take a lot more commission for it as compared with a regular exchange operation. On the other hand, since you are making a purchase, the exchanger will know exactly what you purchased and how much you paid for it. Hence, your anonymity is compromised.</p>



<p>Thankfully, CoinCannon comes to the rescue! CoinCannon does not have any extra commission for the PayPal Payment and the commission rate remains the same as a regular PayPal exchange. Which means, you get to enjoy very low exchange commission with your payment.</p>



<p>In terms of privacy and anonymity, CoinCannon does not require KYC or even Sign Up. Therefore, you do not disclose any personal information with the platform.</p>



<p>Lastly, we offer 24/7 online support. So, in case you have any questions or issues, simply send us a message through the Live Chat section on the <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">main page</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Make a PayPal Payment?</strong></h2>



<p>In order to make PayPal payments without an account, you can use a crypto wallet and pay with Tether or Bitcoin, or a Perfect Money account. We will keep you updated upon adding other options for the payment. Make sure to visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a> regularly to stay up to date. But as a quick hint, there will be a lot more similar services available on CoinCannon very soon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Do I Have to Pay Commission?</strong></h2>



<p>No, there will be no extra commission or hidden exchange fees to use the PayPal Invoice service. The commission rate is the same as making a standard PayPal exchange on the platform which is already pretty low. Please bear in mind, making payments via Bitcoin will have a higher transaction fee due to Bitcoin network fees.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How Can I Make a PayPal Payment Without an Account?</strong></h2>



<p>In short, since you don’t have access to a PayPal account, you send your assets to CoinCannon and the platform will make the payment from its own PayPal account. Currently, we support Bitcoin, Tether TRC20 or Perfect Money USD. Following that, CoinCannon will receive your funds and make the PayPal payment on your behalf.</p>



<p>The process is very simple!</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Enter the CoinCannon Platform. Then, select either Perfect Money, Bitcoin or Tether TRC20 in the “I Give” section. After that, select PayPal USD (Invoice) from the “I Get” Section.</li><li>Type the Sending Amount for the payment. Then, wait until the rates automatically apply and see how much PayPal USD you will have for the payment. By the way, our exchange rates are awesome!</li><li>Click on Exchange and your will go to the second step. Add your invoice link (URL address) in the dedicated section. For example, if you’re buying a service online, add the link to the product page. Type your email address and the phone number section is optional. However, remember that there are many<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> benefits</a> for customers who sign up.</li><li>Review the exchange information carefully. Prove that you’re not a robot (nothing personal J) and click on “Exchange”</li><li>On the forth step, you receive your Track ID. You can see the order status. Click on “Pay Order”. If you make the payment via Perfect Money, you will be directed to the Perfect Money gateway. If you’re sending BTC or Tether, you will receive CoinCannon’s wallet address. At that point, make the payment and attach a screenshot of the payment in the dedicated section.</li><li>Kindly, agree to our terms and conditions and click on “Pay Order”.</li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>That’s It!</strong></h2>



<p>At this point, our team will process your order and make the PayPal payment. The process might take a short while. If you have any questions or issues, you can contact our online support team via the live chat section on the website. Our services expand by the hour! Make sure to visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a> for the latest announcements.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-payment/">Make PayPal Payment Without a PayPal Account [Video]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-payment/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You Don’t Need PayPal Account for PayPal Payments!</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/no-paypal-account-for-paypal-payments/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/no-paypal-account-for-paypal-payments/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 06:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal Account]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal Invoice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal Payments]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5632</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With over 370 million users, having a PayPal account is pretty important for everyone looking to make a purchase. Now, we all know how it is also bombarded with regulations and restrictions. Despite the popularity, PayPal is not available in some countries which raises a big issue. Currently, we need a PayPal account for so [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/no-paypal-account-for-paypal-payments/">You Don’t Need PayPal Account for PayPal Payments!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>With over 370 million users, having a PayPal account is pretty important for everyone looking to make a purchase. Now, we all know how it is also bombarded with regulations and restrictions. Despite the popularity, PayPal is not available in some countries which raises a big issue. Currently, we need a PayPal account for so many online services and products that are absolutely crucial to us. With the restrictions and sanctions, millions of people are left out in need of a reliable payment system. Fortunately, CoinCannon has got the best solution for all these problems. Enter, the PayPal Invoice service. An awesome solution to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/paypal-payment/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">make PayPal payments without a PayPal account</a>. Here are some common questions about PayPal Invoice service:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Learn How to Make <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/paypal-paymenst-in-russia/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">PayPal Payments in Russia</a></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I need to Make PayPal Payments Without PayPal Account?</strong></h2>



<p>Good news is, <strong>you do not need a PayPal account to make PayPal payments online</strong>. For the payment, you can pay with Perfect Money USD or Bitcoin. For that, you will need either a Perfect Money account or a crypto wallet.</p>



<p>As for CoinCannon, it is not mandatory to sign up on the platform or go through KYC. So, all you need is to make the payment via PM USD or BTC.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">No PayPal Account<strong>? No Problem!</strong></h2>



<p>Let’s say you want to buy something online like a gift card. You go to make the purchase and the only way you can pay for it is via PayPal. In the meantime, you don’t have a PayPal account.</p>



<p>At this point, you can head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a>, and select our PayPal Invoice service. Now, with this service, you share the purchase link with CoinCannon team. Then, we go to that website and make the PayPal payment on your behalf. To stick to the example, we buy the gift card you wanted for you. Following that, we send you the gift card to your email.</p>



<p>Using this service, users will not be stuck when they have to buy something with PayPal.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Can I Buy with PayPal Without a PayPal Account?</strong></h2>



<p>Almost everything! But, we recommend online services such as gift cards and accounts since you can immediately have your purchase via email. For example, if you buy a gift card, CoinCannon will send you the username and password in an email. Or, let’s say you want to pay for an application and buy a premium account, with PayPal Invoice, you will have the username and password for the account.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Information Should I Enter in PayPal Invoice?</strong></h2>



<p>Basically, you will need to enter everything required for the purchase. First and foremost, the link for the purchase is necessary. On top of that, you should share account information on the website you want to buy something. The information may include username and password for login on that website. So, keep in mind not to miss anything regarding the purchase on the website you have in mind. However, if you missed something or wanted to talk more about the purchase, contact our support team immediately via the Live Chat on the main page.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Does CoinCannon Hold My Information?</strong></h2>



<p>No, CoinCannon platform will not save neither use your information after the PayPal Invoice order. The data will be sent directly to your email address. Privacy and security are our utmost priority and we make sure to provide them for our customers.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Do I Need to Sign Up on CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p>It is not mandatory to sign up on CoinCannon. Furthermore, there is no KYC required. This is there to ensure anonymity and privacy for the user. The only thing you need is a verified email address and your wallet address. However, there are many benefits to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/paypal-paymenst-in-russia/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Sign Up on HiEcxhange</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>PayPal Invoice Fees</strong></h2>



<p>Fortunately, this service will not cost you any extra fees. The transaction fee for PayPal Invoice is as much as a normal PayPal transaction. In order to see how much you send and how much you receive, simply enter the amount in the exchange box and you will see the transaction fees immediately.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/no-paypal-account-for-paypal-payments/">You Don’t Need PayPal Account for PayPal Payments!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/no-paypal-account-for-paypal-payments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Make PayPal Payments in Russia [No Commission]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-paymenst-in-russia/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-paymenst-in-russia/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 10:43:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Essentials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal Invoice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal Payments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal Russia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Russia PayPal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5103</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you live in Russia or any other country in the world that does not currently have access to PayPal services, CoinCannon provides a perfect solution. Luckily, you can pay for goods and services on CoinCannon without needing a PayPal account. Simply, you can make PayPal payments in Russia using our PayPal Invoice service. This [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-paymenst-in-russia/">How to Make PayPal Payments in Russia [No Commission]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you live in Russia or any other country in the world that does not currently have access to PayPal services, CoinCannon provides a perfect solution. Luckily, you can pay for goods and services on CoinCannon without needing a PayPal account. Simply, you can make PayPal payments in Russia using our PayPal Invoice service. This service is easy, quick and carries no extra fees or commissions. Thankfully, you don’t have to worry about PayPal payments anymore.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><span class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> to make PayPal payments in Russia.</span></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>PayPal in Russia</strong></h2>



<p>Unfortunately, PayPal and other international payment methods have suspended all services in Russia. In the meantime, there are millions of people who are still in need of these services. Basically, numerous online goods and services require PayPal Payments and the suspended service can be harmful for the customers. In that regard, CoinCannon has provided you with the PayPal invoice service.</p>



<p>With this solution, you can instantly make PayPal payments in Russia without needing an account. But that’s not all! The good news is that your anonymity will also be intact. CoinCannon will not require KYC (Know Your Customer) or even Sing Up. So basically, just enter the platform and make the payment without disclosing your personal information.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Make PayPal Payments in Russia?</strong></h2>



<p>In order to make PayPal payments in Russia, you can use a crypto wallet and pay with Tether or Bitcoin, or a Perfect Money account. We will keep you updated upon adding other options for the payment. Make sure to visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a> regularly to stay up to date. But as a quick hint, there will be a lot more similar services available on CoinCannon very soon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Do I Have to Pay Commission?</strong></h2>



<p>No, there will be no extra commission or hidden exchange fees to make PayPal payments in Russia or any other country in the world. The commission rate is the same as making a standard PayPal exchange on the platform which is already pretty low. Please bear in mind, making payments via Bitcoin will have a higher transaction fee due to Bitcoin network fees.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How Do I Make PayPal Payments in Russia?</strong></h2>



<p>In short, since you don’t have access to a PayPal account, you send your assets to CoinCannon and the platform will make the payment from its own PayPal account. Currently, we support Bitcoin, Tether TRC20 or Perfect Money USD. Following that, CoinCannon will receive your funds and make the PayPal payment on your behalf.</p>



<p>The process is very simple!</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Enter the <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> Platform. Then, select either Perfect Money, Bitcoin or Tether TRC20 in the “I Give” section. After that, select PayPal USD (Invoice) from the “I Get” Section.</li><li>Type the Sending Amount for the payment. Then, wait until the rates automatically apply and see how much PayPal USD you will have for the payment. By the way, our exchange rates are awesome!</li><li>Click on Exchange and your will go to the second step. Add your invoice link (URL address) in the dedicated section. For example, if you’re buying a service online, add the link to the product page. Type your email address and the phone number section is optional. However, remember that there are many <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">benefits</a> for customers who sign up.</li><li>Review the exchange information carefully. Prove that you’re not a robot (nothing personal J) and click on “Exchange”</li><li>On the forth step, you receive your Track ID. You can see the order status. Click on “Pay Order”. If you make the payment via Perfect Money, you will be directed to the Perfect Money gateway. If you’re sending BTC or Tether, you will receive CoinCannon’s wallet address. At that point, make the payment and attach a screenshot of the payment in the dedicated section.</li><li>Kindly, agree to our terms and conditions and click on “Pay Order”.</li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>That’s It!</strong></h2>



<p>At this point, our team will process your order and make the PayPal payment. The process might take a short while. If you have any questions or issues, you can contact our online support team via the live chat section on the website. Our services expand by the hour! Make sure to visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a> for the latest announcements.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-paymenst-in-russia/">How to Make PayPal Payments in Russia [No Commission]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-paymenst-in-russia/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
