<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Essentials Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/category/essentials/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/category/essentials/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 09:05:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>CoinCannon Monthly Giveaway: Two $100 Prizes</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/jolixo-monthly-giveaway/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/jolixo-monthly-giveaway/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Essentials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[airdrop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[giveaway]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[monthly giveaway]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[prize]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5882</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From now on, you get to exchange money and win money thanks to CoinCannon monthly giveaway. The rules are super simple, make an order on CoinCannon, leave us a review and sign up to win $100. Every month, TWO lucky winners will take home their prize. With that, you help other CoinCannon customers by leaving [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/jolixo-monthly-giveaway/">CoinCannon Monthly Giveaway: Two $100 Prizes</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>From now on, you get to exchange money and win money thanks to CoinCannon monthly giveaway. The rules are super simple, make an order on CoinCannon, leave us a review and sign up to win $100. Every month, <strong>TWO </strong>lucky winners will take home their prize. With that, you help other CoinCannon customers by leaving us a review and try your chance to earn money along the way. Without further ado, here’s everything to know about the CoinCannon Monthly Giveaway:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Head Over to the Official CoinCannon <a href="https://hi.exchange/campaign/tether-giveaway#participate-section">Tether Giveaway</a> Page</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="CoinCannon Tether Giveaway $200 Every Month! Crypto Airdrop - Win $200" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/mj0L9_-1f_A?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Monthly Giveaway in 4 Easy Steps!</strong></h2>



<p>Fortunately, it is super easy to participate in the campaign. In order to join, users should complete four steps.</p>



<p>Firstly, the participant should make a transaction on CoinCannon. There is no limit or specific requirement for this stage. Pick any direction you want, at any amount you need and you’re good to go.</p>



<p>Secondly, the user must leave CoinCannon a review on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/jolixo-exchanger.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">BestChange</a>. You can find the link for BestChange on the Official Campaign page. And, don’t forget to mention your order number in the comment.</p>



<p>For the third step, participants need to join CoinCannon’s <a href="https://t.me/coincannon_ex " target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Telegram Channel</a>. Once again, you can find the link to the official Telegram channel on the official <a href="https://hi.exchange/campaign/tether-giveaway#participate-section" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Tether giveaway</a> page.</p>



<p>Having finished the steps above, all that’s left to join is to register your Telegram id and Email address. For that, type in the id and email address in the dedicated box available on the campaign page.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Win, But Not Just Once!</strong></h2>



<p>With this campaign, our customers will have a chance to participate in the CoinCannon monthly giveaway every month. Even if you win once, you will get a chance to participate the next month. So basically, you’re always one transaction away to receive a $100 gift.</p>



<p>To clarify, you do not need to make another review in order to participate for the second time. By leaving us a feedback once, you will be eligible to participate every month.</p>



<p>Keep in mind, every user will get only one chance each month. Subsequently, leaving multiple feedbacks will not affect the chance to win.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Monthly Giveaway Gives You Infinite Chances</strong></h2>



<p>This campaign is designed to optimize user experience by providing better feedback for new customers. Thankfully, the open-ended giveaway can better encourage our veteran users to participate.</p>



<p>As for the winner, the lucky person will receive an email from CoinCannon with further details on how to get their prize. So, make sure to check your inbox the first week of each month when we pick the winners.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/jolixo-monthly-giveaway/">CoinCannon Monthly Giveaway: Two $100 Prizes</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/jolixo-monthly-giveaway/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Make PayPal Payment Without a PayPal Account [Video]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-payment/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-payment/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 06:42:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Essentials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Videos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payment Service]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal Invoice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal Payment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5123</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>These days, PayPal Payment is a dominant method of transaction on the internet. A vast majority of online platforms support PayPal as payment method for their goods and services. However, that doesn’t mean that everyone gets equal access to PayPal payment services. Unfortunately, many countries do not have access to PayPal services and subsequently face [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-payment/">Make PayPal Payment Without a PayPal Account [Video]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>These days, PayPal Payment is a dominant method of transaction on the internet. A vast majority of online platforms support PayPal as payment method for their goods and services. However, that doesn’t mean that everyone gets equal access to PayPal payment services. Unfortunately, many countries do not have access to PayPal services and subsequently face payment issues. Furthermore, there are those who rarely need PayPal services and just don’t feel compelled to create an account. But, when the time comes, they might need to make a PayPal payment instantly. Fortunately, CoinCannon PayPal Invoice service is the perfect solution to all problems stated above. It offers multiple benefits and does not cost extra commission. Stay with us as we go over everything to know about our PayPal invoice service.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="How to Make PayPal Payments without a PayPal Account" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Yy3JjVEEHHI?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Make PayPal Payment Without a PayPal Account on<br><a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Can I Make PayPal Payment Without an Account?</strong></h2>



<p>Yes, you don’t necessarily need an official PayPal account in order to make a payment. In order to do this, you will need an exchange platform to make the payment for you. This service is specifically designed for those who do not have access to a PayPal account at the moment. This could be caused by a suspended account for short-term or sanctions imposed on a country which would suspend all PayPal services indefinitely. In any case, you can use the PayPal invoice service to make the PayPal payment instantly.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Does It Better</strong></h2>



<p>However, using the PayPal invoice service is only a good solution as long as you utilize a good exchange platform. Since this is a unique service, the exchangers might take a lot more commission for it as compared with a regular exchange operation. On the other hand, since you are making a purchase, the exchanger will know exactly what you purchased and how much you paid for it. Hence, your anonymity is compromised.</p>



<p>Thankfully, CoinCannon comes to the rescue! CoinCannon does not have any extra commission for the PayPal Payment and the commission rate remains the same as a regular PayPal exchange. Which means, you get to enjoy very low exchange commission with your payment.</p>



<p>In terms of privacy and anonymity, CoinCannon does not require KYC or even Sign Up. Therefore, you do not disclose any personal information with the platform.</p>



<p>Lastly, we offer 24/7 online support. So, in case you have any questions or issues, simply send us a message through the Live Chat section on the <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">main page</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Make a PayPal Payment?</strong></h2>



<p>In order to make PayPal payments without an account, you can use a crypto wallet and pay with Tether or Bitcoin, or a Perfect Money account. We will keep you updated upon adding other options for the payment. Make sure to visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a> regularly to stay up to date. But as a quick hint, there will be a lot more similar services available on CoinCannon very soon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Do I Have to Pay Commission?</strong></h2>



<p>No, there will be no extra commission or hidden exchange fees to use the PayPal Invoice service. The commission rate is the same as making a standard PayPal exchange on the platform which is already pretty low. Please bear in mind, making payments via Bitcoin will have a higher transaction fee due to Bitcoin network fees.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How Can I Make a PayPal Payment Without an Account?</strong></h2>



<p>In short, since you don’t have access to a PayPal account, you send your assets to CoinCannon and the platform will make the payment from its own PayPal account. Currently, we support Bitcoin, Tether TRC20 or Perfect Money USD. Following that, CoinCannon will receive your funds and make the PayPal payment on your behalf.</p>



<p>The process is very simple!</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Enter the CoinCannon Platform. Then, select either Perfect Money, Bitcoin or Tether TRC20 in the “I Give” section. After that, select PayPal USD (Invoice) from the “I Get” Section.</li><li>Type the Sending Amount for the payment. Then, wait until the rates automatically apply and see how much PayPal USD you will have for the payment. By the way, our exchange rates are awesome!</li><li>Click on Exchange and your will go to the second step. Add your invoice link (URL address) in the dedicated section. For example, if you’re buying a service online, add the link to the product page. Type your email address and the phone number section is optional. However, remember that there are many<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> benefits</a> for customers who sign up.</li><li>Review the exchange information carefully. Prove that you’re not a robot (nothing personal J) and click on “Exchange”</li><li>On the forth step, you receive your Track ID. You can see the order status. Click on “Pay Order”. If you make the payment via Perfect Money, you will be directed to the Perfect Money gateway. If you’re sending BTC or Tether, you will receive CoinCannon’s wallet address. At that point, make the payment and attach a screenshot of the payment in the dedicated section.</li><li>Kindly, agree to our terms and conditions and click on “Pay Order”.</li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>That’s It!</strong></h2>



<p>At this point, our team will process your order and make the PayPal payment. The process might take a short while. If you have any questions or issues, you can contact our online support team via the live chat section on the website. Our services expand by the hour! Make sure to visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a> for the latest announcements.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-payment/">Make PayPal Payment Without a PayPal Account [Video]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-payment/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Make PayPal Payments in Russia [No Commission]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-paymenst-in-russia/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-paymenst-in-russia/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 10:43:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Essentials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal Invoice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal Payments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal Russia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Russia PayPal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5103</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you live in Russia or any other country in the world that does not currently have access to PayPal services, CoinCannon provides a perfect solution. Luckily, you can pay for goods and services on CoinCannon without needing a PayPal account. Simply, you can make PayPal payments in Russia using our PayPal Invoice service. This [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-paymenst-in-russia/">How to Make PayPal Payments in Russia [No Commission]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you live in Russia or any other country in the world that does not currently have access to PayPal services, CoinCannon provides a perfect solution. Luckily, you can pay for goods and services on CoinCannon without needing a PayPal account. Simply, you can make PayPal payments in Russia using our PayPal Invoice service. This service is easy, quick and carries no extra fees or commissions. Thankfully, you don’t have to worry about PayPal payments anymore.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><span class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> to make PayPal payments in Russia.</span></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>PayPal in Russia</strong></h2>



<p>Unfortunately, PayPal and other international payment methods have suspended all services in Russia. In the meantime, there are millions of people who are still in need of these services. Basically, numerous online goods and services require PayPal Payments and the suspended service can be harmful for the customers. In that regard, CoinCannon has provided you with the PayPal invoice service.</p>



<p>With this solution, you can instantly make PayPal payments in Russia without needing an account. But that’s not all! The good news is that your anonymity will also be intact. CoinCannon will not require KYC (Know Your Customer) or even Sing Up. So basically, just enter the platform and make the payment without disclosing your personal information.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Make PayPal Payments in Russia?</strong></h2>



<p>In order to make PayPal payments in Russia, you can use a crypto wallet and pay with Tether or Bitcoin, or a Perfect Money account. We will keep you updated upon adding other options for the payment. Make sure to visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a> regularly to stay up to date. But as a quick hint, there will be a lot more similar services available on CoinCannon very soon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Do I Have to Pay Commission?</strong></h2>



<p>No, there will be no extra commission or hidden exchange fees to make PayPal payments in Russia or any other country in the world. The commission rate is the same as making a standard PayPal exchange on the platform which is already pretty low. Please bear in mind, making payments via Bitcoin will have a higher transaction fee due to Bitcoin network fees.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How Do I Make PayPal Payments in Russia?</strong></h2>



<p>In short, since you don’t have access to a PayPal account, you send your assets to CoinCannon and the platform will make the payment from its own PayPal account. Currently, we support Bitcoin, Tether TRC20 or Perfect Money USD. Following that, CoinCannon will receive your funds and make the PayPal payment on your behalf.</p>



<p>The process is very simple!</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Enter the <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> Platform. Then, select either Perfect Money, Bitcoin or Tether TRC20 in the “I Give” section. After that, select PayPal USD (Invoice) from the “I Get” Section.</li><li>Type the Sending Amount for the payment. Then, wait until the rates automatically apply and see how much PayPal USD you will have for the payment. By the way, our exchange rates are awesome!</li><li>Click on Exchange and your will go to the second step. Add your invoice link (URL address) in the dedicated section. For example, if you’re buying a service online, add the link to the product page. Type your email address and the phone number section is optional. However, remember that there are many <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">benefits</a> for customers who sign up.</li><li>Review the exchange information carefully. Prove that you’re not a robot (nothing personal J) and click on “Exchange”</li><li>On the forth step, you receive your Track ID. You can see the order status. Click on “Pay Order”. If you make the payment via Perfect Money, you will be directed to the Perfect Money gateway. If you’re sending BTC or Tether, you will receive CoinCannon’s wallet address. At that point, make the payment and attach a screenshot of the payment in the dedicated section.</li><li>Kindly, agree to our terms and conditions and click on “Pay Order”.</li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>That’s It!</strong></h2>



<p>At this point, our team will process your order and make the PayPal payment. The process might take a short while. If you have any questions or issues, you can contact our online support team via the live chat section on the website. Our services expand by the hour! Make sure to visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a> for the latest announcements.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-paymenst-in-russia/">How to Make PayPal Payments in Russia [No Commission]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-paymenst-in-russia/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PayPal Suspends Services in Russia [Everything to Know]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-suspends-services-russia/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-suspends-services-russia/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 06:07:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Essentials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal RUB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Russia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ukraine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5021</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Unfortunately, PayPal announced on March 4th that they are suspending all services in Russia. However, that doesn’t mean that users’ digital assets are unavailable immediately. As for now, there are lots of details to be announced by PayPal regarding this action. So don’t panic, your money is safe for the moment. On the other hand, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-suspends-services-russia/">PayPal Suspends Services in Russia [Everything to Know]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Unfortunately, PayPal announced on March 4<sup>th</sup> that they are suspending all services in Russia. However, that doesn’t mean that users’ digital assets are unavailable immediately. As for now, there are lots of details to be announced by PayPal regarding this action. So don’t panic, your money is safe for the moment. On the other hand, considering the circumstances, we have presented some solutions for those who are affected by this decision. Although the details remain uncertain, here is everything to know about PayPal in Russia.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><span class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Buy cryptocurrencies instantly on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a><br>No KYC</span></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>PayPal Services</strong><strong></strong></h2>



<p>PayPal’s CEO Dan Schulman said on Saturday that PayPal is suspending services in Russia. This was announced in a letter addressed to the Ukrainian Government.</p>



<p>“Under the current circumstances, we are suspending PayPal services in Russia,” Soon after, Ukraine’s minister of digital transformation Mykhailo Fedorov tweeted the letter. Finally, a PayPal spokesperson officially confirmed the news while clarifying some speculations. Basically, the company will “continue work to process customer withdraws for period of time, ensuring that account balances are dispersed in line with applicable laws and regulations,” the spokesperson told <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/05/paypal-suspends-its-services-in-russia-over-ukraine-war.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CNBC</a>.</p>



<p>Essentially, PayPal will not allow new users to register from Russia which started last week. So for now, the company will dedicate some time for withdrawals and users should not worry about assets in their accounts.</p>



<p>Sadly, considering the scope of this announcement, very little information is released. Users in Russia are shocked by this news and they are rushing to withdraw from their accounts. To make things worse, we have no known specific time limit as to how much time Russians will have to make withdrawals. Rest assured, we will keep you updated on this matter as soon as there is further information.</p>



<p>PayPal has been limiting their services in Russia as far back as 2020. And this latest action was the final nail the coffin. From now on, send and receive functions and making international transfers would not be available for Russians.</p>



<p>Furthermore, Visa and Mastercard are also cutting ties with financial Russian institutions. Initially, sending and receiving money to and from Russia are difficult to say the least.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Can You Do?</strong></h2>



<p>Well, Crypto is the answer. It doesn’t take much to exchange your currencies into crypto. All you need is a crypto wallet and an exchange platform. In that regard, some exchange platforms require KYC (know your customer) and will limit your deposit and withdrawal amount. But the good news is that you can simply head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, and exchange as much as you want within minutes! CoinCannon does not require KYC or even sign up so you can quickly buy crypto without any limit.</p>



<p>In desperate times, cryptocurrencies will basically be the only way to save your money. If not for war or natural disasters, the governments can simply limit investors from making withdrawals from their accounts. We can see this situation happening in both Russia and Canada. Yet with Crypto, you will have access to your money in a digital wallet wherever you are in the world. Just enter your password and you’re good to go.</p>



<p>And by crypto we don’t mean just Bitcoin. In fact, considering the volatility, stablecoins are a solid choice to store your assets somewhere other than banks. Stablecoins have their value pegged to another currency like the US dollar. Fortunately, we already have a list of <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/top-stablecoins-to-buy/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">top stablecoins</a> to buy that are better alternatives for Tether USD.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-suspends-services-russia/">PayPal Suspends Services in Russia [Everything to Know]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-suspends-services-russia/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cryptocurrencies Shine While Banks Disappoint (Opinion)</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrencies-shine-banks-disappoint/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrencies-shine-banks-disappoint/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 18:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Essentials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5007</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>cryptocurrencies are at this point bombarded with highly coordinated and well-funded marketing endeavors. Unfortunately, we see technical terms flying around while they don’t mean nothing to no one. After all, nobody will be in it for the tech without some sweet returns on their investment. In a sad turn of events, the Russia-Ukraine conflict has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrencies-shine-banks-disappoint/">Cryptocurrencies Shine While Banks Disappoint (Opinion)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>cryptocurrencies are at this point bombarded with highly coordinated and well-funded marketing endeavors. Unfortunately, we see technical terms flying around while they don’t mean nothing to no one. After all, nobody will be in it for the tech without some sweet returns on their investment. In a sad turn of events, the Russia-Ukraine conflict has portrayed the significance of one of those overly-commercialized terms that is “decentralized”. Suddenly, a war breaks out in Europe where millions of people have to pack up everything and go. Can you withdraw from a bank in this situation? Are the banks even open? If not for war, what would you do if everyone panicked overnight and lined up to cash out on the ATM machines? </p>



<p>This terrifying experience has happened three times in February alone. Canada, Ukraine and Russia had their people rushing to empty their bank accounts, out of fear, out of desperation and perhaps with a rightful tendency to save their well-earned capital. Skeptics doubt Tether about their dollar reserves, but do the banks have all the assets in your cards printed and ready to go? In this uprising of devastating turmoil, cryptocurrencies are saving lives with an infrastructure that is immune to all missile strikes. In a time when bank servers are basically electrical waste, Bitcoin, Ethereum and other cryptocurrencies are safe in their owners’ pockets.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><span class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Buy Cryptocurrencies Instantly on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a>. <br>[No KYC or Sign Up Required]</span></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Cryptocurrencies Matter!</strong></h2>



<p>Frankly, this is not a love letter crypto coming from a Midwest doomer who wants to shoot the bourgeoisie in the back of the head with a BB gun. In fact, the marketing strategies and the advertised content created by giant exchange apps are revolting to say the least. We do not need Hollywood and TV stars telling us to be bold and invest in the future while they surrender user data to the highest bidder. In fact, Changpeng Zhao can Tweet his libertarian stream of consciousness all day long and we’d still know how he shares transaction information with governments just for a competitive edge over Coinbase and KuCoin.</p>



<p>Having expressed my utter resentment for crypto moguls (like Elon), here is credit where it’s due. Cryptocurrencies are out there in Ukraine, available for payment, holding their investors lifesavings while the banks are obliterated. Cryptocurrencies are now pretty much the primary method of accepting donations from others as they immediately reach their destination without any hassle. On the eastern side of the conflict, there is something going on that could make an even better case for cryptocurrencies.</p>



<p>The Russian Government has shut down the stock market. In a state of panic where the investors fear an upcoming plunge would wipe their capital, someone decided that it’s not a good time for people to pull out. Say what you will about Bitcoin whales, but at least they can’t shut down the whole market and lock your money. Surely, the volatility is a big turn off, but one must remember how fragile a banking system is.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">The Loudest Voice</h2>



<p>Socialist literary critics like Mikhail Bakhtin believed that each language contains multiple other sub-languages that each have their own agenda. And sometimes, one language is the dominant voice for the whole group. Today, the dominant voice is the language of marketing, oversaturated with flowery and top-shelf words meticulously designed to capitalize on our senses. Cryptocurrencies used to be cool, you could trade, hold or simply move these cryptographically secured assets without anyone knowing anything about it. They used to be ours.</p>



<p>What happened in Ukraine, Russia, Canada and what will surely happen in the future is a testament to crypto utility. Cryptocurrencies are dominated by the marketing voice of venture capitalism, drowned in the vicious advertisings of Harvard-graduates with a careless over-competitive attitude that disregards the common folk. This is why I see hope for cryptocurrencies, not because of the massive pumps in Bitcoin value and certainly not for shitcoins. I see hope for cryptocurrencies because at the end of the day, they are our only alternative for a flimsy traditional finance.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrencies-shine-banks-disappoint/">Cryptocurrencies Shine While Banks Disappoint (Opinion)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrencies-shine-banks-disappoint/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
