<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Solana Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/solana/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:45:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Solana to Tether [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-solana-to-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-solana-to-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 07:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6403</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sure, you can exchange Solana to Tether on so many platforms, but CoinCannon is better! Solana (SOL) is one of the fastest blockchain networks out there. It offers lightning speed transaction speeds and super cheap transaction costs. With all that in mind, SOL has a loyal group of institutions using it for their global transactions. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-solana-to-tether/">How to Exchange Solana to Tether [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Sure, you can exchange Solana to Tether on so many platforms, but CoinCannon is better! Solana (SOL) is one of the fastest blockchain networks out there. It offers lightning speed transaction speeds and super cheap transaction costs. With all that in mind, SOL has a loyal group of institutions using it for their global transactions. Subsequently, Solana is one of the top cryptocurrencies by market cap. In this article, we will go over how to exchange Solana to Tether on CoinCannon platform. At CoinCannon, you can have the lowest exchange rates, full anonymity and 24/7 online support all together.</p>



<p>So head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Solana on the left box and Tether on the right and get started!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Solana to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive USDT. Most likely, your Solana wallet supports USDT, so you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Solana?</strong></h2>



<p>In short, Solana is a blockchain platform for decentralized applications (DApps). The network utilizes Proof of Stake consensus algorithm. However, in a world full of PoS blockchain networks, Solana has managed to achieve some impressive figures. The network can support up to 50,000 transactions per second (TPS) and requires 400 milliseconds to build a block. With the quickly increasing number of validators currently at 1,061, the network is one of the fastest out there.</p>



<p>Found in 2017 by Anatoly Yakovenko, a former Qualcomm member, along with Eric Williams and Greg Fitzgerald, the network aimed to create a more efficient and scalable platform.</p>



<p>The team consists of former members of companies such as Google, Apple, Microsoft, Qualcomm, Dropbox, Intel and more.</p>



<p>In that regard, the network is backed by many years of experience in some of the best companies around the world.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>    Continue reading “<a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-solana/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Solana</a>” to learn everything about the network.</p>
</blockquote>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Solana to Tether</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to exchange Solana to Tether USDT, let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Solana to Tether?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Solana on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your SOL to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-you-re-all-set"><strong>You’re All Set!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-solana-to-tether/">How to Exchange Solana to Tether [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-solana-to-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Solana with PayPal [Best Exchange Rates]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-paypal/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-paypal/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 08:37:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4285</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you are looking to buy Solana with PayPal, this article will provide a step-by-step guide. Solana took the market by storm in 2020 as an Ethereum competitor. In terms of scalability it is one of the fastest blockchain networks. The network has massive institutional investors hooked in as a DeFi platform and SOL as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-paypal/">How to Buy Solana with PayPal [Best Exchange Rates]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you are looking to buy Solana with PayPal, this article will provide a step-by-step guide. Solana took the market by storm in 2020 as an Ethereum competitor. In terms of scalability it is one of the fastest blockchain networks. The network has massive institutional investors hooked in as a DeFi platform and SOL as the native token is incredibly successful. You can buy Solana with PayPal seamlessly and anonymously on CoinCannon.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>To get started, go to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> platform to buy Solana with PayPal.</p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-solana"><strong>What is Solana?</strong></h2>



<p>In short, Solana is a blockchain platform for decentralized applications (DApps). The network utilizes Proof of Stake consensus algorithm. However, in a world full of PoS blockchain networks, Solana has managed to achieve some impressive figures. The network can support up to 50,000 transactions per second (TPS) and requires 400 milliseconds to build a block. With the quickly increasing number of validators currently at 1,061, the network is one of the fastest out there.</p>



<p>SOL is currently the 4<sup>th</sup> cryptocurrency with an astonishing $67+ billion market cap. As of November 2021, Solana has had almost 10000% growth in one year.</p>



<p>Continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-solana/">What is Solana</a>” to learn everything about the network.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-buy-with-paypal"><strong>Buy with PayPal</strong></h2>



<p>PayPal is at this point the number one financial platform for digital currencies. In terms of security of your assets, they provide great services. As compared with a bank, keeping money in PayPal account can save you some tax payments in the future. It is widely accepted as a payment method and simply makes a lot of sense. Having enjoyed incredible returns on your SOL investment, you can easily transfer the asset to your PayPal account.</p>



<p>Furthermore, as of 2021, 392 million people have PayPal accounts. In terms of popularity, PayPal is by far the best.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-buy-solana-with-paypal-on-jolixo"><strong>Why Buy Solana with PayPal on CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p>An ideal exchange platform must have three primary characteristics. Privacy, good exchange rates and reliability. CoinCannon has worked hard to provide all three for the customers.</p>



<p>For privacy, the safest way to protect customer information is not asking for it at all. This might be a challenge in many aspects yet anonymity is our utmost priority. Therefore, CoinCannon requires no KYC or even a sign up process.</p>



<p>When it comes to exchange rates, our strategy is to be as competitive as possible. CoinCannon utilizes an automated system to determine the best possible exchange rates at any moment. But you don’t have to take our word for it. You can visit ranking websites such as Bestchange and OkChanger to see our rank for yourself.</p>



<p>Lastly, reliability does not come easy. In order to provide the best exchange services, we offer real 24/7 customer support.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-buy-solana-with-paypal-step-by-step-guide"><strong>Buy Solana with PayPal Step-by-Step Guide</strong></h2>



<p>Here are the five easy steps to make the purchase:</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the homepage first, then select PayPal and Solana from the currency pairs in the first step. enter the amount you want to exchange, after that the amount of SOL you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>



<li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Solana wallet details, email, and phone number.</li>



<li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li>Complete the captcha test and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the PayPal gateway and pay online. After you have transferred your PayPal USD to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>



<li>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the SOL to your wallet ASAP.</li>
</ol>



<p>The exchange process does not take long. However, you can read some of our new, opinion, analysis or comedy articles on <a href="http://www.blog.hi.exchange/">HiExchage blog</a> while waiting.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-paypal/">How to Buy Solana with PayPal [Best Exchange Rates]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-paypal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana (SOL): Dying Out with a Whimper?</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-sol-plunge/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-sol-plunge/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 09:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6241</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Solana (SOL), once a praised contender for Ethereum, is now down 96% form ATH. Maybe, Solana is the popular kid who peaked in high school and settled down getting paid $8 an hour. Because, that’s exactly where it’s hovering at the time of writing this article. Here’s a surprising fact, Solana peaked at an all-time [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-sol-plunge/">&lt;strong&gt;Solana (SOL): Dying Out with a Whimper?&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Solana (SOL), once a praised contender for Ethereum, is now down 96% form ATH. Maybe, Solana is the popular kid who peaked in high school and settled down getting paid $8 an hour. Because, that’s exactly where it’s hovering at the time of writing this article. Here’s a surprising fact, Solana peaked at an all-time high of $260 in November 2021 and is now trading below its initial first day of ICO. Would it be fair to say that Solana was merely a concept of what could be like the Tesla Roadster or the Line City in Saudi Arabia. And in this day and age, concepts sell better than functioning products, they go up and up and up in value and crash like the spaghetti western protagonists. </p>



<p>Nonetheless, this is no philosophical reflection on the nature of modern life and the subsequent products that turn the wheel of economy. And that’s why I put a question mark at the end of the title, these question marks are life savers for journalists to preserve their integrity in case they were morbidly wrong.</p>



<p>For the first time, a crypto exchange is delisting Solana (SOL) and its products from their platform. This is bad news for the already struggling digital asset that used to have strong ties with <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ftx-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">FTX</a>.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-solana-sol-fast-and-loose"><strong>Solana (SOL), Fast and Loose</strong></h2>



<p>According to crypto journalist <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1608309183685840899" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Colin Wu</a>, crypto exchange Matrixport will delist Solana and its associates on December 30<sup>th</sup>. While nobody has even heard of Matrixport, the news sent SOL down yet another steep correction of 13%. On top of that, the exchange has also said they will not launch any of their products in the future.</p>



<p>“Matrixport, the asset management platform founded by Jihan Wu, announced that it will delist SOL and SOL-U dual-currency investment products on December 30, and will not launch new Solana products in the future.”</p>



<p>In the meantime, Vitalik Buterin took on Twitter to give the Solana team some words of encouragement. Buterin believes that “the awful opportunistic money” is now purged from SOL and the future is awesome and stuff!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Some smart people tell me there is an earnest smart developer community in Solana, and now that the awful opportunistic money people have been washed out, the chain has a bright future.<br><br>Hard for me to tell from outside, but I hope the community gets its fair chance to thrive🦾🦾</p>&mdash; vitalik.eth (@VitalikButerin) <a href="https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin/status/1608591727316684804?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 29, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Recently, critics have been mocking the <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-phone-saga/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Solana Phone</a> for being a gimmicky rebranded phone with aimless emphasis on web3. It would be fair to say Solana (SOL) has not been making the wisest decision in 2021 and they do actually play a significant part in their demise.</p>



<p>However, it is terrifying how they could attract heavy investments from investment giants like Grayscale.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Domino Effect?</strong></h2>



<p>As you can tell by the question mark, I am not certain whether delisting Solana from exchanges can be a trend. Yet, the plunge for Solana is part of the bearish Domino-like collapse taking place in the crypto market. Solana had strong ties with FTX, but that’s not all they had to pay for. Essentially, SOL took momentum with the rise of NFTs for having a fast and cheap blockchain to complete NFT transactions. During the NFT boom, the Solana blockchain gained massive traction since other networks had higher transaction fees. With that, SOL had strong rallies coming one after another.</p>



<p>However, consistent network outages began to push Solana down and create fear among investors. On top of that, both Web3 and NFTs have significantly lost popularity in the past couple of months. These two were the big categories that Solana was investing in.</p>



<p>Despite all that, it seems unlikely for SOL to have a quick and short-term recovery as it is now associated with high-risk assets such as Shiba Inu.</p>



<p>According to Arthur Hayes, Solana may still have a chance to bounce back despite being a “shitcoin”. But his reasoning is not something everyone can agree with.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Even though <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24SOL&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$SOL</a> is a complete and utter shitcoin, at some point it will be a buy if the mainstream financial press is dunking on it. Like on the &lt;TOP&gt; news section. <br><br>Nothing ever goes up or down in a straight line. <a href="https://t.co/3BFPcJhzPF">pic.twitter.com/3BFPcJhzPF</a></p>&mdash; Arthur Hayes (@CryptoHayes) <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoHayes/status/1608071980334436353?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 28, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-sol-plunge/">&lt;strong&gt;Solana (SOL): Dying Out with a Whimper?&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-sol-plunge/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Solana with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-perfect-money/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-perfect-money/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 09:29:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perfect Money]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5919</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the ever-evolving world of cryptocurrency, knowing how to buy Solana with Perfect Money is essential for savvy investors. With Solana (SOL) emerging as a formidable player in the blockchain space, acquiring this digital asset has become a priority for many. As we step into 2024, one of the most convenient and secure ways to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy Solana with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In the ever-evolving world of cryptocurrency, knowing how to <strong>buy Solana with Perfect Money</strong> is essential for savvy investors. With Solana (SOL) emerging as a formidable player in the blockchain space, acquiring this digital asset has become a priority for many.</p>



<p> As we step into 2024, one of the most convenient and secure ways to buy Solana is through Perfect Money. This article, <strong>&#8220;How to Buy Solana with Perfect Money [2024 Update]&#8221;</strong> will guide you through the latest methods and strategies to seamlessly buy Solana using Perfect Money.</p>



<p> Whether you&#8217;re a seasoned crypto enthusiast or a newcomer looking to diversify your portfolio, this comprehensive guide will provide you with the insights and tools needed to make informed decisions in the dynamic crypto market.</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-1 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button is-style-outline is-style-outline--1"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-black-color has-text-color has-background has-link-color wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/" style="background-color:#f49d3f">Buy <strong>Solana with Perfect Money</strong> Right Now!</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-do-i-need-to-buy-solana-with-perfect-money"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Solana with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will be sending PM USD and receiving Solana (SOL). Subsequently, you will need a verified and active Perfect Money account with sufficient funds. Make sure that the exchange amount does not exceed your withdrawal limit. On the other hand, you will have to have a reliable crypto wallet that supports Solana (SOL). As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-buy-solana-with-perfect-money"><strong>Why Buy Solana with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>It’s fast, it’s cheap and super easy to use. Basically, PM is one of the most popular payment systems that offers a lot of convenience.</p>



<p>Perfect Money is an e-currency used for making payments on the internet. It is widely accepted as payment option by countless platforms. With Perfect Money, you can do a lot! Be it transferring funds to others or pay for goods and services. Or how about buying cryptocurrencies or even buying fiat currencies. It is a seriously popular payment method for online users. An additional capability is to loan and receipt issuance throughout the system.</p>



<p>The biggest downside of Perfect Money, however, is that you cannot cash Perfect money to your bank account on its website directly. For that, you will need a platform like CoinCannon to exchange your Perfect Money to PayPal and other e-currencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-buy-solana-with-perfect-money"><strong>How to Buy Solana with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>Here are the five easy steps to make the purchase:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 1 : </strong>Enter the homepage first, then select Perfect Money and Solana (SOL) from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of SOL you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>



<li><strong>Step 2 : </strong>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Solana wallet details, email, and phone number.</li>



<li><strong>Step 3 : </strong>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li><strong>Step 4 : </strong>Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the Perfect Money gateway and make the payment to our Perfect Money account. Having transferred your Perfect Money to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>



<li><strong>Step 5 : </strong>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the SOL to your wallet ASAP.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done-and-done"><strong>Done and Done!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Solana to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-jolixo-platform"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Cryptocurrencies are a financial apparatus to maximize privacy and efficiency. Sadly, regulations have been severely affecting the market as they compromise both.</p>



<p><a href="https://hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> seeks to be a platform that offers privacy and efficiency simultaneously while offering some of the most aggressive exchange rates in the market.</p>



<p>To make this happen, the platform does not require KYC or a sign up process. This way, all customers can easily make transactions without a possible compromise on their personal information.</p>



<p>However, privacy is a crucial element and not a luxury. In that regard, the platform offers some of the most competitive rates amongst all online exchanges. The rates are automatically determined utilizing an automated system and are updated as soon as change in value is detected.</p>



<p>Last but not least, by offering true 24/7 support, all customers will be in touch with the team in case anything goes unplanned.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy Solana with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-perfect-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Solana with Payeer USD [Best Rates]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-payeer/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-payeer/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 07:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5781</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you’re looking to buy Solana with Payeer USD, you have to check out CoinCannon. Basically, you can cash in and cash out your Payeer USD and take advantage of full anonymity. But, the privacy does not come at any extra cost. For crypto purchases, you can use CoinCannon to enhance all aspects of your [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-payeer/">How to Buy Solana with Payeer USD [Best Rates]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you’re looking to buy Solana with Payeer USD, you have to check out <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>. Basically, you can cash in and cash out your Payeer USD and take advantage of full anonymity. But, the privacy does not come at any extra cost. For crypto purchases, you can use CoinCannon to enhance all aspects of your transaction. In this case, we will go over how to buy Solana with Payeer USD on the platform. With that, you can invest in the most scalable altcoin in the world using the highest quality exchange that you deserve!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/buy-cryptocurrencies-with-payeer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Buy Cryptocurrency with Payeer</a></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Solana with Payeer?</strong></h2>



<p>In order to make this transaction, you will need a verified Payeer Account and a reliable crypto wallet. Make sure that your wallet does support Solana (SOL). As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. Want a good reason why? How about winning $100 ever month!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Solana?</strong></h2>



<p>In short, Solana is a blockchain platform for decentralized applications (DApps). The network utilizes Proof of Stake consensus algorithm. However, in a world full of PoS blockchain networks, Solana has managed to achieve some impressive figures. The network can support up to 50,000 transactions per second (TPS) and requires 400 milliseconds to build a block. With the quickly increasing number of validators currently at 1,061, the network is one of the fastest out there.</p>



<p>Found in 2017 by Anatoly Yakovenko, a former Qualcomm member, along with Eric Williams and Greg Fitzgerald, the network aimed to create a more efficient and scalable platform.</p>



<p>The team consists of former members of companies such as Google, Apple, Microsoft, Qualcomm, Dropbox, Intel and more.</p>



<p>In that regard, the network is backed by many years of experience in some of the best companies around the world.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"><p>Continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-solana/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Solana</a>” to learn everything about the network.</p></blockquote>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Buy Solana with Payeer?</strong></h2>



<p>First and foremost, Payeer is considered an online digital wallet for better asset management. Be it crypto of fiat, the payment processor is quick, reliable and cheap. In that regard, in a short lifespan of almost 8 years, Payeer is now recognized as one of the very best amongst competitors. Payeer utilizes built-in payment services with giant financial services such as Mastercard, VISA and PayPal.</p>



<p>As of 2021, the Payeer has approximately 7 million users which can transfer funds to each other with extremely low fees. The strength however, lies in diversity. Payeer is far ahead of any similar platform in terms of scale of operation and diversity in supported payment methods. With more than 50 payment approaches, the Payeer wallet offers users various services in one place.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"><p>To learn more about Payeer, continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-payeer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Payeer?</a>”.</p></blockquote>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon for the Win!</strong></h2>



<p>Here’s the deal, exchange platforms are plenty, but the good ones are hard to find. Essentially, what you should be looking for is good exchange rates, anonymity and of course reliability. While these three qualities sound obvious, it’s actually not that easy to find a platform that offers them all at once. With that, platforms often tend to compromise on one of these above-mentioned factors.</p>



<p>Here at CoinCannon, our goal is to provide the ultimate exchange experience. Subsequently, the platform offers all the three important characteristics together.</p>



<p>We respect our customer’s privacy by not asking for their personal information. The best way for anyone to protect their information is to not disclose them at all. In that regard, not having KYC or sign up is the best method.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the platform utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at all times. Our words sound too good? Just pay a visit to ranking websites such as BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>Lastly, according to Murphy’s law “anything that can go wrong will go wrong”. To stay ahead of any problems, we offer 24/7 customer support.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Buy Solana with Payeer USD?</strong></h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Step 1</strong></h3>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Select Payeer USD on the “I Give” field on the left and Solana (SOL) on the “I Get” field on the right.</li><li>Enter the desired amount for the exchange and wait for the site to calculate the amazing exchange rates!</li><li>Click “Exchange”</li></ol>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Step 2</strong></h3>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Enter your Solana Wallet address and E-mail address</li><li>Click “Exchange”</li></ol>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Step 3</strong></h3>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Read the Information</li><li>Complete the CAPTCHA</li><li>Click “Exchange”</li></ol>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Step 4</strong></h3>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>At this point, please check the transaction information and terms and conditions carefully.</li><li>You will be able to see the track id and CoinCannon Payeer account</li><li>Open your Payeer account, click on the account menu and copy the account number that begins by the letter “p” and paste it in the required field.</li><li>Go back to your Payeer account and send the exchange amount to CoinCannon Payeer account.</li><li>Once you have sent the exchange amount, go to the history menu on your Payeer account and copy the operation id for the payment. Then paste the operation id in the required field.</li><li>Kindly agree to the terms and conditions and click on “Pay Order.</li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Solana (SOL) to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-payeer/">How to Buy Solana with Payeer USD [Best Rates]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-payeer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Solana Phone (Saga) Debuts!</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-phone-saga/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-phone-saga/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 07:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Saga]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana Phone]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5571</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>That’s right, the blockchain company Solana has officially introduced the new Solana phone named Saga. Which, following multiple network outages, the name can be a bit ironic. But, innovation is like a river that finds its way by flowing through practicality. For example, when the railroads and airplanes came to be, they barely had any [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-phone-saga/">The Solana Phone (Saga) Debuts!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>That’s right, the blockchain company Solana has officially introduced the new Solana phone named Saga. Which, following multiple network outages, the name can be a bit ironic. But, innovation is like a river that finds its way by flowing through practicality. For example, when the railroads and airplanes came to be, they barely had any use (sarcasm). Today, the new $1000 Solana phone is here to provide a solution to a problem we don’t have and the Saga begins. In any case, though it may be burdensome to avoid any network outage or even bear market jokes, here is an introduction on this technological marvel coming from China who has officially declared that cryptocurrencies will soon go to <a href="https://www.techtimes.com/articles/277053/20220622/bitcoin-plunge-triggers-more-fud-china-claims-crypto-worthless.htm" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">zero</a>. Oh the irony…</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Exchange Solana (SOL) to PayPal on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Saga the Solana Phone!</strong></h2>



<p>First things first, let’s go for the general background like an academic essay. Andy Rubin, an Android OS co-founder started his own project named the “Essential” back in 2017. The Essential phone ran Android without any modifications and that was its point. To run pure Android containing no customization from any major brand. Fast forward, the Essential phone flopped because the production and distribution was a nightmare. On top of that, the security focused phone had another nightmare coming its way. On August 2017, there was a data leak where hundreds of customers received emails from a seemingly official Essential address. The email asked for photo verification then stole and released the user data online. In total, Essential claims to have sold about 150,000 phones before discontinuing the production.</p>



<p>Now, the former engineers and designers from essential gathered together a while ago to give their project another shot. Basically, they were working on a new phone called the Osom OV1. However, the Solana Labs acquired their project to give it an extra shot of crypto in the veins. The new Solana phone goes by the name of Saga is all about web3, DApps and crypto.</p>



<p>Right now, you can preorder the Saga with a $100 deposit out of the $1000 total price. As for deliveries, Solana says sometime in the first quarter of 2023.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Specs</strong></h2>



<p>The Saga will have a 6.67-inch 120 Hz OLED display, 12 GB of RAM and 512GB of storage. Thankfully, it offers the latest Snapdragon 8 plus chip from Qualcomm and a 50-megapixel primary camera paired with a 12-megapixel ultra-wide lens. The specs are very much flagship but that is not the goal here. The Solana phone is here to make the transition from desktop to mobile easier for the user.</p>



<p>What does it mean? According to Solana CEO Anatoly Yakovenko, the device will have some unique features. For those interested in crypto wallets, Web3 and NFTs, the Saga will have extra features. Most importantly, the device will have support for decentralized apps operating on the Solana blockchain. Which means, that there are going to be lots of NFT marketplaces readily available on your phone. With that, you can spend your monthly payments on perfectly screenshotable pictures and stuff!</p>



<p>“The world needs novel hardware companies to support the future that is Web3. Building out an ecosystem that looks to the future without being burdened by past legacy ecosystems is hugely exciting.” Said the Osom CEO Jason Keats.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-phone-saga/">The Solana Phone (Saga) Debuts!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-phone-saga/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Solana to PayPal [2024 Update]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/how-to-exchange-solana-to-paypal-2024-update/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/how-to-exchange-solana-to-paypal-2024-update/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 06:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4214</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you looking to exchange Solana to PayPal? If so, you&#8217;ve come to the right place! In this article we will guide you through converting your Solana cryptocurrency to PayPal funds. Stay up-to-date with the latest trends and methods for seamlessly exchanging digital currencies to facilitate online payments. Join us as we explore the realm of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/how-to-exchange-solana-to-paypal-2024-update/">How to Exchange Solana to PayPal [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Are you looking to <strong><a href="https://hi.exchange/">exchange Solana to PayPal</a></strong>?</p>



<p> If so, you&#8217;ve come to the right place! In this article we will guide you through converting your Solana cryptocurrency to PayPal funds. </p>



<p>Stay up-to-date with the latest trends and methods for seamlessly exchanging digital currencies to facilitate online payments.</p>



<p> Join us as we explore the realm of Solana, a fast and scalable blockchain platform, and PayPal, the renowned online payment gateway. Discover the steps, possibilities, and potential benefits of this transaction. Get ready to navigate the world where cryptocurrencies meet the convenience of PayPal. </p>



<p>Let&#8217;s begin this exciting journey together!</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons alignwide is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-2 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button is-style-outline is-style-outline--2"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-black-color has-text-color has-background has-link-color wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/" style="background-color:#f49d3f">Exchange Soloana to PayPal Right Now!</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-paypal"><strong>Why PayPal?</strong></h2>



<p>PayPal is at this point the number one financial platform for digital currencies. In terms of security of your assets, they provide great services. </p>



<p>As compared with a bank, keeping money in PayPal account can save you some tax payments in the future. It is widely accepted as a payment method and simply makes a lot of sense. </p>



<p>Having enjoyed incredible returns on your SOL investment, you can easily transfer the asset to your PayPal account.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-exchange-solana-to-paypal-step-by-step-guide"><strong>Exchange Solana to PayPal Step-by Step Guide</strong></h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-jolixo-1-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange Solana to PayPal Step-by Step Guide step 1 " class="wp-image-8441" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-jolixo-1-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-jolixo-1-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-jolixo-1-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-jolixo-1-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-jolixo-1.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 1:</strong> As you enter the Homepage on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a>. Select Solana on the left field and PayPal on the right one. Enter the desired amount. You can see the exchange rate being applied to the amount and the USD amount you will receive.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-1-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange Solana to PayPal Step-by Step Guide step 2" class="wp-image-8442" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-1-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-1-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-1-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-1-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-1.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 2:</strong> Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your PayPal account details, email, and phone number.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-2-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange Solana to PayPal Step-by Step Guide step 3 " class="wp-image-8443" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-2-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-2-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-2-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-2-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-2.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 3:</strong> Click on “Next&#8221; one more time and you will be directed to a page to review your order.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-3-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange Solana to PayPal Step-by Step Guide step 4" class="wp-image-8444" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-3-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-3-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-3-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-3-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-3.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 4:</strong> At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-4-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange Solana to PayPal Step-by Step Guide step 5" class="wp-image-8446" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-4-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-4-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-4-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-4-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-4.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 5:</strong> Following that, on the next page, you will have the instructions and our terms and services. Please dedicate some time and read them carefully.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-5-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange Solana to PayPal Step-by Step Guide step 6" class="wp-image-8445" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-5-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-5-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-5-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-5-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Solana_PerfectMoney-5.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 6:</strong> Transfer your Solana to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you.</li>
</ul>



<p>When you have finished all the required steps, our team will deliver the assets to your PayPal account as soon as possible.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-exchange-solana-to-paypal-on-jolixo"><strong>Why Exchange Solana to PayPal on CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p>Cryptocurrencies were introduced with a vision of decentralizing finance. Today, most if not all large exchanges have become very much centralized. Furthermore, they do not offer anonymity which is a crucial factors involving finance.</p>



<p>CoinCannon respects the customers’ anonymity and does not require KYC or a sign-up process. This allows you to maintain privacy while in your financial journey.</p>



<p>Now that we’ve covered anonymity, the second most important quality is the exchange rates. In that regard, CoinCannon is amongst the most competitive when it comes to exchange rates. We offer the best possible rates at any moment utilizing an automated system. You can find us in the top 10 rank on websites such as <a href="http://www.bestchange.com/">BestChange</a> and <a href="http://www.okchanger.com/">OkChanger</a>.</p>



<p>Finally, by providing 24/7 customer support, we make sure you will have a quick but pleasant exchange experience.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/how-to-exchange-solana-to-paypal-2024-update/">How to Exchange Solana to PayPal [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/how-to-exchange-solana-to-paypal-2024-update/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Whales Are Buying Serum (SRM)</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/serum-srm-eth-whales/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/serum-srm-eth-whales/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Serum (SRM)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5252</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Here’s the thing, we all wish we could go back in time and buy Bitcoin or altcoins and quit our jobs and move to Florida. Since the only time machines are in Area 51, the only alternative is to keep a lookout for new altcoins that are ready to explode. Well, apparently Ethereum whales are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/serum-srm-eth-whales/">Ethereum Whales Are Buying Serum (SRM)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Here’s the thing, we all wish we could go back in time and buy Bitcoin or altcoins and quit our jobs and move to Florida. Since the only time machines are in Area 51, the only alternative is to keep a lookout for new altcoins that are ready to explode. Well, apparently Ethereum whales are way ahead of us with Serum (SRM). <strong>&nbsp;</strong>As whales continue to sell their Shiba Inu, new data suggests that they are quickly accumulating Serum (SRM). The new altcoin is essentially a DeFi crypto project associated with crypto exchange FTX.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Buy and Sell Cryptocurrencies on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a><br>No KYC</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Serum (SRM)?</strong></h2>



<p>Basically, Serum is a crypto project that acts as a protocol for decentralized exchanges. SRM is a utility token for the Solana-based decentralized exchange FTX. Primarily, FTX backs Serum (SRM) and FTX chief executive Sam Bankman-Fried is an advisor for the project. &nbsp;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="What is Project Serum?" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/QlrqKfllP10?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<p>According to the official website, Serum protocol allows for fast transactions with costs up to 60% lower. In fact, Serum (SRM) transactions cost an astonishing $0.00001 per transaction. And as for speed, the network has sufficed to say sub-second trading and settlement. With a peak of 65,000 TPS and 400ms block times, Serum (SRM) has made some big claims.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Ethereum Whales Have a New Favorite</strong></h2>



<p>Interestingly, <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/ethereum-whales-buy-usd-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Ethereum whales</a> are pouncing on Serum according to <a href="https://www.whalestats.com/analysis-of-the-top-100-eth-wallets" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">WhaleStats</a>. Last week, the top 100 Ethereum wallets purchased an average of over $1.9 million worth of Serum (SRM). To put that in comparison, the SRM purchases by the same wallets were at $237,875 last week.</p>



<p>Currently, SRM is trading at $2.45 and is ranked as 133<sup>rd</sup> crypto asset by market cap. Furthermore, SRM is down almost 9% in the past week.</p>



<p>And as for FTX, the top 100 ETH wallets purchased an average of $2.25 million worth of FTX Token (FTT) only in the past week. In the meantime, they sold $1.4 million in the same time. Despite the large number, FTX is still a popular purchase considering the scale of accumulation.</p>



<p>On the other hand, Shiba Inu, Elon’s financial toy and his inspiration for unfunny Twitter jokes is disappointing Ethereum Whales. In total, the top 100 ETH addresses sold off an average of $679,410 worth of SHIB last week and purchased $582,686.</p>



<p>And of course, they wouldn’t be Ethereum whales without holding large amounts of ETH. Last week, the top 100 ETH wallets purchased over $7 million worth of ETH while selling $8.5 million. In that regard, Ethereum has also seen outflows last weeks.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="517" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/whalestats4.15-1024x517.webp" alt="" class="wp-image-5254" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/whalestats4.15-1024x517.webp 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/whalestats4.15-300x151.webp 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/whalestats4.15-768x388.webp 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/whalestats4.15.webp 1377w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/serum-srm-eth-whales/">Ethereum Whales Are Buying Serum (SRM)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/serum-srm-eth-whales/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top Energy Efficient Blockchains [Investment Opportunity]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/top-energy-efficient-blockhains/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/top-energy-efficient-blockhains/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 07:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorand]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVALANCHE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Energy Efficient Blockchains]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tezos]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4905</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the annoying chip shortage to power outages all over the world, crypto mining is a thing of the past. Considering the power consumption, regulations will definitely come for gas guzzlers. In that regard, if there is a way forward for cryptocurrencies, it would be the green road of proof of stake. In the long [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/top-energy-efficient-blockhains/">Top Energy Efficient Blockchains [Investment Opportunity]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>From the annoying chip shortage to power outages all over the world, crypto mining is a thing of the past. Considering the power consumption, regulations will definitely come for gas guzzlers. In that regard, if there is a way forward for cryptocurrencies, it would be the green road of proof of stake. In the long run Bitcoin and Ethereum mining can very well become illegal as we’re already facing a huge energy crisis. With that in mind, we have gathered a list of top energy efficient blockchains which are also solid choices for investment in 2022. Basically, these energy efficient blockchains are ranked based on their power consumption in 2021.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><span class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Invest in energy efficient blockchains on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a>.</span></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Future is Green</strong></h2>



<p>Before we proceed, let’s address the hall of shame including Bitcoin and Ethereum as the first and second worst blockchains in terms of power consumption. With 89,780,000,000 kWh each year while Ethereum consumes 17,300,000,000 kWh. To put that in perspective, an average US household consumes an average of 10,600 kWh.</p>



<p>Objectively, that kind of power consumption is too high to be able to dethrone fiat anytime soon. Of Course, the primary argument or BTC power consumption is that the network is designed to use excess electricity from power grids or green energy. But at the end of the day, mining companies are printing money like crazy and do not care for power consumption. The only way forward, is to invest in energy efficient blockchains since upcoming regulations can seriously harm the old ones.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the proof of work algorithm is also slow and archaic compared with PoS. Proof of Stake handles a lot more transactions per second while using a lot less energy. But that is a topic for another day.</p>



<p>Without Further a do, here are the most energy efficient blockchain networks right now:</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">1. <strong>Polkadot</strong></h2>



<p>For the first spot, we have Polkadot network with only 70,237 kWh yearly consumption. This amount is only 6.6 times higher than the average US household.</p>



<p>And here we have yet another third generation blockchain network found by a previous Ethereum member. Initially, Gavin James Wood had a different vision in mind about the (PoS) algorithm. The final goal is to create an infrastructure to create a network of blockchains that are effortlessly communicating with each other.</p>



<p>The multiple blockchain approach provides a better cross-chain interoperability and easier communication. Gavin believes that a single blockchain network can never be complete and a multi-chain architecture will be much more efficient.</p>



<p>The DOT is the token for this multi-chain network. It is currently number 9 by market cap. With the first ICO in 2017, it managed to raise $145 million. Despite being relatively new, it has experienced a huge growth in popularity. DOT has had one of the most successful initial coin offerings in history, raising over 200 million in two ICOs, first one in 2017 and the other in 2020.</p>



<p>To learn everything about the network, continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-polkadot/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Polkadot</a>“</p>



<p>You can buy DOT on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> with the lowest exchange fees.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">2. <strong>Avalanche</strong></h2>



<p>Standing behind Polkadot, the Avalanche network consumes $489,311 kWh in a year. While this number is considerably higher than Polkadot, it is still an impressive figure.</p>



<p>Avalanche Blockchain, is an open, programmable smart contracts platform for decentralized applications. It was launched by AVA labs in 2020 as an Ethereum competitor. In terms of performance, the network offers light-speed transactions with scalability that is far better than Ethereum. As for the cherry on top, the transaction fees on the network are extremely low as compared with Ethereum.</p>



<p>At the same time, compared with the Solana network, the Avalanche network is far more decentralized. This will assure security and reliability for the future to come.</p>



<p>AVAX is the native token of the network and is currently 11th in the ranks. With an impressive $25.3 billion, it is continuing to close the gap with Ethereum.</p>



<p>You can Buy AVAX on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> with no KYC.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">3. <strong>Algorand</strong></h2>



<p>And the Bronze goes to Algorand with 512,670 kWh yearly consumption. ALGO has been defying expectations in the past year and is expected to shine in 2022.</p>



<p>Officially launched in 2019, Algorand is a proof of stake blockchain network with great emphasis on scalability and speed. As on open-source and decentralized network, Algorand is not a new idea to begin with. However, where it proves to be different is the unique design that allows for faster consensus. With a two-tiered structure, this payment-focused network achieves amazing scalability.</p>



<p>Currently, Algorand network can process over 1000 transactions per second while transaction finality takes less than five seconds. At this point you might say that there are faster networks out there. Well, yes but actually no!</p>



<p>We’ve previously talked about the blockchain trilemma on this blog. Essentially, it is difficult and rare for a blockchain to offer security, speed and decentralization. For example, Solana network is one of the fastest ones out there but it is not that decentralized. In that regard, Algorand is maintaining all positive aspects of an ideal blockchain at once.</p>



<p>ALGO is the native token of the network and is currently ranked 23rd with a market cap of over $8.5 billion.</p>



<p>Buy ALGO on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> anonymously.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">4. <strong>Cardano</strong></h2>



<p>The Cardano network is essentially the founder of proof of stake. Considering the massive number of transactions, Cardano has consumed 598,755 kWh last year which is stellar.</p>



<p>The Cardano project launched in 2017. It was the third generation of blockchain networks. One that successfully dealt with some of the greatest challenges of previous generations. Issues such as high gas fees and scalability by introducing the Ouroboros, a proof of stake algorithm to mine blocks which will be further explained in the article.</p>



<p>In 2017, the Cardano project started as a third-gen open-source and public blockchain platform. ADA is the native token of the platform. It is Led by Charles Hoskinson, one of the co-founders of Ethereum. Cardano had a great emphasis on being future-proof by being peer-reviewed and methodically developed by academic experts in the field. Cardano views itself as the updated version of Ethereum. Moving towards building a connected and decentralized system and providing banking services to the unbanked.</p>



<p>Buy ADA instantly and hassle free on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.okchanger.com/exchangers/jolixo" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">OkChanger</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. We are on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bestchange</a> and are always amongst the top exchanges.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/top-energy-efficient-blockhains/">Top Energy Efficient Blockchains [Investment Opportunity]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/top-energy-efficient-blockhains/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>No Altcoin Season Yet! Investor Sentiment is Shifting</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/investor-sentiment-altcoin-season/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/investor-sentiment-altcoin-season/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 06:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin Season]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4796</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Seasons come and go, as the sun circles around us quarter by quarter, we await a season not in our calendars but in our hearts. Indeed, the altcoin season, the holy season of returns is once again delayed. According to CoinShares, the bear market in the recent months is encouraging crypto investors towards Bitcoin and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/investor-sentiment-altcoin-season/">No Altcoin Season Yet! Investor Sentiment is Shifting</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Seasons come and go, as the sun circles around us quarter by quarter, we await a season not in our calendars but in our hearts. Indeed, the altcoin season, the holy season of returns is once again delayed. According to <a href="https://coinshares.com/research/digital-asset-survey">CoinShares</a>, the bear market in the recent months is encouraging crypto investors towards Bitcoin and Ethereum and away from altcoins. Generally speaking, the investor sentiment could take some time to shift in favor of an altcoin season. Especially, the highly volatile market can turn on a dime. However, it seems that previous speculations are shattered as BTC dominance continues to grow.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote is-style-default"><blockquote><p><span class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Exchange cryptocurrencies to PayPal on <a href="http://www.hi.excahnge/">jolixo</a>. No KYC required.</span></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Tis Not the Altcoin Season</strong></h2>



<p>The digital asset manager CoinShares has done a recent study of investor sentiment. Interestingly, investor sentiment in Bitcoin and Ethereum improved in December 2021 following the deep price correction. On the other hand, the appeal to invest in majority of altcoins especially ADA and Solana decline in the meantime.</p>



<p><em>“During the month of December 2021, when market prices were declining sharply, investor sentiment improved for the larger digital assets Bitcoin, Ethereum and multi-asset, while sentiment declined for the smaller assets such as Cardano, Solana and other altcoins.”</em></p>



<p>However, investor sentiment in Polkadot remained unchanged according to the survey.</p>



<p>What does it say about the investors? Considering the higher volatility of such altcoins and Bitcoin’s dominance, investors are more inclined to buy Bitcoin and Ethereum. In that sense, the deep correction spooked the altcoin season away.</p>



<p>Furthermore, allocations to digital assets are correlated to investor sentiment according to the study.</p>



<p>“<em>Allocations to digital assets mirrored the growth outlook for digital assets, where allocations were minimally increased for the larger coins at the expense of altcoins.”</em></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Regulations Coming</strong></h2>



<p>At this point, it is certain that a vast majority of countries would impose heavy regulations on the crypto market. Primarily, the speculation over regulations is single handedly pushing the market down.</p>



<p><em>“There has also been an almost doubling in the number of investors concerned about regulation.</em></p>



<p><em>Regulation has taken the top spot for the key risks amongst investors despite greater clarity on MiCA [Regulation of Markets in Crypto-assets] and the recent decision from the SEC [U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission] to allow a Bitcoin futures ETF [Exchange-Traded Fund].”</em></p>



<p>The growing concerns and frustrating speculations are now amplified as regulators remain quiet and unclear about the upcoming regulations.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.okchanger.com/exchangers/jolixo" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">OkChanger</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. We are on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bestchange</a> and are always amongst the top exchanges.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/investor-sentiment-altcoin-season/">No Altcoin Season Yet! Investor Sentiment is Shifting</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/investor-sentiment-altcoin-season/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top 5 Ethereum Killers for 2022 [Altcoins to Watch]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/top-5-ethereum-killers/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/top-5-ethereum-killers/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 07:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVALANCHE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AVAX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Killer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Luna]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4746</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Have you tried minting an NFT on the Ethereum network or just simply made a transaction on it? If so, you would know about the sky-rocketing gas fees on the network. As Ethereum lags behind delivering the promise of Proof of Stake, Ethereum killers are rising up to dethrone the queen. On the other hand, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/top-5-ethereum-killers/">Top 5 Ethereum Killers for 2022 [Altcoins to Watch]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Have you tried minting an NFT on the Ethereum network or just simply made a transaction on it? If so, you would know about the sky-rocketing gas fees on the network. As Ethereum lags behind delivering the promise of Proof of Stake, Ethereum killers are rising up to dethrone the queen. On the other hand, Ethereum killers are achieving incredible performance indicators and proving blockhain’s utility much better than the old dogs. So much so, that in fact Bitcoin and Ethereum are starting to look obsolete as compared with the up and coming altcoins. If you’re a believer of Ethereum downfall, here are the top 5 Ethereum Killers to invest on for 2022.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><span class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Help kill Ethereum by buying the top 5 altcoins on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> 🙂</span></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Ethereum Killers Rise!</strong></h2>



<p>First and foremost, we need to talk about the ground rules. There are multiple aspects of a blockchain network but for this article, we are specifically focused on scalability, network-fees and decentralized nature of each one. In short, we will take a look at who is actually closer to solve the blockchain trilemma.</p>



<p>It should also be noted that Ethereum 2.0 is set to debut in 2022. In that regard, Ethereum will adopt PoS algorithm which will positively affect all of the characteristics mentioned above. That being said, considering the scale of the transition and the gruesome challenges, it would be fair to maintain a little bit of pessimism. After all, Ethereum is by far the most advanced and extensive blockchain network out there. Not to be a cynic, but we will believe Ethereum 2.0 when we see it.</p>



<p>Simply speaking, Ethereum is currently behind in terms of scalability, gas-fees and environmental harm. The Proof of Work algorithm is simply an archaic technology with considerably low efficiency. Considering the critics, cryptocurrencies have a bad reputation due to the environmental harm resulted from mining and the ongoing chip shortage. With that in mind, all Ethereum killers must be PoS blockchains.</p>



<p>Without further ado, Let’s jump right in!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Solana (SOL)</strong></h2>



<p>Yes, yes, yes. We are fully aware of the network outages and the less than decentralized servers. Solana is not as good of a boy as previously thought. However, it is simply a darling amongst institutional investors and enterprises. And that is what essentially causes rallies for the price. The Solana network is arguably the fastest blockchain network as of early 2022. To make it an even better deal, the network fees are ridiculously low compared to Ethereum. Think of Solana as the Ducati of cryptocurrencies, it’s fast and exotic, but sometimes the network can act up. Interestingly, despite the hiccups on the network, the investors did not dump Solana and move on to other competitors. And that, is a positive sign since Solana labs has ensured investors that the network will not fail them once again.</p>



<p>In short, Solana is a blockchain platform for decentralized applications (DApps). The network utilizes Proof of Stake consensus algorithm. However, in a world full of PoS blockchain networks, Solana has managed to achieve some impressive figures. The network can support up to 50,000 transactions per second (TPS) and requires 400 milliseconds to build a block. With the quickly increasing number of validators currently at 1,061, the network is one of the fastest out there.</p>



<p>However, what good is a fast network if expensive? Well, in terms of transaction fees, the Solana network maintains the most competitive fees across the board. With an average of $0.00025 per transaction, it’s no wonder why many of the largest institutional investors use this network.</p>



<p>This flexible network has smart contract capabilities, DeFi, NFT, Web3 and many more. According to the official website, the ecosystem has currently over 400 running projects.</p>



<p>To learn everything about the network, continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-solana/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Solana?</a>”</p>



<p>You can Buy SOL with the lowest fees on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Cardano (ADA)</strong></h2>



<p>Arguably, Cardano is the well-behaved good boy in your school who reminds the teacher of the forgotten homework. Just look at Charles Hoskinson, an academic-oriented man who double checks everything and is not in a hurry to pump ADA. The Cardano network has perhaps the best reputation for a network. Low gas-fees, high scalability and truly decentralized are what you get from Cardano. Subsequently, Cardano is like the Honda of cryptocurrencies, reliable, robust and sensible. It may not be as fast as a Ducati (Solana) but it’ll go further. Motorcycle references aside, Cardano is going that extra mile to ensure the investors of the security and utility of the network. The peer-reviewed developments are something that nobody else is willing to do.</p>



<p>In 2017, the Cardano project started as a third-gen open-source and public blockchain platform. ADA is the native token of the platform. It is Led by Charles Hoskinson, one of the co-founders of Ethereum. Cardano had a great emphasis on being future-proof by being peer-reviewed and methodically developed by academic experts in the field. Cardano views itself as the updated version of Ethereum. Moving towards building a connected and decentralized system and providing banking services to the unbanked.</p>



<p>To answer what is ADA, we first need to introduce the Cardano project. As a blockchain network, Cardano is an extensive ecosystem with the native token ADA. Cardano takes pride in being one of the first pioneers of the proof of stake algorithm. And surely a successful one at that. It managed to successfully eliminated many of the issues related to crypto. It did an astonishing job dealing with Problems such as high gas fees, scalability and high transaction fees. During this process, ADA, gained immense popularity and rose through the ranks like a champ!</p>



<p>You can Buy ADA with the Lowest fees on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>.</p>



<p>To learn everything about Cardano, continue reading&#8221; <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-ada-a-guide-to-the-cardano-project/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is ADA?</a>&#8220;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Polkadot (DOT)</strong></h2>



<p>Ironically, two of the five Ethereum killers of our list belong to former Ethereum developers. Both Cardano and Polkadot founders used to be primary founders of Ethereum. Considering the state of Ethereum in early 2022, it is not difficult to guess why!</p>



<p>Polkadot is one of the most innovative blockchain networks that successfully gave birth to an impossible idea. What if there was a blockchain network that could connect all other blockchain networks? Well, Polkadot did that and then some! The network managed to triumphantly create the “internet of blockchains” and CoinCannon the gap between other networks. As for the results, we have a highly utilitarian network that offers the best of all worlds through communication and friendship. Ultimately, Polkadot is like the KTM of cryptocurrencies since it is its own thing without looking to follow others.</p>



<p>Initially found in 2016 and launched in 2020, Polkadot is another one of those cases where an Ethereum co-founder decided to walk down the road not taken. And much like ADA, Gavin Wood was able to make waves in the industry with a revolutionary innovation. As of October 2021, Polkadot Coin is the 7th cryptocurrency by market cap, priced at $42. Considering the very young age, Polkadot has deep roots in the industry as a serious blockchain network. In a time period of less than two years, the network has fulfilled all of the advertised promises and is delivering astonishing results.</p>



<p>You can Buy DOT on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> anonymously with the lowest fees.</p>



<p>To learn everything about DOT, continue reading &#8220;<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-polkadot/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Polkadot</a>?&#8221;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Avalanche (AVAX)</strong></h2>



<p>Decentralized Applications (dApps) managed to bring finally bring some real-world use cases to the public. Initially, the Ethereum network was the first one to offer smart contracts and dApps. However, he who shall be first, is not always the best. The Avalanche network climbed the ranks so quickly as a smart contracts network. In fact, the name Avalanche (AVAX) was mostly unheard of before 2021. In a short time, AVAX jumped in the ranks and as of early Q1 2022, it is 12<sup>th</sup> with a market cap of $17 billion USD. Avalanche is like the Yamaha of cryptocurrencies, it’s fast. It’s reliable and it is seriously underrated.</p>



<p>Avalanche Blockchain, is an open, programmable smart contracts platform for decentralized applications. It was launched by AVA labs in 2020 as an Ethereum competitor. In terms of performance, the network offers light-speed transactions with scalability that is far better than Ethereum. As for the cherry on top, the transaction fees on the network are extremely low as compared with Ethereum.</p>



<p>At the same time, compared with the Solana network, the Avalanche network is far more decentralized. This will assure security and reliability for the future to come.</p>



<p>You can Buy AVAX on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo.</a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Terra (LUNA)</strong></h2>



<p>Stablecoins are essentially the blood running in the veins of the crypto market. As a matter of fact, the crypto industry is absolutely reliant on stablecoins. The Terra network managed to fill that gap in the stablecoins and offer an intuitive approach to cryptocurrencies. Undoubtedly, there is a lot of money to be made in providing stablecoins. Subsequently, all that money will find its way to LUNA the native token of the network. With that in mind, LUNA is backed by something that will always have a solid demand. In that sense, Terra is the Kawasaki of cryptocurrencies. Why? Well it’s accessible, but in the meantime offers awesome performance.</p>



<p>The Terra network is an open-source blockchain protocol that works as a payment platform for stablecoins. Essentially, the network creates stablecoins pegged to fiat currencies. These stablecoins constantly track the price of these fiat currencies. Within the network, users can buy, hold, trade or simply exchange all stablecoins.</p>



<p>Perhaps the biggest challenge for any stablecoin is to keep the value pegged and stable. To overcome this challenge, Terra network balances the supply and demand by their governance token LUNA. Used for both governance and mining, LUNA ensures that all stablecoins remain stable. In that regard, LUNA acts as a counterweight in the network. Users can either burn LUNA to mint Terra or simple stake LUNA.</p>



<p>You can buy LUNA on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> without compromising your privacy.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Buy Ethereum Killers on <strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.okchanger.com/exchangers/jolixo" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">OkChanger</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. We are on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bestchange</a> and are always amongst the top exchanges.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/top-5-ethereum-killers/">Top 5 Ethereum Killers for 2022 [Altcoins to Watch]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/top-5-ethereum-killers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana Network Faces Issues Once Again</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-network-faces-issues/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-network-faces-issues/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 06:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sell Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana Network]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4567</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Solana network is facing a new series of issues starting a few days ago. The network had more than 4 hours of downtime in January 4th and as of now there are still transactions failures. Solana Labs has issued a statement regarding the situation. However, one thing is for sure, Solana network found a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-network-faces-issues/">Solana Network Faces Issues Once Again</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Solana network is facing a new series of issues starting a few days ago. The network had more than 4 hours of downtime in January 4<sup>th</sup> and as of now there are still transactions failures. Solana Labs has issued a statement regarding the situation. However, one thing is for sure, Solana network found a hell of a time to find itself in a pickle. Just as the crypto market experienced a crash, the network decided to act up.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><strong><span class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Buy and Sell Solana Anonymously with the lowest exchange fees on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a>.</span></strong></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Solana Network Under Attack?</strong></h2>



<p>A Chinese journalist named Coin Wu reported on Twitter that the downtime was initially due to DDoS attacks. This was a serious allegation that seemed likely because the Solana network is not as decentralized as some of the competitors. In fact, following a strong bull run in 2021, the network experienced a serious outage in September. That is when users found out that a considerable majority of the servers are centralized. Naturally the news was potent enough to cause a deep price correction for SOL.</p>



<p>Shortly after Wu’s Tweet, Anatoly Yakovenko who is the Solana Lab’s co-founder made a statement denying third-party attacks. Yakovenko blamed network congestion for the outage and the ongoing performance problems.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">👋, sorry that’s not at all what happened. There was some congestion due to mis metered transitions, and some users experienced their txs timing out and had to retry.</p>&mdash; toly 🇺🇸 (@aeyakovenko) <a href="https://twitter.com/aeyakovenko/status/1478575366172123140?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 5, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Too Many Chrome Tabs Open!</strong></h2>



<p>Following the Analtoly’s Tweet, the Solana foundation clarified the situation. Essentially, the foundation claims an increased number of high compute transactions caused a bottleneck in performance.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">1/ The Solana Network is currently experiencing degraded performance due to an increase in high compute transactions, which is reducing network capacity to several thousand transactions per second. This is leading to some failed transactions for users.</p>&mdash; Solana Status (@SolanaStatus) <a href="https://twitter.com/SolanaStatus/status/1479126136953053187?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 6, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>This is not the first time Solana faces network issues. Since their official debut in 2020, there have been numerous network problems. Problems of this nature can and will happen from time to time. Nevertheless, as seen back in 2021, they can cause serious damage to the price of the native token. In case these issues remain persistent, they could spook investors and cause a massive dump. In this case, SOL is down more than 23% in only one week. The plunge is partly due to network issues but mostly stems from the bear market of the early January.</p>



<p>The Solana network is one of the fastest and scalable blockchain networks in the world. The smart contract’s blockchain network claims to be the fastest in the world.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.okchanger.com/exchangers/jolixo" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">OkChanger</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. We are on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bestchange</a> and are always amongst the top exchanges.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-network-faces-issues/">Solana Network Faces Issues Once Again</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-network-faces-issues/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
