<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>BTC Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/btc/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 09:03:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Analysis of Bitcoin&#8217;s Continued Drop Amid ETF Approval Expectations</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/analysis-of-bitcoins-continued-drop-amid-etf-approval-expectations/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/analysis-of-bitcoins-continued-drop-amid-etf-approval-expectations/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Leyli Mamikhani]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 06:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=8056</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Despite the most recent changes regarding the Bitcoin ETF, the landscape of virtual currencies is once more in the midst of a profound shift. The most valuable cryptocurrency in the world of digital assets, Bitcoin, has recently declined, losing more than 2.4% of its value. This year has witnessed a stunning 156% acquisition in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/analysis-of-bitcoins-continued-drop-amid-etf-approval-expectations/">Analysis of Bitcoin&#8217;s Continued Drop Amid ETF Approval Expectations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Despite the most recent changes regarding the Bitcoin ETF, the landscape of virtual currencies is once more in the midst of a profound shift. The most valuable cryptocurrency in the world of digital assets, Bitcoin, has recently declined, losing more than 2.4% of its value.</p>



<p>This year has witnessed a stunning <strong>156% acquisition</strong> in the value of the most popular digital currency, Bitcoin. The primary cause for these changes is the conjecture that the launch of ETFs could generate a new wave of demand. Undoubtedly, not all of this can be considered entirely beneficial because there is a lot of speculation in the market on whether or not the approval of these ETFs would lead to profit-taking strategies. Such speculation can potentially negatively impact the shifts in the value of bitcoin.</p>



<p><strong>CryptoQuant</strong> described what happened as a possible<em> <strong>&#8220;sell the news&#8221;</strong></em> incident, referring to the wave that formed upon the news.</p>



<p>The term used above refers to a well-known phenomenon in the capital markets: the rising sentiment, leverage, and asset prices before a positive event, followed by a sharp decline in prices.</p>



<p>This is because smart traders take advantage of overloaded long deals, ensnaring leveraged traders and pressuring them to sell out or liquidate during drops.</p>



<p>The announcement that an ETF for Bitcoin is being approved can be seen as beneficial since it allows institutions to start investing in the cryptocurrency, increasing buying pressure.</p>



<p>The memo stated that &#8220;Bitcoin short holders are experiencing an unrealistic 30% profit margin, which has historically been before price corrections (areas marked with red circles).&#8221; Furthermore, short-term holders keep spending Bitcoin profitably, and returns typically materialize once short-term losses are realized.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Conclusion</h2>



<h1 class="wp-block-heading">ETF Approval: What to Expect from Bitcoin?</h1>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Bitcoin has recently declined, losing 2.4% of its value, and is currently trading at $42,400</li>



<li>2023 has witnessed a stunning 156% acquisition in Bitcoin&#8217;s value</li>



<li>The main cause of this decline can be the conjecture of the launch of ETFs and the newly generated wave of demand.</li>



<li>Bitcoin short holders are experiencing an unrealistic 30% profit margin.</li>



<li>CryptoQuant described what happened as a possible &#8220;sell the news&#8221; incident, referring to the wave that formed upon the news.</li>



<li>Lots of speculation in the market on whether or not the approval of these ETFs would lead to profit-taking strategies that can potentially negatively impact the shifts in the value of bitcoin.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/analysis-of-bitcoins-continued-drop-amid-etf-approval-expectations/">Analysis of Bitcoin&#8217;s Continued Drop Amid ETF Approval Expectations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/analysis-of-bitcoins-continued-drop-amid-etf-approval-expectations/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin [Instant]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin-2/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin-2/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 07:36:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AdvCash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6435</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking to exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin? CoinCannon offers everything you need! Digital currencies have been a quintessential asset for online payments. On top of that, cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin (BTC) are gaining momentum as popular payment methods. In that regard, users will find themselves in the need to exchange their assets into one another. And [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin-2/">How to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin [Instant]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking to exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin? CoinCannon offers everything you need! Digital currencies have been a quintessential asset for online payments. On top of that, cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin (BTC) are gaining momentum as popular payment methods. In that regard, users will find themselves in the need to exchange their assets into one another. And by doing so, the exchange fees can quickly put a dent in their pockets. Fortunately, you can easily exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin with the lowest fees, full anonymity and 24/7 online support. Want to know how?</p>



<p>Head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select AdvCash and Bitcoin in the exchange box and you’re good to go!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a verified and active Advanced Cash (AdvCash) account. Make sure that the transaction amount does not exceed your withdrawal limit. To receive Bitcoin (BTC), you will need a reliable and secure crypto wallet. Primarily, we suggest you use Trust Wallet. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon provides a hassle-free KYC process and no sign up to speed up your work flow. Despite that, there are benefits for those who sign up on CoinCannon. For example, you can take advantage of <a href="https://hi.exchange/jolixo-affiliate" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon affiliate</a> program and earn money online.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Advanced Cash (AdvCash)?</strong></h2>



<p>Before we go on to talk about how to convert AdvCash to Bitcoin, let’s take a quick look at what this digital currency is. AdvCash is a currency used for online payments. It is based in Belize which provides immunity from national laws of other countries for it. As an offshore currency, it is also encrypted much like cryptocurrencies and benefits from better anonymity and security. The Advance Cash company provides an account for users that allows for a variety of currencies to operate through it. In many ways, it is a lot like Payeer.</p>



<p>And much like Payeer, AdvCash supports transfers in both fiat and cryptocurrency form. With a virtual wallet, users can transfer funds and make payments with very low commission. What makes it interesting, is that Advance Cash is also compatible with other payment systems such as WebMoney or Perfect Money. With free international transfers, users get to enjoy a wide variety of currencies all in a virtual wallet. Furthermore, there are both physical and virtual bank cards available for quick and cheap international Visa/Mastercard payments.</p>



<p>The company was founded in 2014 as a competitor for PayPal and much like its peers, it has gained notable success in the past few years. As the need for virtual banking grows, online payment processing companies continue to narrow the gap with PayPal. Although, such companies are not as popular as PayPal, they offer a lot more freedom.</p>



<p>Keep in mind that you can also <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-advcash-to-payeer-usd/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange AdvCash to PayPal</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin?</strong></h2>



<p>Bitcoin is a digital currency that was developed following the housing market crash in January 2009. This cryptocurrency follows the ideas started out by the pseudonymous and mysterious Satoshi Nakamoto in a whitepaper. The identity of the individual or individuals that developed the software is still a mystery. Unlike government-issued currencies, Bitcoin is operated by a decentralized authority and offers the promise of lower transaction fees than traditional online payment mechanisms.</p>



<p>There are no physical Bitcoins and the coins you see are novelty coins that do not have any real value without the code inscribed on them. Bitcoin is only balances retained on a public ledger that everyone has transparent access to, and is verified by a massive amount of computing power along with all Bitcoin transactions. Bitcoins are not issued or supported as a commodity by any banks or governments, nor are individual bitcoins valuable. Although it is not legal tender, the popularity of Bitcoin charts is high, and hundreds of other virtual currencies collectively referred to as Altcoins have been launched following this cryptocurrency.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the homepage first, then select AdvCash USD and Bitcoin from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of BTC you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>



<li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your AdvCash and Payeer wallet details and email. The phone number is optional.</li>



<li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li>Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the AdvCash gateway and make the payment to our AdvCash account. Having transferred your AdvCash USD to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>



<li>By finishing all the steps above, our team will send the Bitcoin to your wallet as soon as possible</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>Just like that, you have now converted AdvCash to BTC. In general, WMZ payments are inconsistent in terms of how long they might take. Give it a few minutes and the AdvCash USD will be in your account ASAP. In the meantime, you can follow up on your order using the Track ID provided for you. Simply enter the track id in the required section on homepage to see at which point your order is. Remember not to share your Track ID with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin-2/">How to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin [Instant]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cryptocurrency Regulations: The SEC is Divided!</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrency-regulations/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrency-regulations/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 11:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6409</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency regulations have been a hot topic in recent years, with governments and regulatory agencies around the world grappling with how to approach this rapidly evolving industry. In the United States, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) plays a key role in regulating the cryptocurrency market. For the most part, the SEC has been showing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrency-regulations/">Cryptocurrency Regulations: The SEC is Divided!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Cryptocurrency regulations have been a hot topic in recent years, with governments and regulatory agencies around the world grappling with how to approach this rapidly evolving industry. In the United States, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) plays a key role in regulating the cryptocurrency market. For the most part, the SEC has been showing an anti-crypto attitude. However, Commissioner Hester Peirce, a well-known advocate for innovation in the crypto space, has recently <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/statement/peirce-rendering-inovation-2023-04-12" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">voiced her dissent</a> against Chair Gary Gensler&#8217;s anti-crypto agenda. Of course, we can be sure about an upcoming shock wave of regulatory action coming for crypto. However, recent debates show how there is internal conflict within the SEC regarding crypto assets.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Commissioner Pierce on Cryptocurrency Regulations</strong></h2>



<p>In a recent speech, Commissioner Peirce criticized the SEC&#8217;s proposal to adjust the definition of &#8220;exchange&#8221; to include decentralized finance (DeFi) protocols. According to Peirce, this change would be counterproductive, promoting stagnation and centralization rather than embracing the potential of new technology.</p>



<p>&#8220;Stagnation, centralization, expatriation, and extinction are the watchwords of this release. Rather than embracing the promise of new technology as we have done in the past, here we propose to embrace stagnation, force centralization, urge expatriation, and welcome extinction of new technology. Accordingly, I dissent,&#8221; said Peirce.</p>



<p>Commissioner Peirce further highlighted that the SEC&#8217;s proposal could potentially violate the First Amendment protections by categorizing blockchain ecosystems as a &#8220;group,&#8221; creating ambiguity around their speech rights.</p>



<p>&#8220;The release&#8217;s ambiguity undermines fundamental First Amendment protections. Because the release makes everybody involved in the relevant blockchain ecosystem part of a &#8216;group,&#8217; it creates significant ambiguity around what speech requires government pre-approval, which will unavoidably chill constitutionally-protected speech,&#8221; Peirce explained.</p>



<p>Peirce also emphasized the importance of the SEC remaining open to the idea of tweaking its rules to accommodate new technologies, something she believes the Commission understood in the 1990s.</p>



<p>&#8220;The Commission of the 1990s understood this basic principle and created space for significant innovations in securities trading. This release, on the other hand, takes the view that any business model that cannot meet the specific requirements of our existing regulatory model does not belong in our markets,&#8221; Peirce stated.</p>



<p>In essence, Peirce argues that the SEC&#8217;s current approach to cryptocurrency regulations is hindering innovation and preventing cutting-edge businesses from entering the market. She believes that a Commission serious about regulating, rather than destroying, the cryptocurrency market should reflect on its past regulatory failures and be open to adapting its rules to accommodate the unique characteristics of cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-sec-s-iron-fist"><strong>The SEC’s Iron Fist</strong></h2>



<p>Peirce&#8217;s dissenting voice within the SEC sheds light on the internal conflict within the regulatory agency regarding how to approach cryptocurrency regulations. Chair Gary Gensler has taken a more stringent stance on cryptocurrencies, expressing concerns about investor protection and market integrity. On the other hand, Commissioner Peirce has been a vocal advocate for embracing innovation and allowing the cryptocurrency market to flourish.</p>



<p>The debate over cryptocurrency regulations is not limited to the SEC. Governments and regulatory agencies worldwide are grappling with how to effectively regulate the rapidly growing cryptocurrency market. Some countries have taken a more progressive approach, recognizing the potential of cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology, while others have adopted a more cautious stance, expressing concerns about risks such as money laundering and fraud.</p>



<p>In the United States, the lack of clear and consistent cryptocurrency regulations has created uncertainty for businesses and investors operating in the crypto space. Many argue that a well-regulated cryptocurrency market could provide significant benefits, such as increased investor protection, market transparency, and economic growth. However, excessive regulation could stifle innovation and hinder the development of the cryptocurrency market.</p>



<p>The SEC, as a key regulatory agency in the U.S., plays a crucial role in shaping cryptocurrency regulations. Commissioner Peirce&#8217;s dissenting voice highlights the need for a balanced and pragmatic approach to regulating cryptocurrencies. While it is important to address risks and protect investors, paralyzing a whole industry does not sound like a democratic approach either.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrency-regulations/">Cryptocurrency Regulations: The SEC is Divided!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrency-regulations/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Bitcoin with Dai [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 10:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6379</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you are looking to buy Bitcoin with Dai, CoinCannon is the ultimate platform for the job. Bitcoin has finally managed to bounce back and move above the critical resistance level at $25k. Subsequently, investors are once again eager to invest in the top crypto asset by market cap. On top of that, the mass [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Buy Bitcoin with Dai [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you are looking to buy Bitcoin with Dai, CoinCannon is the ultimate platform for the job. Bitcoin has finally managed to bounce back and move above the critical resistance level at $25k. Subsequently, investors are once again eager to invest in the top crypto asset by market cap. On top of that, the mass adoption of BTC has turned it into a utilitarian digital asset. Today, thousands of credible online stores accept Bitcoin as payment. Fortunately, you can now pay for goods and services via BTC and there’s lots of stuff you can <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-with-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">buy with Bitcoin</a>. However, if you’re holding DAI, you can instantly exchange Dai into Bitcoin in only a matter of minutes. Want to get started? Head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Dai on the left box and Bitcoin on the right and you’re good to go!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/">How to exchange cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Bitcoin with Dai?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive Bitcoin (BTC). In case your Dai wallet supports BTC, you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is DAI?</strong></h2>



<p>Before we go over how to buy Bitcoin with Dai, let’s take a brief look at Dai as a stablecoin.</p>



<p>DAI is an Ethereum-based stablecoin. A stablecoin is a cryptocurrency with a pegged value to another currency. In case of DAI, it is pegged to the US dollar and much like Tether and USDC, Dai will always be worth $1. Stablecoins are a crucial part of the crypto market as they offer very little volatility. In that regard, investors use stablecoins to save their funds in the form of a reliable and stable asset.</p>



<p>What makes DAI unique is a clever design that eliminates the biggest concerns for stablecoins. Generally speaking, conventional stablecoins require a massive reserve by the company. For example, for every Tether USD, the Tether company must hold $1 USD in their reserve. This is a huge issue for companies as it is difficult to provide liquidity and keep it consistent.</p>



<p>DAI offers a new solution for this problem. By using an automated system of smart contracts on Ethereum blockchain, DAI does now need a reserve. Using collateralized debt denominated in ETH allows DAI to maintain the 1:1 ration with USD. Simply speaking, users can deposit Ethereum or other cryptocurrencies can borrow against the value of their deposit and generate new DAI. The currency is this case is known as collateral.</p>



<p>You can <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange Dai to PayPal</a> on CoinCannon with the lowest exchange fees ever!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Invest in Bitcoin?</strong></h2>



<p>Well, there is hardly anyone these days who is not familiar with the definition of Bitcoin and what the cryptocurrency is capable of carrying out. However, let’s briefly go through what bitcoin is and where it comes from, then we can focus on the benefits of using this cryptocurrency and explain why to buy Bitcoin with Perfect Money.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a Cryptocurrency that was created after the housing market collapse in January 2009. It follows the ideas set out by the enigmatic and pseudonymous Satoshi Nakamoto in a whitepaper. The identity of the individual or individuals who developed this cryptocurrency is still under wraps. Unlike government-issued currencies, Bitcoin provides the guarantee of lower transaction costs than conventional online payment systems and is regulated by a decentralized authority.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a tempting opportunity for investment and great tool for doing financial transactions. In that regard, it has been a solid choice for investment as an asset that is truly decentralized. On top of that, there are countless online platform that accept Bitcoin as payment which makes BTC a utilitarian option for online payments.</p>



<p>So, if You’ve decided to invest in BTC, you can buy Bitcoin with Dai in only a matter of minutes on CoinCannon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-buy-bitcoin-with-dai"><strong>How to Buy Bitcoin with DAI?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Dai (DAI) on the left field and Bitcoin (BTC) on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your BTC wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your DAI to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>You’re All Set!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Bitcoin (BTC) to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Buy Bitcoin with Dai [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 06:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AdvCash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6369</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking to exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin? CoinCannon is the ultimate platform for the job. These days, online platform accept a confusing variety of digital assets including cryptocurrencies. With that, comes to need to exchange these assets into one another on a regular basis. Yet, it could be difficult to find an exchange platform that offers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking to exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin? <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is the ultimate platform for the job. These days, online platform accept a confusing variety of digital assets including cryptocurrencies. With that, comes to need to exchange these assets into one another on a regular basis. Yet, it could be difficult to find an exchange platform that offers great exchange rates and anonymity at the same time. Fortunately, CoinCannon offers the most competitive exchange fees all while providing a hassle-free KYC process for the customers. Today, we will go over how to exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin with no hidden fees, no KYC and 24/7 online support.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange AdvCash to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange direction, you will need a verified AdvCash account. Make sure that the transaction amount does not exceed your withdrawal limit. Furthermore, you will need a reliable crypto wallet to hold Bitcoin. There are multiple options out there, but we do suggest Trust Wallet as a suitable wallet.  As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email address and there is no KYC (know your customer) required. However, there are numerous benefits for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. Want a good reason why? You can win $100 gifts on CoinCannon every single month!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is AdvCash?</strong></h2>



<p>AdvCash is a currency used for online payments. It is based in Belize which provides immunity from national laws of other countries for it. As an offshore currency, it is also encrypted much like cryptocurrencies and benefits from better anonymity and security. The Advance Cash company provides an account for users that allows for a variety of currencies to operate through it. In many ways, it is a lot like Payeer.</p>



<p>And much like Payeer, AdvCash supports transfers in both fiat and cryptocurrency form. With a virtual wallet, users can transfer funds and make payments with very low commission. What makes it interesting, is that Advance Cash is also compatible with other payment systems such as WebMoney or Perfect Money. With free international transfers, users get to enjoy a wide variety of currencies all in a virtual wallet. Furthermore, there are both physical and virtual bank cards available for quick and cheap international Visa/Mastercard payments.</p>



<p>The company was founded in 2014 as a competitor for PayPal and much like its peers, it has gained notable success in the past few years. As the need for virtual banking grows, online payment processing companies continue to narrow the gap with PayPal. Although, such companies are not as popular as PayPal, they offer a lot more freedom.</p>



<p>Continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-advcash/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is AdvCash</a>” to learn everything about Advanced Cash.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Is Bitcoin a Good Investment?</strong></h2>



<p>Well, there is hardly anyone these days who is not familiar with the definition of Bitcoin and what the cryptocurrency is capable of carrying out. However, let’s briefly go through what bitcoin is and where it comes from, then we can focus on the benefits of using this cryptocurrency and explain why to buy Bitcoin with Perfect Money.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a Cryptocurrency that was created after the housing market collapse in January 2009. It follows the ideas set out by the enigmatic and pseudonymous Satoshi Nakamoto in a whitepaper. The identity of the individual or individuals who developed this cryptocurrency is still under wraps. Unlike government-issued currencies, Bitcoin provides the guarantee of lower transaction costs than conventional online payment systems and is regulated by a decentralized authority.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a tempting opportunity for investment and great tool for doing financial transactions. In that regard, it has been a solid choice for investment as an asset that is truly decentralized. On top of that, there are countless online platform that accept Bitcoin as payment which makes BTC a utilitarian option for online payments.</p>



<p>So, if You&#8217;ve decided to invest in BTC, you can exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin in only a matter of minutes on CoinCannon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon to the Moon!</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon homepage</a> first, then select AdvCash USD and Bitcoin from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of BTC you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>



<li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your AdvCash and BTC wallet details and email. The phone number is optional.</li>



<li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li>Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the AdvCash gateway and make the payment to our AdvCash account. Having transferred your AdvCash USD to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>



<li>By finishing all the steps above, our team will send the Bitcoin to your wallet as soon as possible.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-you-re-all-set"><strong>You’re All Set!</strong></h2>



<p>Just like that, you have now exchanged AdvCash to Binance Coin. Give it a few minutes and the BNB will be in your account ASAP. In the meantime, you can follow up on your order using the Track ID provided for you. Simply enter the track id in the required section on homepage to see at which point your order is. Remember not to share your Track ID with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Bitcoin with Tether (USDT) [Video]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 08:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Videos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6332</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Here is a full guide on how to buy Bitcoin with Tether on CoinCannon platform with a whole slew of unique benefits. Perhaps, to exchange Tether to Bitcoin can be the most popular exchange direction in crypto market. Both being the first of their kind, both BTC and USDT remain the king of the category. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-tether/">How to Buy Bitcoin with Tether (USDT) [Video]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Here is a full guide on how to buy Bitcoin with Tether on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">HiEx</a><a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">c</a><a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">hange</a> platform with a whole slew of unique benefits. Perhaps, to exchange Tether to Bitcoin can be the most popular exchange direction in crypto market. Both being the first of their kind, both BTC and USDT remain the king of the category. With that, everyone will need a great platform like CoinCannon to buy Bitcoin with Tether without any compromise. Subsequently, we will go over how easy it is to do that in only a matter of few minutes.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/how-exchange-bitcoin-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Bitcoin to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="Exchange Tether to Bitcoin   Buy BTC with USDT" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xh0FlrOrGnw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Bitcoin with Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive Bitcoin that is reliable and secure. Although there are thousands of options at this moment, we advise you to pay extra attention when choosing a Bitcoin wallet. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon. Want a good reason why? How about winning $100 ever month!</p>



<p>Learn more about our <a href="https://hi.exchange/campaign/tether-giveaway" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Tether Giveaway</a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Bitcoin (BTC)?</strong></h2>



<p>Well, there is hardly anyone these days who is not familiar with the definition of Bitcoin and what the cryptocurrency is capable of carrying out. However, let’s briefly go through what bitcoin is and where it comes from, then we can focus on the benefits of using this cryptocurrency and explain why to buy Bitcoin with Perfect Money.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a Cryptocurrency that was created after the housing market collapse in January 2009. It follows the ideas set out by the enigmatic and pseudonymous Satoshi Nakamoto in a whitepaper. The identity of the individual or individuals who developed this cryptocurrency is still under wraps. Unlike government-issued currencies, Bitcoin provides the guarantee of lower transaction costs than conventional online payment systems and is regulated by a decentralized authority.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a tempting opportunity for investment and great tool for doing financial transactions. Everything is in favor of exchanging your Perfect Money for some BTC when possible.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Pay with Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>Owning Tether is basically like having digital dollars in your pocket, only without needing a bank. Recently, there has been lots of talk about how we do not actually own our money when they are in the banks. Digital money means that banks and governments can freeze our access to our funds for whatever reason they seem justifiable. In 2022, Canada denied protestor’s access to their bank accounts and cut out their rightful ownership of their capital. Such incidents are not rare and should be treated seriously. But, political motivation aside, banks are not always available. For example, we saw how the Ukrainians lost all their capital within the banks as soon as the war started. Once again, the decentralized nature of cryptocurrencies meant that the bankless were the lucky ones in that incident.</p>



<p>Thankfully, the list of online merchants and service providers who accept Tether USDT is sufficiently long. With Tether, you can make purchases online and in person almost anywhere. Be it through a direct wallet address or a payment gateway, USDT is as good as cash these days.</p>



<p>Lastly, USDT offers an extra layer of protection for the user with blockchain technology. As a cryptocurrency, it is anonymous and secure. On top of that, the transaction fees for Tether are very low, as long as you use the TRC20 variant based on the Tron network.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon FTW!</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Buy Bitcoin with Tether?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Tether on the left field and Bitcoin on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your Bitcoin wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your Tether (USDT) to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-easy-as-that"><strong>Easy as That!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the BTC to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-tether/">How to Buy Bitcoin with Tether (USDT) [Video]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Twitter, A Decentralized Reverie…</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-twitter/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-twitter/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 08:36:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ELON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6118</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Upon hearing crypto Twitter, one shall be overwhelmed by the traumatic images of the meme wars. A safe haven for those with bold predictions of both bullish and bearish nature, fortune tellers perhaps. It used to be glamorous, back in the bullish days of our past, it used to be busy. And you can’t deny, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-twitter/">Crypto Twitter, A Decentralized Reverie…</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Upon hearing crypto Twitter, one shall be overwhelmed by the traumatic images of the meme wars. A safe haven for those with bold predictions of both bullish and bearish nature, fortune tellers perhaps. It used to be glamorous, back in the bullish days of our past, it used to be busy. And you can’t deny, there was something special about crypto Twitter, a community of endless bots. Busy streets paved with statements, technical analysis, shilling attempts, NFT sellers, crypto beggars. For that, one may call it a slum, with a handful of slumlords like Elon and CZ running a show. Elon’s acquisition of Twitter is surely a breath of fresh air for the crypto Twitter community. A community of investors bashed by a long-term bear market. And in his reign, other slumlords are now joining to help.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Numbers Go Up!</strong></h2>



<p>Binance, the world’s largest crypto exchange is rushing to chip in the crypto Twitter. Reportedly, Binance is making a team to help Elon incorporate blockchain technology into Twitter’s business model.</p>



<p>For the most part, integrating crypto into Twitter will take some work. With that, Binance’s team will be boots on the ground in Twitter HQ to help the free bird. This is according to a recent report by <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/crypto-exchange-binance-musks-co-investor-help-twitter-with-blockchain-2022-10-28/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Reuters</a>.</p>



<p>While Jack Dorsey, the previous owner of Twitter is planning to develop web5, CZ and Elon will rely on web3 to handle problems. Based on the report, the new Binance team will look toward crypto-based solutions to tackle Twitter issues. At this point, it would be safe to say that even the Binance team doesn’t know exactly what that means. However, one thing is for certain and that is the fact that crypto Twitter is here to pump the bejesus out of crypto.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>All Aboard Crypto Twitter</strong></h2>



<p>Last week, Elon finally managed to make the deal and purchase Twitter for $44 billion. He let that sink in Twitter HQ and fired a whole bunch of top executives.</p>



<p>Previously, Binance had made a pledge to co-invest with Elon back in May. According to Binance, Musk’s leadership could help utilize the web potential and its integration with social media. Furthermore, they expressed their hopefulness for an accelerated adoption rate for crypto assets in such case.</p>



<p>Changpeng Zhao, the CEO of Binance <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1585836479129202688?t=qefpBd450uBr68Sy0BaaSw&amp;s=19">told</a> his followers on Twitter (probably mostly bots) that the money was wired a few days ago.</p>



<p>“Our intern says we wired the $500 million two days ago, probably just as I was being asked about Elon/Twitter.”</p>



<p>Binance was in fact quick to jump on the Crypto Twitter train with a considerable investment.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-twitter/">Crypto Twitter, A Decentralized Reverie…</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-twitter/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Over $1.5 billion Exits Crypto Exchanges in 24 Hours</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-exchanges-record-outflows/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-exchanges-record-outflows/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 07:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6112</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looks like people are finally keeping their coins off crypto exchanges. Now, the current state of the market has been frustratingly stagnant, recent data suggests some bullish movement behind the curtains. Consequently, Elon’s ownership of Twitter will certainly lead to pumping DOGE and possibly BTC. With that, we can expect a rejuvenation coming up to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-exchanges-record-outflows/">Over $1.5 billion Exits Crypto Exchanges in 24 Hours</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looks like people are finally keeping their coins off crypto exchanges. Now, the current state of the market has been frustratingly stagnant, recent data suggests some bullish movement behind the curtains. Consequently, Elon’s ownership of Twitter will certainly lead to pumping DOGE and possibly BTC. With that, we can expect a rejuvenation coming up to the market. Generally speaking, money getting off crypto exchanges shows tendency toward long-term holding which is very bullish. And now, data shows over $1.5 billion Bitcoin has got off crypto exchanges only in 24 hours. Indeed, this is triggered by the sink-carrying Elon and the hope of future pumps and shills.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Keep Assets Off Crypto Exchanges</strong></h2>



<p>According to <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1585833582597050369" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">IntoTheBlock</a>, a massive amount of BTC is rushing out of crypto exchanges. Just in a single day, tens of thousands of Bitcoin worth well over a billion has moved.</p>



<p>Specifically, more than 70,000 BTC has moved out which is the largest amount in the past six months. With the current rates, the tokens are valued at $1.52 billion.</p>



<p><em>“Bitcoin just recorded its largest net outflow from exchanges in six months. Over 70,000 BTC worth $1.52 billion left exchanges on October 26.”</em></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="1024" height="531" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Over-1.5-billion-Exists-Crypto-Exchanges-in-24-Hours.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-6114" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Over-1.5-billion-Exists-Crypto-Exchanges-in-24-Hours.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Over-1.5-billion-Exists-Crypto-Exchanges-in-24-Hours-300x156.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Over-1.5-billion-Exists-Crypto-Exchanges-in-24-Hours-768x398.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Last week, Bitcoin finally moved back above $20k after many weeks of consolidating around $19,000. With a recent high of $21,013, the bullish action may have sown the seed of hope in investors after a year-long bear market.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Hopium?</strong></h2>



<p>Certainly, record amount of outflows is a good sign for the troubled market. This, can indicated a new accumulation phase as well as gearing up for the long-run.</p>



<p>On top of that, Recent reports from <a href="https://www.fidelitydigitalassets.com/sites/default/files/documents/2022_Institutional_Investor_Digital_Assets_Study.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">fidelity</a> also shows that nearly 60% of institutional investors holding crypto.</p>



<p>“The increased adoption reflected in the data speaks to a strong first half of the year for the digital assets industry. While the markets have faced many headwinds in recent months, we believe that digital assets</p>



<p>fundamentals remain strong and that the institutionalization of the market over the past several years has positioned it to weather recent events. Institutional investors are experienced in managing through cycles, and the largely inherent factors that they cited as appealing in this study will likely remain as the market emerges from this period.”</p>



<p>At this point, the recent takeover of the $20k support seems to have motivated the investors. Considering the outflows from crypto exchanges and the investors sentiment, it would be more likely for the market to make some positive action. Tell us what you think in the comments.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-exchanges-record-outflows/">Over $1.5 billion Exits Crypto Exchanges in 24 Hours</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-exchanges-record-outflows/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Bitcoin to Webmoney [No Fees]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bitcoin-to-webmoney/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bitcoin-to-webmoney/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 07:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Webmoney]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6108</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you’re looking to exchange Bitcoin to Webmoney, CoinCannon is all you need. Fundamentally, BTC has been the centerpiece of all crypto market and will likely remain as the crowned king. With that, many investors will look to exchange BTC to various e-currencies. However, it is not that easy to find some exchange pairs online. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bitcoin-to-webmoney/">How to Exchange Bitcoin to Webmoney [No Fees]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you’re looking to exchange Bitcoin to Webmoney, <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is all you need. Fundamentally, BTC has been the centerpiece of all crypto market and will likely remain as the crowned king. With that, many investors will look to exchange BTC to various e-currencies. However, it is not that easy to find some exchange pairs online. Even still, you may find a platform that offers your pair but they seldom charge additional fees on the transaction. Luckily, CoinCannon offers a wide variety of exchange pairs all while charging no fees. On top of that, you get to enjoy full anonymity and 24/7 online support. In this article, we will go over how to exchange Bitcoin to Webmoney on CoinCannon.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/how-exchange-bitcoin-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Bitcoin to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Bitcoin to Webmoney?</strong></h2>



<p>For this transaction, you will need a verified and active Webmoney account. Make sure that the exchange amount does not exceed your deposit limit for WMZ. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon. Want a good reason why? How about winning $100 ever month!</p>



<p>Learn more about our <a href="https://hi.exchange/campaign/tether-giveaway" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Tether Giveaway</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Bitcoin?</strong></h2>



<p>This might still be a question to many, before reading about how to exchange, one must know where Bitcoins come from. Bitcoin is a digital currency that was developed following the housing market crash in January 2009. This cryptocurrency follows the ideas started out by the pseudonymous and mysterious Satoshi Nakamoto in a whitepaper. The identity of the individual or individuals that developed the software is still a mystery. Unlike government-issued currencies, Bitcoin is operated by a decentralized authority and offers the promise of lower transaction fees than traditional online payment mechanisms.</p>



<p>There are no physical Bitcoins and the coins you see are novelty coins that do not have any real value without the code inscribed on them. Bitcoin is only balances retained on a public ledger that everyone has transparent access to, and is verified by a massive amount of computing power along with all Bitcoin transactions. Bitcoins are not issued or supported as a commodity by any banks or governments, nor are individual bitcoins valuable. Although it is not legal tender, the popularity of Bitcoin charts is high, and hundreds of other virtual currencies collectively referred to as Altcoins have been launched following this cryptocurrency.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Webmoney?</strong></h2>



<p>WebMoney is an online payment system and a comprehensive tool for online business operations. It was originally developed as a money transfer system for US dollars in Russia in 1998 and since then, nearly 40 million people from all over the globe have joined the program.</p>



<p>WebMoney provides digital currency purses that can hold popular national currencies. The payment platform provides a P2P credit purse, global payment solutions, retail services, local payment products, online billing, and direct integration with other global financial service providers. On top of that, a number of countries worldwide are currently working on WebMoney and consumers pay WebMoney for the services of different companies from Spain, Poland, and Belgium.</p>



<p>Continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-webmoney/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Webmoney</a>”.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon for the Win!</strong></h2>



<p>Every exchange platform must maintain three important characteristics. Anonymity, affordability and reliability. We pride ourselves as a professional platform that offers all three.</p>



<p>For anonymity, CoinCannon requires no KYC or even a sign up process. The best way to protect your information is to not share them with anyone. And for that, we respect our customers and do not ask for their personal info.</p>



<p>As for affordability, CoinCannon utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. By doing so, we have managed to stay on top of the ranks on websites such as Bestchange and OkChanger.</p>



<p>Lastly, reliability is ensured for our customers with 24/7 online support. In case anything goes wrong, you will have our immediate support until the issue is resolved.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Bitcoin to Webmoney (WMZ)?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Enter the homepage first, then select Bitcoin on the left field and Webmoney WMZ on the right. Enter the amount you want to exchange and wait for the exchange rate to apply.</li><li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Webmoney address details and email address.</li><li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li><li>Complete the captcha and click on “exchange” to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. At this point, you will have the CoinCannon wallet address to send the Bitcoin to.&nbsp; After you have transferred your BTC, click on Pay Order button. Don’t forget to attach the screenshot for the BTC payment. your order will process swiftly.</li><li>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the Webmoney to your wallet ASAP.</li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>All Good!</strong></h2>



<p>Just like that, you have now exchanged Bitcoin to Webmoney. In general, Webmoney payments don’t take very long to process. Give it a few minutes and the WMZ will be in your wallet quickly. In the meantime, you can follow up on your order using the Track ID provided for you. Simply enter the track id in the required section on homepage to see at which point your order is. Remember not to share your Track ID with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bitcoin-to-webmoney/">How to Exchange Bitcoin to Webmoney [No Fees]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bitcoin-to-webmoney/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Young Investors Remain Faithful in Crypto Market</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/young-investos-interested-in-crypto-market/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/young-investos-interested-in-crypto-market/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 07:41:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6094</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Yes, the crypto market has been a mess all throughout 2022. And of course, it has been mirroring the US stock market for quite a long time. However, the slump is almost entirely associated with the current state of the world. In a sense, investment in both crypto and stock has been underwhelming to say [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/young-investos-interested-in-crypto-market/">Young Investors Remain Faithful in Crypto Market</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Yes, the crypto market has been a mess all throughout 2022. And of course, it has been mirroring the US stock market for quite a long time. However, the slump is almost entirely associated with the current state of the world. In a sense, investment in both crypto and stock has been underwhelming to say the least. However, when it comes to the future, recent studies suggest that young investors still prefer the crypto market. A recent study by Bank of America has revealed some very interesting results. In short, the numbers indicate that people are losing interest in traditional investments. Continue reading as we go over the key points.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Crypto Market Vs. Stocks</strong></h2>



<p>Recently, the market research firm Escalent did a <a href="https://newsroom.bankofamerica.com/content/newsroom/press-releases/2022/10/bank-of-america-private-bank-study-finds-younger-investors-turni.html">study</a> on behalf of the Bank of America. They polled 1,052 wealthy respondents across the U.S. All respondents were over the age of 21 and maintained at last $3 million in assets.</p>



<p>Interestingly, investors between the age of 21 to 42 have only invested a quarter of their assets in stocks. Consequently, 75% of them believe that “it’s no longer possible to achieve above-average returns” on traditional assets. Clearly, this indicates a loss of faith in stocks and other traditional assets. And wouldn’t you know it, their top choice for the moment is crypto.</p>



<p>Furthermore, almost a third of investors in the same age group have faith in crypto market. According to the study, for them, crypto “presents a leading opportunity to create wealth.” As for other investments, the same group is also interested in such as private equity, debt and ESG-related ventures.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="752" height="659" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Young-Investors-Remain-Faithful-in-Crypto-Market.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-6097" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Young-Investors-Remain-Faithful-in-Crypto-Market.jpg 752w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Young-Investors-Remain-Faithful-in-Crypto-Market-300x263.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 752px) 100vw, 752px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">This is the Way…</h2>



<p>Speaking of crypto, 64% of young investors claimed that hey understand crypto quite well. On top of that, 35% of them believe crypto market to be a mainstream investment platform in half a decade.</p>



<p>With that, 15% of young investors had crypto in their portfolio while 32% believed digital assets to be a great long-term investment.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="669" height="468" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Young-Investors-Remain-Faithful-in-Crypto-Market-2.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-6096" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Young-Investors-Remain-Faithful-in-Crypto-Market-2.jpg 669w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Young-Investors-Remain-Faithful-in-Crypto-Market-2-300x210.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 669px) 100vw, 669px" /></figure>



<p>However, it is also important to take a look at crypto related stocks. In that regard, nearly half of young investors have stocks belonging to digital asset space. Moreover, around 60% of them have direct exposure to crypto assets. And where would we be without talking about NFTs? Yes, they are interested in NFTs. In fact, 59% of the young investors have expressed their interest in expensive JPG files.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/young-investos-interested-in-crypto-market/">Young Investors Remain Faithful in Crypto Market</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/young-investos-interested-in-crypto-market/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis; October 18, 2022</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/bitcoin-price-analysis-october-18/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/bitcoin-price-analysis-october-18/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 09:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6089</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Once again, Bitcoin price failed to surpass $20,000. It is likely for BTC to have another correction. However, the $18,900 support Is currently too strong. Here is a summary of Bitcoin price in the past 24 hours: Exchange Bitcoin to PayPal on CoinCannon Bitcoin price failed to break through $20,000. Currently, the price is below [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/bitcoin-price-analysis-october-18/">Bitcoin Price Analysis; October 18, 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Once again, Bitcoin price failed to surpass $20,000. It is likely for BTC to have another correction. However, the $18,900 support Is currently too strong. Here is a summary of Bitcoin price in the past 24 hours:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><a href="/Users/Admin/Desktop/Work/Coinbase%20Exchange%20Sold%20User%20Data%20to%20ICE%20(Shocking)" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Bitcoin to PayPal</a> on CoinCannon</p></blockquote></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list"><li>Bitcoin price failed to break through $20,000.</li><li>Currently, the price is below $19,400 and the 1-hour candles are below the SMA100.</li><li>On the 1-hour chart, we see a new downtrend forming with resistance at $19,250.</li><li>BTC is likely to move toward $18,900 in short-term.</li></ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Bitcoin Price Action Analysis</strong></h2>



<p>With a recovery, Bitcoin managed to move above $19,500 and at some point reached $19,800. However, the sellers took control and pushed BTC down. With that, BTC climbed only as high as $19,939 and then had a correction.</p>



<p>Subsequently, the price lost the $19,500 and $19,400. The sellers brought BTC down below the 50% Fibonacci retracement level from the latest rally from $18,271 to $19,939. At the moment, BTC is trading below $19,400 and the 1-hour candles are below the SMA100. On the 1-hour chart, we see a new downtrend forming with resistance at $19,250.</p>



<p>The $19,220 is the first resistance for BTC followed closely by $19,250. Breaking through this level can pump BTC back above $19,500. Despite that, the primary resistance is still the $20,000. Further growth can push the price all the way up to $21,200.</p>



<p>On the other hand, if Bitcoin price fails to surpass $19,250, the correction will continue. In which case, the $19,000 is a key support level followed closely by $18,900. This level is close to the 61.8% Fibonacci retracement level from the latest rise. Dipping below $18,900 can increase the selling pressure and bring BTC down to $18,500.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="700" height="323" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Bitcoin-Price-Analysis-October-18-2022.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-6091" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Bitcoin-Price-Analysis-October-18-2022.jpg 700w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Bitcoin-Price-Analysis-October-18-2022-300x138.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Technical Indicators</strong></h2>



<p>MACD indicator: at the time of writing this article the 1-hour MACD indicator for BTC is on a downward momentum.</p>



<p>RSI: the 1-hour relative strength index is currently at 50.</p>



<p>Resistance levels: Right now, the $19,250, $20,000 and $20,500 are crucial resistance levels for BTC.</p>



<p>Support levels: The $18,900 is currently the key support level for the price.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/bitcoin-price-analysis-october-18/">Bitcoin Price Analysis; October 18, 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/bitcoin-price-analysis-october-18/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Crypto Legislation Approved in EU Parliament</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-legislation-eu-parliament/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-legislation-eu-parliament/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 08:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6074</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Gone are the days without crypto legislation and lightly regulated digital assets. Now, while the upcoming regulations can reduce rug pulls and shitcoins, they also mean taxing crypto taking out the X factor. For the most part, it was less regulations for digital assets that distinguished them. Essentially, every crypto legislation anywhere in the world [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-legislation-eu-parliament/">New Crypto Legislation Approved in EU Parliament</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Gone are the days without crypto legislation and lightly regulated digital assets. Now, while the upcoming regulations can reduce rug pulls and shitcoins, they also mean taxing crypto taking out the X factor. For the most part, it was less regulations for digital assets that distinguished them. Essentially, every crypto legislation anywhere in the world means asking for user info (KYC) and taxing their transaction. Funny enough, large crypto exchange platforms are doing exactly what the governments ask of them. After all, platforms such as Binance, Coinbase, KuCoin and Kraken simply can’t lose their share of the market by non-conformity.</p>



<p>This is something we could see coming years ago when crypto remained decentralized but all of the ecosystem or the apparatus built around it was heavily centralized. Sadly, this is the point where decentralized money flows into centralized channels of crypto legislation. Back in April, the EU lawmakers voted in favor of a series of harsh <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/crypto-regulations-eu-parliament/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">crypto regulations</a>. And now, the officials have approved the regulatory framework.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Buy Cryptocurrencies with Full Anonymity on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Crypto Legislation</strong></h2>



<p>As of October, the EU parliament is persistently moving toward adopting the infamous bill. Ideally, the new regulations on digital assets will safeguard financial assets and put cryptocurrencies on a leash.</p>



<p>It comes as a package called Markets in Crypto Assets Regulation (MiCA). And MiCA, has just got the green light by the council according to ECON Committee Press. Initially, the provisional agreements for MiCA formed back in June. The negotiators emphasized on transparency authorization and crypto transaction disclosures as the best measures to fight financial crimes.</p>



<p>“The new legal framework will support market integrity and financial stability by regulating public offers of crypto-assets. Finally, the agreed text includes measures against market manipulation and preventing money laundering, terrorist financing and other criminal activities.”</p>



<p>Earlier this year, President of the European Central Bank Christine Lagarde said it was critically important to pass MiCA. This was in a meeting with the Economic and Financial Affairs Council (ECOFIN) in Paris.</p>



<p>In part, the EU may have serious concerns about Russia trying to curb sanctions using cryptocurrencies. At this point, the crypto legislation is inching closer to pass.</p>



<p>Stefan Berger, a lead member of European Parliament said,</p>



<p>“MiCA is a European success. We are the first continent to have a crypto-asset regulation. In the Wild West of the crypto-world, MiCA will be a global standard setter. MiCA will ensure a harmonised market, provide legal certainty for crypto-asset issuers, guarantee a level playing field for service providers and ensure high standards for costumer protection.</p>



<p>Tokenization will be as groundbreaking for the financial world as the introduction of the joint market was in the 17th century. With the MiCA regulation, reliable authorisation and supervisory structures for new tokens are now being created for the first time.”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-legislation-eu-parliament/">New Crypto Legislation Approved in EU Parliament</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-legislation-eu-parliament/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
