<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Cardano Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/cardano/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 10:17:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cardano-ada-to-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cardano-ada-to-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 08:39:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6393</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking for the best platform to exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether? CoinCannon is all you need. Cardano is one of the top cryptocurrencies by market cap and has a pretty strong community of investors. Today, it’s hard to find an online exchanger that doesn’t have ADA on their supported currency list. Despite that, it is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cardano-ada-to-tether/">Exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking for the best platform to exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether? CoinCannon is all you need. Cardano is one of the top cryptocurrencies by market cap and has a pretty strong community of investors. Today, it’s hard to find an online exchanger that doesn’t have ADA on their supported currency list. Despite that, it is still difficult to find a platform that offers the lowest exchange rates and full anonymity. Fortunately, you can instantly exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether without compromising on anything! In this article, we will go over everything you need to know on how to convert ADA to USDT.</p>



<p>So, head over to <strong><a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a></strong>, choose Cardano (ADA) on the left field and Tether (USDT) on the right one and start your exchange.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive USDT. Most likely, your Cardano wallet supports USDT, so you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Cardano (ADA)?</strong></h2>



<p>The Cardano project launched in 2017. It was the third generation of blockchain networks. One that successfully dealt with some of the greatest challenges of previous generations. Issues such as high gas fees and scalability by introducing the Ouroboros, a proof of stake algorithm to mine blocks which will be further explained in the article.</p>



<p>In 2017, the Cardano project started as a third-gen open-source and public blockchain platform. ADA is the native token of the platform. It is Led by Charles Hoskinson, one of the co-founders of Ethereum. Cardano had a great emphasis on being future-proof by being peer-reviewed and methodically developed by academic experts in the field. Cardano views itself as the updated version of Ethereum. Moving towards building a connected and decentralized system and providing banking services to the unbanked.</p>



<p>ADA is the native token of the network. Currently, ADA stands in 7th place in the ranks with a market cap of 13.5 billion USD.</p>



<p>To learn everything about Cardano and ADA continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-ada-a-guide-to-the-cardano-project/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is ADA?</a>”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether (USDT)?</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT, let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon for the Win!</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Cardano on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your ADA to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-all-good"><strong>All Good!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cardano-ada-to-tether/">Exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cardano-ada-to-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Djed Stablecoin Goes Live on Cardano Mainnet</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/djed-stablecoin/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/djed-stablecoin/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 08:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6305</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Certainly, it is a brave move for Cardano to issue Djed stablecoin right now. For those who do not now, Djed is an algorithmic stablecoin not backed by US dollar. And as far as that idea goes, many of those who came before, are now embarrassingly dead in the dumps! In fact, a big reason [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/djed-stablecoin/">&lt;strong&gt;Djed Stablecoin Goes Live on Cardano Mainnet&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Certainly, it is a brave move for Cardano to issue Djed stablecoin right now. For those who do not now, Djed is an algorithmic stablecoin not backed by US dollar. And as far as that idea goes, many of those who came before, are now embarrassingly dead in the dumps! In fact, a big reason that the crypto has been bearish for more than a year is Terra USD, an algorithmic stablecoin. Now, Djed stablecoin is supposed to be different, not in its idea, not in its operation, but somehow different in how much we trust its founder. Is that enough for investors?</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn all about <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/algorithmic-stablecoin-djed-cardano/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Djed Algorithmic Stablecoin</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Djed Stablecoin: Algorithmically Backed</strong></h2>



<p>Do not be discouraged if you read the title above and have no idea what it means. Perhaps, we live in times when we are supposed to read titles and not understand them and that’s okay. Maybe, it’s all about trust, just trust Charles Hoskinson and know that he is a kind soul. So of course, you and I can read a lot about how they use an algorithm to regulate the supply and demand and keep the value at $1. But, I cheated a lot in high school and then went on to study literature so I have no idea how algorithms work. But no worries, I used ChatGPT and it told me to trust the algorithm, so my anthropocentric views on comprehension are now slowly dying out.</p>



<p>And as a literature major, I like the sound of having a “new era” as Cardano’s marketing team keeps saying. They also keep saying how Djed stablecoin is a huge milestone for the whole DeFi sector which sound pretty awesome.</p>



<p>The point is, at this point in time, we simply cannot understand how things work. They will explain, and they will elaborate, but at the end of the day, it all comes down to faith. So, all we have to do is to listen to marketing departments, the advertising and Twitter announcements and invest in something we believe.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-news"><strong>The News!</strong></h2>



<p>Yes, there’s some exciting and perhaps life-changing news! Djed stablecoin is now live on the Mainnet. It was live on testnet back in May 2022 and now it’s alive. But before you get overwhelmed, there’s even more exciting news and details!</p>



<p>Djed stablecoin is backed by ADA which we literally sell with full anonymity on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> platform. The almighty algorithm will issue more ADA coins upon price increase and conversely buy off from the market upon decline. Basically, the system interferes with the value through supply and demand.</p>



<p>A few weeks ago, <a href="https://coti.io/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">COTI</a>, the platform that issued Djed announced the transition to a multi-chain network for the asset. This would add support for private payment networks and simultaneously bring down deposit fees to half. According to COTI, the changes could significantly help the mass adoption of crypto assets as payment.</p>



<p>“This launch signifies a massive step for the crypto industry, as well as COTI, as the [upgrade] will increase the growth of the widespread adoption of crypto payments for enterprises that are yet to adopt crypto payment solutions.”</p>



<p>They had a successful security audit before the official launch. With that, COTI took to <a href="https://medium.com/cotinetwork/a-new-era-for-stablecoins-begins-djed-is-live-on-mainnet-55971971f2a8" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Medium</a> to announce that a “new ear” is on its way.</p>



<p>“The much anticipated public mainnet launch of Djed heralds a new era for stablecoins. Launching Djed is a significant milestone for COTI, the Cardano ecosystem, and for the DeFi ecosystem as a whole. Being a decentralized open-source protocol, Djed is community-driven, as it brings an opportunity for users to hold, mint, and burn DJED and SHEN.”</p>



<p>To be honest, I do not know how to handle all the good news about Djed stablecoin. On one hand, it’s going to start a new ear and on the other, it is a big milestone for DeFi. Personally speaking, I will pray and give thanks to the algorithm gods!</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/djed-stablecoin/">&lt;strong&gt;Djed Stablecoin Goes Live on Cardano Mainnet&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/djed-stablecoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ADA Price Analysis; October 9, 2022</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-october-9/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-october-9/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 12:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6060</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ADA price fell down to $0.43 and $0.4250 on August 28 and had support. With that, it managed to form a recovery and surpassed $0.45 and then $0.50 and settled at $0.53 on September 10. At that point, Cardano faced strong resistance and had a correction. Subsequently, the price fell down to $0.4150 and found [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-october-9/">ADA Price Analysis; October 9, 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>ADA price fell down to $0.43 and $0.4250 on August 28 and had support. With that, it managed to form a recovery and surpassed $0.45 and then $0.50 and settled at $0.53 on September 10. At that point, Cardano faced strong resistance and had a correction. Subsequently, the price fell down to $0.4150 and found support. By stabilizing, Cardano made another move and climbed up to $0.4350 but failed to break through. Currently, ADA price is around $0.4220.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color"><a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a> Instantly on CoinCannon</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>ADA Price Action Analysis</strong></h2>



<p>Taking a look at the 4-hour chart, we see ADA facing a strong resistance at $0.60 and falling down as low as $0.4150. Then, it had some support and managed to bounce back with a recovery. However, it soon failed to surpass $0.4350 and dipped as low as $0.42.</p>



<p>At this point, the $0.4150 is the first support level for Cardano. In case of good support, the price can one again make an attempt to surpass the downtrend on the chart. For that, the $0.4250 is the level to beat followed by $0.43 on the SMA100. The $0.4350 and $0.44 are the next resistance levels to follow.</p>



<p>On the other hand, if ADA price fails to surpass $0.43, there could be further correction. For the bearish scenario, the $0.42 and $0.4150 are key support levels. In case of losing them, the $0.40 and $0.38 are the following support levels.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="700" height="316" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/ADAUSDT_2022-10-09_13-32-22.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-6062" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/ADAUSDT_2022-10-09_13-32-22.jpg 700w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/ADAUSDT_2022-10-09_13-32-22-300x135.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Technical Indicators</strong></h2>



<p>MACD indicator: at the time of writing this article the 4-hour MACD indicator for ADA is on a downward momentum.</p>



<p>RSI: the 1-hour relative strength index is approximately 50.</p>



<p>Resistance levels: the first support level will be $0.4250 followed by $0.43. The $0.45 will be the next resistance level.</p>



<p>Support levels: the first support for ADA is at $0.4150 followed by $0.40. and then $0.38 will be next.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-october-9/">ADA Price Analysis; October 9, 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-october-9/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ADA Price Analysis; September 25, 2022</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-september-25/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-september-25/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 09:24:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6038</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ADA price fell below $0.4250 on August 29 and had support then bounced back. With the recovery, the price surpassed $0.46 and $0.50 and reached $0.53 on September 10. At that point, Cardano faced strong resistance and failed to break through despite the efforts. Subsequently, it went for another correction and came back down to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-september-25/">ADA Price Analysis; September 25, 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>ADA price fell below $0.4250 on August 29 and had support then bounced back. With the recovery, the price surpassed $0.46 and $0.50 and reached $0.53 on September 10. At that point, Cardano faced strong resistance and failed to break through despite the efforts. Subsequently, it went for another correction and came back down to $0.4350 on September 19. Further ore, with the new found support, it climbed back up to $0.48 on September 23 but once again failed. Currently, ADA price is at $0.45.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a> Instantly on CoinCannon</p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>ADA Price Action Analysis</strong></h2>



<p>Taking a look at the 4-hour chart, we see Cardano hitting a strong ceiling at $0.60 and having to back down. After that, it lost the $0.50 and settled at $0.4250 with the new support. Subsequently, Cardano managed to bounce back and recover. With that, it went all the way up to $0.53 on September 10 but failed to break through and settled back down at $0.4350.</p>



<p>Currently, the $0.49 is a key resistance level for ADA. In case of a successful breakthrough, the $0.52 is the next resistance followed by $0.54 on the trendline. In case of stabilizing, Cardano can move toward $0.58 and $0.60.</p>



<p>On the other hand, if ADA price fails to surpass $0.50, there could be further correction. For the bearish scenario, the $0.45 is the first support level on the SMA100. In case of losing this level, the $0.4250 is the key support level. Further decline can bring ADA down to $0.41 and $0.40.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="700" height="318" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/ADA-Price-Analysis-and-Prediction-September-25-2022.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-6040" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/ADA-Price-Analysis-and-Prediction-September-25-2022.jpg 700w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/ADA-Price-Analysis-and-Prediction-September-25-2022-300x136.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Technical Indicators</strong></h2>



<p>MACD indicator: at the time of writing this article the 4-hour MACD indicator for ADA is on a downward momentum.</p>



<p>RSI: the 1-hour relative strength index is approximately 50.</p>



<p>Resistance levels: the first support level will be $0.50 followed by $0.55. The $0.60 will be the next resistance level.</p>



<p>Support levels: the first support for ADA is at $0.44 followed by $0.43. and then $0.4250 will be next.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-september-25/">ADA Price Analysis; September 25, 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-september-25/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ADA Price Analysis; September 18, 2022</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-september-18/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-september-18/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 12:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6006</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ADA price fell down to $0.43 and $0.4250 on August 29 and had support before going further down. With that, Cardano managed to stabilize at this level and go for a recovery attempt. Subsequently, the price managed to surpass $0.45 and $0.50 and reach $0.53 by September 10. At that point, ADA faced strong resistance [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-september-18/">ADA Price Analysis; September 18, 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>ADA price fell down to $0.43 and $0.4250 on August 29 and had support before going further down. With that, Cardano managed to stabilize at this level and go for a recovery attempt. Subsequently, the price managed to surpass $0.45 and $0.50 and reach $0.53 by September 10. At that point, ADA faced strong resistance and despite multiple attempts, failed to break through. Therefore, it fell down to $0.46 with a correction. Currently, ADA price is at $0.49.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a> Instantly on CoinCannon</p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>ADA Price Action Analysis</strong></h2>



<p>Taking a look at the 4-hour chart, we see Cardano hitting a resistance at $0.60 and having to back down. By losing the $0.50, the price fell down to $0.4250 but had support at this level. With a recovery, Cardano climbed as high as $0.53 on September 10 but faced resistance. After that, it settled back down at $0.4550.</p>



<p>Currently, the $0.50 is the first resistance level for Cardano. In case of a successful breakthrough, the $0.53 will be the next one. Furthermore, if ADA manages to surpass these levels, the $0.55, $0.58 and $0.60 are next in line.</p>



<p>On the other hand, if ADA price fails to surpass $0.50, there could be further correction. For the correction, the $0.48 on the SMA100 is the first support level. In case of losing it, the $0.45 and $0.4250 are the next support levels.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="700" height="314" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/ADA-Price-Analysis-and-Prediction-September-18-2022.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-6008" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/ADA-Price-Analysis-and-Prediction-September-18-2022.jpg 700w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/ADA-Price-Analysis-and-Prediction-September-18-2022-300x135.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Technical Indicators</strong></h2>



<p>MACD indicator: at the time of writing this article the 4-hour MACD indicator for ADA is on a upward momentum.</p>



<p>RSI: the 1-hour relative strength index is approximately 55.</p>



<p>Resistance levels: the first support level will be $0.50 followed by $0.55. The $0.60 will be the next resistance level.</p>



<p>Support levels: the first support for ADA is at $0.49 followed by $0.45. and then $0.4250 will be next.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-september-18/">ADA Price Analysis; September 18, 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-september-18/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Cardano with Payeer USD [Instant]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-cardano-with-payeer/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-cardano-with-payeer/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 07:08:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5978</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you’re a fan of Charles Hoskinson and already have a Payeer account, you can buy Cardano with Payeer USD on CoinCannon. With the Vasil hard fork on the horizon, investing in Cardano (ADA) has never been this appealing. Despite that, Vasil is not the only winning card ADA holds. Recently, a new study found [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-cardano-with-payeer/">How to Buy Cardano with Payeer USD [Instant]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you’re a fan of Charles Hoskinson and already have a Payeer account, you can buy Cardano with Payeer USD on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>. With the Vasil hard fork on the horizon, investing in Cardano (ADA) has never been this appealing. Despite that, Vasil is not the only winning card ADA holds. Recently, a new study found that Cardano blockchain was the second best network in terms of <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/polkadot-dot-blockchain/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">energy consumption</a>. Essentially, this would guaranty that Cardano will be exempt from any upcoming regulations against gas guzzling cryptocurrencies. Regardless, you will need a reliable and secure platform to invest in ADA which we will introduce in this article. Without further ado, here’s a full guide on how to buy Cardano with Payeer USD on CoinCannon platform.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color"><a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a> on CoinCannon</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Cardano with Payeer?</strong></h2>



<p>For this transaction, you will be sending Payeer USD and receive Cardano (ADA) in your wallet. Naturally, you will need to have a verified and active Payeer account with sufficient funds. Make sure that the exchange amount does not exceed your withdrawal limit. On the other hand, you will need a reliable crypto wallet that supports Cardano (ADA) to receive the funds. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon. Want a good reason why? How about winning $100 ever month!</p>



<p>Learn more about our <a href="https://hi.exchange/campaign/tether-giveaway" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Tether Giveaway</a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Cardano (ADA)?</strong></h2>



<p>The Cardano project launched in 2017. It was the third generation of blockchain networks. One that successfully dealt with some of the greatest challenges of previous generations. Issues such as high gas fees and scalability by introducing the Ouroboros, a proof of stake algorithm to mine blocks which will be further explained in the article.</p>



<p>In 2017, the Cardano project started as a third-gen open-source and public blockchain platform. ADA is the native token of the platform. It is Led by Charles Hoskinson, one of the co-founders of Ethereum. Cardano had a great emphasis on being future-proof by being peer-reviewed and methodically developed by academic experts in the field. Cardano views itself as the updated version of Ethereum. Moving towards building a connected and decentralized system and providing banking services to the unbanked.</p>



<p>ADA is the native token of the network. Currently, ADA stands in 7th place in the ranks with a market cap of almost 32 billion USD.</p>



<p>To learn everything about Cardano and ADA continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-ada-a-guide-to-the-cardano-project/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is ADA?</a>”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Use Payeer?</strong></h2>



<p>First and foremost, Payeer is considered an online digital wallet for better asset management. Be it crypto of fiat, the payment processor is quick, reliable and cheap. In that regard, in a short lifespan of almost 8 years, Payeer is now recognized as one of the very best amongst</p>



<p>competitors. Payeer utilizes built-in payment services with giant financial services such as Mastercard, VISA and PayPal.</p>



<p>As of 2022, the Payeer has approximately 7 million users which can transfer funds to each other with extremely low fees. The strength however, lies in diversity. Payeer is far ahead of any similar platform in terms of scale of operation and diversity in supported payment methods. With more than 50 payment approaches, the Payeer wallet offers users various services in one place.</p>



<p>To learn more about Payeer, continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-payeer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Payeer?</a>”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Essentially, you need three primary qualities in an ideal exchange platform. Anonymity, good rates and reliability. The CoinCannon team consists of traders and professionals who have felt the need for an ideal exchange and pursued their vision.</p>



<p>First and foremost, all users need to protect their personal information especially when it comes down to financial transactions. Unfortunately, a vast majority of exchange apps and platforms make massive profits off of selling user data. Best case scenario, they are legally bound to disclose user information with national authorities for any reason. In that regard, the best method to protect your privacy is to not disclose them with anyone at all. CoinCannon does not require customers to go through KYC (know your customer) or even a mandatory sign up. In that regard, it is simply as safe as one can get making an exchange.</p>



<p>On the other hand, privacy is not a reason to pay more on your exchange. With that in mind, the platform offers some of the most competitive exchange rates you can find anywhere. Don’t take our word for it. You can simply pay a visit to ranking websites such as BestChange or OkChanger and see compare our rates with others.</p>



<p>Last but not least, not everything goes as planned in the digital world. Subsequently, the platform provides true online 24/7 customer support for the users.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Buy Cardano with Payeer?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Enter the homepage first, then select Payeer USD and Cardano from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of ADA you will receive will automatically calculate.</li><li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your ADA wallet details, email, and phone number.</li><li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li><li>Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the Payeer gateway and make the payment to our Payeer account. Having transferred your Payeer USD to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li><li>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the Cardano to your wallet as soon as possible.</li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Success!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Cardano (ADA) to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-cardano-with-payeer/">How to Buy Cardano with Payeer USD [Instant]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-cardano-with-payeer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ADA Price Analysis; September 11, 2022</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-september-11/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-september-11/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 08:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5972</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ADA price climbed as high as $0.60 on August 14 but couldn’t break through and backed down. Subsequently, ADA lost the uptrend at $0.55 and entered a red zone. With that, it lost the $0.50 and fell down to $0.4250 on August 29 but found support at that level. At that point, ADA price managed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-september-11/">ADA Price Analysis; September 11, 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>ADA price climbed as high as $0.60 on August 14 but couldn’t break through and backed down. Subsequently, ADA lost the uptrend at $0.55 and entered a red zone. With that, it lost the $0.50 and fell down to $0.4250 on August 29 but found support at that level. At that point, ADA price managed to bounce back and set for recovery then surpassed the $0.45 and $0.50. Yesterday, Cardano regained the $0.52 and $0.53 but failed move any further. Currently, ADA is exchanging hands at $0.52.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color"><a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a> Instantly on CoinCannon</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>ADA Price Action Analysis</strong></h2>



<p>Taking a look at the 4-hour chart, we see ADA hitting a strong resistance at $0.60 and turning back down. By losing the $0.50 on August 26, Cardano fell as low as $0.4250 but found solid support at this level. Consequently, the price had a breather and managed to bounce back and move as high as $0.53.</p>



<p>At the moment, the $0.53 is the first resistance level for Cardano followed by $0.55 on a downtrend. In case of breaking this trendline and stabilizing above it, ADA can climb as high as $0.60 and $0.65.</p>



<p>On the other hand, if ADA price fails to surpass $0.53, there will be further correction. For the bearish scenario, the $0.48 on the SMA100 is the first support level. After that, the $0.45 will be the next support level. Further decline can bring ADA down to $0.43 and $0.4250.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="700" height="313" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/ADA-Price-Analysis-and-Prediction-September-11-2022.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-5974" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/ADA-Price-Analysis-and-Prediction-September-11-2022.jpg 700w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/ADA-Price-Analysis-and-Prediction-September-11-2022-300x134.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Technical Indicators</strong></h2>



<p>MACD indicator: at the time of writing this article the 4-hour MACD indicator for ADA is on a upward momentum.</p>



<p>RSI: the 1-hour relative strength index is approximately 55.</p>



<p>Resistance levels: the first support level will be $0.53 followed by $0.55. The $0.60 will be the next resistance level.</p>



<p>Support levels: the first support for ADA is at $0.48 followed by $0.45. and then $0.4250 will be next.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-september-11/">ADA Price Analysis; September 11, 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-september-11/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ADA Price Analysis and Prediction; August 29, 2022</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 08:59:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5897</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ADA price had set on a rally starting from August 13 and reached $0.60. However, it failed to surpass this critical level and had to bac down. With that, Cardano broke the uptrend at $0.55 and lost it. Furthermore, ADA price lost the $0.50 support level and fell down to $0.44 on August 22. At [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price/">&lt;strong&gt;ADA Price Analysis and Prediction; August 29, 2022&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>ADA price had set on a rally starting from August 13 and reached $0.60. However, it failed to surpass this critical level and had to bac down. With that, Cardano broke the uptrend at $0.55 and lost it. Furthermore, ADA price lost the $0.50 support level and fell down to $0.44 on August 22. At that point, the price found support and bounced back with a recovery attempt. Yet again, Cardano failed to move above $0.48 and dipped back down to $0.42. Currently, ADA is trading at $0.43.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color"><a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a> Instantly on CoinCannon</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>ADA Price Action Analysis</strong></h2>



<p>Taking a look at the 4-hour chart, we see ADA managed to reach $0.60 on August 4 riding on an uptrend. However, it hit a strong ceiling at the price and had to back down. Subsequently, Cardano entered a bearish zone by losing the $0.55 and fell as low as $0.42. Once again, it got support at this level.</p>



<p>At the moment, the $0.42 is the key support level for ADA. In case of providing strong support, we can expect a new recovery attempt. For that, the $0.45 located on the SMA100 is the first resistance level for ADA. Following that, the $0.50 on the 50% Fibonacci retracement level will come next. Then, the $0.55, $0.58 and $0.60 will be the next resistance levels for Cardano.</p>



<p>On the other hand, if ADA price fails to surpass $0.44 and $0.45, and subsequently loses the $0.42, further decline will be imminent. For the bearish scenario, the $0.40 will be the next support level for ADA. Further decline can bring the price down to $0.38 and $0.35.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="700" height="314" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/ADA-Price-Analysis-and-Prediction-August-29-2022.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-5899" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/ADA-Price-Analysis-and-Prediction-August-29-2022.jpg 700w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/ADA-Price-Analysis-and-Prediction-August-29-2022-300x135.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Technical Indicators</strong></h2>



<p>MACD indicator: at the time of writing this article the 4-hour MACD indicator for ADA is on a downward momentum.</p>



<p>RSI: the 1-hour relative strength index is approximately 40.</p>



<p>Resistance levels: the first support level will be $0.45 followed by $0.50. The $0.60 will be the next resistance level.</p>



<p>Support levels: the first support for ADA is at $0.42 followed by $0.40. and then $0.35 will be next.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price/">&lt;strong&gt;ADA Price Analysis and Prediction; August 29, 2022&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ADA Price Analysis and Prediction; August 14, 2022</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-august-14/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-august-14/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 08:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5813</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ADA price had some strong support at $0.45 at the bottom of the channel and bounced back. With that, the price managed to surpassed $0.50 and reach $0.55. At that point, Cardano faced resistance and had to back down. Subsequently, it lost the $0.50 support and didn’t lost the bull run. Despite reaching $0.55 multiple [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-august-14/">ADA Price Analysis and Prediction; August 14, 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>ADA price had some strong support at $0.45 at the bottom of the channel and bounced back. With that, the price managed to surpassed $0.50 and reach $0.55. At that point, Cardano faced resistance and had to back down. Subsequently, it lost the $0.50 support and didn’t lost the bull run. Despite reaching $0.55 multiple times and failing, ADA price finally broke through this level yesterday and settled at $0.60. Currently, ADA is trading at $0.59.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color"><a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a> Instantly on CoinCannon</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>ADA Price Action Analysis</strong></h2>



<p>Taking a look at the 4-hour chart, we see ADA finally surpassing $0.55 and failing multiple times. On August 10<sup>th</sup>, ADA fell down to $0.50 but had support by the trendline and had a pivot. Finally, it managed to break through and climb all the way up to %0.60.</p>



<p>At this point, the $0.50 is the key resistance level located on the long-term downtrend. In case of a successful breakthrough, the $0.65 and $0.70 are the next resistance levels.</p>



<p>On the other hand, if ADA price fails to surpass $0.60, there could be further correction ahead. For the bearish scenario, the $0.55 is the first support level followed by $0.50.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="700" height="314" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/ADA-Price-Analysis-and-Prediction-August-14-2022.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-5815" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/ADA-Price-Analysis-and-Prediction-August-14-2022.jpg 700w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/ADA-Price-Analysis-and-Prediction-August-14-2022-300x135.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Technical Indicators</strong></h2>



<p>MACD indicator: at the time of writing this article the 4-hour MACD indicator for ADA is on an upward momentum.</p>



<p>RSI: the 1-hour relative strength index is approximately 75.</p>



<p>Resistance levels: the first support level will be $0.60 followed by $0.65. The $0.70 will be the next resistance level.</p>



<p>Support levels: the first support for ADA is at $0.55 followed by $0.50. and then $0.46 will be next.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-august-14/">ADA Price Analysis and Prediction; August 14, 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-august-14/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Cardano (ADA) with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-cardano-ada/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-cardano-ada/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 06:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5732</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you’re looking to buy Cardano (ADA) with Perfect Money, here is a full 2024 guide on how to do it on CoinCannon. When it comes to altcoins, Cardano has perhaps the best reputation in terms of reliability in the business. In terms of performance, Cardano (ADA) is one of the fastest yet most efficient [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-cardano-ada/">How to Buy Cardano (ADA) with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you’re looking to <strong>buy Cardano (ADA) with Perfect Money</strong>, here is a full 2024 guide on how to do it on CoinCannon. </p>



<p>When it comes to altcoins, Cardano has perhaps the best reputation in terms of reliability in the business. In terms of performance, Cardano (ADA) is one of the fastest yet most efficient blockchains in the world. Impressively, ADA is currently the 8<sup>th</sup> cryptocurrency with a market cap of $15.7 billion. If you would like to make an investment, you can buy Cardano (ADA) on CoinCannon platform with no added fees.</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-1 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button is-style-outline is-style-outline--1"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-black-color has-text-color has-background has-link-color wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/" style="background-color:#f49d3f">Buy Cardano (ADA) with Perfect Money Right Now!</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-buy-cardano-with-perfect-money"><strong>Why Buy Cardano with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>Perfect Money is an e-currency for making payments on the internet. It is widely accepted as payment option by countless platforms. With Perfect Money, you can do a lot! </p>



<p>Be it transferring funds to others or pay for goods and services. Or how about buying cryptocurrencies or even buying fiat currencies. It is a seriously popular payment method for online users. An additional capability is to loan and receipt issuance throughout the system.</p>



<p>The biggest downside of Perfect Money, however, is that you cannot cash Perfect money to your bank account on its website directly. For that, you will need a platform like CoinCannon to exchange your Perfect Money to PayPal and other e-currencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-buy-cardano-ada-with-perfect-money"><strong>How to Buy Cardano (ADA) with Perfect Money</strong></h2>



<p>All it takes is 5 easy steps:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Enter the homepage first, then select Perfect Money and Cardano (ADA) from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of ADA you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>



<li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Cardano wallet details, email, and phone number.</li>



<li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li>Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the Perfect Money gateway and make the payment to our Perfect Money account. Having transferred your Perfect Money to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>



<li>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the Cardano to your wallet as soon as possible</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-finished"><strong>Finished</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Cardano to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. </p>



<p>Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-jolixo-platform"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p><a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">CoinCannon </a>is an online exchange that offers everything you need from a platform.</p>



<p>Truthfully, it is a rare combination for an online exchange to offer anonymity, lowest exchange rates and unparalleled reliability altogether.</p>



<p>We respect our customer’s privacy by not asking for their personal information. The best way for anyone to protect their information is to not disclose them at all. In that regard, not having KYC or sign up is the best method.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the platform utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at all times. Our words sound too good? Just pay a visit to ranking websites such as BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>Lastly, according to Murphy’s law “anything that can go wrong will go wrong”. To stay ahead of any problems, we offer 24/7 customer support.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-cardano-ada/">How to Buy Cardano (ADA) with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-cardano-ada/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ADA Price Analysis and Prediction; July 17, 2022</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-july-17/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-july-17/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 08:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5680</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ADA price failed to surpass $0.50 on July 9 and had to fall as low as $0.42. At some point, the price touched $0.40 but found support and did not fall lower. With that, the price had a chance for rally and reached $0.46 by surpassing the SMA100. Currently, ADA price is at $0.46. Exchange [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-july-17/">ADA Price Analysis and Prediction; July 17, 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>ADA price failed to surpass $0.50 on July 9 and had to fall as low as $0.42. At some point, the price touched $0.40 but found support and did not fall lower. With that, the price had a chance for rally and reached $0.46 by surpassing the SMA100. Currently, ADA price is at $0.46.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color"><a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a> Instantly on CoinCannon</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>ADA Price Action Analysis</strong></h2>



<p>Taking a look at the 4-hour chart, we see Cardano bound in the range between $0.40 and $0.70. ADA failed to surpass $0.50 a few days ago and found support at the bottom at $0.40. By stabilizing at this level, it had a chance to set for recover and climbed back to $0.46.</p>



<p>Currently, the $0.48 on the downtrend is the first resistance level for ADA price. In case of a successful breakthrough, the $0.50 and $0.55 will be next. The next key resistance level is $0.60.</p>



<p>On the other hand, if ADA price fails to surpass $0.48, there could be further correction ahead. In this case, the $0.44 on the SMA100 is the first support level for Cardano. In case of losing this level, we could expect further decline.</p>



<p>For the bearish scenario, the $0.40 and then the $0.35 will be the next support levels for the price.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="700" height="313" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/ADA-Price-Analysis-and-Prediction-July-17-2022.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-5682" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/ADA-Price-Analysis-and-Prediction-July-17-2022.jpg 700w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/ADA-Price-Analysis-and-Prediction-July-17-2022-300x134.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Technical Indicators</strong></h2>



<p>MACD indicator: at the time of writing this article the 4-hour MACD indicator for ADA is on an upward momentum.</p>



<p>RSI: the 1-hour relative strength index is approximately 60.</p>



<p>Resistance levels: the first support level will be $0.48 followed by $0.50. The $0.60 will be the next resistance level.</p>



<p>Support levels: the first support for ADA is at $0.45 followed by $0.40. and then $0.35 will be next.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-july-17/">ADA Price Analysis and Prediction; July 17, 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/ada-price-analysis-july-17/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano (ADA) on Top of Grayscale Holdings</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/cardano-ada-on-grayscale/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/cardano-ada-on-grayscale/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 07:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grayscale]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5649</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The crypto asset management giant has been actively accumulating some top altcoins for a while. As the latest update to their holdings, Cardano (ADA) stands on top of the smart contract platforms with a massive share. While the firm has been selling crypto assets at huge discounts, the latest update to the holdings can signal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/cardano-ada-on-grayscale/">Cardano (ADA) on Top of Grayscale Holdings</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The crypto asset management giant has been actively accumulating some top altcoins for a while. As the latest update to their holdings, Cardano (ADA) stands on top of the smart contract platforms with a massive share. While the firm has been selling crypto assets at huge discounts, the latest update to the holdings can signal some changes in their long-term strategy.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Cardano (ADA) for Smart Contracts Holdings</strong></h2>



<p>In a new <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/en/news-release/2022/07/08/2476578/0/en/Grayscale-Digital-Large-Cap-Fund-Grayscale-DeFi-Fund-and-Grayscale-Smart-Contract-Platform-Ex-Ethereum-Fund-Announce-Rebalancing-of-Funds-for-Second-Quarter-2022.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">report</a>, Grayscale’s GSCPxE Fund has allocated funds towards multiple Ethereum competitors. Cardano (ADA), Solana (SOL) and Polkadot (DOT) stand on top of the list.</p>



<p>“At the end of the day on July 6th, 2022, the GSCPxE Fund’s fund components were a basket of the following assets and weightings:</p>



<p>Cardano (ADA), 31.69%</p>



<p>Solana (SOL), 25.43%</p>



<p>Polkadot (DOT), 13.90%</p>



<p>Avalanche (AVAX), 10.87%</p>



<p>Polygon (MATIC), 8.45%</p>



<p>Cosmos (ATOM), 5.29%</p>



<p>Algorand (ALGO), 4.37%.”</p>



<p>Interestingly, the payment focused altcoin Stellar (XLM) is now removed from the list. Grayscale states that this is due to a rebalancing of funds. XLM has had an underwhelming performance as of late.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>DeFi</strong> and Digital Large Cap Funds</h2>



<p>the latest rebalancing has also affected Grayscale’s DeFi holdings as well. The world’s largest BTC fund has also been making big changes in the DeFi sector. Currently, Grayscale’s biggest DeFi holding is Uniswap (UNI) which is a decentralized exchange based on Ethereum.</p>



<p>“At the end of the day on July 6, 2022, the DeFi Fund’s Fund Components were a basket of the following assets and weightings.</p>



<p>Uniswap (UNI), 56.35%</p>



<p>MakerDAO (MKR), 13.49%</p>



<p>Aave (AAVE), 12.44%</p>



<p>Curve DAO Token (CRV), 7.48%</p>



<p>Amp (AMP), 5.52%</p>



<p>Compound (COMP), 4.72%”</p>



<p>As for the big boys, Grayscale made some radical changes in the digital large cap funds by slashing five coins from the list.</p>



<p>“Grayscale has adjusted the Digital Large Cap Fund’s portfolio by selling certain amounts of the existing Fund Components in proportion to their respective weightings. As a result of the rebalancing, Bitcoin Cash, Chainlink, Litecoin, Polkadot and Uniswap have been removed from the Digital Large Cap Fund. No new tokens were added to the Digital Large Cap Fund.</p>



<p>At the end of the day on July 7th, 2022, the Digital Large Cap Fund’s fund components were a basket of the following assets and weightings:</p>



<p>Bitcoin (BTC), 68.88%</p>



<p>Ethereum (ETH), 25.22%</p>



<p>Cardano (ADA), 2.71%</p>



<p>Solana (SOL), 2.23%</p>



<p>Avalanche (AVAX), 0.96%”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/cardano-ada-on-grayscale/">Cardano (ADA) on Top of Grayscale Holdings</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/cardano-ada-on-grayscale/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
