<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>crypto to e-currency Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/category/crypto-to-e-currency-articles/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/category/crypto-to-e-currency-articles/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 11:37:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Bitcoin to PayPal [2023 Update]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/how-exchange-bitcoin-to-paypal/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/how-exchange-bitcoin-to-paypal/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 14:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=3223</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How to exchange your bitcoins to PayPal with all the KYC problems that normal Crypto Exchanges make for Bitcoin users, has always been a hassle. The nature of Cryptocurrency is to stay anonymous whenever you want. Plus, those procedures known as Know Your Customer is not always easy to complete when in an emergency. Decentralized [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/how-exchange-bitcoin-to-paypal/">How to Exchange Bitcoin to PayPal [2023 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>How to exchange your bitcoins to PayPal with all the KYC problems that normal Crypto Exchanges make for Bitcoin users, has always been a hassle. The nature of Cryptocurrency is to stay anonymous whenever you want. Plus, those procedures known as Know Your Customer is not always easy to complete when in an emergency. Decentralized exchanges like CoinCannon on the other hand have made the process of exchanging your crypto assets a much easier process just like the way you can <a href="/directions/popular/exchange-bitcoin-paypal">exchange Bitcoin to PayPal</a> on CoinCannon. <strong>Actually not just easier but also more efficient as most of the time you get exactly 1$ or even more for every 1$ worth of your bitcoin. </strong></p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-1 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button is-style-fill"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-text-color has-background wp-element-button" href="/directions/popular/exchange-bitcoin-paypal" style="color:#050569;background-color:#f19b2d">Exchange BTC to PayPal Now!</a></div>
</div>



<p></p>



<p>PayPal is an online banking service that enables you to use a protected internet account to pay for goods and services. Any money earned stays in your PayPal account and can be used with the balance topped up by your allocated cards or bank account when paying for things.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p><a href="#exchange-guide">Jump to How to Exchange BTC to PayPal step by step guide</a></p>
</blockquote>



<p>For Bitcoin users, however, this service can make the Bitcoin to Cash process much faster. let&#8217;s be realistic, you can&#8217;t find many stores out there who accept Bitcoin as a payment method yet. So, it&#8217;s better to have the option to use our BTC in a from of money more widely accepted whenever we need them.  This is when knowing how to exchange your BTC to PayPal comes handy! <br>In this article, we will explain<strong> how to</strong> <strong>exchange Bitcoin to PayPal instantly</strong> and get the exact market value of your cryptocurrency in your PayPal account.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-bitcoin-and-how-does-it-work">What is Bitcoin and How does it work?</h2>



<p>This might still be a question to many, before reading about how to exchange, one must know where Bitcoins come from. Bitcoin is a digital currency that was developed following the housing market crash in January 2009. This cryptocurrency follows the ideas started out by the pseudonymous and mysterious Satoshi Nakamoto in a whitepaper. The identity of the individual or individuals that developed the software is still a mystery. Unlike government-issued currencies, Bitcoin is operated by a decentralized authority and offers the promise of lower transaction fees than traditional online payment mechanisms.</p>



<p>There are no physical Bitcoins and the coins you see are novelty coins that do not have any real value without the code inscribed on them. Bitcoin is only balances retained on a public ledger that everyone has transparent access to, and is verified by a massive amount of computing power along with all Bitcoin transactions. Bitcoins are not issued or supported as a commodity by any banks or governments, nor are individual bitcoins valuable. Although it is not legal tender, the popularity of Bitcoin charts is high, and hundreds of other virtual currencies collectively referred to as Altcoins have been launched following this cryptocurrency.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-can-i-exchange-bitcoin-to-paypal">Can I exchange Bitcoin to PayPal?</h2>



<p>Yes, you can get US Dollar, Pounds or Euros in your PayPal account in exchange for your cryptocurrencies at most of the exchanges. But are all of them as fast as CoinCannon? you&#8217;ll know the moment you check the process and rates.</p>



<p>Conducted through trustworthy exchange agents &#8211; such as <a href="/">jolixo</a> with 24/7 support and immediate exchange without any waiting period- you can <strong><a href="/directions/popular/exchange-bitcoin-paypal">exchange Bitcoins for PayPal</a>  </strong>or any other currency of your choice. This process means immediate cash with the least commission possible, without having to go through the time-consuming process of crypto exchanges.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Below, you can read the step by step guide on how to exchange BTC to PayPal through CoinCannon in a very simple procedure.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-get-the-best-value-of-my-bitcoins-in-paypal">How to get the best value of my Bitcoins in PayPal?</h2>



<p>You just have to type hi.exchange in your address bar. And NO! Although there&#8217;s a Sign Up button on this page, <strong>you don&#8217;t need to sign up for performing any sort of exchange at our website</strong>. But if you do, you&#8217;ll enjoy the following features:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Order log that you can check and track at any moment</li>



<li>The privilege of entering a referral program that helps you to gain money by referring your fellow traders to hi.exchange</li>



<li>Based on your activities, discounts on future orders</li>



<li>News on sales and discounts</li>
</ul>



<p><a name="exchange-guide"></a></p>



<p><a name="exchange-guide"></a>Therefore, if you&#8217;re willing to carry out your exchange using CoinCannon, just go the <a href="/directions/popular/exchange-bitcoin-paypal" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bitcoin to PayPal exchange page</a> and follow the following steps in order:</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li>Select Bitcoin from the box on the left and PayPal on the right</li>



<li>Enter the BTC amount you want to exchange to PayPal and behold the most competitive exchange rates!</li>



<li>Before clicking &#8220;Next&#8221;, please read the instructions and &#8220;PayPal fees guide&#8221; carefully</li>



<li>&nbsp;By clicking “Next” and enter your PayPal details and your email address. Please note that we contact you using the email address you provide therefore it&#8217;s important that you enter a valid email address</li>



<li>Once again, press Next, and you are taken to the next level where you are asked to review your order. Please click on Review and Check. Read and agree to the terms and AML policy.</li>



<li>By clicking on &#8220;Confirm&#8221; you are taken to the 4th and last step where you have to pay your order</li>



<li>Obtain a tracking ID, an address, and an Explorer URL</li>



<li>At this stage we ask you to read the instruction carefully. Please do read them carefully!</li>



<li>Transfer your crypto to the Hi Exchange wallet provided to you</li>



<li>Click on the “Confirm Payment” button, sit back and enjoy the money that soon will be in your PayPal account</li>
</ol>



<p>There are some points worth mentioning regarding your BTC cash out:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>You can request for PayPal USD, EUR or GBP from &#8220;I Get&#8221; section of the first Step. After you typed the BTC amount in the &#8220;I Give&#8221; section, in a blink of an eye, the automated system calculates how much you&#8217;ll receive in your PayPal account for your Bitcoins. <strong>The rate is pretty amazing, right?</strong> don&#8217;t worry we&#8217;re not going to go bankrupt.</li>



<li>You receive a tracking ID, an address, and Explorer URL. You can follow your order using those information or request support from customer service</li>



<li>You should transfer the Bitcoins needs to the wallet specified in the last step</li>



<li>Please read the instructions and disclaimer carefully before sending the bitcoins</li>



<li>Don&#8217;t forget clicking &#8220;I&#8217;ve Paid&#8221; button after you have transferred the BTC to out wallet </li>
</ul>



<p>Once the transaction gets confirmed on blockchain network, Your Bitcoin to PayPal exchange will be completed easily and automatically without any waiting period by fulfilling the easy steps that we explained.</p>



<p>You can always count on us. In case of any questions and problems, you can contact us via WhatsApp, Telegram, Facebook, Email, Skype, Contact Form, and Live Chat. We get back to you ASAP!</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/how-exchange-bitcoin-to-paypal/">How to Exchange Bitcoin to PayPal [2023 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/how-exchange-bitcoin-to-paypal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin [Instant]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin-2/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin-2/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 07:36:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AdvCash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6435</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking to exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin? CoinCannon offers everything you need! Digital currencies have been a quintessential asset for online payments. On top of that, cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin (BTC) are gaining momentum as popular payment methods. In that regard, users will find themselves in the need to exchange their assets into one another. And [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin-2/">How to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin [Instant]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking to exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin? CoinCannon offers everything you need! Digital currencies have been a quintessential asset for online payments. On top of that, cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin (BTC) are gaining momentum as popular payment methods. In that regard, users will find themselves in the need to exchange their assets into one another. And by doing so, the exchange fees can quickly put a dent in their pockets. Fortunately, you can easily exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin with the lowest fees, full anonymity and 24/7 online support. Want to know how?</p>



<p>Head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select AdvCash and Bitcoin in the exchange box and you’re good to go!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a verified and active Advanced Cash (AdvCash) account. Make sure that the transaction amount does not exceed your withdrawal limit. To receive Bitcoin (BTC), you will need a reliable and secure crypto wallet. Primarily, we suggest you use Trust Wallet. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon provides a hassle-free KYC process and no sign up to speed up your work flow. Despite that, there are benefits for those who sign up on CoinCannon. For example, you can take advantage of <a href="https://hi.exchange/jolixo-affiliate" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon affiliate</a> program and earn money online.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Advanced Cash (AdvCash)?</strong></h2>



<p>Before we go on to talk about how to convert AdvCash to Bitcoin, let’s take a quick look at what this digital currency is. AdvCash is a currency used for online payments. It is based in Belize which provides immunity from national laws of other countries for it. As an offshore currency, it is also encrypted much like cryptocurrencies and benefits from better anonymity and security. The Advance Cash company provides an account for users that allows for a variety of currencies to operate through it. In many ways, it is a lot like Payeer.</p>



<p>And much like Payeer, AdvCash supports transfers in both fiat and cryptocurrency form. With a virtual wallet, users can transfer funds and make payments with very low commission. What makes it interesting, is that Advance Cash is also compatible with other payment systems such as WebMoney or Perfect Money. With free international transfers, users get to enjoy a wide variety of currencies all in a virtual wallet. Furthermore, there are both physical and virtual bank cards available for quick and cheap international Visa/Mastercard payments.</p>



<p>The company was founded in 2014 as a competitor for PayPal and much like its peers, it has gained notable success in the past few years. As the need for virtual banking grows, online payment processing companies continue to narrow the gap with PayPal. Although, such companies are not as popular as PayPal, they offer a lot more freedom.</p>



<p>Keep in mind that you can also <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-advcash-to-payeer-usd/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange AdvCash to PayPal</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin?</strong></h2>



<p>Bitcoin is a digital currency that was developed following the housing market crash in January 2009. This cryptocurrency follows the ideas started out by the pseudonymous and mysterious Satoshi Nakamoto in a whitepaper. The identity of the individual or individuals that developed the software is still a mystery. Unlike government-issued currencies, Bitcoin is operated by a decentralized authority and offers the promise of lower transaction fees than traditional online payment mechanisms.</p>



<p>There are no physical Bitcoins and the coins you see are novelty coins that do not have any real value without the code inscribed on them. Bitcoin is only balances retained on a public ledger that everyone has transparent access to, and is verified by a massive amount of computing power along with all Bitcoin transactions. Bitcoins are not issued or supported as a commodity by any banks or governments, nor are individual bitcoins valuable. Although it is not legal tender, the popularity of Bitcoin charts is high, and hundreds of other virtual currencies collectively referred to as Altcoins have been launched following this cryptocurrency.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the homepage first, then select AdvCash USD and Bitcoin from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of BTC you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>



<li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your AdvCash and Payeer wallet details and email. The phone number is optional.</li>



<li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li>Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the AdvCash gateway and make the payment to our AdvCash account. Having transferred your AdvCash USD to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>



<li>By finishing all the steps above, our team will send the Bitcoin to your wallet as soon as possible</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>Just like that, you have now converted AdvCash to BTC. In general, WMZ payments are inconsistent in terms of how long they might take. Give it a few minutes and the AdvCash USD will be in your account ASAP. In the meantime, you can follow up on your order using the Track ID provided for you. Simply enter the track id in the required section on homepage to see at which point your order is. Remember not to share your Track ID with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin-2/">How to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin [Instant]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Payeer USD to Tether USDT</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-payeer-usd-to-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-payeer-usd-to-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 08:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6406</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking to exchange Payeer USD to Tether USDT? CoinCannon is all you need! Exchanging digital currencies can be a hassle sometimes, especially when you want crypto assets. For the most part, it might be easy to convert assets, but finding an exchanger with no compromise is hard. Fortunately, CoinCannon offers everything online customers need to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-payeer-usd-to-tether/">How to Exchange Payeer USD to Tether USDT</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking to exchange Payeer USD to Tether USDT? CoinCannon is all you need! Exchanging digital currencies can be a hassle sometimes, especially when you want crypto assets. For the most part, it might be easy to convert assets, but finding an exchanger with no compromise is hard. Fortunately, CoinCannon offers everything online customers need to convert their assets. Thanks to a hassle-free KYC process and super-competitive exchange fees, you can instantly exchange Payeer USD to Tether USDT.</p>



<p>Get started! Head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Payeer USD on the left box and Tether USDT on the right and you’re good to go.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Payeer USD to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange direction, you will need a verified and active Payeer account. Make sure that the transaction amount does not exceed your withdrawal limit. In order to receive Tether (USDT), you will need a reliable crypto wallet. There are too many options out there, but CoinCannon suggests customers to use Trust Wallet. Furthermore, make sure you pay attention to the TRC20 and ERC20 variants for Tether as they use different networks for transactions and require different wallet addresses.</p>



<p>On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Payeer and How Does it Work?</strong></h2>



<p>First and foremost, Payeer is considered an online digital wallet for better asset management. Be it crypto of fiat, the payment processor is quick, reliable and cheap. In that regard, in a short lifespan of almost 8 years, Payeer is now recognized as one of the very best amongst competitors. Payeer utilizes built-in payment services with giant financial services such as Mastercard, VISA and PayPal.</p>



<p>As of 2021, the Payeer has approximately 7 million users which can transfer funds to each other with extremely low fees. The strength however, lies in diversity. Payeer is far ahead of any similar platform in terms of scale of operation and diversity in supported payment methods. With more than 50 payment approaches, the Payeer wallet offers users various services in one place.</p>



<p>To learn more about Payeer, continue reading “<a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-payeer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Payeer?</a>”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Payeer USD to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Payeer USD to Tether USDT</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Payeer on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>By now, you will go to the Payeer gateway. Transfer your Payeer USD to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-payeer-usd-to-tether/">How to Exchange Payeer USD to Tether USDT</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-payeer-usd-to-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Exchange AdvCash to Tether USDT [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-tether-usdt/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-tether-usdt/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 08:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AdvCash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6389</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking for the ultimate platform to exchange AdvCash to Tether USDT? CoinCannon is the ultimate platform for the job! So far, AdvCash has been one of the most crypto-friendly payment processors out there. Regardless, the anonymity factor remains an issue as users may be concerned with their privacy. Fortunately, our platform eliminates all the downsides [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-tether-usdt/">&lt;strong&gt;Exchange AdvCash to Tether USDT [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking for the ultimate platform to exchange AdvCash to Tether USDT? <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is the ultimate platform for the job! So far, AdvCash has been one of the most crypto-friendly payment processors out there. Regardless, the anonymity factor remains an issue as users may be concerned with their privacy. Fortunately, our platform eliminates all the downsides associated with converting AdvCash to crypto assets. You can instantly convert your AdvCash to Tether USDT with the lowest exchange fees and a hassle-free KYC process that maximizes privacy. On top of that, you will have 24/7 online support for the utmost reliability. In this article, we will go over everything you need to know on how to exchange AdvCash to Tether USDT.</p>



<p>So get started! Head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select AdvCash on the left box and Tether on the right one and you’re good to go!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">how to exchange AdvCash to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange AdvCash to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange direction, you will need a verified and active AdvCash account. Make sure that the transaction amount does not exceed your withdrawal limit. In order to receive Tether (USDT), you will need a reliable crypto wallet. There are too many options out there, but CoinCannon suggests customers to use Trust Wallet. Furthermore, make sure you pay attention to the TRC20 and ERC20 variants for Tether as they use different networks for transactions and require different wallet addresses.</p>



<p>On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is AdvCash?</strong></h2>



<p>Before we talk about how to convert AdvCash to Tether USDT, let’s have a brief introduction on what the payment processor is. AdvCash is a currency used for online payments. It is based in Belize which provides immunity from national laws of other countries for it. As an offshore currency, it is also encrypted much like cryptocurrencies and benefits from better anonymity and security. The Advance Cash company provides an account for users that allows for a variety of currencies to operate through it. In many ways, it is a lot like the payment processor Payeer.</p>



<p>And much like Payeer, AdvCash supports transfers in both fiat and cryptocurrency form. With a virtual wallet, users can transfer funds and make payments with very low commission. What makes it interesting, is that Advance Cash is also compatible with other payment systems such as WebMoney or Perfect Money. With free international transfers, users get to enjoy a wide variety of currencies all in a virtual wallet. Furthermore, there are both physical and virtual bank cards available for quick and cheap international Visa/Mastercard payments.</p>



<p>The company was founded in 2014 as a competitor for PayPal and much like its peers, it has gained notable success in the past few years. As the need for virtual banking grows, online payment processing companies continue to narrow the gap with PayPal. Although, such companies are not as popular as PayPal, they offer a lot more freedom.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange AdvCash to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon is the Best Exchange!</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange AdvCash to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select AdvCash on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>By now, you will go to the AdvCash gateway. Transfer your AdvCash to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-you-re-all-set"><strong>You’re all Set!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-tether-usdt/">&lt;strong&gt;Exchange AdvCash to Tether USDT [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-tether-usdt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy IOTA with Payeer [Private and Secure]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-iota-with-payeer/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-iota-with-payeer/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 10:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy IOTA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IOTA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MIOTA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4374</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You can directly buy IOTA with Payeer USD on CoinCannon if you have a Payeer account. The exchange will be fully private and backed by 24/7 customer support. IOTA has been around for a while but only recently the network experienced a massive growth in popularity. Having signed partnership contracts with companies like Volkswagen and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-iota-with-payeer/">How to Buy IOTA with Payeer [Private and Secure]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>You can directly buy IOTA with Payeer USD on CoinCannon if you have a Payeer account. The exchange will be fully private and backed by 24/7 customer support. IOTA has been around for a while but only recently the network experienced a massive growth in popularity. Having signed partnership contracts with companies like Volkswagen and Bosch, IOTA platform is nothing short of extraordinary. Good news is that you can Buy and Sell MIOTA on CoinCannon with the best rates at any time.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Head on over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> to buy IOTA with Payeer.</p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-iota"><strong>What is IOTA?</strong></h2>



<p>To explain IOTA, we must first discuss distributed ledgers. A distributed ledger is simply a database that is shared by multiple participants like sites, servers, institutions etc. It is essentially a network within which the transactions can be witnessed and saved by all participants.</p>



<p>IOTA is a distributed ledger which executes and records the transactions between devices and computers in the internet of things (IoT) ecosystem. In simpler terms, it is a network that utilizes its own cryptocurrency called MIOTA for transactions.</p>



<p>In terms of utility, it benefits from a massively improved scalability and transaction speed. The platform has a system of nodes (proof of stake) for consensus called Tangle.</p>



<p>As of December 2021, MIOTA is currently ranked as the 47th cryptocurrency with a market cap of $3.2 billion.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-buy-iota-with-payeer"><strong>Why Buy IOTA with Payeer?</strong></h2>



<p>First and foremost, Payeer is considered an online digital wallet for better asset management. Be it crypto of fiat, the payment processor is quick, reliable and cheap. In that regard, in a short lifespan of almost 8 years, Payeer is now recognized as one of the very best amongst competitors. Payeer utilizes built-in payment services with giant financial services such as Mastercard, VISA and PayPal.</p>



<p>As of 2021, the Payeer has approximately 7 million users which can transfer funds to each other with extremely low fees. The strength however, lies in diversity. Payeer is far ahead of any similar platform in terms of scale of operation and diversity in supported payment methods. With more than 50 payment approaches, the Payeer wallet offers users various services in one place.</p>



<p>To learn more about Payeer, continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-payeer/">What is Payeer</a>?”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-buy-iota-with-payeer-on-jolixo"><strong>Why Buy IOTA with Payeer on CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p><strong>CoinCannon is an online exchange that offers everything you need from a platform.</strong></p>



<p>Truthfully, it is a rare combination for an online exchange to offer anonymity, lowest exchange rates and unparalleled reliability altogether.</p>



<p>We respect our customer’s privacy by not asking for their personal information. The best way for anyone to protect their information is to not disclose them at all. In that regard, not having KYC or sign up is the best method.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the platform utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at all times. Our words sound too good? Just pay a visit to ranking websites such as BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>Lastly, according to Murphy’s law “anything that can go wrong will go wrong”. To stay ahead of any problems, we offer 24/7 customer support.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-step-by-step-guide"><strong>Step-by-Step Guide</strong></h2>



<p>Select Payeer USD on the “I Give” field on the left and IOTA on the “I Get” field on the right.</p>



<p>Enter the desired amount for the exchange and wait for the site to calculate the <strong>amazing exchange rates</strong>!</p>



<p>Click “Exchange”</p>



<p>Enter your IOTA Wallet address and E-mail address</p>



<p>Click “Exchange”</p>



<p>Read the Information</p>



<p>Complete the CAPTCHA</p>



<p>Click “Exchange”</p>



<p></p>



<p>At this point, please check the transaction information and terms and conditions carefully.</p>



<p>You will be able to see the track id and CoinCannon Payeer account</p>



<p>Open your Payeer account, click on the account menu and copy the account number that begins by the letter “p” and paste it in the required field.</p>



<p>Go back to your Payeer account and send the exchange amount to CoinCannon Payeer account.</p>



<p>Once you have sent the exchange amount, go to the history menu on your Payeer account and copy the operation id for the payment. Then paste the operation id in the required field.</p>



<p>Kindly agree to the terms and conditions and click on “Pay Order.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-finished"><strong>Finished!</strong></h2>



<p>At this point, our sales team will immediately get to work and make the IOTA payment to your wallet. The process does not take long, however, you can spend some time reading articles on <a href="blog.hi.exchange">CoinCannon Blog</a>. The blog has a wide variety of subjects from technical price analysis to satire pieces about the market.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-iota-with-payeer/">How to Buy IOTA with Payeer [Private and Secure]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-iota-with-payeer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Polkadot with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-polkadot-with-perfect-money/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-polkadot-with-perfect-money/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 11:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy Polkadot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perfect Money]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4387</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you’re looking to know how to buy Polkadot with Perfect Money look no further as we will provide a full 2024 guide and the best platform to make the exchange. DOT has been amongst the very best altcoins in the past two years. Utilizing a revolutionary idea as well as great leadership by Gavin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-polkadot-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy Polkadot with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you’re looking to know how to buy Polkadot with Perfect Money look no further as we will provide a full 2024 guide and the best platform to make the exchange. </p>



<p>DOT has been amongst the very best altcoins in the past two years. Utilizing a revolutionary idea as well as great leadership by Gavin Wood, the network is reaching new heights. </p>



<p>In this article, we will guide you on how to buy Polkadot with Perfect Money and to avoid sky-high exchange rates. Furthermore, you don’t have to share your personal information with the platform unlike big trading apps.</p>



<p>Get started right now, head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> to buy DOT.</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-2 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button is-style-outline is-style-outline--1"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-black-color has-text-color has-background has-link-color wp-element-button" href="http://www.hi.exchange/" style="background-color:#f49d3f">Buy <strong>DOT</strong> with <strong>Perfect Money</strong> Right Now!</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-buy-polkadot-with-perfect-money"><strong>Why Buy Polkadot with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>Perfect Money is an e-currency used for making payments on the internet. It is widely accepted as payment option by countless platforms. With Perfect Money, you can do a lot! Be it transferring funds to others or pay for goods and services. Or how about buying cryptocurrencies or even buying fiat currencies. It is a seriously popular payment method for online users. An additional capability is to loan and receipt issuance throughout the system.</p>



<p>The biggest downside of Perfect Money, however, is that you cannot cash Perfect money to your bank account on its website directly. For that, you will need a platform like CoinCannon to exchange your Perfect Money to PayPal and other e-currencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-buy-polkadot-with-perfect-money"><strong>How to Buy Polkadot with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>Here are the five easy steps to make the purchase:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 1 : </strong>Enter the homepage first, then select Perfect Money and Polkadot from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of DOT you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>



<li><strong>Step 2 : </strong>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Polkadot wallet details, email, and phone number.</li>



<li><strong>Step 3 : </strong>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li><strong>Step 4 : </strong>Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the Perfect Money gateway and make the payment to our Perfect Money account. Having transferred your Perfect Money to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>



<li><strong>Step 5 : </strong>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the Polkadot to your wallet ASAP.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-that-was-easy"><strong>That Was Easy!</strong></h2>



<p>The sales team will immediately process the exchange and make the DOT payment to your wallet. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-to-choose-jolixo"><strong>Why to choose CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p><a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> was found with the vision to create a solid exchange platform that offers everything the customers need. And the platform successfully dealt with all the challenges. Ideally speaking, an online exchange must offer privacy, efficiency and reliability altogether.</p>



<p>Cryptocurrencies are losing the anonymity as more and more institutions continue to sell user data to both regulators and the highest bidders. To prevent your data from getting in the wrong hands, the best method is to not share it with unnecessary platforms. In that regard, CoinCannon platform respects customer privacy by not asking for it at all. No KYC or sign up is mandatory on the website.</p>



<p>Protecting your privacy on the other hand is not a luxury. In that regard, it is not easy to find an exchange that offers both privacy and low exchange rates simultaneously. However, CoinCannon has managed to offer both at the same time. The exchange rates are competitive as you can see for yourself on ranking websites such as BestChange and OkChanger.</p>



<p>Last but not least, reliability is a proof of work that comes with experience. The platform offers 24/7 customer support to ensure all potential problems are immediately dealt with.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-polkadot-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy Polkadot with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-polkadot-with-perfect-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Tether with Payeer USD [No KYC]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-payeer/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-payeer/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 11:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy USDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5774</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you already have a Payeer account, you can buy Tether with Payeer USD on CoinCannon. On CoinCannon platform, you will pay the lowest exchange fees on your transaction and don’t have to compromise your personal information. On top of that, all transactions will have 24/7 online support to ensure the utmost quality of service. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-payeer/">How to Buy Tether with Payeer USD [No KYC]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you already have a Payeer account, you can buy Tether with Payeer USD on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>. On CoinCannon platform, you will pay the lowest exchange fees on your transaction and don’t have to compromise your personal information. On top of that, all transactions will have 24/7 online support to ensure the utmost quality of service. Since the early days of crypto, Tether (USDT) has been so inevitably utilitarian that all of us have to use it. Basically, it is a stablecoin that we buy and sell to hedge against the market volatility. In this article, we will go over everything you need to buy Tether with Payeer USD on our platform.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/buy-cryptocurrencies-with-payeer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Buy Cryptocurrencies with Payeer</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Tether with Payeer?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange direction, you will need a verified and active Payeer account to make the payments. Plus, you will also need to have a secure crypto wallet that supports Tether (USDT). As for the CoinCannon, all you need is an email address since no KYC (know your customer) is mandatory. Having said that, there are many advantages for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. By signing up, you will take part in our monthly airdrops with multiple $100 gifts!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Tether (USDT)?</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to buy Tether USDT, let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/how-exchange-tether-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Tether to PayPal</a></p>
</blockquote>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Buy Tether with Payeer?</strong></h2>



<p>First and foremost, Payeer is considered an online digital wallet for better asset management. Be it crypto of fiat, the payment processor is quick, reliable and cheap. In that regard, in a short lifespan of almost 8 years, Payeer is now recognized as one of the very best amongst competitors. Payeer utilizes built-in payment services with giant financial services such as Mastercard, VISA and PayPal.</p>



<p>As of 2021, the Payeer has approximately 7 million users which can transfer funds to each other with extremely low fees. The strength however, lies in diversity. Payeer is far ahead of any similar platform in terms of scale of operation and diversity in supported payment methods. With more than 50 payment approaches, the Payeer wallet offers users various services in one place.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>To learn more about Payeer, continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-payeer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Payeer</a>?”.</p>
</blockquote>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Number One!</strong></h2>



<p>Here’s the deal, exchange platforms are plenty, but the good ones are hard to find. Essentially, what you should be looking for is good exchange rates, anonymity and of course reliability. While these three qualities sound obvious, it’s actually not that easy to find a platform that offers them all at once. With that, platforms often tend to compromise on one of these above-mentioned factors.</p>



<p>Here at CoinCannon, our goal is to provide the ultimate exchange experience. Subsequently, the platform offers all the three important characteristics together.</p>



<p>We respect our customer’s privacy by not asking for their personal information. The best way for anyone to protect their information is to not disclose them at all. In that regard, not having KYC or sign up is the best method.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the platform utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at all times. Our words sound too good? Just pay a visit to ranking websites such as BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>Lastly, according to Murphy’s law “anything that can go wrong will go wrong”. To stay ahead of any problems, we offer 24/7 customer support.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Buy Tether with Payeer USD?</strong></h2>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Step 1</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Select Payeer USD on the “I Give” field on the left and Tether (USDT) on the “I Get” field on the right.</li>



<li>Enter the desired amount for the exchange and wait for the site to calculate the amazing exchange rates!</li>



<li>Click “Exchange”</li>
</ol>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Step 2</strong></h3>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter your Tether Wallet address and E-mail address</li>



<li>Click “Exchange”</li>
</ol>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Step 3</h3>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Read the Information</li>



<li>Complete the CAPTCHA</li>



<li>Click “Exchange”</li>
</ol>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Step 4</h3>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>At this point, please check the transaction information and terms and conditions carefully.</li>



<li>You will be able to see the track id and CoinCannon Payeer account</li>



<li>Open your Payeer account, click on the account menu and copy the account number that begins by the letter “p” and paste it in the required field.</li>



<li>Go back to your Payeer account and send the exchange amount to CoinCannon Payeer account.</li>



<li>Once you have sent the exchange amount, go to the history menu on your Payeer account and copy the operation id for the payment. Then paste the operation id in the required field.</li>



<li>Kindly agree to the terms and conditions and click on “Pay Order.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the USDT to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-payeer/">How to Buy Tether with Payeer USD [No KYC]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-payeer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Dash with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-dash-with-perfect-money/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-dash-with-perfect-money/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 10:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy Dash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DASH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange DASH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perfet Money]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4848</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As the cryptocurrency landscape continues to grow, knowing how to efficiently purchase digital assets is essential. In this 2024 update, we will guide you on how to buy Dash with Perfect Money, a trusted online payment system. Dash, celebrated for its privacy and speed, remains a favored choice among crypto enthusiasts. Perfect Money provides a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-dash-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy Dash with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>As the cryptocurrency landscape continues to grow, knowing how to efficiently purchase digital assets is essential. In this 2024 update, we will guide you on how to <strong><a href="https://hi.exchange/">buy Dash with Perfect Money</a></strong>, a trusted online payment system.</p>



<p>Dash, celebrated for its privacy and speed, remains a favored choice among crypto enthusiasts. Perfect Money provides a secure and seamless way to transfer funds globally, making it ideal for purchasing cryptocurrencies.</p>



<p>This article offers a concise, step-by-step guide to help you navigate the process of buying Dash with Perfect Money. Whether you&#8217;re an experienced investor or new to digital currencies, our guide ensures you have the most up-to-date information to make informed decisions.</p>



<p>From setting up your Perfect Money account to choosing the right exchange and completing your purchase, we&#8217;ve got you covered. Let&#8217;s dive in and explore how to <strong>buy Dash with Perfect Money</strong> efficiently and securely in 2024.</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-3 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button is-style-outline is-style-outline--2"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-black-color has-text-color has-background has-link-color wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/" style="background-color:#f49d3f">Buy Dash with Perfect Money Right Now!</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-buy-dash-with-perfect-money"><strong>Why Buy Dash with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>Perfect Money is an e-currency for making payments on the internet. It is widely accepted as payment option by countless platforms. </p>



<p>With Perfect Money, you can do a lot! Be it transferring funds to others or pay for goods and services. Or how about buying cryptocurrencies or even buying fiat currencies. </p>



<p>It is a seriously popular payment method for online users. An additional capability is to loan and receipt issuance throughout the system.</p>



<p>The biggest downside of Perfect Money, however, is that you cannot cash Perfect money to your bank account on its website directly. For that, you will need a platform like CoinCannon to exchange your Perfect Money to PayPal and other e-currencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-buy-dash-with-perfect-money"><strong>How to Buy Dash with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>All it takes is 5 easy steps:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 1 :</strong> Enter the homepage first, then select Perfect Money and Dash from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of Dash you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-1-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Buy Dash with Perfect Money Step 1 " class="wp-image-8637" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-1-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-1-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-1-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-1-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-1.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 2 : </strong>Press Next and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Dash wallet details, email, and phone number.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-2-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Buy Dash with Perfect Money Step 2" class="wp-image-8636" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-2-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-2-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-2-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-2-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-2.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 3 : </strong>One more time, click on the “Next” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-3-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Buy Dash with Perfect Money Step 3" class="wp-image-8635" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-3-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-3-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-3-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-3-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-3.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 4 :</strong> Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Confirm” button to go to the Perfect Money gateway and make the payment to our Perfect Money account. Having transferred your Perfect Money to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-4-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Buy Dash with Perfect Money Step 4" class="wp-image-8634" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-4-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-4-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-4-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-4-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-4.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the Dash to your wallet as soon as possible</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-5-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Buy Dash with Perfect Money Step 5" class="wp-image-8633" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-5-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-5-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-5-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-5-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/PerfectMoney-Dash-5.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will immediately process your order and send the funds to your wallet. The process might take a short while. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-jolixo"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p>Essentially, you need three primary qualities in an ideal exchange platform. Anonymity, good rates and reliability. The CoinCannon team consists of traders and professionals who have felt the need for an ideal exchange and pursued their vision.</p>



<p>First and foremost, all users need to protect their personal information especially when it comes down to financial transactions. Unfortunately, a vast majority of exchange apps and platforms make massive profits off of selling user data. </p>



<p>Best case scenario, they are legally bound to disclose user information with national authorities for any reason. In that regard, the best method to protect your privacy is to not disclose them with anyone at all. <a href="https://hi.exchange/">CoinCannon </a>does not require customers to go through KYC (know your customer) or even a mandatory sign up. In that regard, it is simply as safe as one can get making an exchange.</p>



<p>On the other hand, privacy is not a reason to pay more on your exchange. With that in mind, the platform offers some of the most competitive exchange rates you can find anywhere. Don’t take our word for it. You can simply pay a visit to ranking websites such as BestChange or OkChanger and see compare our rates with others.</p>



<p>Last but not least, not everything goes as planned in the digital world. Subsequently, the platform provides true online 24/7 customer support for the users.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-dash-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy Dash with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-dash-with-perfect-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange TonCoin to PayPal [No KYC]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-toncoin-to-paypal/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-toncoin-to-paypal/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 08:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Telegram]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TON]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6302</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Here is the best platform to exchange TonCoin to PayPal with full anonymity and no added fees: CoinCannon. TonCoin (TON) is one of the newer altcoins, aiming to deliver quick and efficient transactions. Now, while their timing may be a bit late for the absolutely saturated competition, their success tells us a lot about their [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-toncoin-to-paypal/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange TonCoin to PayPal [No KYC]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Here is the best platform to exchange TonCoin to PayPal with full anonymity and no added fees: <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>. TonCoin (TON) is one of the newer altcoins, aiming to deliver quick and efficient transactions. Now, while their timing may be a bit late for the absolutely saturated competition, their success tells us a lot about their potential. In this article, we will go over what is TonCoin (TON) and tell you all about how to exchange TonCoin to PayPal. And that is on a platform that does not compromise on privacy or charge the customer any extra fees for their added benefits.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-toncoin-ton"><strong>What is TonCoin (TON)?</strong></h2>



<p>TonCoin (TON) is a high-speed, secure, and scalable blockchain platform and cryptocurrency. It was created in 2018 by the Russian-based Telegram messenger team with the aim of delivering a fast, secure, and scalable infrastructure for decentralized applications. TonCoin utilizes a multi-blockchain architecture, sharding, and an innovative consensus algorithm called &#8220;Proof-of-Stake-Vote&#8221; to achieve high speed and scalability.</p>



<p>One of the key features of TonCoin is its high-speed transactions, with the ability to process millions of transactions per second. This makes it suitable for a wide range of use cases, from decentralized exchanges to micropayments and gaming. TonCoin also provides robust security features, including end-to-end encryption and multi-sig support.</p>



<p>Another advantage of TonCoin is its multi-blockchain architecture, which allows for greater scalability and allows for the creation of custom blockchain solutions for specific use cases. This allows developers to create highly optimized blockchain solutions that are tailored to their specific requirements.</p>



<p>TonCoin also offers a unique consensus algorithm, &#8220;Proof-of-Stake-Vote&#8221;, which combines the benefits of Proof-of-Stake and Delegated Proof-of-Stake. This consensus algorithm allows for fast and efficient consensus, while also providing a high degree of security. This consensus algorithm also enables TonCoin to have a more democratic governance structure, with token holders having the ability to vote on important network decisions.</p>



<p>In conclusion, TonCoin offers a highly scalable and secure blockchain platform, with a focus on high-speed transactions, multi-blockchain architecture, and a unique consensus algorithm. With its wide range of use cases, robust security features, and democratic governance structure, TonCoin has the potential to become a major player in the cryptocurrency and blockchain space.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange TonCoin to PayPal?</strong></h2>



<p>PayPal is an online trade company that, through online transfers, facilitates payments between parties. Its system allows clients to set up an account on its platform that is linked to the user’s credit card or checking account. Upon confirmation of identification and proof of funds, through the website or application of the company, users can begin sending or receiving payments online to and from other PayPal accounts.</p>



<p>As mentioned above, in order to transfer money to others using the receiver’s email address or mobile phone number, PayPal account holders can use the website or mobile application of the company. Within only a matter of minutes, transactions go through and the company promises that transfers are immediately available for payment or withdrawal to a bank account.</p>



<p>The ease of use and the wide acceptance makes the exchange cryptocurrencies to PayPal one of the best options when you need some cash to spend online.</p>



<p>All that said, you also have the ability to exchange TonCoin (TON) to Perfect Money USD, Payeer USD or Webmoney USD.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon is Better!</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it&#8217;s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that&#8217;s why we don&#8217;t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don&#8217;t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That&#8217;s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange TonCoin to PayPal?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select TonCoin (TON) on the left field and PayPal on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your PayPal account details, TON wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your TonCoin to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>After the steps mentioned above, our team will immediately process your order. Keep in mind that PayPal payments might take a while to complete. In the meantime, you can pay a visit to CoinCannon Blog and read some of the latest news articles about the crypto market. If you have any questions or problems, you can get in touch with the 24/7 online support section on the website.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-toncoin-to-paypal/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange TonCoin to PayPal [No KYC]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-toncoin-to-paypal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Solana with PayPal [Best Exchange Rates]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-paypal/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-paypal/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 08:37:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4285</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you are looking to buy Solana with PayPal, this article will provide a step-by-step guide. Solana took the market by storm in 2020 as an Ethereum competitor. In terms of scalability it is one of the fastest blockchain networks. The network has massive institutional investors hooked in as a DeFi platform and SOL as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-paypal/">How to Buy Solana with PayPal [Best Exchange Rates]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you are looking to buy Solana with PayPal, this article will provide a step-by-step guide. Solana took the market by storm in 2020 as an Ethereum competitor. In terms of scalability it is one of the fastest blockchain networks. The network has massive institutional investors hooked in as a DeFi platform and SOL as the native token is incredibly successful. You can buy Solana with PayPal seamlessly and anonymously on CoinCannon.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>To get started, go to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> platform to buy Solana with PayPal.</p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-solana"><strong>What is Solana?</strong></h2>



<p>In short, Solana is a blockchain platform for decentralized applications (DApps). The network utilizes Proof of Stake consensus algorithm. However, in a world full of PoS blockchain networks, Solana has managed to achieve some impressive figures. The network can support up to 50,000 transactions per second (TPS) and requires 400 milliseconds to build a block. With the quickly increasing number of validators currently at 1,061, the network is one of the fastest out there.</p>



<p>SOL is currently the 4<sup>th</sup> cryptocurrency with an astonishing $67+ billion market cap. As of November 2021, Solana has had almost 10000% growth in one year.</p>



<p>Continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-solana/">What is Solana</a>” to learn everything about the network.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-buy-with-paypal"><strong>Buy with PayPal</strong></h2>



<p>PayPal is at this point the number one financial platform for digital currencies. In terms of security of your assets, they provide great services. As compared with a bank, keeping money in PayPal account can save you some tax payments in the future. It is widely accepted as a payment method and simply makes a lot of sense. Having enjoyed incredible returns on your SOL investment, you can easily transfer the asset to your PayPal account.</p>



<p>Furthermore, as of 2021, 392 million people have PayPal accounts. In terms of popularity, PayPal is by far the best.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-buy-solana-with-paypal-on-jolixo"><strong>Why Buy Solana with PayPal on CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p>An ideal exchange platform must have three primary characteristics. Privacy, good exchange rates and reliability. CoinCannon has worked hard to provide all three for the customers.</p>



<p>For privacy, the safest way to protect customer information is not asking for it at all. This might be a challenge in many aspects yet anonymity is our utmost priority. Therefore, CoinCannon requires no KYC or even a sign up process.</p>



<p>When it comes to exchange rates, our strategy is to be as competitive as possible. CoinCannon utilizes an automated system to determine the best possible exchange rates at any moment. But you don’t have to take our word for it. You can visit ranking websites such as Bestchange and OkChanger to see our rank for yourself.</p>



<p>Lastly, reliability does not come easy. In order to provide the best exchange services, we offer real 24/7 customer support.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-buy-solana-with-paypal-step-by-step-guide"><strong>Buy Solana with PayPal Step-by-Step Guide</strong></h2>



<p>Here are the five easy steps to make the purchase:</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the homepage first, then select PayPal and Solana from the currency pairs in the first step. enter the amount you want to exchange, after that the amount of SOL you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>



<li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Solana wallet details, email, and phone number.</li>



<li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li>Complete the captcha test and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the PayPal gateway and pay online. After you have transferred your PayPal USD to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>



<li>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the SOL to your wallet ASAP.</li>
</ol>



<p>The exchange process does not take long. However, you can read some of our new, opinion, analysis or comedy articles on <a href="http://www.blog.hi.exchange/">HiExchage blog</a> while waiting.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-paypal/">How to Buy Solana with PayPal [Best Exchange Rates]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-paypal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy DOGE with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-doge-with-perfect-money/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-doge-with-perfect-money/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 08:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy DOGE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perfect Money]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4340</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If your favorite breed of dog is Shiba Inu, then Dogecoin is right up your alley. In this article, we will provide a step-by-step guide on how to buy DOGE with Perfect Money without having to go through KYC or sign up. DOGE is the king of all meme coins but in terms of scalability [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-doge-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy DOGE with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If your favorite breed of dog is Shiba Inu, then Dogecoin is right up your alley.</p>



<p>In this article, we will provide a step-by-step guide on<strong> how to buy DOGE with Perfect Money</strong> without having to go through KYC or sign up.</p>



<p> DOGE is the king of all meme coins but in terms of scalability and transaction fees, it is just as good as the others.</p>



<p>If you’re thinking of buying Dogecoin, CoinCannon is one of the best platforms you can find.</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-4 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button is-style-outline is-style-outline--3"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-black-color has-text-color has-background has-link-color wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/" style="background-color:#f49d3f">Buy <strong>DOGE</strong> with <strong>Perfect Money</strong> Right Now!</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-buy-doge-with-perfect-money"><strong>Why Buy DOGE with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>Perfect Money is an e-currency used for making payments on the internet. It is widely accepted as payment option by countless platforms. With Perfect Money, you can do a lot! Be it transferring funds to others or pay for goods and services. Or how about buying cryptocurrencies or even buying fiat currencies. It is a seriously popular payment method for online users. An additional capability is to loan and receipt issuance throughout the system.</p>



<p>The biggest shortcoming of Perfect Money is that you cannot cash Perfect money to your bank account on its website directly. For that, you will need a platform like CoinCannon to exchange your Perfect Money to PayPal and other e-currencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-buy-doge-with-perfect-money"><strong>How to Buy DOGE with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>All you have to do is go through five simple steps.</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 1:</strong> Enter the homepage first, then select Perfect Money and DOGE from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of DOGE you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-1-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Buy DOGE with Perfect Money - Step 1" class="wp-image-8645" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-1-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-1-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-1-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-1-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-1.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 2:</strong> Press Next and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your DOGE wallet details, email, and phone number.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-2-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Buy DOGE with Perfect Money - step 2" class="wp-image-8644" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-2-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-2-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-2-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-2-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-2.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 3:</strong> One more time, click on the “Next” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-3-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Buy DOGE with Perfect Money - step 3" class="wp-image-8643" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-3-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-3-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-3-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-3-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-3.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 4:</strong> Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Confirm” button to go to the Perfect Money gateway and make the payment to our Perfect Money account. Having transferred your Perfect Money to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-4-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Buy DOGE with Perfect Money - step 4" class="wp-image-8642" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-4-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-4-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-4-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-4-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-4.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 5:</strong> By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the Dogecoin to your wallet ASAP.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-5-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Buy DOGE with Perfect Money - step 5" class="wp-image-8641" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-5-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-5-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-5-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-5-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Dogecoin-PerfectMoney-5.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done-and-done"><strong>Done and Done!</strong></h2>



<p>Having completed the steps above, our sales team will immediately process your order and make the payment. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-jolixo"><strong>Why CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p>Three reasons: Privacy, efficiency and reliability. <a href="https://hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> offers everything you need from an online exchange platform.</p>



<p>The primary reason for the cryptocurrencies’ success was the cryptic nature. The blockchain platform allows the users to protect their privacy and personal information. However, more and more exchanges are now making it mandatory for users to disclose their information. CoinCannon does not ask for any personal information and it is not mandatory to sign up to use the services.</p>



<p>As for efficiency, CoinCannon offers some of the most competitive exchange rates. The platform utilizes an automated system to determine the best rates and stay ahead of the competition. You can check out ranking websites such as BestChange and OkChanger to see the platform’s rank for yourself.</p>



<p>Lastly, the website offers true 24/7 customer support to be in touch with customers at all times.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-doge-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy DOGE with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-doge-with-perfect-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange DAI to PayPal [lowest commission]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 09:45:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange DAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Maker DAO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4432</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>if you&#8217;re Looking to cash out your stablecoins, you can exchange DAI to PayPal on CoinCannon with the lowest exchange fees. DAI is the latest stablecoin added to CoinCannon platform along with, USDC and TUSD. Created with a unique architecture, DAI is a different kind of stable coin that offers better reliability compared with others. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/">How to Exchange DAI to PayPal [lowest commission]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>if you&#8217;re Looking to cash out your stablecoins, you can <strong>exchange DAI to PayPal on CoinCannon</strong> with the lowest exchange fees. DAI is the latest stablecoin added to CoinCannon platform along with, USDC and TUSD. Created with a unique architecture, DAI is a different kind of stable coin that offers better reliability compared with others. In this article, we will go through everything you need to exchange DAI to PayPal on CoinCannon website. You can also exchange DAI to other currencies on the platform.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-dai"><strong>What is DAI?</strong></h2>



<p>DAI is an Ethereum-based stablecoin. A stablecoin is a cryptocurrency with a pegged value to another currency. In case of DAI, it is pegged to the US dollar and much like Tether and USDC, Dai will always be worth $1. Stablecoins are a crucial part of the crypto market as they offer very little volatility. In that regard, investors use stablecoins to save their funds in the form of a reliable and stable asset.</p>



<p>What makes DAI unique is a clever design that eliminates the biggest concerns for stablecoins. Generally speaking, conventional stablecoins require a massive reserve by the company. For example, for every Tether USD, the Tether company must hold $1 USD in their reserve. This is a huge issue for companies as it is difficult to provide liquidity and keep it consistent.</p>



<p>DAI offers a new solution for this problem. By using an automated system of smart contracts on Ethereum blockchain, DAI does now need a reserve. Using collateralized debt denominated in ETH allows DAI to maintain the 1:1 ration with USD. Simply speaking, users can deposit Ethereum or other cryptocurrencies can borrow against the value of their deposit and generate new DAI. The currency is this case is known as collateral.</p>



<p>Currently, DAI has a market cap of over $9 billion and is ranked as 19<sup>th</sup> cryptocurrency.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-exchange-dai-to-paypal"><strong>Why Exchange DAI to PayPal?</strong></h2>



<p>PayPal is an online trade company that, through online transfers, facilitates payments between parties. Its system allows clients to set up an account on its platform that is linked to the user’s credit card or checking account. Upon confirmation of identification and proof of funds, through the website or application of the company, users can begin sending or receiving payments online to and from other PayPal accounts.</p>



<p>As mentioned above, in order to transfer money to others using the receiver’s email address or mobile phone number, PayPal account holders can use the website or mobile application of the company. Within only a matter of minutes, transactions go through and the company promises that transfers are immediately available for payment or withdrawal to a bank account.</p>



<p>The ease of use and the wide acceptance makes the exchange cryptocurrencies to PayPal one of the best options when you need some cash to spend online.</p>



<p>All that said, you also have the ability to exchange DAI to Perfect Money USD, Payeer USD or Webmoney USD.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-jolixo"><strong>Why CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p><strong>CoinCannon is an online exchange that offers everything you need from a platform.</strong></p>



<p>Truthfully, it is a rare combination for an online exchange to offer anonymity, lowest exchange rates and unparalleled reliability altogether.</p>



<p>We respect our customer’s privacy by not asking for their personal information. The best way for anyone to protect their information is to not disclose them at all. In that regard, not having KYC or sign up is the best method.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the platform utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at all times. Our words sound too good? Just pay a visit to ranking websites such as BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>Lastly, according to Murphy’s law “anything that can go wrong will go wrong”. To stay ahead of any problems, we offer 24/7 customer support.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-exchange-dai-to-paypal"><strong>How to Exchange DAI to PayPal?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select DAI on the left field and PayPal on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your PayPal account details, email, and phone number.</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your DAI to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>At this point, our team will process the order and make the payment to your account. PayPal payments might take some time. We suggest you read some of the articles on <a href="blog.hi.exchange">CoinCannon Blog</a> as you wait for the transaction.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/">How to Exchange DAI to PayPal [lowest commission]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
