<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>ELON Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/elon/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 06:55:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Faces Lawsuit for “Dogecoin Pyramid Scheme”</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/dogecoin-pyramid-sheme-elon/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/dogecoin-pyramid-sheme-elon/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 06:55:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin pyramid scheme]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ELON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elongate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5550</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There is a literary theory called formalism which is pretty boring but has a practical message. One should take everything at face value instead of acknowledging endless extrinsic benefactors. Now, taking Elon’s clownery on Twitter at face value, he was undoubtedly promoting a Dogecoin pyramid scheme. But guess what, nobody can prove it just like [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/dogecoin-pyramid-sheme-elon/">Elon Musk Faces Lawsuit for “Dogecoin Pyramid Scheme”</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>There is a literary theory called formalism which is pretty boring but has a practical message. One should take everything at face value instead of acknowledging endless extrinsic benefactors. Now, taking Elon’s clownery on Twitter at face value, he was undoubtedly promoting a Dogecoin pyramid scheme. But guess what, nobody can prove it just like nobody can prove Epstein didn’t kill himself. Today, the world of finance is taking a serious beating from social media due to well-coordinated pumps and dumps. And Elon, standing on top of the world, is running his own Dogecoin pyramid scheme to compensate for all of his far-fetched projects. After all, someone has to raise trillions of dollars to send humans to mars where extreme solar radiation will give you cancer. However, one investor has sued Elon and his companies for a lot of money and all we can say to him is Godspeed!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Buy and Sell Dogecoin Instantly on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a><br>No KYC</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-dogecoin-pyramid-scheme"><strong>Dogecoin Pyramid Scheme</strong></h2>



<p>Ha ha it’s so funny, Elon posted a meme on Twitter. Welp, Keith Johnson doesn’t think so. Mr. Johnson has bravely sued the meme mongering clown billionaire and his companies for a fair $258 billion. Basically, he is claiming that they promoted a Dogecoin pyramid scheme with their support for DOGE.</p>



<p>According to <a href="https://assets2.pacermonitor.com/filings/Johnson_v_Musk_et_al/Johnson_v_Musk_et_al__nysdce-22-05037__0001.0.pdf?X-Amz-Security-Token=IQoJb3JpZ2luX2VjELn%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2FwEaCXVzLWVhc3QtMSJHMEUCICe8v9QbE5ucxkNw%2F4uIyKQkjJprelAClmtWXaGaR63yAiEAmtTds26Or20TjflZQuFt8E5KHvARjGVAJVpAzkBd4iYq3AQIwv%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2FARADGgw5MjQ2NTE0MDgzOTgiDHdleGUYt3IzNA4WxCqwBMxc7LYGv%2F3FmkzepvB1iEhKy4WrV60iR%2BC6sgRWd7KRvpeKutlBGRhY%2BSpmfSN2P5eTxK1sprMAOk4RMJbwXMB2IwFCatBro0IJPS26eMo3TpqDLwCVQAfqVqTxlvqdgOv%2Fvesj6yET6XWuPEY08iW2ZbF%2F9fqXXy3ujKokd2%2BOMPORrbBGZ3wYx5E1Ux7GsuU7a55EJfmihcgkf22mcb2yW%2F25nolZn26PATe1SVfwfc%2BJPOFpch%2BpIDZDINfzNgnYW%2BNc60KcB%2FWBluXiuINNUw%2FqBPcx4FgwyAyTTt0%2BbPFpQnYc%2FzQ9XDwgOOge%2FK8mT3q3svyKADAW4LOmGnjxCMshOnxLrcWVA5pdQT6Xp1V56%2Br%2BSXD986u3EHnCTGoTiIP311bCYq1o4pcpjdcrCZE%2F%2F3rtF%2FehTr%2By3Iy9%2FdH3Dbp4RUl7%2BP16eOQvUeCCEukWX8M9OgFLYcvrdsAox1l%2Fw%2FUQ3dfLYpia7fVObcoo%2FRUN8ak85FMqBkgyKGB7mfCqDLM6vU%2Bw5Hianz3hWo9WuCcTEvKsqv%2FY6L0rIAC1uFw%2FC%2F4%2F%2Bs3qDpJhu%2BnvZGCCGv9%2FVPfjwvAI9XcQ6%2Bc2TC7kx5%2BPm7PyY0SKBM5C4a6JTMPcKog44sq9HTTeMawq1fBvsbBITYxKmjxRuE4rFCn2seFta5Elc54qv1Y0X5P0oQkjOESiNWyArByjoh4KLwtS9xiAA9Uh5Av0sFrFeGm5LKvXQaQz5YXAMOG6rZUGOqkB0oSanITZYUmLZlbgCjFCckfK8%2FTGfAR1DMznAy%2FFM1HNAh9Bi6glBFifnM68QF9sBoXrOZOICHPvTnPyEPQjClub0Bg1Fj9%2BH%2FL3rYsdeci303GLJtGoeuG5dMfIQI9hzTVw7qOi81%2FF68mt0OeLODNJNcw2j1nyQmb8%2FfWKut0BOzkDDZIchN9jIbI3ViOdimrq960jFJj7YVWSOD%2FrDKyHANsocddz9A%3D%3D&amp;X-Amz-Algorithm=AWS4-HMAC-SHA256&amp;X-Amz-Date=20220616T172931Z&amp;X-Amz-SignedHeaders=host&amp;X-Amz-Expires=599&amp;X-Amz-Credential=ASIA5OSMEZQHHGKLHKVM%2F20220616%2Fus-east-1%2Fs3%2Faws4_request&amp;X-Amz-Signature=e89dbab48532f1335e571cea705859ffa86dd08c2139a572d86c7cdbfb8c62c4" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">court documents</a>, Keith Johnson argues that Dogecoin is “simply a fraud whereby greater fools are deceived into buying a coin at a higher price. The documents are currently held with the US district court in southern district of New York.</p>



<p>Johnson is calling for the court to clarify the case as a class-action lawsuit. With that, he is asking for $86 billion in damages for the class, as well as $172 billion for treble damages.</p>



<p>Initially, Keith Johnson argues that Elon and his companies utilized “unethical, torturous and criminal conduct in promoting Dogecoin. Hence, billions of investors lost billions of dollars into the Dogecoin pyramid scheme. As for the numbers, Johnson states that musk made $86 billion “as a result of their wire fraud, gambling enterprise, false advertising, deceptive practices, and other unlawful conduct.”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Too Vague, and Silly!</h2>



<p>Billionaire Elon Musk is seeking to have the multi-billion-dollar lawsuit against him dismissed, which alleges he illegally promoted Dogecoin pyramid scheme. The lawsuit, which was filed by a group of investors, accuses Musk of perpetrating a scandal.</p>



<p>Attorneys representing the Tesla CEO are arguing that the lawsuit is baseless, and Musk&#8217;s statements about Dogecoin were too vague and silly to be considered actual endorsements of the cryptocurrency. Additionally, the lawyers contend that DOGE is a legitimate cryptocurrency with a market cap of around $10 billion. </p>



<p>Musk&#8217;s legal team stated, &#8220;There is nothing unlawful about tweeting words of support for or funny pictures about a legitimate cryptocurrency that continues to hold a market cap of nearly $10 billion. This court should dismiss the complaint and put a stop to plaintiffs&#8217; fantasy.&#8221; this statement matters a lot. Because apparently the court is dealing with a bunch of 12 year olds in this lawsuit!</p>



<p>The lawsuit filed by investors claims that Musk purposely drove the price of Dogecoin up by 36,000% over a two-year period before letting it crash. The suit also alleges that Dogecoin was a security, and Musk knew that it had no intrinsic value.</p>



<p>In addition, the Dogecoin Foundation is another defendant in the lawsuit and is also seeking to have it dismissed.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-elongate"><strong>Elongate</strong></h2>



<p>Elon may be the richest man on earth, but, almost all of his wealth is tied up in stocks for his companies. And, ding ding ding, all his stocks are holding the biggest bubbles in history. Don’t believe it? Then why would Bill gates hold a $2-billion-dollar short position on Tesla? Despite Elon’s wealth, his companies are constantly desperate for cash flow because bubbles take lots of money to continue.</p>



<p>Previously, Elon has stated that he holds Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH) and Dogecoin (DOGE). To make it more interesting, he had previously <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/elon-musk-says-the-us-should-do-nothing-about-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">said</a> that the US lawmakers should “do nothing” about crypto.</p>



<p>As to why he loves DOGE, he had said that it is the “people’s crypto”. You would think that in this day and age, communist style of deception would not work but you would be wrong. Today, everything is “people’s thing” everyone is doing it for “the people” just like the gulags were for the “people”.</p>



<p>In the world of insane maximalists and mislead retail investors, Elon’s Dogecoin pyramid scheme was an unfair one. While the current bear market is purging market from all the crazy NFT money and stimulus checks, Elon will continue to take from “the people”.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/dogecoin-pyramid-sheme-elon/">Elon Musk Faces Lawsuit for “Dogecoin Pyramid Scheme”</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/dogecoin-pyramid-sheme-elon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Twitter, A Decentralized Reverie…</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-twitter/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-twitter/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 08:36:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ELON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6118</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Upon hearing crypto Twitter, one shall be overwhelmed by the traumatic images of the meme wars. A safe haven for those with bold predictions of both bullish and bearish nature, fortune tellers perhaps. It used to be glamorous, back in the bullish days of our past, it used to be busy. And you can’t deny, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-twitter/">Crypto Twitter, A Decentralized Reverie…</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Upon hearing crypto Twitter, one shall be overwhelmed by the traumatic images of the meme wars. A safe haven for those with bold predictions of both bullish and bearish nature, fortune tellers perhaps. It used to be glamorous, back in the bullish days of our past, it used to be busy. And you can’t deny, there was something special about crypto Twitter, a community of endless bots. Busy streets paved with statements, technical analysis, shilling attempts, NFT sellers, crypto beggars. For that, one may call it a slum, with a handful of slumlords like Elon and CZ running a show. Elon’s acquisition of Twitter is surely a breath of fresh air for the crypto Twitter community. A community of investors bashed by a long-term bear market. And in his reign, other slumlords are now joining to help.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Numbers Go Up!</strong></h2>



<p>Binance, the world’s largest crypto exchange is rushing to chip in the crypto Twitter. Reportedly, Binance is making a team to help Elon incorporate blockchain technology into Twitter’s business model.</p>



<p>For the most part, integrating crypto into Twitter will take some work. With that, Binance’s team will be boots on the ground in Twitter HQ to help the free bird. This is according to a recent report by <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/crypto-exchange-binance-musks-co-investor-help-twitter-with-blockchain-2022-10-28/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Reuters</a>.</p>



<p>While Jack Dorsey, the previous owner of Twitter is planning to develop web5, CZ and Elon will rely on web3 to handle problems. Based on the report, the new Binance team will look toward crypto-based solutions to tackle Twitter issues. At this point, it would be safe to say that even the Binance team doesn’t know exactly what that means. However, one thing is for certain and that is the fact that crypto Twitter is here to pump the bejesus out of crypto.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>All Aboard Crypto Twitter</strong></h2>



<p>Last week, Elon finally managed to make the deal and purchase Twitter for $44 billion. He let that sink in Twitter HQ and fired a whole bunch of top executives.</p>



<p>Previously, Binance had made a pledge to co-invest with Elon back in May. According to Binance, Musk’s leadership could help utilize the web potential and its integration with social media. Furthermore, they expressed their hopefulness for an accelerated adoption rate for crypto assets in such case.</p>



<p>Changpeng Zhao, the CEO of Binance <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1585836479129202688?t=qefpBd450uBr68Sy0BaaSw&amp;s=19">told</a> his followers on Twitter (probably mostly bots) that the money was wired a few days ago.</p>



<p>“Our intern says we wired the $500 million two days ago, probably just as I was being asked about Elon/Twitter.”</p>



<p>Binance was in fact quick to jump on the Crypto Twitter train with a considerable investment.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-twitter/">Crypto Twitter, A Decentralized Reverie…</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-twitter/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DOGE Price Analysis and Predictions; October 17, 2021</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/doge-price-analysis-and-predictions-october-17-2021/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/doge-price-analysis-and-predictions-october-17-2021/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 08:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ELON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4033</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>DOGE price has been in an upward channel in the past few days. On Friday, by touching the bottom managed to bounce back and reach as high as $0.2450. At that point, it had to back down and today dipped below the middle of the channel at dipped to $0.2330. In this zone, the SMA100 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/doge-price-analysis-and-predictions-october-17-2021/">DOGE Price Analysis and Predictions; October 17, 2021</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>DOGE price has been in an upward channel in the past few days. On Friday, by touching the bottom managed to bounce back and reach as high as $0.2450. At that point, it had to back down and today dipped below the middle of the channel at dipped to $0.2330. In this zone, the SMA100 kept the price from further decline and recovered the price up to $0.2350. Currently, the price is around $0.2365.</p>



<p>If you are looking to buy or sell DogeCoin, you can <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/">learn how</a> to exchange DOT or other digital currencies with complete anonymity on <a href="http://hi.exchange">jolixo</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>DOGE Price Action Analysis</strong></h2>



<p>Taking a look at the 1-hour chart, we find DOGE still inside the channel and is continuing forward by bouncing between the ceiling and the bottom. Yesterday, the price reached the top at around $0.2450 but failed to stabilize and dipped below the $0.2350 support today. Once again, the SMA100 kept the price from further decline and brought DOGE back to above $0.2350.</p>



<p>In case the $0.2350 to $0.2330 zone manages to support the price, DOGE could once again reach for the top.</p>



<p>For the bullish scenario, the $0.24 zone is the first resistance level for DOGE price followed by $0.2450 and $0.25.</p>



<p>On the other hand, if the price fails to surpass the $0.24 and lose the $0.2350 support, there could be further price correction.</p>



<p>For the bearish scenario, the $0.2330 near the SMA100 and then the bottom of the channel at $0.23 are the crucial support levels. Further decline and losing the bottom could Bring DOGE down to $0.2250 and $0.22 and give it up.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="700" height="314" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/DOGEUSDT_2021-10-17_10-15-23.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-4035" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/DOGEUSDT_2021-10-17_10-15-23.jpg 700w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/DOGEUSDT_2021-10-17_10-15-23-300x135.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Technical Indicators</strong></h2>



<p>MACD indicator: at the time of writing this article the 1-hour MACD for Dogecoin is on a downward momentum</p>



<p>RSI: the relative strength index is approximately 45.</p>



<p>Resistance levels: the first one will be $0.24. Following that, we can expect $0.2450 to $0.2460 zone and then $0.2450 to $0.25 zone to be resistance levels on the way. </p>



<p>Support levels: first and foremost, the $0.2360 to $0.2350 zone will support the price. After that, the $0.2330 will be the next one. And then the $0.2250 and finally $0.22 will support the price next.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Buy and Sell DOGE on CoinCannon</strong></h2>



<p><a href="http://hi.exchange">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.okchanger.com/exchangers/jolixo">OkChanger</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. We are on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/">Bestchange</a> and are always amongst the top exchanges.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/doge-price-analysis-and-predictions-october-17-2021/">DOGE Price Analysis and Predictions; October 17, 2021</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/doge-price-analysis-and-predictions-october-17-2021/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SHIB Skyrockets with an 87% Rally in One Day</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/shib-skyrockets-with-an-87-rally-in-one-day/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/shib-skyrockets-with-an-87-rally-in-one-day/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 08:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ELON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MEMECOIN]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PUMP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shib]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBA INU]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=3953</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHIB (Shiba Inu), one of the more questionable cryptocurrencies had a massive pump on October 4 following an Elon Musk tweet. SHIB the Trouble Maker Some call it a memecoin, others call it a shitcoin. Elon Musk however, is having so much fun with this specific coin. The Ethereum-based SHIB, is as the anonymous creators [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/shib-skyrockets-with-an-87-rally-in-one-day/">SHIB Skyrockets with an 87% Rally in One Day</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>SHIB (Shiba Inu), one of the more questionable cryptocurrencies had a massive pump on October 4 following an Elon Musk tweet.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>SHIB the Trouble Maker</strong></h2>



<p>Some call it a memecoin, others call it a <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-shitcoin/">shitcoin</a>. Elon Musk however, is having so much fun with this specific coin.</p>



<p>The Ethereum-based SHIB, is as the anonymous creators call it a “decentralized meme token that evolved into a vibrant ecosystem”. To be honest, in terms of utility, Shiba does not bring a lot to the table. Being a part of the ERC20 network, the transaction fees are high and scalability is not as good as the competition. Furthermore, we do not know much about the creators as they have kept their identity a secret. We did an extensive job <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-shiba-inu/">introducing and explaining Shiba Inu</a>.</p>



<p>Recently, Coinbase added SHIB to their list of supported cryptocurrencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Floki Frunkpuppy</strong> </h2>



<p>As a surprise to no one, Elon Musk got a Shiba Inu puppy and posted a cute picture on twitter. At that point, it was only natural for the fans to purchase Shiba Inu coin to show support.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="de" dir="ltr">Floki Frunkpuppy <a href="https://t.co/xAr8T0Jfdf">pic.twitter.com/xAr8T0Jfdf</a></p>&mdash; Elon Musk (@elonmusk) <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1444840184500129797?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">October 4, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Subsequently, the massive pump resulted in a 112% rise in value for SHIB before a price correction bringing the profits down to 87%. Furthermore, this was happening at the same time Bitcoin was having a good bull run pushing it above the infamous $50k resistance level.</p>



<p>Following the initial breakout, Shiba was down in the slumps at $0.00000692 last week. The latest breakout managed to remove a zero and push the price to reach $0.00002374 according to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/shiba-inu/">CoinMarketCap</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>ShibaSwap</strong></h2>



<p>The Decentralized Finance (DeFi) platform ShibaSwap launched on July. It gave users the ability to earn passive income, stake, swap and provide liquidity using SHIB. This platform can be beneficial in long-term for holders. Also, being listed on Coinbase, one of the few exchanges active in the US will also provide better accessibility an ease of inflows for the memecoin at hand.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><a href="http://hi.exchange">jolixo</a> is an online decentralized platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and digital currencies. Our automated systems automatically determine the best exchange rates based on the competition. Furthermore, we provide 24l7 customer support. You can visit <a href="http://blog.hi.exchange">CoinCannon Blog</a> to stay up to date with our latest opinion articles, technical price analysis and news.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/shib-skyrockets-with-an-87-rally-in-one-day/">SHIB Skyrockets with an 87% Rally in One Day</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/shib-skyrockets-with-an-87-rally-in-one-day/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is Shitcoin</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-shitcoin/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-shitcoin/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 08:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ELON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=3896</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This article will define what is Shitcoin, how they came to be and some practical methods to detect them. Unfortunately, it is quite a considerable threat for the cryptocurrency market. However, a vast majority of shitcoins have the same behavior and can easily be identified. Shitcoin Definition Generally speaking, any cryptocurrency or digital currency must [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-shitcoin/">What is Shitcoin</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>This article will define what is Shitcoin, how they came to be and some practical methods to detect them. Unfortunately, it is quite a considerable threat for the cryptocurrency market. However, a vast majority of shitcoins have the same behavior and can easily be identified.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Shitcoin Definition</strong></h2>



<p>Generally speaking, any cryptocurrency or digital currency must first have utility. They maintain a purpose and provide practical utility toward the purpose. Secondly, based on the pragmatic capabilities of the currency, they have a certain value.</p>



<p>In that regard, value, and utility are two primary qualities preserved for solid cryptocurrencies and digital currencies.</p>



<p>Shitcoins are all those who lack both utility and value. They are worth next to nothing in terms of value. However, utilizing certain methods, the creators can hold the value as high as possible for a short period of time. In other words, they create a bubble that will eventually burst.</p>



<p>AT this point, it is worth taking a look at the methodology of creating, pumping and dumping a shitcoin.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Shitcoins and their promises</strong></h2>



<p>Following the introduction of Bitcoin in 2009, many attempts were made to create altcoins with pretty much the same characteristics. This creation would provide the creators with absolute control over their cryptocurrencies.</p>



<p>Primarily, all currencies have a limited supply. It is essentially the limit that creates scarcity, therefore keeping the value high or increasing it by demand. For example, Bitcoin’s supply is limited to 21 million. In case the supply grows, the increased quantity of that currency will dilute the value, causing decrease. In that regard, the value will decline due to the low scarcity.</p>



<p>With that perspective in mind, Shitcoins keep the demands high hence the high value. But at some point, due to the lack of utility, the bubble will burst.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Methodology</strong></h2>



<p>It all begins with an Initial Coin Offering (ICO). A network introduces itself and set up a first sale of their coin. Before this even takes place, the creators are the only owners of the coin. With the ICO, the first wave of demands, shoot the price high as the creators accumulate on large sums of money technically overnight. Basically, it is the marketing techniques that assure the high demand.</p>



<p>It is almost impossible for any cryptocurrency or digital currency to have great utility in the beginning. Therefore, the glorious promises of their success is the prominent factor for the demand. Investors are seldom greedy; they are looking for the highest profit in the shortest amount of time.</p>



<p>Many Shitcoins fail shortly after their ICO. The creators make a massive amount of money following the offering and sell almost all their coins. To put it simply, they dump the market following a successful pump.</p>



<p>On the other hand, there are some cryptocurrencies that stay around for a long time after their ICO. They utilize highly effective marketing techniques and sell the promise of developed future applications. Again, these marketing efforts will provide high demands for the coin.</p>



<p>One recurring pattern for Shitcoin is the fact that, numerous pump events can be tempting for the investors. Say you hear about a certain cryptocurrency that has had more than a handful of massive pumps. In that case, despite knowing the risky nature of the coin, you might still invest.</p>



<p>While all this is happening, the skyrocketing of the price does two things. First, inflation within the value increases drastically, the bubble grows bigger. Second, with the massive and sudden rise in inflation, volatility grows like crazy! Much like any other ecosystem in the world, entropy increase within the system and very soon, chaos will ensue.</p>



<p>As for the last step, the bubble will burst, a sharp plunge in price liquidates all the long positions on the cryptocurrencies and lowers the value of people’s investments. This sobering decline hits the investors with the realization that any second they hesitate to sell the coins; they will lose more money. Hence the sellout and the negative demands bring the price to nothing.</p>



<p>Taking a look at the primary plunge in price that initiates the downfall, most of the times it is the largest investors (whales) that are the creators themselves.</p>



<p>A classic example of a shitcoin is <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/bitconnect-trading-bot-was-a-2-billion-scam-says-sec/">Bitconnect</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Do not Fall Prey to Shitcoin</strong></h2>



<p>By dissecting the common fraudulent methodology of shitcoin, we can highlight some of the recurring patterns and universal elements. These patterns and elements can help us investors detect the same cases in the future and avoid them.</p>



<p>To begin with, ICO’s are risky. Sure, they promise of great rewards in a short time but one must consider both sides of the spectrum as one can lose all the invested money. If you are interested to take part in an ICO, make sure to do adequate research looking into what the cryptocurrency promises to do, who the creators are and how are they going to achieve their goal. According to your own judgement, is it possible that they can realistically fulfill their promises? If the creators are anonymous, can you put your faith into masked strangers?</p>



<p>The biggest contribution factor that everyone must consider however, is marketing. If the company is selling you their vision of the future, take it with more than a grain and even more than a pinch but a fistful of salt. The marketing statements are always primarily for profit and increasing the demand. The marketing statements are not concrete and guaranteed promises. Unfortunately, Shitcoins sometimes have a <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/friday-special-tales-from-the-chain-chapter-iii-the-shitcoin-soldier/">cult like following on social media</a>. In some cases, it is proven that the company members and staff were managing and leading the fan pages and pump events disguised as independent investors.</p>



<p>Lastly, do not go all in. There is so much information that the investors are unaware of. There are numerous contributing factors to the value. Investors do not have all the data.</p>



<p>Remember Murphy’s law, anything that can go wrong, will go wrong.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">jolixo</h2>



<p><a href="http://hi.exchange">Hi.exchange</a> is an online decentralized platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and digital currencies. Our automated systems automatically determine the best exchange rates based on the competition. Furthermore, we provide 24l7 customer support. You can visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange">Hi exchange Blog</a> to stay up to date with our latest opinion articles, technical price analysis and news.</p>



<p></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-shitcoin/">What is Shitcoin</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-shitcoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Friday Special, Tales from the Chain; Chapter III: The Shitcoin Soldier</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/friday-special-tales-from-the-chain-chapter-iii-the-shitcoin-soldier/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/friday-special-tales-from-the-chain-chapter-iii-the-shitcoin-soldier/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 10:06:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[CoinCannon Special]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ELON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shitcoin Army]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=3891</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Journey from Pontiac Aztec to Lambo doesn’t have to be Long; Welcome, to the tale of the shitcoin soldier! Some people walk, other run, but only a few, only a select group of elite, they FLY! They avoid all the drama, all the wait and the agony of investing on cryptocurrencies that have already [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/friday-special-tales-from-the-chain-chapter-iii-the-shitcoin-soldier/">Friday Special, Tales from the Chain; Chapter III: The Shitcoin Soldier</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Journey from Pontiac Aztec to Lambo doesn’t have to be Long; Welcome, to the tale of the shitcoin soldier!</p>



<p>Some people walk, other run, but only a few, only a select group of elite, they FLY! They avoid all the drama, all the wait and the agony of investing on cryptocurrencies that have already peaked. Life is all about cutting corners, pain is only a choice. The shitcoin soldier is ahead, simply because he knows the Fried Chicken blockchain network and their native token FRCN holds the brightest future of them all.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Shitcoin Soldier, A Gallant<strong> Journey</strong></h2>



<p>Despite the fact that he knows a very specific secret, his kind heart wouldn’t let the shitcoin soldier to hide the key to success. Hence, the outspoken nature of his twitter account comes to light as his dedicated tweets fill your feed. As soon as you feast your eyes upon the bio of his account, you see the name of the target shitcoin. Then the keywords describing his or her (we don’t discriminate here) life are followed. Contradictory as all hell, phrases describing ideological orientation, specific gender qualities and dietary needs are there to introduce this witty soul. A big fish in a small pond.</p>



<p>Getting past the bio, his tweets and replies all indicate dedication and faith. The shitcoin soldier is an apostle of the shitcoin creed. Soon to be rewarded by a Lambo in the future, they spread the good word of money. The soldado knows that one day, the promised pump shall commence. The bulls will run down all the <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/friday-special-tales-from-the-chain-chapter-ii-the-conspiracy-boomer/">Conspiracy Boomers</a> and previous skeptics. The Shitcoin Army will ride those 600% profit statistics triumphantly.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Drop Becomes the Ocean, Soldiers Become an Army</strong></h2>



<p>They always find each other, they stick to the plan and develop a hierarchical structure. They join the community on public pages and celebrate their ingenious decisions. However, one must tread lightly approaching their sect. The Shitcoin army has eyes and ears everywhere, they read all tweets about their beloved shitcoin. To summon the devotees, all you need to do is name their coin in your tweet using a hashtag. A few moments later, their judgement shall fall upon your statement.</p>



<p>At that point, may god help you if your opinion stands opposed to theirs (talking from personal experience). Their wrathful and furious tagging of their friends beneath your tweet will surely let you know of their collective strength.</p>



<p>However, much like a double-edged sword, they do have a soft side. Compliment their shitcoin and the embrace of this high IQ community will keep you warm in the cold days of bearish market.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Irony</strong></h2>



<p>Known as the black sheep of the crypto community, the fate of their investments tend to be doomed from the beginning. Taking part in ICOs, pump and dump events and falling prey to massive OTC deals, can seriously damage their investments. But, and there is always a but, sometimes they make it.</p>



<p>Not all the time but sometimes, they Shitcoin soldiers find a tech guru that backs their shitcoin, *cough* Elon *cough*, be it for the meme or money laundering.</p>



<p>On these rare events, one fully comprehends the perplexity of the financial markets and the endless possibilities that are missed. After all, <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/a-trading-hamster-outperforms-sp-500-in-trading/">a hamster’s portfolio had more profit than the S&amp;P 500 IN 2021</a>.</p>



<p>Perhaps sanity fails us sometimes, perhaps the financial adventures sometimes reward the unsane. Taking a look at the cryptocurrencies, there are more than a handful of shitcoins that skyrocketed in a very short-time.</p>



<p>And with that existential crisis in mind, and the storming of critical thoughts in our heads, I bid you adieu.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Disclaimer</strong></h2>



<p>The following story is not directly calling out on any specific individual. Even though it might sound like someone you know, it is only a light-hearted (hopefully) comedic story intended for entertainment purposes. Every Investor must do adequate research to determine whether a specific cryptocurrency is a shitcoin or not. We do not intend to make fun of any person for their investment decisions or use derogatory terms to describe them. This is all comedy.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">jolixo</h2>



<p><a href="http://hi.exchange">Hi.exchange</a> is an online decentralized platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and digital currencies. Our automated systems automatically determine the best exchange rates based on the competition. Furthermore, we provide 24l7 customer support. You can visit <a href="http://blog.hi.exchange">Hi exchange Blog</a> to stay up to date with our latest opinion articles, technical price analysis and news.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/friday-special-tales-from-the-chain-chapter-iii-the-shitcoin-soldier/">Friday Special, Tales from the Chain; Chapter III: The Shitcoin Soldier</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/friday-special-tales-from-the-chain-chapter-iii-the-shitcoin-soldier/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
