<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Altcoins Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/altcoins/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 12:43:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Revealing Arthur Hayes&#8217; Top Altcoin Picks for 2024</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/revealing-arthur-hayes-top-altcoin-picks-for-2024/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/revealing-arthur-hayes-top-altcoin-picks-for-2024/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Leyli Mamikhani]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 12:43:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=8188</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As the bearish trend of 2024 unfolds, Arthur Hayes, the former CEO of Bitmax, has shared insights into his chosen altcoins for the year. Departing from his Bitcoin focus, Hayes is now eyeing strategic investments in Solana and Bonk, signaling a shift in his cryptocurrency portfolio. In a recent press release, Hayes expressed concern about [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/revealing-arthur-hayes-top-altcoin-picks-for-2024/">Revealing Arthur Hayes&#8217; Top Altcoin Picks for 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>As the bearish trend of 2024 unfolds, Arthur Hayes, the former CEO of Bitmax, has shared insights into his chosen altcoins for the year. Departing from his Bitcoin focus, Hayes is now eyeing strategic investments in Solana and Bonk, signaling a shift in his cryptocurrency portfolio.</p>



<p>In a recent press release, Hayes expressed concern about Bitcoin&#8217;s struggle to maintain its position above $40,000, predicting potential further declines in the upcoming weeks. In response to this market sentiment, he has diversified his investments into the promising altcoins Solana and Bonk.</p>



<p>Hayes anticipates a 30% correction from Bitcoin&#8217;s recent high of $48,000 in 2024, especially following the approval of Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs). He identifies potential support levels ranging from $30,000 to $35,000. Taking a proactive stance, Hayes has already exited positions in Solana and Bonk at $35,000, even if it meant a modest loss.</p>



<p>Positioning Bitcoin and cryptocurrencies as the last bastion of global open markets, Hayes asserts their ability to predict better fluctuations in the dollar&#8217;s liquidity compared to traditional financial markets. In the event of Bitcoin falling below $35,000, Hayes plans to invest in Solana (SOL), an innovative contract platform, and Dogwifhat (WIF), a meme asset on Ethereum, employing a &#8220;fishing from the bottom&#8221; strategy.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-text-align-center is-style-default has-medium-font-size is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>&#8220;I would choose Solana and WIF over Bitcoin&#8221;  </p>
<cite>Arthur Hayes</cite></blockquote>



<p>Dogwifhat is trading at $0.343, showing a significant 50% increase in the last 24 hours. In contrast, Solana is priced at $86.16, reflecting a 5.5% uptick from the previous day. While Dogwifhat&#8217;s recent price movements have displayed volatility between $0.330 and $0.355, some experts predict a potential return to around $0.45, similar to mid-January levels. Despite Hayes&#8217; optimism, technical indicators offer mixed signals, introducing an element of uncertainty to Dogwifhat&#8217;s future price.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/revealing-arthur-hayes-top-altcoin-picks-for-2024/">Revealing Arthur Hayes&#8217; Top Altcoin Picks for 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/revealing-arthur-hayes-top-altcoin-picks-for-2024/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Whales Are Buying Serum (SRM)</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/serum-srm-eth-whales/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/serum-srm-eth-whales/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Serum (SRM)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5252</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Here’s the thing, we all wish we could go back in time and buy Bitcoin or altcoins and quit our jobs and move to Florida. Since the only time machines are in Area 51, the only alternative is to keep a lookout for new altcoins that are ready to explode. Well, apparently Ethereum whales are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/serum-srm-eth-whales/">Ethereum Whales Are Buying Serum (SRM)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Here’s the thing, we all wish we could go back in time and buy Bitcoin or altcoins and quit our jobs and move to Florida. Since the only time machines are in Area 51, the only alternative is to keep a lookout for new altcoins that are ready to explode. Well, apparently Ethereum whales are way ahead of us with Serum (SRM). <strong>&nbsp;</strong>As whales continue to sell their Shiba Inu, new data suggests that they are quickly accumulating Serum (SRM). The new altcoin is essentially a DeFi crypto project associated with crypto exchange FTX.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Buy and Sell Cryptocurrencies on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a><br>No KYC</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Serum (SRM)?</strong></h2>



<p>Basically, Serum is a crypto project that acts as a protocol for decentralized exchanges. SRM is a utility token for the Solana-based decentralized exchange FTX. Primarily, FTX backs Serum (SRM) and FTX chief executive Sam Bankman-Fried is an advisor for the project. &nbsp;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="What is Project Serum?" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/QlrqKfllP10?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<p>According to the official website, Serum protocol allows for fast transactions with costs up to 60% lower. In fact, Serum (SRM) transactions cost an astonishing $0.00001 per transaction. And as for speed, the network has sufficed to say sub-second trading and settlement. With a peak of 65,000 TPS and 400ms block times, Serum (SRM) has made some big claims.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Ethereum Whales Have a New Favorite</strong></h2>



<p>Interestingly, <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/ethereum-whales-buy-usd-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Ethereum whales</a> are pouncing on Serum according to <a href="https://www.whalestats.com/analysis-of-the-top-100-eth-wallets" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">WhaleStats</a>. Last week, the top 100 Ethereum wallets purchased an average of over $1.9 million worth of Serum (SRM). To put that in comparison, the SRM purchases by the same wallets were at $237,875 last week.</p>



<p>Currently, SRM is trading at $2.45 and is ranked as 133<sup>rd</sup> crypto asset by market cap. Furthermore, SRM is down almost 9% in the past week.</p>



<p>And as for FTX, the top 100 ETH wallets purchased an average of $2.25 million worth of FTX Token (FTT) only in the past week. In the meantime, they sold $1.4 million in the same time. Despite the large number, FTX is still a popular purchase considering the scale of accumulation.</p>



<p>On the other hand, Shiba Inu, Elon’s financial toy and his inspiration for unfunny Twitter jokes is disappointing Ethereum Whales. In total, the top 100 ETH addresses sold off an average of $679,410 worth of SHIB last week and purchased $582,686.</p>



<p>And of course, they wouldn’t be Ethereum whales without holding large amounts of ETH. Last week, the top 100 ETH wallets purchased over $7 million worth of ETH while selling $8.5 million. In that regard, Ethereum has also seen outflows last weeks.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="1024" height="517" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/whalestats4.15-1024x517.webp" alt="" class="wp-image-5254" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/whalestats4.15-1024x517.webp 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/whalestats4.15-300x151.webp 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/whalestats4.15-768x388.webp 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/whalestats4.15.webp 1377w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/serum-srm-eth-whales/">Ethereum Whales Are Buying Serum (SRM)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/serum-srm-eth-whales/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase is Considering Listing 50 New Altcoins</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/coinbase-altcoins-listing/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/coinbase-altcoins-listing/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 09:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5229</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase has announce a list of possible altcoins for listing on the exchange. The crypto exchange titan is considering 50 altcoins to join the exchange list. So, if you’re a buy the rumor, sell the news investor, a Coinbase listing could jump start a rally for the chosen ones. A vast majority of these altcoins [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/coinbase-altcoins-listing/">Coinbase is Considering Listing 50 New Altcoins</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Coinbase has announce a list of possible altcoins for listing on the exchange. The crypto exchange titan is considering 50 altcoins to join the exchange list. So, if you’re a buy the rumor, sell the news investor, a Coinbase listing could jump start a rally for the chosen ones. A vast majority of these altcoins are in fact Ethereum-based while five of them are based on the Solana network.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Buy and Sell Top Altcoins on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> No KYC</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>New Altcoins on Coinbase</strong></h2>



<p>Although the exact information is still unclear, Coinbase says that they will provide information regarding the new listings in advance. This is to increase transparency on the new listings. These few dozen altcoins are set to go on Coinbase in the second quarter of 2022.</p>



<p>“Starting immediately and as part of an effort to increase transparency by providing as much information symmetry as possible, Coinbase will be using this blog post as a pilot to communicate assets under consideration for listing in Q2 2022.”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Who is on The List?</strong></h2>



<p>First and foremost, in the spirit of chivalry, Coinbase is considering adding two stablecoins issued by its competitors. Binance USD (BUSD) and Gemini Dollar (GUSD) are set for consideration by the US based exchange platform. But, there shall be no pump for a stablecoin!</p>



<p>Another noteworthy altcoin under consideration is Coin98 (C98) which is in fact not a code name for a virus. C98 is the native token of the decentralized finance platform Coin98 which has managed to make quite a reputation as a successful finance platform.</p>



<p>As for SOL-based digital assets, the most notable one may be STEPN (GMT) which is essentially a utility token. STEPN is a lifestyle crypto project.&nbsp; GMT has had a staggering 22,000% growth since March and is currently trading at $2.25.</p>



<p>As for others, most of them are less-known with low market capitalization as expected. Coinbase has previously stated that they were “bringing on more, often newly created assets or lesser-known tokens that could come with additional trading risks, including higher price swings and increased order cancellations”.</p>



<p>As of April 13, 2022, Coinbase supports 168 crypto assets on the platform.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/coinbase-altcoins-listing/">Coinbase is Considering Listing 50 New Altcoins</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/coinbase-altcoins-listing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top 5 Altcoins for a low-risk Investment in 2022</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/top-5-altcoins-for-a-low-risk-investment/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/top-5-altcoins-for-a-low-risk-investment/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 06:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Top 5]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=3435</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Currently, Bitcoin is trading around $39,000 which means for your investment to double, the market cap has to increase by hundreds of billions. Obviously, altcoins are not this way. But, it&#8217;s really not easy to choose the right altcoin. In this article, we will go over the the top 5 altcoins to buy in 2022. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/top-5-altcoins-for-a-low-risk-investment/">Top 5 Altcoins for a low-risk Investment in 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Currently, Bitcoin is trading around $39,000 which means for your investment to double, the market cap has to increase by hundreds of billions. Obviously, altcoins are not this way. But, it&#8217;s really not easy to choose the right altcoin. In this article, we will go over the the top 5 altcoins to buy in 2022. Primarily, these top 5 altcoins are chosen for the long haul hence the low-risk nature. </p>



<p>Ask any crypto skeptic about their greatest concerns over the market and they will surely tell you the primary reason for their cynical view is simply the volatility. The meme wars on twitter and the absolute swarm of shitcoins in the market is also not helping. In a decentralized and low-regulated market, Investors need to feel safe about their investments. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><span class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Buy Cryptocurrencies on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a></span></p><p><span class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">No KYC</span></p></blockquote></figure>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Content</strong></h3>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li><strong>What Distinguishes the Top 5 Altcoins?</strong></li><li><strong>Ethereum</strong></li><li><strong>ADA</strong></li><li><strong>Algorand</strong></li><li><strong>Polkadot</strong></li><li><strong>VeChain</strong></li><li><strong>Where to buy the top 5 altcoins</strong></li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Distinguishes the Top 5 Altcoins?</strong></h2>



<p>To begin with, an investor must look for the chief premise behind the cryptocurrency to invest in. There are questions to ask and certain information gaps to fill. In that case, we should look for certain qualities such as the infrastructure, the platform, the function and the possible progress in the future. Fortunately, the top 5 altcoins we are going to introduce are well-known for providing solid platforms with revolutionary technological inventions. Despite moving in different directions, all of them are highly progressive, especially when it comes to adoption of new technology. According to numerous analysts, these 5 altcoins are safe bets for the future:</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong><a href="http://ethereum.org" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Ethereum</a></strong></h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="840" height="400" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/image.jpg" alt="Ethereum - top 5 altcoins
" class="wp-image-3436" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/image.jpg 840w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/image-300x143.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/image-768x366.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 840px) 100vw, 840px" /></figure>



<p>Long and short of it, Ethereum is a decentralized blockchain platform. It is essentially a decentralized public ledger for verifying and recording transactions. However, it is considered as one of the largest and most diverse networks out there. </p>



<p>The open-source platform provides a plethora of services to millions of people without geographical restrictions. On the platform, users can create or share services such as business, financial or even entertainment. Therefore, we have an ecosystem where users can pay fees in form of crypto to use the services.</p>



<p>The native cryptocurrency of the platform is Ether (ETH). In terms of market value, it is second, standing only behind Bitcoin. ETH was a revolutionary currency since it managed to compensate for many of Bitcoin`s shortcomings. Problems such as, high gas fees, scalability and even the high transaction fees. However, day by day we see the Ethereum platform utilize revolutionary methods to make the ecosystem even more efficient. &nbsp;</p>



<p>Considering the progressive outlook and the impressive background, investing on ETH can be considered as a safe bet for the future.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong><a href="http://cardano.org" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ADA</a></strong></h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="840" height="400" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/cardano-2.jpg" alt="ADA - Cardano - top 5 altcoins" class="wp-image-3437" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/cardano-2.jpg 840w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/cardano-2-300x143.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/cardano-2-768x366.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 840px) 100vw, 840px" /></figure>



<p>And here we have a crowd favorite! The third generation of the blockchain platform that has a cult following. It was Founded by Charles Hoskinson, one of the main creators of Ethereum. The Cardano project not only was more efficient than the previous ones, it revolutionized the blockchain technology. The Cardano project is one of the leading pioneers of the proof of stake algorithm. As compared with the proof of work, it is vastly more efficient and eco-friendly. You can read a more extensive introduction in <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-ada-a-guide-to-the-cardano-project/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is ADA</a>.</p>



<p>ADA, the native token of the Cardano platform is currently the number 5 cryptocurrency by market cap. In terms of investments, as of August 3, 2021, there is more than $31 billion in the stake pools. A staggering number that is almost double of what ETH investors have staked.</p>



<p>The distinguishing element for ADA is that Cardano has a huge emphasis on scientific literature. Their progressive methods must be approved by academics all around the world. In a sense, they care equally for both quality and quantity of progress.</p>



<p>The rate at which Cardano is expanding is a testament to their forward thinking methods. With smart contracts, stablecoin  &#8220;Djed&#8221; and many more additions coming to the platform, ADA is looking like a snack!</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Algorand</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="840" height="400" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Exchange-Algorand-ALGO-to-PayPal-lowest-Fees-1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-5095" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Exchange-Algorand-ALGO-to-PayPal-lowest-Fees-1.jpg 840w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Exchange-Algorand-ALGO-to-PayPal-lowest-Fees-1-300x143.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Exchange-Algorand-ALGO-to-PayPal-lowest-Fees-1-768x366.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 840px) 100vw, 840px" /></figure>



<p>Officially launched in 2019, Algorand is a proof of stake blockchain network with great emphasis on scalability and speed. As on open-source and decentralized network, Algorand is not a new idea to begin with. However, where it proves to be different is the unique design that allows for faster consensus. With a two-tiered structure, this payment-focused network achieves amazing scalability.</p>



<p>Currently, Algorand network can process over 1000 transactions per second while transaction finality takes less than five seconds. At this point you might say that there are faster networks out there. Well, yes but actually no!</p>



<p>We’ve previously talked about the blockchain trilemma on this blog. Essentially, it is difficult and rare for a blockchain to offer security, speed and decentralization. For example, Solana network is one of the fastest ones out there but it is not that decentralized. In that regard, Algorand is maintaining all positive aspects of an ideal blockchain at once.</p>



<p>ALGO is currently 29th in the ranks with a market cap of $4.6 billion. You can buy ALGO on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong><a href="http://polkadot.network" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Polkadot</a></strong></h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="840" height="400" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Polkadot_OG.jpg" alt="Polkadot - top 5 altcoins" class="wp-image-3439" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Polkadot_OG.jpg 840w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Polkadot_OG-300x143.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/Polkadot_OG-768x366.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 840px) 100vw, 840px" /></figure>



<p>And here we have yet another third generation blockchain network found by a previous Ethereum member. Initially, Gavin James Wood had a different vision in mind about the (PoS) algorithm. The final goal is to create an infrastructure to create a network of blockchains that are effortlessly communicating with each other.</p>



<p>The multiple blockchain approach provides a better cross-chain interoperability and easier communication. Gavin believes that a single blockchain network can never be complete and a multi-chain architecture will be much more efficient.</p>



<p>The DOT is the token for this multi-chain network. It is currently number 9 by market cap. With the first ICO in 2017, it managed to raise $145 million. Despite being relatively new, it has experienced a huge growth in popularity. DOT has had one of the most successful initial coin offerings in history, raising over 200 million in two ICOs, first one in 2017 and the other in 2020.</p>



<p>All in all, DOT is a solid choice for investment for three reasons: first, the infrastructure is solid and forward looking. Second, the tremendous success can be a testament of the potential for growth. Third, the network is in no way limited to one blockchain making the future technology implementations effortless.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">VeChain</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="840" height="400" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Exchange-VeChain-VET-to-PayPal-Best-Rates.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-5094" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Exchange-VeChain-VET-to-PayPal-Best-Rates.jpg 840w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Exchange-VeChain-VET-to-PayPal-Best-Rates-300x143.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Exchange-VeChain-VET-to-PayPal-Best-Rates-768x366.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 840px) 100vw, 840px" /></figure>



<p>At this point, we all know how blockchain technology can go far beyond a platform for cryptocurrencies. VeChain is a perfect example of a pragmatic blockchain network designed to increase efficiency in business.</p>



<p>The network utilizes distributed ledger technology (DLT) to streamline and manage supply chain complexities. Basically, the VeChain platform enhances supply chain management and business related processes and eases the flow of information. As a sophisticated data management network, it provides a mapped out view of an organization by managing all data.</p>



<p>In a conventional supply chain ecosystem, the data for business processes can be distributed in multiple silos. This can negatively affect business flow in the ecosystem which could ultimately decrease efficiency. VeChain network solves this issue by disintermediating information from all data silos.</p>



<p>VET is currently 42 in the ranks with a market cap of almost $3 billion. It is also one of the low risk altcoins with a good track record. You can also Buy VET on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>You can Buy The Top 5 Altcoins on CoinCannon</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>



<p> &nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/top-5-altcoins-for-a-low-risk-investment/">Top 5 Altcoins for a low-risk Investment in 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/top-5-altcoins-for-a-low-risk-investment/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
