<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>ETH Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/eth/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 09:48:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Lark Davis: Ethereum&#8217;s 2024 Wealth Potential &#8211; Watch the Video!</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/lark-davis-ethereums-2024-wealth-potential-watch-the-video/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/lark-davis-ethereums-2024-wealth-potential-watch-the-video/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Leyli Mamikhani]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 08:58:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Videos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum 2024]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=8170</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lark Davis &#8211; the well-known audacious researcher and forecaster of renowned digital currency analysts &#8211; ecstatic digital currency enthusiasts and investors regarding his prediction of Ethereum in 2024. In his most recent YouTube video, Davis dug into the untapped potential of Ethereum and insisted that crypto bases are the way to get rich with Ethereum. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/lark-davis-ethereums-2024-wealth-potential-watch-the-video/">Lark Davis: Ethereum&#8217;s 2024 Wealth Potential &#8211; Watch the Video!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Lark Davis &#8211; the well-known audacious researcher and forecaster of renowned digital currency analysts &#8211; ecstatic digital currency enthusiasts and investors regarding his prediction of Ethereum in 2024.</p>



<p>In his most recent YouTube video, Davis dug into the untapped potential of Ethereum and insisted that crypto bases are the way to get rich with Ethereum. However, this is by no means an easy or straightforward path.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="Ethereum Will Make Millionaires In 2024, BUT Not How You Think" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/dYiBe72ww6k?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Ethereum price path in 2024</h2>



<p>According to Davis, Ethereum can reach $10,000 to $15,000. He emphasizes that simply buying and holding Ethereum is not a golden ticket to wealth. At Ethereum&#8217;s current price of $2,295, investors are likely to see a 600% return, which is very remarkable. But Davis points to more lucrative opportunities.</p>



<p>There are fundamental financial changes in Ethereum layer two solutions. Networks built on top of Ethereum to increase its scalability and efficiency. He emphasizes that these layer two platforms, such as StarkNet, ZK Sync, and others, are much more than Ethereum. They cause the explosive growth of the price of this currency.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Prospects for 2024 Ethereum price growth</h2>



<p>According to Davis, these Layer 2 networks should be monitored for new token listings. He mentions Celestia as an example, which witnessed a 500% gain just one month after going public. Keeping an eye on these new listings can be significant for people hoping to make substantial earnings rapidly.</p>



<p>Davis also highlights the possibility of airdrops in the Layer 2 space. He shares details on how to take part in these airdrops by chain activities and staking, such as the Manta Network and zkSync programs. Compared to conventional ETH investments, these airdrops have the potential to be more profitable, more immediate, and generate greater returns.</p>



<p>The value of the largest altcoin was $2,295 at the time of publication. A few analysts expect it to increase to $2,500 in the final five days of the year. The weekly and daily charts for Ethereum are currently showing green, and the Fear and Greed indicator is shifting in favor of Greed, indicating strong bullishness. Furthermore, Ether is anticipated to be among the leaders of the anticipated uptrend in 2024.</p>



<p>Source:  <a href="https://coinpedia.org/news/ethereum-will-make-millionaires-in-2024-predicts-crypto-expert-lark-davis/">coinpedia</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/lark-davis-ethereums-2024-wealth-potential-watch-the-video/">Lark Davis: Ethereum&#8217;s 2024 Wealth Potential &#8211; Watch the Video!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/lark-davis-ethereums-2024-wealth-potential-watch-the-video/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT Instantly</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether-usdt/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether-usdt/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 07:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6386</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>CoinCannon is the ultimate platform to exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT instantly! Exchanging crypto assets into one another is a seemingly simple task. However, finding a platform that offers the best exchange rates and anonymity at the same time is no easy feat. With all the strict user verification out there, user privacy is slowly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether-usdt/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT Instantly&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>CoinCannon is the ultimate platform to exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT instantly! Exchanging crypto assets into one another is a seemingly simple task. However, finding a platform that offers the best exchange rates and anonymity at the same time is no easy feat. With all the strict user verification out there, user privacy is slowly losing its value. Fortunately, our platform provides a hassle-free KYC process that speeds up your exchange process and massively improves security. On top of that, we offer 24/7 online support to ensure the utmost reliability for our customers. In this article, we will go over everything you need to know on how to exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT on CoinCannon.</p>



<p>So get started, head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Ethereum ETH on the left box, and Tether USDT on the right one and you’re good to go!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-paypal-2/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Ethereum to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-do-i-need-to-exchange-ethereum-to-tether-usdt"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive USDT. In case your Ether wallet supports ETH, you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-dai/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Ethereum (ETH)?</strong></h2>



<p>As an open-source decentralized blockchain platform, Ethereum is perhaps the most diverse and innovative one out there. In its essence, it is a decentralized public ledger for verifying and recording transactions. The Ethereum is considered as a second-gen blockchain platform, improving upon the high gas fees, scalability issues and high transactions fees of previous platforms. This open-source platform has no geographical restrictions and has always been the tip of the spear as far as innovation goes. Essential services such as Smart contracts, NFT`s and decentralized apps were first introduced on the Ethereum platform. As for the cherry on top, the native token of the Ethereum platform called Ether or ETH is second in terms of market value standing only behind Bitcoin.</p>



<p>With the Ethereum 2.0 launch in August 2022, the network totally switched to proof of stake. With that, Ethereum network will have much better scalability and very low gas fees. On top of that, all the criticism regarding energy consumption will go away. Many consider the 2.0 upgrade as a great investment opportunity since ETH is very much likely to have a rally. Nonetheless, Ethereum is the second most popular cryptocurrency in the world for good reason. Their team has always been on the forefront of innovation which could potentially attract capital and provide great returns.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT, let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Ethereum on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your Ethereum to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether-usdt/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT Instantly&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether-usdt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 07:12:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6362</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In case you’re looking to exchange Ethereum to Tether, CoinCannon is the ultimate platform! In general, holding volatile assets for long is a risky move. With that, stablecoins are a great solution to hold digital assets without the risk of volatility. Speaking of risks, Tether has been the oldest and the most popular stablecoin simply [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In case you’re looking to exchange Ethereum to Tether, <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is the ultimate platform! In general, holding volatile assets for long is a risky move. With that, stablecoins are a great solution to hold digital assets without the risk of volatility. Speaking of risks, Tether has been the oldest and the most popular stablecoin simply because of its unparalleled reliability. Despite all that, investors need an exchange platform that doesn’t compromise on their privacy. Although you can exchange ETH to USDT in numerous platforms, CoinCannon offers top-tier anonymity all while charging no hidden fees. In this article, we will go over everything you need to know on how to exchange Ethereum to Tether (USDT).</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn How to <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-do-i-need-to-exchange-ethereum-to-tether"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Ethereum to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive USDT. In case your Ether wallet supports Tether, you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Ethereum?</strong></h2>



<p>Ethereum is a decentralized blockchain platform that is open-source and known for its diversity and innovation. Its main purpose is to serve as a decentralized public ledger for verifying and recording transactions. Compared to previous platforms, Ethereum has improved upon scalability issues, high gas fees, and high transaction fees, making it a second-generation blockchain platform. It has no geographical restrictions and has been a leader in innovation, introducing essential services like smart contracts, NFTs, and decentralized apps. Additionally, its native token, Ether or ETH, is the second-highest in market value after Bitcoin.</p>



<p>In August 2022, Ethereum launched version 2.0, which switched the network to proof of stake. This upgrade has significantly improved scalability and lowered gas fees, while also addressing criticism about energy consumption. This upgrade is seen as a great investment opportunity, as ETH is likely to rally. Ethereum is the second most popular cryptocurrency globally due to its innovative team, potential for attracting capital, and providing great returns.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Ethereum to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to exchange Ethereum to Tether (USDT), let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon for the Win!</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Ethereum on the left field and Tether (USDT) on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your Ethereum to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>You’re All Set!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the USDT to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Winter, Stablecoin Collapse and the Regulatory War on Crypto</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-winter/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-winter/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 08:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6358</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A dreadful age, the crypto winter, a time of reduced volatility and insane liquidations. Yes, another plunge strikes and the numbers are disturbing at best. With all that, the US regulators are now playing the big bear part by going on full crackdown mode on cryptocurrencies. Primarily, the argument is that pretty much all crypto [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-winter/">&lt;strong&gt;Crypto Winter, Stablecoin Collapse and the Regulatory War on Crypto&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A dreadful age, the crypto winter, a time of reduced volatility and insane liquidations. Yes, another plunge strikes and the numbers are disturbing at best. With all that, the US regulators are now playing the big bear part by going on full crackdown mode on cryptocurrencies. Primarily, the argument is that pretty much all crypto assets are securities. By doing so, the regulatory attitude toward these assets would be much more restrictive. Now, despite Elon’s tweets, law enforcement agencies and financial regulators are squeezing the market. As predicted, crypto regulations are in full swing and the market’s reaction has been short of confident.</p>



<p>In the meantime, the Silicon Valley Bank had full breakdown and failed. Consequently, the crisis escalated to a whole another level. The Circle issued USD Coin depegged from the US dollar and fell down to $0.89 from $1. Worse yet, Ethereum gas fees have now gone through the roof. At the moment, <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/usd-coin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">USDC</a> is down 11% and is trading at $0.88. which is terrifying for the market. Simultaneously <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/multi-collateral-dai/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">DAI</a>, and algorithmic stablecoin is also down 10% and is trading at $0.9. For the time being, Tether is holding on pretty well. Ironically, Coinbase had previously warned about Tether and had called USDC a much more reliable option. <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6FwmGLzyRDk&amp;embeds_euri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.google.com%2F&amp;feature=emb_logo" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How the turntables</a>!</p>



<p>As the latest wave of crypto winter, almost half a billion dollars of crypto was liquidated in 24 hours. This came after a powerful law enforcement agency targeted Ethereum with a lawsuit. And when it comes to lawsuits, they can be devastating for crypto assets as we saw with the <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ripple-lawsuit-continues-as-sec-tries-to-cheat/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Ripple lawsuit</a>. Nonetheless, the Silvergate Bank may have pushed BTC down below $23k, but this time an Ethereum vibe-check has created another bearish wave.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-crypto-winter-continues"><strong>Crypto Winter Continues</strong></h2>



<p>Yesterday, over $429,000,000 worth of Bitcoin and crypto assets were liquidated in less than a day. Following a series of bad news, the market had a negative reaction which followed by a plummet across the board.</p>



<p>New data from <a href="https://www.coinglass.com/LiquidationData" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Coinglass</a> shows 137,969 traders lost their bet on crypto assets on March 10<sup>th</sup>. Specifically, Bitcoin and Ethereum took the crown in lost investments with $141 million and $110 million in liquidations respectively.</p>



<p>Both BTC and Ether are down 6% at the time of writing this article. BTC is currently trading at $20,366 and Ethereum is at $1,406. In terms of price action, both assets have not had a significant recovery but remain stable.</p>



<p>Subsequently, other crypto assets including Solana, Litecoin, DOGE and Polygon (MATIC) followed the same path in the yellow wood.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Sliding into an Ice Age?</strong></h2>



<p>Primarily, three things caused this derailment. One, the Biden administration stated that they would impose a 30% tax on crypto miners. Two, the New York’s Attorney General filed a lawsuit on Ethereum calling it a security. And three, the Silicon Valley Bank’s failure.</p>



<p>Now, the depegging of USDC and Dai can also jump start a bandwagon effect but we should wait and see how fast they recover. However, USDC’s reputation will likely take a big hit even if they manage to perform a miraculous recovery. After all, shouldn’t stablecoins be stable?</p>



<p>As for Ethereum, the lawsuit is a serious deal and the increased gas fees mean that investors cannot cash out their shitcoins soon enough. So, Ethereum will likely slide into a long-term bear trap even if they fix this mess.</p>



<p>Now, unless Elon can be very funny on Twitter and post a whole lot of dog pictures, this crypto winter is probably just beginning. With the onslaught of regulations and the recurring collapse of fraudulent centralized entities run by Adderall-popping tech demons, investors should proceed with extreme caution.</p>



<p>But honestly, why is my Twitter timeline overwhelmed by Elon’s memes?</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-winter/">&lt;strong&gt;Crypto Winter, Stablecoin Collapse and the Regulatory War on Crypto&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-winter/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Ethereum with Payeer USD [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-ethereum-with-payeer-usd/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-ethereum-with-payeer-usd/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 08:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[buy Ethereym]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5739</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking to buy ETH? You can buy Ethereum with Payeer USD on CoinCannon and take advantage of superior privacy and anonymity. Over the past few years, Payeer has been dominating the competition as a popular payment system. It offers next to nothing transaction fees, instant payments and supports a diverse group of e-currencies and cryptocurrencies. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-ethereum-with-payeer-usd/">How to Buy Ethereum with Payeer USD [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking to buy ETH? You can buy Ethereum with Payeer USD on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> and take advantage of superior privacy and anonymity. Over the past few years, Payeer has been dominating the competition as a popular payment system. It offers next to nothing transaction fees, instant payments and supports a diverse group of e-currencies and cryptocurrencies. Unfortunately, due to strict regulations, your transactions on Payeer are not fully private. And this is where CoinCannon shines as an excellent option to add that extra layer of security. And for that, you will not pay any extra since the platform does not charge any additional fees. In this article, we will go over everything you need to buy Ethereum with Payeer USD.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/buy-cryptocurrencies-with-payeer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Buy Cryptocurrencies with Payeer</a> on CoinCannon</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-do-i-need-to-buy-ethereum-with-payeer"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Ethereum with Payeer?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange direction, you will need to have a verified Payeer account and a reliable crypto wallet. These accounts are necessary to send and receive the funds. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-payeer"><strong>What is Payeer?</strong></h2>



<p>First and foremost, Payeer is considered an online digital wallet for better asset management. Be it crypto of fiat, the payment processor is quick, reliable and cheap. In that regard, in a short lifespan of almost 8 years, Payeer is now recognized as one of the very best amongst competitors. Payeer utilizes built-in payment services with giant financial services such as Mastercard, VISA and PayPal.</p>



<p>As of 2021, the Payeer has approximately 7 million users which can transfer funds to each other with extremely low fees. The strength however, lies in diversity. Payeer is far ahead of any similar platform in terms of scale of operation and diversity in supported payment methods. With more than 50 payment approaches, the Payeer wallet offers users various services in one place.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>To learn more about Payeer, continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-payeer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Payeer?</a>”.</p>
</blockquote>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-buy-ethereum"><strong>Why Buy Ethereum?</strong></h2>



<p>As an open-source decentralized blockchain platform, Ethereum is perhaps the most diverse and innovative one out there. In its essence, it is a decentralized public ledger for verifying and recording transactions. The Ethereum is considered as a second-gen blockchain platform, improving upon the high gas fees, scalability issues and high transactions fees of previous platforms. This open-source platform has no geographical restrictions and has always been the tip of the spear as far as innovation goes. Essential services such as Smart contracts, NFT`s and decentralized apps were first introduced on the Ethereum platform. As for the cherry on top, the native token of the Ethereum platform called Ether or ETH is second in terms of market value standing only behind Bitcoin.</p>



<p>With the <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/ethereum-2-0-upgrade-date/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Ethereum 2.0</a> coming in August, the network will fully switch to proof of stake. With that, Ethereum network will have much better scalability and very low gas fees. On top of that, all the criticism regarding energy consumption will go away. Many consider the 2.0 upgrade as a great investment opportunity since ETH is very much likely to have a rally. Nonetheless, Ethereum is the second most popular cryptocurrency in the world for good reason. Their team has always been on the forefront of innovation which could potentially attract capital and provide great returns.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-jolixo-ftw"><strong>CoinCannon FTW</strong></h2>



<p>&nbsp;CoinCannon is an online exchange that offers everything you need from a platform.</p>



<p>Truthfully, it is a rare combination for an online exchange to offer anonymity, lowest exchange rates and unparalleled reliability altogether.</p>



<p>We respect our customer’s privacy by not asking for their personal information. The best way for anyone to protect their information is to not disclose them at all. In that regard, not having KYC or sign up is the best method.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the platform utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at all times. Our words sound too good? Just pay a visit to ranking websites such as BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>Lastly, according to Murphy’s law “anything that can go wrong will go wrong”. To stay ahead of any problems, we offer 24/7 customer support.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-buy-ethereum-with-payeer-usd"><strong>How to Buy Ethereum with Payeer USD?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Select Payeer USD on the “I Give” field on the left and Ethereum (ETH) on the “I Get” field on the right.</li>



<li>Enter the desired amount for the exchange and wait for the site to calculate the amazing exchange rates!</li>



<li>Click “Exchange”</li>
</ol>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-step-2"><strong>Step 2</strong></h3>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter your Ether Wallet address and E-mail address</li>



<li>Click “Exchange”</li>
</ol>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-step-3"><strong>Step 3</strong></h3>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Read the Information</li>



<li>Complete the CAPTCHA</li>



<li>Click “Exchange”</li>
</ol>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-step-4"><strong>Step 4</strong></h3>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>At this point, please check the transaction information and terms and conditions carefully.</li>



<li>You will be able to see the track id and CoinCannon Payeer account</li>



<li>Open your Payeer account, click on the account menu and copy the account number that begins by the letter “p” and paste it in the required field.</li>



<li>Go back to your Payeer account and send the exchange amount to CoinCannon Payeer account.</li>



<li>Once you have sent the exchange amount, go to the history menu on your Payeer account and copy the operation id for the payment. Then paste the operation id in the required field.</li>



<li>Kindly agree to the terms and conditions and click on “Pay Order.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-all-good"><strong>All Good!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the ETH to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-ethereum-with-payeer-usd/">How to Buy Ethereum with Payeer USD [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-ethereum-with-payeer-usd/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Ethereum to Payeer [No Fees]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-payeer/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-payeer/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 05:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6083</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you’re looking to exchange Ethereum to Payeer USD, CoinCannon is all you need. Payeer has been growing more popular as a top performing payment system. With that, the use case for Payeer USD is now broader that ever. Luckily, you don’t have to exchange ETH to other currencies before investing it into Payeer USD. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-payeer/">How to Exchange Ethereum to Payeer [No Fees]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you’re looking to exchange Ethereum to Payeer USD, <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is all you need. Payeer has been growing more popular as a top performing payment system. With that, the use case for Payeer USD is now broader that ever. Luckily, you don’t have to exchange ETH to other currencies before investing it into Payeer USD. And of course, this does not come as a luxury since CoinCannon does not charge any additional fees. On top of that, you will get full anonymity thanks to our hassle-free KYC.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Ethereum to Payeer?</strong></h2>



<p>For this transaction, you will need a verified and active Payeer account. Make sure that the deposit limit does not exceed your transaction amount. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon. Want a good reason why? How about winning $100 ever month!</p>



<p>Learn more about our <a href="https://hi.exchange/campaign/tether-giveaway" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Tether Giveaway</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Ethereum?</strong></h2>



<p>There are more than a few reasons why ETH is a great investment. To begin with, how about a 1000% growth in 2021? The Ethereum network has been on the forefront of blockchain innovation longer than any other network. As of 2021, almost all revolutionary innovations were introduced on the Ethereum network. Smart contracts, DApps, NFTs are only the tip of the iceberg.</p>



<p>Taking a look at the state of Bitcoin, due to the massive market cap, it will take a lot more money for BTC to grow 100%. With Ethereum however, it will take notably lower investment for the same increase in value. This is one reason why JP Morgan called ETH a better investment for 2022.</p>



<p>In terms of utility, ETH is developing fast. With the rise of metaverse and web 3.0 we will most definitely see increased demand for ETH.</p>



<p>All in all, ETH is as good as investment as Bitcoin if not better.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Use Payeer?</strong></h2>



<p>First and foremost, Payeer is considered an online digital wallet for better asset management. Be it crypto of fiat, the payment processor is quick, reliable and cheap. In that regard, in a short lifespan of almost 8 years, Payeer is now recognized as one of the very best amongst competitors. Payeer utilizes built-in payment services with giant financial services such as Mastercard, VISA and PayPal.</p>



<p>As of 2021, the Payeer has approximately 7 million users which can transfer funds to each other with extremely low fees. The strength however, lies in diversity. Payeer is far ahead of any similar platform in terms of scale of operation and diversity in supported payment methods. With more than 50 payment approaches, the Payeer wallet offers users various services in one place.</p>



<p>To learn more about Payeer, continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-payeer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Payeer?</a>”</p>



<p><strong>CoinCannon FTW!</strong></p>



<p>CoinCannon is an online exchange that offers everything you need from a platform.</p>



<p>Truthfully, it is a rare combination for an online exchange to offer anonymity, lowest exchange rates and unparalleled reliability altogether.</p>



<p>We respect our customer’s privacy by not asking for their personal information. The best way for anyone to protect their information is to not disclose them at all. In that regard, not having KYC or sign up is the best method.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the platform utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at all times. Our words sound too good? Just pay a visit to ranking websites such as BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>Lastly, according to Murphy’s law “anything that can go wrong will go wrong”. To stay ahead of any problems, we offer 24/7 customer support.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Ethereum to Payeer?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Enter the homepage first, then select Ethereum (ETH) and Payeer USD from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of Payeer USD you will receive will automatically calculate.</li><li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Payeer wallet details and email. The phone number is optional.</li><li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li><li>Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” once you have sent (ETH) to CoinCannon’s wallet address. Having transferred your Ethereum to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li><li>By finishing all the steps above, our team will send the Payeer to your wallet as soon as possible</li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>Just like that, you have now exchanged Ethereum (ETH) to Payeer USD. In general, Payeer payments are inconsistent in terms of how long they might take. Give it a few minutes and the Payeer USD will be in your account ASAP. In the meantime, you can follow up on your order using the Track ID provided for you. Simply enter the track id in the required section on homepage to see at which point your order is. Remember not to share your Track ID with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-payeer/">How to Exchange Ethereum to Payeer [No Fees]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-payeer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money [2024 Update]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-perfect-money/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-perfect-money/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 10:03:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perfect Money]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5825</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As of October 2022, Ethereum is one of the hottest cryptocurrencies. If you are looking for a platform to exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money and not compromise on anything, you are in luck. CoinCannon platform is the best place to exchange cryptocurrencies with multiple advantages which we will go over later in this article. In [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-perfect-money/">How to Exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>As of October 2022, Ethereum is one of the hottest cryptocurrencies. If you are looking for a platform to exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money and not compromise on anything, you are in luck. </p>



<p><a href="http://www.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> platform is the best place to exchange cryptocurrencies with multiple advantages which we will go over later in this article. In the meantime, Perfect Money users may not find it easy to find platforms who support them. </p>



<p>Thankfully, CoinCannon is an official Perfect Money partner that is also verified. In this article, we will go over everything you need to know to exchange Ethereum to PM.</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-1 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button is-style-outline is-style-outline--1"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-black-color has-text-color has-background has-link-color wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/" style="background-color:#f49d3f">Exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-do-i-need-to-exchange-ethereum-to-perfect-money"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>For this transaction, you will need a crypto wallet to send ETH. In order to receive Perfect Money USD, you need to have a verified and active PM account. </p>



<p>As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-should-i-exchange-ethereum-to-pm"><strong>Should I Exchange Ethereum to PM?</strong></h2>



<p>Perfect Money is simply a digital currency that can be used as a payment system for non-cash payments. A vast majority of the transaction are payments on the internet for online services. In terms of what you can do with Perfect Money, the sky is the limit.</p>



<p>You can use PM to:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Transference of money between users</li>



<li>Accepting payments on your website</li>



<li>Payment for goods and services on the Internet</li>



<li>Purchases of Bitcoins, gold, US dollars, and Euros</li>



<li>Loan and receipt issuance throughout the system</li>



<li>Earn additional revenue by participating in a partnership plan</li>
</ul>



<p>The biggest downside of Perfect Money, however, is that you cannot cash Perfect money to your bank account on its website directly. For that, you will need a platform like CoinCannon to exchange your Perfect Money to PayPal and other e-currencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-exchange-ethereum-to-perfect-money"><strong>How to Exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money</strong>?</h2>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 1: </strong>Enter the homepage first, then select Ethereum and Perfect Money from the currency pairs in the first step. enter the amount you want to exchange, after that the amount of PM USD you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-1-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money step by step - step 1" class="wp-image-8596" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-1-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-1-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-1-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-1-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-1.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 2: </strong>Press Next and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Perfect Money wallet details, email, and phone number (Optional).</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-2-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money step by step - step 2" class="wp-image-8595" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-2-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-2-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-2-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-2-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-2.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 3: </strong>One more time, click on the “Next” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-3-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money step by step - step 3" class="wp-image-8594" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-3-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-3-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-3-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-3-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-3.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 4: </strong>Pass the captcha test and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the PM gateway and pay online. After you have transferred your ETH to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-4-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money step by step - step 4" class="wp-image-8593" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-4-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-4-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-4-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-4-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-4.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 5: </strong>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the PM USD to your wallet ASAP.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-5-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money step by step - step 5" class="wp-image-8592" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-5-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-5-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-5-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-5-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ethereum-PerfectMoney-5.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Perfect Money USD to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. </p>



<p>In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-jolixo-platform"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>To exchange any cryptocurrency, you will need to find a good platform first. However, despite the diversity, it is quite a difficult task to find a good online exchange. The problem begins by compromising on your standards. You will want good exchange rates, privacy and reliability altogether. And that is hard to find!</p>



<p>Harsh regulations are pushing exchanges to disclose customer data to governments. This goes against the initial purpose of crypto which is absolute anonymity. Even worse, user data is a commodity, large institutions buy your information at a certain price. The best way to make sure your data is safe, is to not share them at all.</p>



<p>However, it is a luxury to offer no KYC, hence many exchanges charge customers with ridiculous exchange rates to compensate for the anonymity.</p>



<p><a href="https://hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> on the other hand gives you everything all at once. Want privacy? We have no KYC. Want the best exchange rates? Well, simply visit Bestchange or OkChanger and see for yourself how we are always on top of their lists.</p>



<p>And to make sure everything goes right, we offer 24/7 customer support</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-perfect-money/">How to Exchange Ethereum to Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-perfect-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bill Murray Lost $200k to Crypto Hackers</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-hackers-bill-murray/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-hackers-bill-murray/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bill murray]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6011</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>And it would be a waste of opportunity to not ask bill “Who You Gonna Call?” when crypto hackers attack. Rest assured, that won’t be the only Bill Murray based joke you read in this article. However, losing the jpeg image of a cartoon punk can be a devastating loss when it’s an expensive NFT. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-hackers-bill-murray/">Bill Murray Lost $200k to Crypto Hackers</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>And it would be a waste of opportunity to not ask bill “Who You Gonna Call?” when crypto hackers attack. Rest assured, that won’t be the only Bill Murray based joke you read in this article. However, losing the jpeg image of a cartoon punk can be a devastating loss when it’s an expensive NFT. Thankfully, Mr. Murray managed to save his NFTs following the cyber-attack on his personal collection. Despite that, crypto hackers managed to steal hundreds of thousands of dollars. Sadly, Bill Murray had raised the money during his NFT charity auction. And of course, there was an official police report on the matter but it was “Lost in Translation” (told you the jokes won’t stop).</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Crypto Hackers</strong></h2>



<p>A group of criminals targeted Bill Murray’s NFT charity auction and managed to steal 119.2 ETH. At the moment, this is worth around $185,000 that was raised for the charity. This attack took place during the auction and the charity lost the funds almost immediately. Furthermore, the crypto hackers made an attempt to steal non-fungible tokens from Murray’s personal wallet. According to <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2022/09/02/hacker-steals-bill-murrays-crypto-after-185k-nft-charity-auction/">Coindesk</a>, the voice of Garfield holds two CryptoPunk NFTs. Just for reference, some CryptoPunks NFTs are worth more than a 4-bedroom house with over 2 acers lot in Austin!</p>



<p>Thankfully, Bill Murray knew who he was gonna call and his virtual wallet security team Venkman came in to help. The NFT consultancy firm successfully diffused the attacks on Murray’s personal wallet. As for the money for charity, the team was not able to recover the Ethereum.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="500" height="500" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/crypto-hackers.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-6015" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/crypto-hackers.jpg 500w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/crypto-hackers-300x300.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/crypto-hackers-150x150.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 500px) 100vw, 500px" /><figcaption>Because Murray Played Garfield and This is an NFT!</figcaption></figure>



<p>In the meantime, Murray’s team stated that they have filed a police report and are following up with the issue. According to the team, they have partnered with crypto analytics company Chainalysis to identify the thief.</p>



<p>However, much like a lot of Murray’s movies, there is a happy ending to the story. Despite the loss, one Coinbase user donated $187,000 worth of ETH to the charity. Bill Murray was working with Chive Charities which is a non-profit that was raising funds.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>NFT Heist</strong></h2>



<p>Fundamentally speaking, a vast majority of crypto scams stem from user error. That is not to say that digital wallets are absolutely secure. However, a massive number of offers, suggestions and messages can often confuse the user to make the wrong move. Word to the wise, everyone can be the target for a crypto scam and it is not just celebrities who lose their charity money. For that, we advise you to always dedicate the time to thoroughly review and asses the legitimacy of the emails, messages and the links you receive.</p>



<p>That being said, crypto hackers are most attracted to high profile individual who are certain to hold valuable items. Back in May, Seth Green lost four Bore Ape NFTs to a phishing scam. In general, a phishing scam occurs when thieves steal user data by tricking them with tainted links. And as we have mentioned before, the best way to protect your personal information is to not share it with anyone at all. If you are using OTC exchange platforms, make sure they do not require KYC. For that, <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is one of the best exchangers you can find.</p>



<p>According to Solidus Labs CEO, Chen Arad, the high profile celebrities are not the only ones under attack. “Scammers do not discriminate and target anyone they think they can get money from, from celebrities to royalty to average people,” said Arad.</p>



<p>At the end of the day, many of us do not have the ability to have our own cyber security team. However, paying more attention to basic details and being cautious can go a long way to protect our funds. With that said, take a look at the Groundhog NFT jpeg as it is the last Bill Murray joke in this article.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="400" height="400" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/G57p0EAx_400x400.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-6016" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/G57p0EAx_400x400.jpg 400w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/G57p0EAx_400x400-300x300.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/G57p0EAx_400x400-150x150.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 400px) 100vw, 400px" /><figcaption>Groundhog day reference joke! Oh, and it&#8217;s also and NFT!</figcaption></figure>



<p></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-hackers-bill-murray/">Bill Murray Lost $200k to Crypto Hackers</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-hackers-bill-murray/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Ethereum to PayPal [Video Guide]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-paypal-2/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-paypal-2/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 05:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Videos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6003</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>On CoinCannon platform, you can exchange Ethereum to PayPal with ultimate anonymity. Finally, as of September 2022, Ethereum has officially moved on to Proof of Stake. Generally speaking, we saw no massive movement in price and one could call it anticlimactic. However, the Ethereum merge will payoff big time in the future when upcoming regulations [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-paypal-2/">How to Exchange Ethereum to PayPal [Video Guide]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>On <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> platform, you can exchange Ethereum to PayPal with ultimate anonymity. Finally, as of September 2022, Ethereum has officially moved on to Proof of Stake. Generally speaking, we saw no massive movement in price and one could call it anticlimactic. However, the <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/ethereum-merge/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Ethereum merge</a> will payoff big time in the future when upcoming regulations arrive. With that, ETH will be on the winning side of cryptocurrencies with a green and Eco-friendly smile. Until then, you can exchange Ethereum to PayPal on CoinCannon platform with no added fees. On top of that, all transaction will have 24/7 online support. Here is everything you need to know on how to cash out Ethereum.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="How to Exchange Ethereum to PayPal on CoinCannon [No KYC]" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/l5ykmDjJFOY?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Ethereum to PayPal?</strong></h2>



<p>For this transaction, you send Ethereum from your wallet and receive PayPal USD on your account. Naturally, you will need a verified and active PayPal account to receive the funds. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon. Want a good reason why? How about winning $100 ever month!</p>



<p>Learn more about our <a href="https://hi.exchange/campaign/tether-giveaway" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Tether Giveaway</a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Ethereum?</strong></h2>



<p>Ethereum, launched in 2015, is a blockchain-based, decentralized, and open-source software platform that is employed for Ether, its own dedicated cryptocurrency. Ethereum allows Smart Contracts and Distributed Applications to be developed and operate without any downtime, fraud, control, or intrusion from a third party.</p>



<p>Ethereum is not only a platform but also a programming language (Turing complete) operating on a blockchain, assisting developers in developing and publishing distributed applications.</p>



<p>Ethereum (ETH), the Ethereum network’s cryptocurrency, is probably the second most popular digital token after Bitcoin (BTC). Indeed, as the second largest cryptocurrency by market cap, comparison between Ether and BTC is only natural.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>PayPal is King for a Reason!</strong></h2>



<p>PayPal is an online trade company that, through online transfers, facilitates payments between parties. Its system allows clients to set up an account on its platform that is linked to the user’s credit card or checking account. Upon confirmation of identification and proof of funds, through the website or application of the company, users can begin sending or receiving payments online to and from other PayPal accounts.</p>



<p>As mentioned above, in order to transfer money to others using the receiver’s email address or mobile phone number, PayPal account holders can use the website or mobile application of the company. Within only a matter of minutes, transactions go through and the company promises that transfers are immediately available for payment or withdrawal to a bank account.</p>



<p>The ease of use and the wide acceptance makes the exchange cryptocurrencies to PayPal one of the best options when you need some cash to spend online.</p>



<p>All that said, you also have the ability to exchange ETH to Perfect Money USD or Tether USD.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Of course, in order to exchange Ethereum to PayPal, you will first need a reliable exchange platform. For that, CoinCannon is one of the best options out there.</p>



<p>Every exchange platform must maintain three important characteristics. Anonymity, affordability and reliability. We pride ourselves as a professional platform that offers all three.</p>



<p>For anonymity, CoinCannon requires no KYC or even a sign up process. The best way to protect your information is to not share them with anyone. And for that, we respect our customers and do not ask for their personal info.</p>



<p>As for affordability, CoinCannon utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. By doing so, we have managed to stay on top of the ranks on websites such as Bestchange and OkChanger.</p>



<p>Lastly, reliability is ensured for our customers with 24/7 online support. In case anything goes wrong, you will have our immediate support until the issue is resolved.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Ethereum to PayPal</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Ethereum (ETH) on the left field and PayPal on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li><li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your PayPal account details, email, and phone number.</li><li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li><li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li><li>On this step, please spend the time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li><li>Transfer your ETH to the CoinCannon Skrill address that is provided for you.</li><li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>Just like that, you have now exchanged Ethereum (ETH) to PayPal. In general, PayPal payments are inconsistent in terms of how long they might take. Give it a few minutes and the PayPal USD will be in your account ASAP. In the meantime, you can follow up on your order using the Track ID provided for you. Simply enter the track id in the required section on homepage to see at which point your order is. Remember not to share your Track ID with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-paypal-2/">How to Exchange Ethereum to PayPal [Video Guide]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-paypal-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Merge, Countdown and Institutional Investors</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/ethereum-merge/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/ethereum-merge/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 07:34:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Merge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5986</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At this moment, all eyes are on Ethereum merge and the final stages of the countdown. This, a revolutionary step for the blockchain is a significant step for a $1 trillion market hoping to expand. And of course, there will be no expansion possible with the current rates of energy consumption to mine cryptocurrencies. While [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ethereum-merge/">Ethereum Merge, Countdown and Institutional Investors</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>At this moment, all eyes are on Ethereum merge and the final stages of the countdown. This, a revolutionary step for the blockchain is a significant step for a $1 trillion market hoping to expand. And of course, there will be no expansion possible with the current rates of energy consumption to mine cryptocurrencies. While the White House is bringing down a hail storm of regulations on <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/white-house-on-digital-assets/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">digital assets</a>, Ethereum is hours away from sailing into the new land which is Proof of Stake. Can it be the moment when all the GPU scalpers who robbed us of our 120 fps gaming during the pandemic learn a lesson? Will it eventually bring down the big 4 mining companies who cause power grid failures in third world countries and get richer?</p>



<p>Ethereum, the second largest cryptocurrency by market cap is now crossing a CoinCannon away from the <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/tales-from-the-chain-chapter-v-bitcoin-maximalist/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bitcoin maximalists</a>. All hands on deck, even Google has added a new year style countdown for Ethereum merge. But, there’s also a catch and it is there to bring suspense to this article so that you would keep on reading. So, keep on skimming and scanning this piece to find out what the institutional investors are doing hours before this so called revolution.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color"><a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a><br>[No KYC]</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Search “Ethereum Merge” on Google</strong></h2>



<p>Yeah, there is a countdown for Ethereum merge on Google and it’s more exciting that the bomb countdown in CS:GO. Just kidding, nothing is more exciting than the bomb countdown in CS:GO when you’re camping behind the crates to snipe the bejesus out of a toxic kid. Nonetheless, everything is news and every news is supposed to be super-exciting these days. Here’s the latest image of the countdown I personally took on Google to make the article more visually engaging.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="854" height="443" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Ethereum-Merge.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-5989" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Ethereum-Merge.jpg 854w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Ethereum-Merge-300x156.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Ethereum-Merge-768x398.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 854px) 100vw, 854px" /></figure>



<p>Naturally, speculations are growing over what would happen when the transition is complete. With that, some believe there will be a rally for ETH and others expect a dip. In the meantime, it would be quite possible that nothing significant would happen. Much like Tolkien stories, we have a battle of optimism Vs. Pessimism going on in Crypto Twitter as they are bleeding in their mention wars. A magnificent battle of bots, retail investors and social media marketing specialists is now on full swing in Twitter, or should I say on Twitter?</p>



<p>Regardless, we will have some answers when the countdown ends. Until then however, institutional investors are selling ETH and jumping on their life boats. That’s right, big players are now backing down from Ethereum merge.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Institutional investors</strong></h2>



<p>Maybe, the Ethereum merge is not exciting but anxiety-inducing. After all, planting the bomb in CS: GO is exciting but when the other team does it, it will cause you anxiety. Picture yourself, rushing to defuse the bomb while you know there’s 14-year-old toxic kid is waiting to land a perfect 360 headshot on you.</p>



<p>Consequently, a quick look at Digital Asset Fund Flows Weekly report by <a href="https://coinshares.com/research/digital-asset-fund-flows" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinShares</a> is saying a lot about the merge. According to the report, institutional investors are pulling out, from the countdown perhaps.</p>



<p>“Digital asset investment products saw outflows totaling $63 million, the fifth consecutive week of outflows…</p>



<p>Ethereum was the primary focus of the outflows, totaling $62 million last week, this comes despite the improved certainty of the merge and perhaps highlights a concern amongst investors that the event might not go as planned.”</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="561" height="414" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/CoinSharesA-Ethereum-Merge.webp" alt="" class="wp-image-5988" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/CoinSharesA-Ethereum-Merge.webp 561w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/CoinSharesA-Ethereum-Merge-300x221.webp 300w" sizes="(max-width: 561px) 100vw, 561px" /></figure>



<p>In the meantime, BTC has also had a bad five weeks losing only $13 million in the last week. While this is Childs play compared to some of the biggest outflows $BTC and $ETH have seen, it’s not exactly okay either.</p>



<p>Cardano (ADA), Solana (SOL) and Ripple (XRP) saw minor inflows this week. Solana has had the largest inflows this year with $114 million according to CoinShares. Perhaps, the extremely exciting Solana phone is why no one is anxious over SOL network outages.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ethereum-merge/">Ethereum Merge, Countdown and Institutional Investors</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/ethereum-merge/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum price Analysis; September 12, 2022</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/ethereum-price-analysis-september-12/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/ethereum-price-analysis-september-12/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 10:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5981</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum price failed to surpass $1,700. Currently, ETH is looking bullish and can likely break above the $1,800 level. Here is a summary of Ethereum price in the past 24 hours: Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal on CoinCannon with Lowest Fees Ethereum is set on a new rally and has stabilized above $1,700. Currently, the price [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ethereum-price-analysis-september-12/">Ethereum price Analysis; September 12, 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Ethereum price failed to surpass $1,700. Currently, ETH is looking bullish and can likely break above the $1,800 level. Here is a summary of Ethereum price in the past 24 hours:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color"><a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a> on CoinCannon with Lowest Fees</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list"><li>Ethereum is set on a new rally and has stabilized above $1,700.</li><li>Currently, the price is above $1,700 and the 1-hour candles are above the SMA100.</li><li>On the 1-hour chart, we see a new uptrend forming with support level at $1,725.</li><li>In order to reach $1,800 in short-term, ETH must surpass $1,780 level.</li></ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Ethereum Price Action Analysis</strong></h2>



<p>ETH managed to remain above the $1,650 support and set on a new rally. With that, the price moved above $1,700 and the SMA100. Consequently, ETH broke through $1,750 and reached a monthly high of $1,788.</p>



<p>At the moment, ETH is having a slight correction and has lost the $1,750 support. Furthermore, ETH has moved below the 23.6% Fibonacci retracement level from the latest fall rise from $1,620 to $1,788. Currently, Ethereum price is over $1,700 and the 1-hour candles are above the SMA100. On the 1-hour chart, we see a new uptrend forming with support level at $1,725.</p>



<p>The first resistance level for the price is at $1,750 followed closely by $1,780. Breaking through $1,780can pave the way to reach $1,820. Further growth can bring ETH to $1,880 which is the last stop before regaining $2,000.</p>



<p>On the other hand, if Ethereum price fails to surpass $1,780, there could be further correction ahead. In which case, the $1,720 and $1,700 will be the first support levels. The $1,700 is near the 50% Fibonacci retracement level and losing it could be detrimental. Losing this level can bring ETH down to $1,650.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="700" height="323" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Ethereum-price-Analysis-September-12-2022.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-5983" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Ethereum-price-Analysis-September-12-2022.jpg 700w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Ethereum-price-Analysis-September-12-2022-300x138.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Technical Indicators</strong></h2>



<p>MACD indicator: at the time of writing this article the 1-hour MACD for Ethereum is on an upward movement.</p>



<p>RSI: the relative strength index is currently 50.</p>



<p>Resistance levels: for the bullish run, the $1,780 and $1,820 are absolutely necessary to surpass.</p>



<p>Support levels: at this point, the $1,700 is the crucial support level for ETH.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ethereum-price-analysis-september-12/">Ethereum price Analysis; September 12, 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/ethereum-price-analysis-september-12/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum price Analysis; September 5, 2022</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/ethereu-price-analysis-september-5/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/ethereu-price-analysis-september-5/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 09:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5937</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum price is still consolidating above $1,550. In case ETH manages to surpass $1,620, there could be a new bull run. Here is a summary of Ethereum price in the past 24 hours: Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal on CoinCannon with Lowest Fees Ethereum is hovering above the $1,520 and $1,500 support levels. Currently, Ether is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ethereu-price-analysis-september-5/">Ethereum price Analysis; September 5, 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Ethereum price is still consolidating above $1,550. In case ETH manages to surpass $1,620, there could be a new bull run. Here is a summary of Ethereum price in the past 24 hours:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a> on CoinCannon with Lowest Fees</p></blockquote></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list"><li>Ethereum is hovering above the $1,520 and $1,500 support levels.</li><li>Currently, Ether is trading above the $1,550 level and the 1-hour candles are above the SMA100.</li><li>In case ETH remains above $1,550 level, it could form a new rally.</li></ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Ethereum Price Action Analysis</strong></h2>



<p>Ethereum finally gained some positive momentum and surpassed $1,620 as well as the SMA100. Despite that, ETH failed to hold above $1,620 and hit a 24-hour high of $1,648 before having a correction. With that, ETH lost the $1,580 and $1,550 and reached a 24-hour low of $1,535. Then, the buyers attempted to set Ethereum for recovery and bring it back above 23.6% Fibonacci retracement level from the latest fall from $1,648 to $1,535. Currently, the price is below $1,535 and the 1-hour candles are above the SMA100. On the 1-hour chart, we see a new uptrend forming with support level at $1,560.</p>



<p>The first resistance level for Ethereum is at $1,600 which is near the 50% Fibonacci retracement level. Following that, the $1,620 and $1,650 will be the next resistance levels. Further growth can pave the way for ETH to reach $1,700.</p>



<p>On the other hand, if Ethereum price fails to surpass $1,600, there could be a new downtrend. In that case, the $1,560 will be a key support level right on the SMA100. Then, the $1,530 and $1,500 will come next to hold the decline. In case of failure, ETH could fall as low as $1,420.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="700" height="323" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Ethereum-price-Analysis-September-5-2022.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-5939" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Ethereum-price-Analysis-September-5-2022.jpg 700w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Ethereum-price-Analysis-September-5-2022-300x138.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Technical Indicators</strong></h2>



<p>MACD indicator: at the time of writing this article the 1-hour MACD for Ethereum is on an upward movement.</p>



<p>RSI: the relative strength index is currently 50.</p>



<p>Resistance levels: for the bullish run, the $1,600 and $1,700 are absolutely necessary to surpass.</p>



<p>Support levels: at this point, the $1,535 is the crucial support level for ETH.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ethereu-price-analysis-september-5/">Ethereum price Analysis; September 5, 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/ethereu-price-analysis-september-5/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
