<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Stablecoin Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/stablecoin/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 10:08:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>How to Buy Bitcoin with Dai [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 10:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6379</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you are looking to buy Bitcoin with Dai, CoinCannon is the ultimate platform for the job. Bitcoin has finally managed to bounce back and move above the critical resistance level at $25k. Subsequently, investors are once again eager to invest in the top crypto asset by market cap. On top of that, the mass [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Buy Bitcoin with Dai [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you are looking to buy Bitcoin with Dai, CoinCannon is the ultimate platform for the job. Bitcoin has finally managed to bounce back and move above the critical resistance level at $25k. Subsequently, investors are once again eager to invest in the top crypto asset by market cap. On top of that, the mass adoption of BTC has turned it into a utilitarian digital asset. Today, thousands of credible online stores accept Bitcoin as payment. Fortunately, you can now pay for goods and services via BTC and there’s lots of stuff you can <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-with-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">buy with Bitcoin</a>. However, if you’re holding DAI, you can instantly exchange Dai into Bitcoin in only a matter of minutes. Want to get started? Head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Dai on the left box and Bitcoin on the right and you’re good to go!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/">How to exchange cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Bitcoin with Dai?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive Bitcoin (BTC). In case your Dai wallet supports BTC, you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is DAI?</strong></h2>



<p>Before we go over how to buy Bitcoin with Dai, let’s take a brief look at Dai as a stablecoin.</p>



<p>DAI is an Ethereum-based stablecoin. A stablecoin is a cryptocurrency with a pegged value to another currency. In case of DAI, it is pegged to the US dollar and much like Tether and USDC, Dai will always be worth $1. Stablecoins are a crucial part of the crypto market as they offer very little volatility. In that regard, investors use stablecoins to save their funds in the form of a reliable and stable asset.</p>



<p>What makes DAI unique is a clever design that eliminates the biggest concerns for stablecoins. Generally speaking, conventional stablecoins require a massive reserve by the company. For example, for every Tether USD, the Tether company must hold $1 USD in their reserve. This is a huge issue for companies as it is difficult to provide liquidity and keep it consistent.</p>



<p>DAI offers a new solution for this problem. By using an automated system of smart contracts on Ethereum blockchain, DAI does now need a reserve. Using collateralized debt denominated in ETH allows DAI to maintain the 1:1 ration with USD. Simply speaking, users can deposit Ethereum or other cryptocurrencies can borrow against the value of their deposit and generate new DAI. The currency is this case is known as collateral.</p>



<p>You can <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange Dai to PayPal</a> on CoinCannon with the lowest exchange fees ever!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Invest in Bitcoin?</strong></h2>



<p>Well, there is hardly anyone these days who is not familiar with the definition of Bitcoin and what the cryptocurrency is capable of carrying out. However, let’s briefly go through what bitcoin is and where it comes from, then we can focus on the benefits of using this cryptocurrency and explain why to buy Bitcoin with Perfect Money.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a Cryptocurrency that was created after the housing market collapse in January 2009. It follows the ideas set out by the enigmatic and pseudonymous Satoshi Nakamoto in a whitepaper. The identity of the individual or individuals who developed this cryptocurrency is still under wraps. Unlike government-issued currencies, Bitcoin provides the guarantee of lower transaction costs than conventional online payment systems and is regulated by a decentralized authority.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a tempting opportunity for investment and great tool for doing financial transactions. In that regard, it has been a solid choice for investment as an asset that is truly decentralized. On top of that, there are countless online platform that accept Bitcoin as payment which makes BTC a utilitarian option for online payments.</p>



<p>So, if You’ve decided to invest in BTC, you can buy Bitcoin with Dai in only a matter of minutes on CoinCannon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-buy-bitcoin-with-dai"><strong>How to Buy Bitcoin with DAI?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Dai (DAI) on the left field and Bitcoin (BTC) on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your BTC wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your DAI to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>You’re All Set!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Bitcoin (BTC) to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Buy Bitcoin with Dai [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Ethereum to DAI [No Fees]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-dai/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-dai/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 07:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6315</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you’re looking to exchange Ethereum to DAI, CoinCannon is all you need! Volatile assets such as ETH and BTC will definitely have some risks associated with them. However, investors can easily convert them into stablecoins to stop the loss at a certain period of time. Thankfully, exchanging crypto assets into one another does not [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-dai/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange Ethereum to DAI [No Fees]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you’re looking to exchange Ethereum to DAI, <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is all you need! Volatile assets such as ETH and BTC will definitely have some risks associated with them. However, investors can easily convert them into stablecoins to stop the loss at a certain period of time. Thankfully, exchanging crypto assets into one another does not have massive fees so it’s a pretty safe bet. As far as stablecoins go, DAI has been a top choice for crypto enthusiasts as it is perhaps very different than the others. In this article, we will go over everything you need to know on how to exchange Ethereum to DAI on CoinCannon platform.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Ethereum to DAI?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive DAI. In case your Ether wallet supports DAI, you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Ethereum?</strong></h2>



<p>As an open-source decentralized blockchain platform, Ethereum is perhaps the most diverse and innovative one out there. In its essence, it is a decentralized public ledger for verifying and recording transactions. The Ethereum is considered as a second-gen blockchain platform, improving upon the high gas fees, scalability issues and high transactions fees of previous platforms. This open-source platform has no geographical restrictions and has always been the tip of the spear as far as innovation goes. Essential services such as Smart contracts, NFT`s and decentralized apps were first introduced on the Ethereum platform. As for the cherry on top, the native token of the Ethereum platform called Ether or ETH is second in terms of market value standing only behind Bitcoin.</p>



<p>With the <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/ethereum-2-0-upgrade-date/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Ethereum 2.0</a> launch in August 2022, the network totally switched to proof of stake. With that, Ethereum network will have much better scalability and very low gas fees. On top of that, all the criticism regarding energy consumption will go away. Many consider the 2.0 upgrade as a great investment opportunity since ETH is very much likely to have a rally. Nonetheless, Ethereum is the second most popular cryptocurrency in the world for good reason. Their team has always been on the forefront of innovation which could potentially attract capital and provide great returns.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Ethereum to DAI?</strong></h2>



<p>DAI is an Ethereum-based stablecoin. A stablecoin is a cryptocurrency with a pegged value to another currency. In case of DAI, it is pegged to the US dollar and much like Tether and USDC, Dai will always be worth $1. Stablecoins are a crucial part of the crypto market as they offer very little volatility. In that regard, investors use stablecoins to save their funds in the form of a reliable and stable asset.</p>



<p>What makes DAI unique is a clever design that eliminates the biggest concerns for stablecoins. Generally speaking, conventional stablecoins require a massive reserve by the company. For example, for every Tether USD, the Tether company must hold $1 USD in their reserve. This is a huge issue for companies as it is difficult to provide liquidity and keep it consistent.</p>



<p>DAI offers a new solution for this problem. By using an automated system of smart contracts on Ethereum blockchain, DAI does now need a reserve. Using collateralized debt denominated in ETH allows DAI to maintain the 1:1 ration with USD. Simply speaking, users can deposit Ethereum or other cryptocurrencies can borrow against the value of their deposit and generate new DAI. The currency is this case is known as collateral.</p>



<p>Currently, DAI has a market cap of over $5 billion and is ranked as 17th cryptocurrency.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Ethereum to DAI</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Ethereum on the left field and DAI on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your DAI wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your Ethereum to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-that-s-it"><strong>That’s it!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the DAI to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-dai/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange Ethereum to DAI [No Fees]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-dai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Djed Stablecoin Goes Live on Cardano Mainnet</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/djed-stablecoin/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/djed-stablecoin/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 08:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6305</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Certainly, it is a brave move for Cardano to issue Djed stablecoin right now. For those who do not now, Djed is an algorithmic stablecoin not backed by US dollar. And as far as that idea goes, many of those who came before, are now embarrassingly dead in the dumps! In fact, a big reason [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/djed-stablecoin/">&lt;strong&gt;Djed Stablecoin Goes Live on Cardano Mainnet&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Certainly, it is a brave move for Cardano to issue Djed stablecoin right now. For those who do not now, Djed is an algorithmic stablecoin not backed by US dollar. And as far as that idea goes, many of those who came before, are now embarrassingly dead in the dumps! In fact, a big reason that the crypto has been bearish for more than a year is Terra USD, an algorithmic stablecoin. Now, Djed stablecoin is supposed to be different, not in its idea, not in its operation, but somehow different in how much we trust its founder. Is that enough for investors?</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn all about <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/algorithmic-stablecoin-djed-cardano/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Djed Algorithmic Stablecoin</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Djed Stablecoin: Algorithmically Backed</strong></h2>



<p>Do not be discouraged if you read the title above and have no idea what it means. Perhaps, we live in times when we are supposed to read titles and not understand them and that’s okay. Maybe, it’s all about trust, just trust Charles Hoskinson and know that he is a kind soul. So of course, you and I can read a lot about how they use an algorithm to regulate the supply and demand and keep the value at $1. But, I cheated a lot in high school and then went on to study literature so I have no idea how algorithms work. But no worries, I used ChatGPT and it told me to trust the algorithm, so my anthropocentric views on comprehension are now slowly dying out.</p>



<p>And as a literature major, I like the sound of having a “new era” as Cardano’s marketing team keeps saying. They also keep saying how Djed stablecoin is a huge milestone for the whole DeFi sector which sound pretty awesome.</p>



<p>The point is, at this point in time, we simply cannot understand how things work. They will explain, and they will elaborate, but at the end of the day, it all comes down to faith. So, all we have to do is to listen to marketing departments, the advertising and Twitter announcements and invest in something we believe.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-news"><strong>The News!</strong></h2>



<p>Yes, there’s some exciting and perhaps life-changing news! Djed stablecoin is now live on the Mainnet. It was live on testnet back in May 2022 and now it’s alive. But before you get overwhelmed, there’s even more exciting news and details!</p>



<p>Djed stablecoin is backed by ADA which we literally sell with full anonymity on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> platform. The almighty algorithm will issue more ADA coins upon price increase and conversely buy off from the market upon decline. Basically, the system interferes with the value through supply and demand.</p>



<p>A few weeks ago, <a href="https://coti.io/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">COTI</a>, the platform that issued Djed announced the transition to a multi-chain network for the asset. This would add support for private payment networks and simultaneously bring down deposit fees to half. According to COTI, the changes could significantly help the mass adoption of crypto assets as payment.</p>



<p>“This launch signifies a massive step for the crypto industry, as well as COTI, as the [upgrade] will increase the growth of the widespread adoption of crypto payments for enterprises that are yet to adopt crypto payment solutions.”</p>



<p>They had a successful security audit before the official launch. With that, COTI took to <a href="https://medium.com/cotinetwork/a-new-era-for-stablecoins-begins-djed-is-live-on-mainnet-55971971f2a8" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Medium</a> to announce that a “new ear” is on its way.</p>



<p>“The much anticipated public mainnet launch of Djed heralds a new era for stablecoins. Launching Djed is a significant milestone for COTI, the Cardano ecosystem, and for the DeFi ecosystem as a whole. Being a decentralized open-source protocol, Djed is community-driven, as it brings an opportunity for users to hold, mint, and burn DJED and SHEN.”</p>



<p>To be honest, I do not know how to handle all the good news about Djed stablecoin. On one hand, it’s going to start a new ear and on the other, it is a big milestone for DeFi. Personally speaking, I will pray and give thanks to the algorithm gods!</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/djed-stablecoin/">&lt;strong&gt;Djed Stablecoin Goes Live on Cardano Mainnet&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/djed-stablecoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange USD Coin to Tether [No Fees]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-usd-coin-to-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-usd-coin-to-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 07:29:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USD Coin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6297</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In case you’re diversifying assets, you can exchange USD Coin to Tether on CoinCannon in only a few minutes. Stablecoins are a critical category of crypto assets, but there’s still lots of debate on which ones are more reliable. Regardless of all debates, diversification of assets is pretty much the safest solutions. With that, CoinCannon [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-usd-coin-to-tether/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange USD Coin to Tether [No Fees]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In case you’re diversifying assets, you can exchange USD Coin to Tether on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> in only a few minutes. Stablecoins are a critical category of crypto assets, but there’s still lots of debate on which ones are more reliable. Regardless of all debates, diversification of assets is pretty much the safest solutions. With that, CoinCannon aims to speed up this process by providing a fully anonymous platform to exchange USD Coin to Tether. On top of that, our customers enjoy some unique advantages such as super-competitive exchange rates, hassle-free KYC and 24/7 online support.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange USD Coin to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>This one’s easy! You need a crypto wallet to send and receive the digital assets. Thankfully, it’s quite a difficult job to find a crypto wallet that doesn’t support both USDT and USDC. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon. Want a good reason why? How about winning $100 ever month!</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>Learn more about our <a href="https://hi.exchange/campaign/tether-giveaway" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Tether Giveaway</a></p>
</blockquote>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is USD Coin (USDC)?</strong></h2>



<p>USD Coin owns the world’s largest stablecoin industry ecosystem in the world. It is a cryptocurrency that is pegged to US dollar in terms of value. That means that each USCD will always be worth $1. Stablecoins are used as a hedge against inflation and volatility in the crypto market. However, they can also be used as an alternative way to hold assets on the blockchain network.</p>



<p>As good as stablecoins might sound, there has always been concern about the companies not being honest about their dollar reserve. Basically, for every 1 USDC the company issues, they must hold $1 in their accounts. As a matter of fact, there are rumors regarding some large companies not having the dollar equivalent of their stablecoin. If a solid reserve does not back a stablecoin, the currency will lose value and seriously damage the investor’s funds. In that regard, USD Coin aims to provide full transparency about their reserves.</p>



<p>USDC is managed by a consortium called Centre which is a part of the payment technology company Circle. Much like TrueUSD, they offer monthly attestation reports by Grant Thornton to ensure investors regarding their reserves. Where they differ from TrueUSD, is that TrueUSD only holds dollar in different accounts but USD Coin also holds other assets such as gold.</p>



<p>You can also <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-usd-coin-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange USD Coin to PayPal</a> with very low exchange fees.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How is Tether Different?</strong></h2>



<p>In short, both USDC and USDT are basically the same idea. They are both stablecoins backed by a reserve of US dollar or liquid assets. Basically, for every Tether or USD Coin, their companies hold $1 in their reserve. Statistically speaking, Tether has never depegged from US Dollar. Furthermore, it is the oldest stablecoin to date with quite a solid reputation.</p>



<p>Before reading about how to convert Tether to USDC, let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon FTW!</strong></h2>



<p>CoinCannon is an OTC exchanger that offers everything you need from a platform.</p>



<p>Truthfully, it is a rare combination for an online exchange to offer anonymity, lowest exchange rates and unparalleled reliability altogether.</p>



<p>We respect our customer’s privacy by not asking for their personal information. The best way for anyone to protect their information is to not disclose them at all. In that regard, not having KYC or sign up is the best method.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the platform utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at all times. Our words sound too good? Just pay a visit to ranking websites such as BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>Lastly, according to Murphy’s law “anything that can go wrong will go wrong”. To stay ahead of any problems, we offer 24/7 customer support.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange USD Coin to Tether?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the homepage first, then select USDC (USD Coin) on the left field and USDT on the right. Enter the amount you want to exchange and wait for the exchange rate to apply.</li>



<li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Tether wallet details, email, and phone number.</li>



<li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li>Complete the captcha and click on “exchange” to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. At this point, you will have the CoinCannon wallet address to send the USDC to.&nbsp; After you have transferred your cryptocurrency, click on Pay Order button. Don’t forget to attach the screenshot for the USDC payment. your order will process swiftly.</li>



<li>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the Tether (USDT) to your wallet ASAP.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-all-good"><strong>All Good</strong></h2>



<p>Just like that, you have now converted USDC to Tether. In general, crypto payments don’t take very long to process. Give it a few minutes and the USDT will be in your wallet quickly. In the meantime, you can follow up on your order using the Track ID provided for you. Simply enter the track id in the required section on homepage to see at which point your order is. Remember not to share your Track ID with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-usd-coin-to-tether/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange USD Coin to Tether [No Fees]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-usd-coin-to-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange DAI to PayPal [lowest commission]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 09:45:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange DAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Maker DAO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4432</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>if you&#8217;re Looking to cash out your stablecoins, you can exchange DAI to PayPal on CoinCannon with the lowest exchange fees. DAI is the latest stablecoin added to CoinCannon platform along with, USDC and TUSD. Created with a unique architecture, DAI is a different kind of stable coin that offers better reliability compared with others. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/">How to Exchange DAI to PayPal [lowest commission]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>if you&#8217;re Looking to cash out your stablecoins, you can <strong>exchange DAI to PayPal on CoinCannon</strong> with the lowest exchange fees. DAI is the latest stablecoin added to CoinCannon platform along with, USDC and TUSD. Created with a unique architecture, DAI is a different kind of stable coin that offers better reliability compared with others. In this article, we will go through everything you need to exchange DAI to PayPal on CoinCannon website. You can also exchange DAI to other currencies on the platform.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-dai"><strong>What is DAI?</strong></h2>



<p>DAI is an Ethereum-based stablecoin. A stablecoin is a cryptocurrency with a pegged value to another currency. In case of DAI, it is pegged to the US dollar and much like Tether and USDC, Dai will always be worth $1. Stablecoins are a crucial part of the crypto market as they offer very little volatility. In that regard, investors use stablecoins to save their funds in the form of a reliable and stable asset.</p>



<p>What makes DAI unique is a clever design that eliminates the biggest concerns for stablecoins. Generally speaking, conventional stablecoins require a massive reserve by the company. For example, for every Tether USD, the Tether company must hold $1 USD in their reserve. This is a huge issue for companies as it is difficult to provide liquidity and keep it consistent.</p>



<p>DAI offers a new solution for this problem. By using an automated system of smart contracts on Ethereum blockchain, DAI does now need a reserve. Using collateralized debt denominated in ETH allows DAI to maintain the 1:1 ration with USD. Simply speaking, users can deposit Ethereum or other cryptocurrencies can borrow against the value of their deposit and generate new DAI. The currency is this case is known as collateral.</p>



<p>Currently, DAI has a market cap of over $9 billion and is ranked as 19<sup>th</sup> cryptocurrency.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-exchange-dai-to-paypal"><strong>Why Exchange DAI to PayPal?</strong></h2>



<p>PayPal is an online trade company that, through online transfers, facilitates payments between parties. Its system allows clients to set up an account on its platform that is linked to the user’s credit card or checking account. Upon confirmation of identification and proof of funds, through the website or application of the company, users can begin sending or receiving payments online to and from other PayPal accounts.</p>



<p>As mentioned above, in order to transfer money to others using the receiver’s email address or mobile phone number, PayPal account holders can use the website or mobile application of the company. Within only a matter of minutes, transactions go through and the company promises that transfers are immediately available for payment or withdrawal to a bank account.</p>



<p>The ease of use and the wide acceptance makes the exchange cryptocurrencies to PayPal one of the best options when you need some cash to spend online.</p>



<p>All that said, you also have the ability to exchange DAI to Perfect Money USD, Payeer USD or Webmoney USD.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-jolixo"><strong>Why CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p><strong>CoinCannon is an online exchange that offers everything you need from a platform.</strong></p>



<p>Truthfully, it is a rare combination for an online exchange to offer anonymity, lowest exchange rates and unparalleled reliability altogether.</p>



<p>We respect our customer’s privacy by not asking for their personal information. The best way for anyone to protect their information is to not disclose them at all. In that regard, not having KYC or sign up is the best method.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the platform utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at all times. Our words sound too good? Just pay a visit to ranking websites such as BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>Lastly, according to Murphy’s law “anything that can go wrong will go wrong”. To stay ahead of any problems, we offer 24/7 customer support.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-exchange-dai-to-paypal"><strong>How to Exchange DAI to PayPal?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select DAI on the left field and PayPal on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your PayPal account details, email, and phone number.</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your DAI to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>At this point, our team will process the order and make the payment to your account. PayPal payments might take some time. We suggest you read some of the articles on <a href="blog.hi.exchange">CoinCannon Blog</a> as you wait for the transaction.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/">How to Exchange DAI to PayPal [lowest commission]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange USD Coin to PayPal [No Fees]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-usd-coin-to-paypal/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-usd-coin-to-paypal/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 07:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy USDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange USDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USD Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4586</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Want more stablecoins? You can now exchange USD Coin to PayPal on CoinCannon platform with the lowest exchange fees. USD Coin is yet another dollar backed stablecoins that offers excellent transparency for investors. Hundreds of companies are now using USDC to hold their assets thanks to the security and reliability. It is yet another strong [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-usd-coin-to-paypal/">How to Exchange USD Coin to PayPal [No Fees]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Want more stablecoins? <strong>You can now exchange USD Coin to PayPal on CoinCannon platform</strong> with the lowest exchange fees. USD Coin is yet another dollar backed stablecoins that offers excellent transparency for investors. Hundreds of companies are now using USDC to hold their assets thanks to the security and reliability. It is yet another strong competitor for Tether as investors look for better options. Users can now exchange USD Coin to PayPal, Perfect Money, or Webmoney anonymously.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote has-border-color" style="border-color:#0693e3"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Get Started, head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> to Exchange USD Coin to PayPal.</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is USD Coin (USDC)?</strong></h2>



<p>USD Coin owns the world’s largest stablecoin industry ecosystem in the world. It is a cryptocurrency that is pegged to US dollar in terms of value. That means that each USCD will always be worth $1. Stablecoins are used as a hedge against inflation and volatility in the crypto market. However, they can also be used as an alternative way to hold assets on the blockchain network.</p>



<p>As good as stablecoins might sound, there has always been concern about the companies not being honest about their dollar reserve. Basically, for every 1 USDC the company issues, they must hold $1 in their accounts. As a matter of fact, there are rumors regarding some large companies not having the dollar equivalent of their stablecoin. If a solid reserve does not back a stablecoin, the currency will lose value and seriously damage the investor’s funds. In that regard, USD Coin aims to provide full transparency about their reserves.</p>



<p>USDC is managed by a consortium called Centre which is a part of the payment technology company Circle. Much like TrueUSD, they offer monthly attestation reports by Grant Thornton to ensure investors regarding their reserves. Where they differ from TrueUSD, is that TrueUSD only holds dollar in different accounts but USD Coin also holds other assets such as gold.</p>



<p>You can also buy USD Coin with Perfect Money USD and Payeer USD on CoinCannon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange USD Coin to PayPal?</strong></h2>



<p>PayPal is an online trade company that facilitates payments between parties through online transfers. Its system allows clients to set up an account on its platform that is linked to the user’s credit card or checking account. Upon confirmation of identification and proof of funds, through the website or application of the company, users can begin sending or receiving payments online to and from other PayPal accounts.</p>



<p>As mentioned above, in order to transfer money to others using the receiver’s email address or mobile phone number, PayPal account holders can use the website or mobile application of the company. Within only a matter of minutes, transactions go through and the company promises that transfers are immediately available for payment or withdrawal to a bank account.</p>



<p>The ease of use and the wide acceptance makes the exchange cryptocurrencies to PayPal one of the best options when you need some cash to spend online.</p>



<p>All that said, you also have the ability to exchange USD Coin (USDC) to Perfect Money USD, Payeer USD or Webmoney USD.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon is Better!</strong></h2>



<p>Cryptocurrencies are a financial apparatus to maximize privacy and efficiency. Sadly, regulations have been severely disrupting the market as they compromise both.</p>



<p>CoinCannon seeks to be a platform that offers privacy and efficiency simultaneously while offering some of the most aggressive exchange rates in the market.</p>



<p>To make this happen, the platform does not require KYC or a sign up process. This way, all customers can easily make transactions without a possible compromise on their personal information.</p>



<p>However, privacy is a crucial element and not a luxury. In that regard, the platform offers some of the most competitive rates amongst all online exchanges. The rates are automatically determined utilizing an automated system and are updated as soon as change in value is detected.</p>



<p>Last but not least, by offering true 24/7 support, all customers will be in touch with the team in case anything goes unplanned.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange USD Coin to PayPal?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select USD Coin on the left field and PayPal on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your PayPal account details, USDC wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, <strong>please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions</strong>.</li>



<li>Transfer your USD Coin to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>When you complete the steps, our team will immediately process your order. Keep in mind that PayPal payments might take a while to transfer. In the meantime, you can pay a visit to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a> and read some of the latest news articles about the crypto market. If you have any questions or problems, you can get in touch with the 24/7 online support section on the website.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-usd-coin-to-paypal/">How to Exchange USD Coin to PayPal [No Fees]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-usd-coin-to-paypal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy TrueUSD with Payeer [No KYC]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-trueusd-with-payeer/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-trueusd-with-payeer/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 08:11:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TrueUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6124</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you’re looking for the best stablecoin, you can now buy TrueUSD with Payeer on CoinCannon. CoinCannon provides full anonymity with no mandatory KYC or sign up process. And the good news is that the platform offers the lowest possible transaction fees. TrueUSD is a fully transparent and regulated stablecoin. They provide monthly reports on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-trueusd-with-payeer/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Buy TrueUSD with Payeer [No KYC]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you’re looking for the best stablecoin, you can now buy TrueUSD with Payeer on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>. CoinCannon provides full anonymity with no mandatory KYC or sign up process. And the good news is that the platform offers the lowest possible transaction fees. TrueUSD is a fully transparent and regulated stablecoin. They provide monthly reports on their reserve which is crucial for investors to know about. Users can now easily buy TrueUSD on CoinCannon and take advantage of the many benefits the platform offers.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy TrueUSD with Payeer?</strong></h2>



<p>For this transaction, you will need a verified and active Payeer account. Make sure that the transaction amount does not exceed your withdrawal limit. To receive TUSD, you will need a crypto wallet that supports TrueUSD. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon. Want a good reason why? How about winning $100 every month!</p>



<p>Learn more about our <a href="https://hi.exchange/campaign/tether-giveaway" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Tether Giveaway</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is TrueUSD?</strong></h2>



<p>TrueUSD (TUSD) is a stablecoin based on the Ethereum (ERC20) network. Stablecoins are cryptocurrencies that have their value pegged to another currency. In this case, as you might have guessed it, TUSD is backed by US dollar. However, the question is, why would someone create another stablecoin in this highly saturated market? The answer is, no one offers better transparency and security as much as TrueUSD.</p>



<p>Time and time again, we have heard concerns about Tether not being honest about their dollar reserve. Essentially, a stablecoin issuer must hold as much USD as they have their stablecoin in circulation. Sadly, these companies do not provide full clarity regarding their reserve. Subsequently, in case things get out of hand, the value of the stablecoin can drop in a matter of minutes.</p>



<p>TrueUSD has an emphasis on honesty and transparency to fight the bad reputation about stablecoins. They offer legal protections and real-time audits for users. All of the circulating supply of the token is fully collateralized by USD. The crypto exchange TrustToken issued TUSD in 2018. The TrustToken exchange has mandated a monthly audit for TUSD which means that the users are assured about the state of the reserve. Despite being based on the Ethereum network, TUSD has extremely low transaction fees. This is due to the fact that TrustToken generates revenue from their US dollar based holdings in different accounts. Here on CoinCannon, we will exchange your TrueUSD with astonishingly low exchange fees!</p>



<p>You also have the option to exchange TrueUSD to PayPal, Perfect Money and Webmoney on CoinCannon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Use Payeer?</strong></h2>



<p>First and foremost, Payeer is considered an online digital wallet for better asset management. Be it crypto of fiat, the payment processor is quick, reliable and cheap. In that regard, in a short lifespan of almost 8 years, Payeer is now recognized as one of the very best amongst competitors. Payeer utilizes built-in payment services with giant financial services such as Mastercard, VISA and PayPal.</p>



<p>As of 2021, the Payeer has approximately 7 million users which can transfer funds to each other with extremely low fees. The strength however, lies in diversity. Payeer is far ahead of any similar platform in terms of scale of operation and diversity in supported payment methods. With more than 50 payment approaches, the Payeer wallet offers users various services in one place.</p>



<p>To learn more about Payeer, continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-payeer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Payeer?</a>”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon FTW!</strong></h2>



<p>To exchange any cryptocurrency, you will need to find a good platform first. However, despite the diversity, it is quite a difficult task to find a good online exchange. The problem begins by compromising on your standards. You will want good exchange rates, privacy and reliability altogether. And that is hard to find!</p>



<p>Harsh regulations are pushing exchanges to disclose customer data to governments. This goes against the initial purpose of crypto which is absolute anonymity. Even worse, user data is a commodity, large institutions buy your information at a certain price. The best way to make sure your data is safe, is to not share them at all.</p>



<p>However, it is a luxury to offer no KYC, hence many exchanges charge customers with ridiculous exchange rates to compensate for the anonymity.</p>



<p>CoinCannon on the other hand gives you everything all at once. Want privacy? We have no KYC. Want the best exchange rates? Well, simply visit Bestchange or OkChanger and see for yourself how we are always on top of their lists.</p>



<p>And to make sure everything goes right, we offer 24/7 customer support</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Buy TrueUSD with Payeer?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Enter the homepage first, then select Payeer USD and TUSD from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of TrueUSD you will receive will automatically calculate.</li><li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your TUSD wallet details, email, and phone number.</li><li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li><li>Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the Payeer gateway and make the payment to our Payeer account. Having transferred your Payeer USD to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Success!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the TrueUSD to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-trueusd-with-payeer/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Buy TrueUSD with Payeer [No KYC]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-trueusd-with-payeer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy USD Coin with Payeer [No KYC]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-usd-coin-with-payeer-usdc/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-usd-coin-with-payeer-usdc/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 06:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USD Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5818</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you’re looking for a Tether (USDT) alternative, you can buy USD Coin with Payeer USD right here on CoinCannon. A few years ago, Tether was pretty much the only stablecoin investors cared about. However, as of 2022, USDC is about to surpass Tether both in market cap and popularity. With over $54 billion in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-usd-coin-with-payeer-usdc/">How to Buy USD Coin with Payeer [No KYC]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you’re looking for a Tether (USDT) alternative, you can<strong> buy USD Coin with Payeer USD</strong> right here on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>. A few years ago, Tether was pretty much the only stablecoin investors cared about. However, as of 2022, USDC is about to surpass Tether both in market cap and popularity. With over $54 billion in market cap as of August 2022, USDC is here to stay. With all the demand, we here at CoinCannon have provided an ideal platform to buy USD Coin with Payeer USD in only a matter of minutes. All your transactions on CoinCannon are fully anonymous and backed by 24/7 online support. Without further ado, let’s go over everything you need to know to buy USD Coin with Payeer USD:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/buy-cryptocurrencies-with-payeer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Buy Cryptocurrency with Payeer</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy USD Coin with Payeer?</strong></h2>



<p>For this direction, you will need to send Payeer USD from a verified and active Payeer account. On the other side, CoinCannon will send USD Coin to your crypto wallet. Make sure that your crypto wallet does support USDC and the wallet address is correct. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon. Want a good reason why? How about winning $100 ever month!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is USD Coin (USDC)?</strong></h2>



<p>USD Coin owns the world’s largest stablecoin industry ecosystem in the world. It is a cryptocurrency that is pegged to US dollar in terms of value. That means that each USCD will always be worth $1. Stablecoins are used as a hedge against inflation and volatility in the crypto market. However, they can also be used as an alternative way to hold assets on the blockchain network.</p>



<p>As good as stablecoins might sound, there has always been concern about the companies not being honest about their dollar reserve. Basically, for every 1 USDC the company issues, they must hold $1 in their accounts. As a matter of fact, there are rumors regarding some large companies not having the dollar equivalent of their stablecoin. If a solid reserve does not back a stablecoin, the currency will lose value and seriously damage the investor’s funds. In that regard, USD Coin aims to provide full transparency about their reserves.</p>



<p>USDC is managed by a consortium called Centre which is a part of the payment technology company Circle. Much like TrueUSD, they offer monthly attestation reports by Grant Thornton to ensure investors regarding their reserves. Where they differ from TrueUSD, is that TrueUSD only holds dollar in different accounts but USD Coin also holds other assets such as gold.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"><p>You can also <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-usd-coin-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange USD Coin to PayPal</a> with very low exchange fees.</p></blockquote>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Buy USD Coin with Payeer?</strong></h2>



<p>First and foremost, Payeer is considered an online digital wallet for better asset management. Be it crypto of fiat, the payment processor is quick, reliable and cheap. In that regard, in a short lifespan of almost 8 years, Payeer is now recognized as one of the very best amongst competitors. Payeer utilizes built-in payment services with giant financial services such as Mastercard, VISA and PayPal.</p>



<p>As of 2021, the Payeer has approximately 7 million users which can transfer funds to each other with extremely low fees. The strength however, lies in diversity. Payeer is far ahead of any similar platform in terms of scale of operation and diversity in supported payment methods. With more than 50 payment approaches, the Payeer wallet offers users various services in one place.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"><p>To learn more about Payeer, continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-payeer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Payeer?</a>”</p></blockquote>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Best Platform for the Job!</strong></h2>



<p>To exchange any cryptocurrency, you will need to find a good platform first. However, despite the diversity, it is quite a difficult task to find a good online exchange. The problem begins by compromising on your standards. You will want good exchange rates, privacy and reliability altogether. And that is hard to find!</p>



<p>Harsh regulations are pushing exchanges to disclose customer data to governments. This goes against the initial purpose of crypto which is absolute anonymity. Even worse, user data is a commodity, large institutions buy your information at a certain price. The best way to make sure your data is safe, is to not share them at all.</p>



<p>However, it is a luxury to offer no KYC, hence many exchanges charge customers with ridiculous exchange rates to compensate for the anonymity.</p>



<p>CoinCannon on the other hand gives you everything all at once. Want privacy? We have no KYC. Want the best exchange rates? Well, simply visit Bestchange or OkChanger and see for yourself how we are always on top of their lists.</p>



<p>And to make sure everything goes right, we offer 24/7 customer support</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Buy USD Coin with Payeer USD?</strong></h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">1</h3>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Select Payeer USD on the “I Give” field on the left and Ripple (XRP) on the “I Get” field on the right.</li><li>Enter the desired amount for the exchange and wait for the site to calculate the amazing exchange rates!</li><li>Click “Exchange”</li></ol>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>2</strong></h3>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Enter your Ripple Wallet address and E-mail address</li><li>Click “Exchange”</li></ol>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>3</strong></h3>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Read the Information</li><li>Complete the CAPTCHA</li><li>Click “Exchange”</li></ol>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>4</strong></h3>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>At this point, please check the transaction information and terms and conditions carefully.</li><li>You will be able to see the track id and CoinCannon Payeer account</li><li>Open your Payeer account, click on the account menu and copy the account number that begins by the letter “p” and paste it in the required field.</li><li>Go back to your Payeer account and send the exchange amount to CoinCannon Payeer account.</li><li>Once you have sent the exchange amount, go to the history menu on your Payeer account and copy the operation id for the payment. Then paste the operation id in the required field.</li><li>Kindly agree to the terms and conditions and click on “Pay Order.</li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Easy as That!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the USD Coin (USDC) to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-usd-coin-with-payeer-usdc/">How to Buy USD Coin with Payeer [No KYC]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-usd-coin-with-payeer-usdc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stablecoin Regulations Imminent Amid UST Crash</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/stablecoin-regulations-ust-crash/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/stablecoin-regulations-ust-crash/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 06:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FED]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Federal Reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rate Hikes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra USD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UST]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UST Crash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5382</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ideas sound great on paper, a stablecoin backed by Bitcoin is an awesome idea. And of course, the smart and educated team marketing the idea to the public are also pretty convincing. But, every now and then, one of these ideas fail. Every now and then, awful ideas with poor execution backed by top-notch marketing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/stablecoin-regulations-ust-crash/">Stablecoin Regulations Imminent Amid UST Crash</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Ideas sound great on paper, a stablecoin backed by Bitcoin is an awesome idea. And of course, the smart and educated team marketing the idea to the public are also pretty convincing. But, every now and then, one of these ideas fail. Every now and then, awful ideas with poor execution backed by top-notch marketing ventures annihilate people’s investments overnight. Worse yet, they mess up so much that all regulators rush to regulate the hell out of the sector. On well, stablecoin regulations were certain, but now, stablecoin regulations are reigning down upon crypto at hypersonic speeds. Federal Reserve, the one and only, is now charging up for a legislative attack on stablecoins. And clearly, the FED has got everything they need to impose harsh and paralyzing stablecoin regulations.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Exchange Stablecoins to PayPal with No Fess on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Stablecoin Regulations Coming in Hot!</strong></h2>



<p>The U.S. Federal Reserve has not been a fan of <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/regulatory-actions-against-stablecoins-are-coming/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">stablecoins</a> or cryptocurrencies in general. However, following Terra USD (UST) crash, they are voicing their concern regarding the volatility. As for their bright and clever solutions, they are pushing government backed digital assets as the “better” alternative.</p>



<p>As part of an extensive report on financial stability in numerous sectors, the Fed <a href="https://www.federalreserve.gov/publications/files/financial-stability-report-20220509.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">reports</a> on Stablecoins. While identifying the associated risks, they mention how private stablecoins fail to peg their currency to the value of the US dollar.</p>



<p>Primarily, the Fed cites lose liquidity for digital assets and blockchain projects as a strong risk factor.</p>



<p>“Structural vulnerabilities persist at money market funds and some other mutual funds, and the rapidly growing stablecoin sector is vulnerable to runs.</p>



<p>Stablecoins typically aim to be convertible, at par, to dollars, but they are backed by assets that may lose value or become illiquid during stress; hence, they face redemption risks similar to those of prime and tax-exempt MMFs [money market funds].</p>



<p>These vulnerabilities may be exacerbated by a lack of transparency regarding the riskiness and liquidity of assets backing stablecoins.</p>



<p>Additionally, the increasing use of stablecoins to meet margin requirements for levered trading in other cryptocurrencies may amplify volatility in demand for stablecoins and heighten redemption risks.”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Terra USD (UST) Down</strong></h2>



<p>This week, Terra USD (UST), a stablecoin backed by Bitcoin lost its peg to the US dollar. It fell as low as $0.68. Subsequently, the Luna Foundation Guard (LFG) responsible for UST came up with a quick response, the non-profit organization supporting the Terra (LUNA) ecosystem rapidly allocated $1.5 billion in assets to recover the price. Since then, UST has crawled back up to $0.90. In the meantime, stakeholders are pulling out their assets out of fear, making it difficult to stabilize the value.</p>



<p>In the report, Federal Reserve discusses the issue by calling out the risks involved. With that, they offer central bank digital currencies (CBDC) as an alternative operating within a regulated framework.</p>



<p>“A CBDC has the potential to support financial stability. In a rapidly digitizing economy, the proliferation of new types of digital money, including stablecoins, could present risks to both individual users and the financial system as a whole.</p>



<p>A CBDC could provide the public with broad access to digital money that is free from credit and liquidity risk.”</p>



<p>Arguably, the Terra USD (UST) is a blessing in disguise for the Fed. They get a golden chance to say “I told you so” and impose stablecoin regulations. Then, they get to move forward with an <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/cbdc-the-ultimate-financial-apparatus-for-governments/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">oppressive</a> CBDC program.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/stablecoin-regulations-ust-crash/">Stablecoin Regulations Imminent Amid UST Crash</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/stablecoin-regulations-ust-crash/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano’s Algorithmic Stablecoin Djed Goes Live</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/algorithmic-stablecoin-djed-cardano/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/algorithmic-stablecoin-djed-cardano/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 06:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorithmic Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Djed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5369</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Well, stablecoins will be huge in a cashless future where you don’t actually own your money. In fact, one would venture further from reality and say we actually need MORE stablecoins. And in this sector, an algorithmic stablecoin is just what the doctor ordered. For a truly decentralized future, Cardano has let go of ADA’s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/algorithmic-stablecoin-djed-cardano/">Cardano’s Algorithmic Stablecoin Djed Goes Live</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Well, stablecoins will be huge in a cashless future where you don’t actually own your money. In fact, one would venture further from reality and say we actually need MORE stablecoins. And in this sector, an algorithmic stablecoin is just what the doctor ordered. For a truly decentralized future, Cardano has let go of ADA’s decline in value and has finally introduced “Djed”. An algorithmic stablecoin that is functions pretty much the same as Dai using an algorithm to hold its value. Djed is now officially live on public testnet.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Buy Stablecoins on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a><br>No Fees!</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is an Algorithmic Stablecoin?</strong></h2>



<p>You know how for each Tether the company “holds” one US dollar somewhere in their reserve? (press X for doubt). An algorithmic stablecoin does not need a reserve to hold value. Instead, it relies on, you guessed it, an algorithm that essentially stabilizes the value.</p>



<p>The said algorithm will issue more coins upon price increase and conversely buy off from the market upon decline. Basically, the system interferes with the value through supply and demand.</p>



<p>Of course, algorithmic stablecoins have been facing strong criticism from experts. Some of them have failed and lost value temporarily or permanently. On the other hand, advocates call it a true decentralized digital asset that offers great salability which eliminates all user error.</p>



<p>Currently, Dai is by far the most successful algorithmic stablecoin. Continue reading <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/top-stablecoins-to-buy/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Top Stablecoins to Buy [Ranked by Security]</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Djed</strong></h2>



<p>The smart contracts platform Cardano (ADA) has officially released Djed on public testnet. Cardano teamed up with blockchain payments ecosystem COTI to launch the project.</p>



<p>Yesterday, COTI published a <a href="https://medium.com/cotinetwork/djed-public-testnet-is-live-b0b0b13552e0" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">blog post</a> saying that Djed, the first-ever algorithmic stablecoin is now live on Cardano platform.</p>



<p>“We are excited to announce that after months of intense work along with the Cardano team, the public testnet version of Djed is now released!</p>



<p>Djed is a decentralized, algorithmic stablecoin that is built on Cardano. An algorithmic stablecoin maintains stability through a combination of collateral and a reserve token.</p>



<p>In this case, Shen is Djed’s reserve coin and has the role of ensuring price stability – specifically it guarantees the collateralization rate and the peg of the stablecoin.”</p>



<p>According to COTI, the testnet phase will ensure that Djed is stable and secure and technically robust. As for final release, COTI is saying some tome in June of this year.</p>



<p>Back in last July, Cardano CEO Charles Hoskinson announced this project as part of their long-term plan. According to Hoskinson, the plan is to incorporate Djed into ADA’s smart contracts protocol called Plutus.</p>



<p>“One of the things we’re doing with this stablecoin [project] – after we clean it up a little bit more, because it’s so involved and there are so many moving pieces to it that have to be carefully thought about – is actually implementing it into Plutus as a Plutus native application.”</p>



<p>Currently, Cardano’s ADA is down 13% in seven days and is trading at $0.783.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/algorithmic-stablecoin-djed-cardano/">Cardano’s Algorithmic Stablecoin Djed Goes Live</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/algorithmic-stablecoin-djed-cardano/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top Stablecoins to Buy [Ranked by Security]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/top-stablecoins-to-buy/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/top-stablecoins-to-buy/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 06:23:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TrueUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USD Coin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4892</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>“Anything that can go wrong, will go wrong”. This is called Murphy’s law and it has been consistently true all throughout history. Why is it important for stablecoins? Well, potentially any stablecoin can lose value due to a multitude of reasons. Be it network issues or simply a lack of sufficient dollar reserve, stablecoins can [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/top-stablecoins-to-buy/">Top Stablecoins to Buy [Ranked by Security]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>“Anything that can go wrong, will go wrong”. This is called Murphy’s law and it has been consistently true all throughout history. Why is it important for stablecoins? Well, potentially any stablecoin can lose value due to a multitude of reasons. Be it network issues or simply a lack of sufficient dollar reserve, stablecoins can drop in value as we have seen with IRON stablecoin. In that regard, security is the utmost priority when it comes to stablecoins. At this point, Tether is still the predominant stablecoin but there are rumors about its connection with Chinese real estate giants that are making investors uncomfortable. And here we are with a list of top stablecoins to buy with solid reputations to introduce as Tether alternatives.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><span class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Looking for top stablecoins to buy? Head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>.</span></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Security Comes First</strong></h2>



<p>Considering the pegged value, the only reason to choose a stablecoin over another is the security. Primarily, a secure stablecoin is one that holds just as much US dollar reserve as the issued coins. However, there are tricks that some issuers can resort to for hiding their lack of reserve.</p>



<p>Generally speaking, an ideal stablecoin issuer must be fully transparent about how much dollar they are holding and in what form. And form, is what brings us to the second trick. Issuers can potentially hold different forms of assets for their reserve. Sometimes, these assets are in form of bonds or security papers issued from questionable companies. For example, the fallen real estate giant Evergrande used security papers to pay off or loan other companies. Subsequently, if you have security papers from Evergrande, good luck turning it into cash as it is exactly worth zero in 2022.</p>



<p>Bear in mind, these two tricks are just the tip of the iceberg as there are thousands of ways an stablecoin issuer can conceal their true dollar reserve. With that in mind, our top picks for stablecoins to buy are ranked by transparency and low diversity in assets. However, there is one outlier that utilizes a different method to hold a pegged value which we will talk about later in this article.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Top Stablecoins to Buy Available on CoinCannon</strong></h2>



<p>You can invest on stablecoins or exchange your cryptocurrencies to stablecoins on CoinCannon platform. CoinCannon gives you three good reasons to join in:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Anonymity: The platform does not require KYC (know your customer)</li><li>Efficiency: Very, very, low exchange fees. Our rates are seriously competitive</li><li>24/7 online Support: That’s right, we’re available to talk all day every day!</li></ul>



<p>On top of that, you can find guide articles for every exchange direction on <a href="//blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a>. CoinCannon blog is an all-in-one crypto blog where you can follow the latest <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/category/news/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">news</a>, <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/category/exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">guide articles</a>, <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/category/cryptocurrency/price-analysis/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">price analysis</a> and much more!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>TrueUSD</strong></h2>



<p>TrueUSD (TUSD) is a stablecoin based on the Ethereum (ERC20) network. Stablecoins are cryptocurrencies that have their value pegged to another currency. In this case, as you might have guessed it, TUSD is backed by US dollar. However, the question is, why would someone create another stablecoin in this highly saturated market? The answer is, no one offers better transparency and security as much as TrueUSD.</p>



<p>Time and time again, we have heard concerns about Tether not being honest about their dollar reserve. Essentially, a stablecoin issuer must hold as much USD as they have their stablecoin in circulation. Sadly, these companies do not provide full clarity regarding their reserve. Subsequently, in case things get out of hand, the value of the stablecoin can drop in a matter of minutes.</p>



<p>TrueUSD has an emphasis on honesty and transparency to fight the bad reputation about stablecoins. They offer legal protections and real-time audits for users. All of the circulating supply of the token is fully collateralized by USD. The crypto exchange TrustToken issued TUSD in 2018. The TrustToken exchange has mandated a monthly audit for TUSD which means that the users are assured about the state of the reserve. Despite being based on the Ethereum network, TUSD has extremely low transaction fees. This is due to the fact that TrustToken generates revenue from their US dollar based holdings in different accounts. Here on CoinCannon, we will exchange your TrueUSD with astonishingly low exchange fees!</p>



<p>TrueUSD is Certainly on top of our Stablecoins to Buy list!</p>



<div class="wp-block-columns is-layout-flex wp-container-core-columns-is-layout-1 wp-block-columns-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-column is-layout-flow wp-block-column-is-layout-flow" style="flex-basis:100%">
<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"><p>Buy and Sell TrueUSD on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a>.</p></blockquote>
</div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>USD Coin</strong></h2>



<p>USD Coin owns the world’s largest stablecoin industry ecosystem in the world. It is a cryptocurrency that is pegged to US dollar in terms of value. That means that each USCD will always be worth $1. Stablecoins are used as a hedge against inflation and volatility in the crypto market. However, they can also be used as an alternative way to hold assets on the blockchain network.</p>



<p>As good as stablecoins might sound, there has always been concern about the companies not being honest about their dollar reserve. Basically, for every 1 USDC the company issues, they must hold $1 in their accounts. As a matter of fact, there are rumors regarding some large companies not having the dollar equivalent of their stablecoin. If a solid reserve does not back a stablecoin, the currency will lose value and seriously damage the investor’s funds. In that regard, USD Coin aims to provide full transparency about their reserves.</p>



<p>USDC is managed by a consortium called Centre which is a part of the payment technology company Circle. Much like TrueUSD, they offer monthly attestation reports by Grant Thornton to ensure investors regarding their reserves. Where they differ from TrueUSD, is that TrueUSD only holds dollar in different accounts but USD Coin also holds other assets such as gold.</p>



<div class="wp-block-columns is-layout-flex wp-container-core-columns-is-layout-2 wp-block-columns-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-column is-layout-flow wp-block-column-is-layout-flow" style="flex-basis:100%">
<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"><p>Buy and Sell USD Coin on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a>.</p></blockquote>
</div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>DAI</strong></h2>



<p>DAI is an Ethereum-based stablecoin. A stablecoin is a cryptocurrency with a pegged value to another currency. In case of DAI, it is pegged to the US dollar and much like Tether and USDC, Dai will always be worth $1. Stablecoins are a crucial part of the crypto market as they offer very little volatility. In that regard, investors use stablecoins to save their funds in the form of a reliable and stable asset.</p>



<p>What makes DAI unique is a clever design that eliminates the biggest concerns for stablecoins. Generally speaking, conventional stablecoins require a massive reserve by the company. For example, for every Tether USD, the Tether company must hold $1 USD in their reserve. This is a huge issue for companies as it is difficult to provide liquidity and keep it consistent.</p>



<p>DAI offers a new solution for this problem. By using an automated system of smart contracts on Ethereum blockchain, DAI does now need a reserve. Using collateralized debt denominated in ETH allows DAI to maintain the 1:1 ration with USD. Simply speaking, users can deposit Ethereum or other cryptocurrencies can borrow against the value of their deposit and generate new DAI. The currency is this case is known as collateral.</p>



<div class="wp-block-columns is-layout-flex wp-container-core-columns-is-layout-3 wp-block-columns-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-column is-layout-flow wp-block-column-is-layout-flow" style="flex-basis:100%">
<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"><p>Buy and Sell DAI on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a>.</p></blockquote>
</div>
</div>



<p></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/top-stablecoins-to-buy/">Top Stablecoins to Buy [Ranked by Security]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/top-stablecoins-to-buy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ARK Invest Ventures into Crypto Market</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/ark-invest-venture-into-crypto-market/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/ark-invest-venture-into-crypto-market/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 06:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ARK Invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathie Wood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USD Coin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4644</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ARK Invest, a prominent investment management firm has announced an upcoming investment in the crypto market. ARK invest has announced the investment to take place in the form of a merger. Specifically, the firm is merging with the stablecoin firm Circle mostly known for USD Coin (USDC). The news comes at a time when Cathie [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ark-invest-venture-into-crypto-market/">ARK Invest Ventures into Crypto Market</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>ARK Invest, a prominent investment management firm has announced an upcoming investment in the crypto market. ARK invest has announced the investment to take place in the form of a merger. Specifically, the firm is merging with the stablecoin firm Circle mostly known for USD Coin (USDC). The news comes at a time when Cathie Wood’s stocks are performing worse than Lana Del Rey on SNL. On the other hand, Circle maintains a positive reputation as a trusted firm.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><span class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Exchange cryptocurrencies to PayPal with the lowest exchange rates on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>.</span></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>ARK for ARK’s Sake!</strong></h2>



<p>First and foremost, let’s talk gossip about ARK Invest and Cathie Wood. If hedge fund managers are the financial rock stars of our time, then Cathie Wood will be Chad Kroeger from Nickelback. Cathie Woods is a notoriously controversial figure in the world of finance. Predominantly, she is known for her hardcore support of meme stocks and <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-shitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">shitcoins</a>. But more importantly, she is a devoted supporter of the crypto market. So much so, that she has boldly predicted Bitcoin to reach $500,000 by 2026. In fact, ARK Invest was the first public fund manager to invest in Bitcoin.</p>



<p>Cathie Wood stocks performed incredible well in 2021 due to the special circumstances of that time. And as you would expect a big “but”, her stocks are now down in the dumps as of early 2022. Analysts are calling ARK Invest a lost cause at this point that is not worth buying the dip for. And what would ARK do when performing poorly? Well, they’re making big moves into the crypto market.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Crypto Market Sells!</strong></h2>



<p>Having put the gossip behind us, let’s discuss the details. Cathie Wood has recently announced that ARK Invest is buying shares of a SPAC (special purpose acquisition company) which is merging with the stablecoin firm Circle. A SPAC is a publicly traded company with the purpose of acquiring a private company and making it public. This is an alternative method for an initial public offering (IPO) to make a company public.</p>



<p>ARK Fintech Innovation exchange-traded fund (ETF) has spent $705,820 on 69,300 shares of Concord Acquisition Corporation (CND). CND is the SPAC at hand that is merging with Circle. The merger will take place in summer of 2022 while the new company will be worth $4.5 billion.</p>



<p>Jeremy Allaire, the CEO of Circle said in a recent interview with CNBC: “We just see an incredible opportunity to grow rapidly and grow around the world, and we think that this set of transactions and becoming a public company really sets us up to be a trusted platform in this digital currency industry.”</p>



<p>USD Coin is one of the most trusted stablecoins in the crypto market and it offers excellent transparency on their current US dollar reserves. You can buy and sell USD Coin on CoinCannon anonymously with the lowest exchange fees.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.okchanger.com/exchangers/jolixo" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">OkChanger</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. We are on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bestchange</a> and are always amongst the top exchanges.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ark-invest-venture-into-crypto-market/">ARK Invest Ventures into Crypto Market</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/ark-invest-venture-into-crypto-market/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
