<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Tether USDT Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/tether-usdt/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 09:10:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Dogecoin to Tether [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dogecoin-to-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dogecoin-to-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 11:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6439</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking for the best platform to exchange Dogecoin to Tether? CoinCannon is all you need. For the past two years, DOGE has been a hot topic of conversation. Despite all the huge growth in short periods of time, Dogecoin remains as a highly volatile crypto asset. In that regard, most investors tend to convert DOGE [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dogecoin-to-tether/">How to Exchange Dogecoin to Tether [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking for the best platform to exchange Dogecoin to Tether? CoinCannon is all you need. For the past two years, DOGE has been a hot topic of conversation. Despite all the huge growth in short periods of time, Dogecoin remains as a highly volatile crypto asset. In that regard, most investors tend to convert DOGE to Tether USDT in case they’re looking to hold assets for a while. However, it’s not easy to find an anonymous exchange platform that offers low exchange fees. In this article, we will go over everything you need to know on how to exchange Dogecoin to Tether USDT.</p>



<p>So, get started! Head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Dogecoin and Tether on the box and you’re good to go.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Dogecoin to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive USDT. Most likely, your Dogecoin wallet supports USDT, so you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Dogecoin (DOGE)?</strong></h2>



<p>Dogecoin started off as somewhat of a joke, but it developed a following after it was created. By the end of 2017, Dogecoin was a part of the cryptocurrency bubble that sent up the prices of several coins dramatically. Dogecoin lost much of its value after the bubble burst in 2018, but it still has a core of supporters who trade it and use it to tip Twitter and Reddit content.</p>



<p>Dogecoin (DOGE) is an open-source, peer-to-peer cryptocurrency. It is called an altcoin and as mentioned, many believe it is an almost sarcastic meme coin. Although it was seemingly developed as a joke, the blockchain of Dogecoin still has value. It derives its underlying technology from Litecoin. The low price and infinite supply of Dogecoin are noteworthy features of this cryptocurrency, which uses a scrypt algorithm.</p>



<p>You can read more about <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-dogecoin-how-it-work/">What is Dogecoin</a> at our article fully dedicated to this Cryptocurrency in case you need to do your research about this coin.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Dogecoin to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>At this point, it’s good to briefly introduce Tether. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Dogecoin to Tether?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Dogecoin (DOGE) on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your DOGE to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether USDT to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dogecoin-to-tether/">How to Exchange Dogecoin to Tether [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dogecoin-to-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange BNB to USDT [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bnb-to-usdt/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bnb-to-usdt/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 08:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6412</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Here’s the easiest way to exchange BNB to USDT instantly with full anonymity! Binance Coin (BNB) is one of the top crypto assets by market cap. For the most part, this popularity stem’s from Binance’s massive scale as an exchange platform. Now, while users can easily exchange BNB to USDT on Binance platform, they will [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bnb-to-usdt/">How to Exchange BNB to USDT [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Here’s the easiest way to exchange BNB to USDT instantly with full anonymity! Binance Coin (BNB) is one of the top crypto assets by market cap. For the most part, this popularity stem’s from Binance’s massive scale as an exchange platform. Now, while users can easily exchange BNB to USDT on Binance platform, they will have to compromise on their privacy to do the job. Primarily, Binance requires a much stricter KYC process to authenticate users. On top of that, they will have to comply with multiple governments and share user data with the authorities. Fortunately, CoinCannon cuts down all complications by offering a truly hassle-free KYC process. Furthermore, privacy will not come as a luxury sine CoinCannon offer the lowest exchange fees. With all that, here is a full guide on how to exchange Binance Coin to Tether USDT in only a matter of minutes.</p>



<p>So, head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, choose Binance Coin (BNB) on the left field and Tether (USDT) on the right one and start your exchange.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange BNB to USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive USDT. Most likely, your Cardano wallet supports USDT, so you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Binance Coin (BNB)?</strong></h2>



<p>Before we go over how to exchange BNB to USDT, let’s go over a brief introduction on Binance Coin. Initially found in China, Binance began as an online cryptocurrency exchange with a strong emphasis on altcoin trading. It didn’t take long for Binance to be crowned as the number one exchange in the world. Amongst the numerous motivating factors and reasons for this profound success, the primary one was high liquidity, low transaction fees and additional discounts for users who made payments by its native coin, BNB. The massive platform has a staggering capacity to process approximately 1.4 million orders per second, offering trading for more than 500 cryptocurrencies and virtual tokens.</p>



<p>As for trading, Binance offers seven trade orders of Limit order, Market order, stop limit order, stop market order, Trailing stop order, Post only order and Limit TP/SL order. Despite the varying transaction fees for withdrawal based on the currency and its amount, there is no transaction fee for deposits.</p>



<p>Initially introduced as an ERC20 Ethereum based cryptocurrency in 2017, BNB has now moved on to Binance’s own blockchain named Binance chain. As the native coin for Binance exchange, BNB was primarily a utility token to motivate users for transaction fee discounts. However, the applications for Binance coin have now expanded dramatically since you can now use Binance Coin for financial services, entertainment, online services and many more.</p>



<p>With all this development happening in a short time period, the 26,500% overall price increase (correct as of January 2022) since being introduced in 2017 is well justified. As of June 4th 2021 BNB has a market cap of $53.7 billion dollars and is only ranked behind Bitcoin and Ethereum.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange BNB to USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>At this point, it’s good to briefly introduce Tether. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange BNB to USDT</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Cardano on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your ADA to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-and-you-re-all-set"><strong>And You’re All Set!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bnb-to-usdt/">How to Exchange BNB to USDT [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bnb-to-usdt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Payeer USD to Tether USDT</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-payeer-usd-to-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-payeer-usd-to-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 08:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6406</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking to exchange Payeer USD to Tether USDT? CoinCannon is all you need! Exchanging digital currencies can be a hassle sometimes, especially when you want crypto assets. For the most part, it might be easy to convert assets, but finding an exchanger with no compromise is hard. Fortunately, CoinCannon offers everything online customers need to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-payeer-usd-to-tether/">How to Exchange Payeer USD to Tether USDT</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking to exchange Payeer USD to Tether USDT? CoinCannon is all you need! Exchanging digital currencies can be a hassle sometimes, especially when you want crypto assets. For the most part, it might be easy to convert assets, but finding an exchanger with no compromise is hard. Fortunately, CoinCannon offers everything online customers need to convert their assets. Thanks to a hassle-free KYC process and super-competitive exchange fees, you can instantly exchange Payeer USD to Tether USDT.</p>



<p>Get started! Head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Payeer USD on the left box and Tether USDT on the right and you’re good to go.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Payeer USD to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange direction, you will need a verified and active Payeer account. Make sure that the transaction amount does not exceed your withdrawal limit. In order to receive Tether (USDT), you will need a reliable crypto wallet. There are too many options out there, but CoinCannon suggests customers to use Trust Wallet. Furthermore, make sure you pay attention to the TRC20 and ERC20 variants for Tether as they use different networks for transactions and require different wallet addresses.</p>



<p>On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Payeer and How Does it Work?</strong></h2>



<p>First and foremost, Payeer is considered an online digital wallet for better asset management. Be it crypto of fiat, the payment processor is quick, reliable and cheap. In that regard, in a short lifespan of almost 8 years, Payeer is now recognized as one of the very best amongst competitors. Payeer utilizes built-in payment services with giant financial services such as Mastercard, VISA and PayPal.</p>



<p>As of 2021, the Payeer has approximately 7 million users which can transfer funds to each other with extremely low fees. The strength however, lies in diversity. Payeer is far ahead of any similar platform in terms of scale of operation and diversity in supported payment methods. With more than 50 payment approaches, the Payeer wallet offers users various services in one place.</p>



<p>To learn more about Payeer, continue reading “<a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-payeer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Payeer?</a>”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Payeer USD to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Payeer USD to Tether USDT</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Payeer on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>By now, you will go to the Payeer gateway. Transfer your Payeer USD to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-payeer-usd-to-tether/">How to Exchange Payeer USD to Tether USDT</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-payeer-usd-to-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Solana to Tether [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-solana-to-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-solana-to-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 07:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6403</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sure, you can exchange Solana to Tether on so many platforms, but CoinCannon is better! Solana (SOL) is one of the fastest blockchain networks out there. It offers lightning speed transaction speeds and super cheap transaction costs. With all that in mind, SOL has a loyal group of institutions using it for their global transactions. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-solana-to-tether/">How to Exchange Solana to Tether [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Sure, you can exchange Solana to Tether on so many platforms, but CoinCannon is better! Solana (SOL) is one of the fastest blockchain networks out there. It offers lightning speed transaction speeds and super cheap transaction costs. With all that in mind, SOL has a loyal group of institutions using it for their global transactions. Subsequently, Solana is one of the top cryptocurrencies by market cap. In this article, we will go over how to exchange Solana to Tether on CoinCannon platform. At CoinCannon, you can have the lowest exchange rates, full anonymity and 24/7 online support all together.</p>



<p>So head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Solana on the left box and Tether on the right and get started!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Solana to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive USDT. Most likely, your Solana wallet supports USDT, so you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Solana?</strong></h2>



<p>In short, Solana is a blockchain platform for decentralized applications (DApps). The network utilizes Proof of Stake consensus algorithm. However, in a world full of PoS blockchain networks, Solana has managed to achieve some impressive figures. The network can support up to 50,000 transactions per second (TPS) and requires 400 milliseconds to build a block. With the quickly increasing number of validators currently at 1,061, the network is one of the fastest out there.</p>



<p>Found in 2017 by Anatoly Yakovenko, a former Qualcomm member, along with Eric Williams and Greg Fitzgerald, the network aimed to create a more efficient and scalable platform.</p>



<p>The team consists of former members of companies such as Google, Apple, Microsoft, Qualcomm, Dropbox, Intel and more.</p>



<p>In that regard, the network is backed by many years of experience in some of the best companies around the world.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>    Continue reading “<a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-solana/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Solana</a>” to learn everything about the network.</p>
</blockquote>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Solana to Tether</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to exchange Solana to Tether USDT, let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Solana to Tether?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Solana on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your SOL to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-you-re-all-set"><strong>You’re All Set!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-solana-to-tether/">How to Exchange Solana to Tether [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-solana-to-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cardano-ada-to-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cardano-ada-to-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 08:39:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6393</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking for the best platform to exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether? CoinCannon is all you need. Cardano is one of the top cryptocurrencies by market cap and has a pretty strong community of investors. Today, it’s hard to find an online exchanger that doesn’t have ADA on their supported currency list. Despite that, it is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cardano-ada-to-tether/">Exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking for the best platform to exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether? CoinCannon is all you need. Cardano is one of the top cryptocurrencies by market cap and has a pretty strong community of investors. Today, it’s hard to find an online exchanger that doesn’t have ADA on their supported currency list. Despite that, it is still difficult to find a platform that offers the lowest exchange rates and full anonymity. Fortunately, you can instantly exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether without compromising on anything! In this article, we will go over everything you need to know on how to convert ADA to USDT.</p>



<p>So, head over to <strong><a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a></strong>, choose Cardano (ADA) on the left field and Tether (USDT) on the right one and start your exchange.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive USDT. Most likely, your Cardano wallet supports USDT, so you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Cardano (ADA)?</strong></h2>



<p>The Cardano project launched in 2017. It was the third generation of blockchain networks. One that successfully dealt with some of the greatest challenges of previous generations. Issues such as high gas fees and scalability by introducing the Ouroboros, a proof of stake algorithm to mine blocks which will be further explained in the article.</p>



<p>In 2017, the Cardano project started as a third-gen open-source and public blockchain platform. ADA is the native token of the platform. It is Led by Charles Hoskinson, one of the co-founders of Ethereum. Cardano had a great emphasis on being future-proof by being peer-reviewed and methodically developed by academic experts in the field. Cardano views itself as the updated version of Ethereum. Moving towards building a connected and decentralized system and providing banking services to the unbanked.</p>



<p>ADA is the native token of the network. Currently, ADA stands in 7th place in the ranks with a market cap of 13.5 billion USD.</p>



<p>To learn everything about Cardano and ADA continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-ada-a-guide-to-the-cardano-project/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is ADA?</a>”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether (USDT)?</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT, let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon for the Win!</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Cardano on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your ADA to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-all-good"><strong>All Good!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cardano-ada-to-tether/">Exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cardano-ada-to-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Tron with Tether USDT [Instant]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tron-with-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tron-with-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 08:42:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tron (TRX)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6373</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking to buy Tron with Tether? Look no further than CoinCannon. Generally speaking, buying cryptocurrencies and exchanging them into one another is an easy task. However, most exchange platforms tend to compromise on security or offer high exchange rates. With that, it can be difficult to find an online exchange platform that offers everything you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tron-with-tether/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Buy Tron with Tether USDT [Instant]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking to buy Tron with Tether? Look no further than CoinCannon. Generally speaking, buying cryptocurrencies and exchanging them into one another is an easy task. However, most exchange platforms tend to compromise on security or offer high exchange rates. With that, it can be difficult to find an online exchange platform that offers everything you need. Subsequently, CoinCannon provides unparalleled anonymity all while charging no hidden fees on your transaction. With all that, you can easily Buy Tron with Tether (USD) in only a matter of minutes. So head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Tether USDT on the left field, and Tron on the right and start the action!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Tron with Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive Tron (TRX). In case your USDT wallet supports Tether, you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Tron (TRX)?</strong></h2>



<p>Tron is a decentralized, blockchain-based platform that aims to build a free, global entertainment system for digital content with distributed storage technology and enables digital content to be shared easily and cost-effectively.</p>



<p>The TRON ecosystem basically acts as a platform for content-sharing. In this platform, TRX is the payment for users who create or post content, resulting in a fairer and more open monetization mechanism than those that control conventional social media networks. It also allows users to share their content without having to go through a middleman, such as the Google Play Store or Apple Store. This means that TRON is helping to push the decentralized application market (dApps).</p>



<p>Tron was founded by a non-profit organization based in Singapore called the Tron Foundation in September 2017. This foundation is led by Justin Sun, CEO, and benefits from a dedicated in-house development team that includes distinguished stalwarts in technology.</p>



<p>Tron attempts to CoinCannon the gap between content creators and content consumers by eliminating the middleman by using the features of the blockchain and peer-to-peer (P2P) network technology. The result is an overall cost reduction for the consumer and better collection for the content producer through direct receipts, which offers a win-win situation.</p>



<p>To learn everything about Tron (TRX) continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-tron-trx/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Tron?</a>”</p>



<p>If you are interested in investing in Tron (TRX), you can easily and instantly buy Tron with Tether (USDT) or a variety of other digital currencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Buy Tron with Tether (USDT)?</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to buy Tron (TRX) with Tether (USDT), let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon is the Best Exchange!</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Buy Tron with Tether (USDT)?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">Homepage</a> on CoinCannon. Select Tether USDT on the left field and Tron (TRX) on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your TRX wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your USDT to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-that-s-it"><strong>That’s It!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tron (TRX) to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tron-with-tether/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Buy Tron with Tether USDT [Instant]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tron-with-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 07:12:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6362</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In case you’re looking to exchange Ethereum to Tether, CoinCannon is the ultimate platform! In general, holding volatile assets for long is a risky move. With that, stablecoins are a great solution to hold digital assets without the risk of volatility. Speaking of risks, Tether has been the oldest and the most popular stablecoin simply [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In case you’re looking to exchange Ethereum to Tether, <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is the ultimate platform! In general, holding volatile assets for long is a risky move. With that, stablecoins are a great solution to hold digital assets without the risk of volatility. Speaking of risks, Tether has been the oldest and the most popular stablecoin simply because of its unparalleled reliability. Despite all that, investors need an exchange platform that doesn’t compromise on their privacy. Although you can exchange ETH to USDT in numerous platforms, CoinCannon offers top-tier anonymity all while charging no hidden fees. In this article, we will go over everything you need to know on how to exchange Ethereum to Tether (USDT).</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn How to <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-do-i-need-to-exchange-ethereum-to-tether"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Ethereum to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive USDT. In case your Ether wallet supports Tether, you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Ethereum?</strong></h2>



<p>Ethereum is a decentralized blockchain platform that is open-source and known for its diversity and innovation. Its main purpose is to serve as a decentralized public ledger for verifying and recording transactions. Compared to previous platforms, Ethereum has improved upon scalability issues, high gas fees, and high transaction fees, making it a second-generation blockchain platform. It has no geographical restrictions and has been a leader in innovation, introducing essential services like smart contracts, NFTs, and decentralized apps. Additionally, its native token, Ether or ETH, is the second-highest in market value after Bitcoin.</p>



<p>In August 2022, Ethereum launched version 2.0, which switched the network to proof of stake. This upgrade has significantly improved scalability and lowered gas fees, while also addressing criticism about energy consumption. This upgrade is seen as a great investment opportunity, as ETH is likely to rally. Ethereum is the second most popular cryptocurrency globally due to its innovative team, potential for attracting capital, and providing great returns.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Ethereum to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to exchange Ethereum to Tether (USDT), let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon for the Win!</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Ethereum on the left field and Tether (USDT) on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your Ethereum to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>You’re All Set!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the USDT to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Crypto to Tether USDT [Lowest Fees]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-to-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-to-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 07:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange crypto to tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5617</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Very often, you will have to exchange crypto to Tether USDT in order to avoid market volatility. As of 2022, Tether USDT is still the dominant stablecoin in the market and the top US dollar crypto equivalent. Whether you trade or hodl, Tether USDT is the ultimate mediator apparatus for everyone. However, although making the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-to-tether/">How to Exchange Crypto to Tether USDT [Lowest Fees]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Very often, you will have to exchange crypto to Tether USDT in order to avoid market volatility. As of 2022, Tether USDT is still the dominant stablecoin in the market and the top US dollar crypto equivalent. Whether you trade or hodl, Tether USDT is the ultimate mediator apparatus for everyone. However, although making the exchange is easy, it matters a lot which platform you choose to exchange crypto to Tether. For one, not all platforms offer the same exchange rates and you may have to pay more for the order. More importantly, anonymity is also a key feature user should keep in mind. For that, a reliable exchange platform like <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is absolutely necessary. In this article, we will go over how to exchange crypto to Tether and why CoinCannon is the best platform to do the job.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/how-exchange-tether-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How To Exchange Tether USDT To PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Crypto to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>Generally speaking, exchanging assets to Tether is for times when you want to pay less commission and be ready for the next purchase. When you <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange cryptocurrency to PayPal</a>, the cost for the exchange is considerably higher and it takes a longer time to have the assets in your account. On top of that, the next time you want to buy cryptocurrencies, you will once again have to pay high commission and wait longer. With Tether, the transactions are almost immediate and have a very low cost of transaction.</p>



<p>Comparatively, Tether is good for those who are actively monitoring the market to make their next move. Thankfully, numerous Forex platforms also accept Tether as payment so it has even more utility. On the other hand, PayPal is generally a safer method to store assets with much more regulations. Naturally, it is good for those looking for better security and purchasing options.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Tether (USDT)?</strong></h2>



<p>&nbsp;Before reading about how to exchange crypto to Tether (USDT), let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Crypto to Tether on CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p>very exchange platform must maintain three important characteristics. Anonymity, affordability and reliability. We pride ourselves as a professional platform that offers all three.</p>



<p>For anonymity, CoinCannon requires no KYC or even a sign up process. The best way to protect your information is to not share them with anyone. And for that, we respect our customers and do not ask for their personal info.</p>



<p>As for affordability, CoinCannon utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. By doing so, we have managed to stay on top of the ranks on websites such as Bestchange and OkChanger.</p>



<p>Lastly, reliability is ensured for our customers with 24/7 online support. In case anything goes wrong, you will have our immediate support until the issue is resolved.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Crypto to Tether (USDT) on CoinCannon</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the homepage first, then select the cryptocurrency you want on the left field and Tether TRC20 or ERC20 on the right. Enter the amount you want to exchange and wait for the exchange rate to apply.</li>



<li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Tether wallet details, email, and phone number.</li>



<li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li>Complete the captcha and click on “exchange” to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. At this point, you will have the CoinCannon wallet address to send the cryptocurrency to. &nbsp;After you have transferred your cryptocurrency, click on Pay Order button. Don’t forget to attach the screenshot for the payment. your order will process swiftly.</li>



<li>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the Tether to your wallet ASAP.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>And Done!</strong></h2>



<p>Usually, Tether payments are very quick to go through. For that, give it a few minutes and you will have the USDT in your wallet. In the meantime, you can follow up on your order using the Track ID provided for you. Simply enter the track id in the required section on homepage to see at which point your order is. Remember not to share your Track ID with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-to-tether/">How to Exchange Crypto to Tether USDT [Lowest Fees]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-to-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Bitcoin to Tether (USDT) + Video</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bitcoin-to-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bitcoin-to-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 05:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Videos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin to tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5656</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Unlike a few years ago, you do not have to exchange Bitcoin to Tether (USDT) in order to pay for something. These days, having Bitcoin in your wallet is pretty much as good as cash. You can spend BTC for plethora of purchasing options. As we previously talked about the things you can buy with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bitcoin-to-tether/">How to Exchange Bitcoin to Tether (USDT) + Video</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Unlike a few years ago, you do not have to exchange Bitcoin to Tether (USDT) in order to pay for something. These days, having Bitcoin in your wallet is pretty much as good as cash. You can spend BTC for plethora of purchasing options. As we previously talked about the things you can <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/buy-with-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">buy with Bitcoin</a>, the options are endless. However, the volatility makes it hard for us to be hodlers and that is where stablecoins come to play. Most investors exchange Bitcoin to Tether to hedge against the volatility and find a safe haven until their next opportunity to invest. With that, we will go over how to exchange Bitcoin to Tether on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> platform with the lowest exchange fees.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-crypto-to-tether/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Crypto to Tether (USDT)</a> with No KYC</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="How to Exchange Bitcoin to Tether (USDT) [No KYC]" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/NVPzLhSctEU?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div><figcaption>Check Out CoinCannon YouTube Channel</figcaption></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Bitcoin to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>Generally speaking, exchanging assets to Tether is for times when you want to pay less commission and be ready for the next purchase. When you <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/">exchange cryptocurrency to PayPal</a>, the cost for the exchange is considerably higher and it takes a longer time to have the assets in your account. On top of that, the next time you want to buy cryptocurrencies, you will once again have to pay high commission and wait longer. With Tether, the transactions are almost immediate and have a very low cost of transaction.</p>



<p>Comparatively, Tether is good for those who are actively monitoring the market to make their next move. Thankfully, numerous Forex platforms also accept Tether as payment so it has even more utility. On the other hand, PayPal is generally a safer method to store assets with much more regulations. Naturally, it is good for those looking for better security and purchasing options.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Tether (USDT)?</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to exchange crypto to Tether (USDT), let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon for the Win!</strong></h2>



<p>Of course, in order to exchange Bitcoin to Tether, you will first need a reliable exchange platform. For that, <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is one of the best options out there.</p>



<p>Every exchange platform must maintain three important characteristics. Anonymity, affordability and reliability. We pride ourselves as a professional platform that offers all three.</p>



<p>For anonymity, CoinCannon requires no KYC or even a sign up process. The best way to protect your information is to not share them with anyone. And for that, we respect our customers and do not ask for their personal info.</p>



<p>As for affordability, CoinCannon utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. By doing so, we have managed to stay on top of the ranks on websites such as Bestchange and OkChanger.</p>



<p>Lastly, reliability is ensured for our customers with 24/7 online support. In case anything goes wrong, you will have our immediate support until the issue is resolved.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Bitcoin to Tether (USDT)</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Enter the homepage first, then select Bitcoin (BTC) on the left field and Tether TRC20 or ERC20 on the right. Enter the amount you want to exchange and wait for the exchange rate to apply.</li><li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Tether wallet details, email, and phone number.</li><li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li><li>Complete the captcha and click on “exchange” to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. At this point, you will have the CoinCannon wallet address to send the Bitcoin to.&nbsp; After you have transferred your cryptocurrency, click on Pay Order button. Don’t forget to attach the screenshot for the BTC payment. your order will process swiftly.</li><li>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the Tether to your wallet ASAP.</li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>That’s it!</strong></h2>



<p>Just like that, you have now exchanged Bitcoin to Tether. In general, Tether payments don’t take very long to process. Give it a few minutes and the Tether USDT will be in your wallet quickly. In the meantime, you can follow up on your order using the Track ID provided for you. Simply enter the track id in the required section on homepage to see at which point your order is. Remember not to share your Track ID with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bitcoin-to-tether/">How to Exchange Bitcoin to Tether (USDT) + Video</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bitcoin-to-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Buy Tether with Skrill – USDT Buying Guide</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-skrill/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-skrill/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 07:24:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Skrill]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether TRC20]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5723</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you already have a Skrill account, you can buy Tether with Skrill on CoinCannon platform. CoinCannon provides full anonymity for all customers and does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. Skrill is quickly becoming one of the most popular payment platforms in the world and that is for good reason. For [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-skrill/">Buy Tether with Skrill – USDT Buying Guide</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you already have a Skrill account, you can <strong>buy Tether with Skrill</strong> on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> platform. CoinCannon provides full anonymity for all customers and does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. Skrill is quickly becoming one of the most popular payment platforms in the world and that is for good reason. For the most part, Skrill offers very low transaction fees and sometimes zero fees. On top of that, it has also managed to maintain a positive reputation when it comes to security. Fortunately, CoinCannon provides services for Skrill users. In today’s article, we will go over everything you need to buy Tether with Skrill.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-skrill-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Skrill to PayPal</a> on CoinCannon</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Tether with Skrill?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need an active and verified Skrill account with sufficient funds. Furthermore, you will need a crypto wallet for the Tether USDT. As for CoinCannon platform, all you need to provide is your correct crypto wallet address and an e-mail address. Bear in mind that it is not mandatory to sign up on CoinCannon but there are benefits for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Skrill?</strong></h2>



<p>Skrill is a payment system based in London. It started out back in 2001 with focus on money transfers. However, soon the payment system expanded services into e-commerce and online purchases.</p>



<p>However, what Skrill offers as a payment system is a safe and cheap way of transferring funds. The anti-fraud system is in fact a successful way to provide security for the users. This is for the most part to prevent data theft and stay on top of all suspicious activity. Currently, Skrill is active is the United States which maintains some of the highest security standards for payment systems.</p>



<p>As for convenience, there are two key factors in favor of Skrill. First, users can link their bank account to the payment system and take advantage of easy payments. Second, having an e-wallet ensures that transactions are quick, cheap and smooth. All transactions within the e-wallet have very low fees and are done instantly.</p>



<p>You can also <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-skrill-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange Skrill to PayPal</a> with the lowest fees on CoinCannon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Buy Tether with Skrill?</strong></h2>



<p>Tether USDT is currently the most popular stablecoin in the world. The value of USDT is pegged to the US dollar which means that it will always be worth $1. What it does is a cryptocurrency with a stable value to store investor’s funds. In that case, the investors can hold their capital in form of Tether USDT without worrying about the volatility.</p>



<p>However, volatility is not the only reason to buy Tether USDT. It is very quick and cheap to buy cryptocurrencies with Tether USDT. The transaction fees are next to nothing and it basically takes a few seconds to buy crypto with Tether. In general, Tether USDT has lots of utility whether you’re a crypto trader, Forex trader or a long-term holder.</p>



<p>Furthermore, numerous merchants have started accepting Tether payments in the past few years. Whether in online stores or physical shops, you can use Tether USDT payments. In that regard, having Tether in your crypto wallet is basically as good as cash in 2022.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon to the Moon!</strong></h2>



<p>Every exchange platform must maintain three important characteristics. Anonymity, affordability and reliability. We pride ourselves as a professional platform that offers all three.</p>



<p>For anonymity, CoinCannon requires no KYC or even a sign up process. The best way to protect your information is to not share them with anyone. And for that, we respect our customers and do not ask for their personal info.</p>



<p>As for affordability, CoinCannon utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. By doing so, we have managed to stay on top of the ranks on websites such as Bestchange and OkChanger.</p>



<p>Lastly, reliability is ensured for our customers with 24/7 online support. In case anything goes wrong, you will have our immediate support until the issue is resolved.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Buy Tether with Skrill?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Enter the Homepage on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">HiEx</a><a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">c</a><a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">hange</a>. Select Skrill USD on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li><li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your Tether TRC20 wallet address and email. Phone number is optional.</li><li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li><li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li><li>On this step, please spend the time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li><li>Transfer your Skrill USD to the CoinCannon Skrill address that is provided for you.</li><li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>All Good!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether USDT to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-skrill/">Buy Tether with Skrill – USDT Buying Guide</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-skrill/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
