<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>PayPal Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/paypal/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 07:23:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Free Virtual Debit Card &#124; No KYC</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/virtual-debit-card/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/virtual-debit-card/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 09:13:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Digital Currencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[debit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[debit card]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mastercard]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[visa]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=8720</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you&#8217;re reading this blog post, it means that you need to purchase something online or register somewhere but don&#8217;t have a debit card to use. Obviously, a virtual debit card is the answer right? No! a virtual debit card is not necessarily the best solution for your needs simply because you will have to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/virtual-debit-card/">Free Virtual Debit Card | No KYC</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you&#8217;re reading this blog post, it means that you need to purchase something online or register somewhere but don&#8217;t have a debit card to use. Obviously, a virtual debit card is the answer right? No! a virtual debit card is not necessarily the best solution for your needs simply because you will have to pay a lot more fees. let&#8217;s face it, there is no such thing as a free debit card. Instead, you will have have to pay a whole lot of extra fees for a virtual debit card that is a pain in the bottom area! On top of that, you have to fill out forms, wait for confirmation, give out all your personal information and worry about the card declining! </p>



<p>So what if I told you that there&#8217;s a totally better option? With zero extra fees, and it comes instantly with no sign up, how about that? </p>



<p><strong>With CoinCannon Online Payments, you can pay with 100+ currencies including crypto and e-currencies, and CoinCannon will use its own debit card to pay for you! </strong></p>



<p>By doing this, you can instantly pay for your purchase without paying any extra fees. You will have PayPal, Visa card and MasterCard payments anywhere on the vast expanse of web, anytime you need! </p>



<p>Ready to go? Click on the button below and get started!</p>



<p></p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-1 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button has-custom-width wp-block-button__width-100 is-style-outline is-style-outline--1"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-white-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-background-color has-text-color has-background has-link-color wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/En/solutions/online-payment?cur_from=USDTTRC20"><mark style="background-color:#0693e3" class="has-inline-color has-white-color">G</mark>et Your Virtual Debit Card</a></div>
</div>



<p></p>



<p>Need more information? Continue reading!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-use-a-virtual-debit-card">Why use a virtual debit card?</h2>



<p>Depending on where you live and your life choices 🙂  you might not have a debit card! in that case, there comes a time where you need to purchase something online and they only take a handful of debit cards for payment. having a virtual debit card let&#8217;s you bypass all that regulatory shenanigan but at a cost! </p>



<p>there&#8217;s also another scenario in which you find yourself in need of a free debit card! And that&#8217;s when you&#8217;re going to register on a website or application and they ask for your card info! In such cases of presumptuous capitalist demand, do not give them what they ask for! I mean, if a presumably &#8220;free&#8221; website is asking for your debit card information, it will only mean that at some point, their customer journey is designed to bill you and take money (trust me, I&#8217;ve been in marketing for years!).</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="Buy Everything Using Only Crypto! Meet Online Payments" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/XElLN5HP7fg?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-not-use-a-prepaid-debit-card">Why Not Use a Prepaid Debit Card?</h2>



<p>And now, you&#8217;re looking for a virtual debit card to get around the problem. But here&#8217;s a list of new problems that you&#8217;ll have:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Having to pay activation fee, purchase fee, exchange rate fee, third party markup fee!</li>



<li>A long process of purchasing your prepaid debit card</li>



<li>Sharing your personal information for a so called &#8220;free debit card&#8221;</li>



<li>Risking the purchase of a card that might not work! </li>



<li>Having to sign up on a sketchy website and believe me, they will send you promotional emails!</li>
</ul>



<p>After all, a virtual debit card is not exactly legit, is it?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-jolixo-has-to-offer">What CoinCannon has to Offer</h2>



<p>A better solution! here&#8217;s how it works:</p>



<p>You open <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/en">jolixo</a>, choose the currency you want to pay with</p>



<figure class="wp-block-gallery has-nested-images columns-default is-cropped wp-block-gallery-2 is-layout-flex wp-block-gallery-is-layout-flex">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="1024" height="275" data-id="8721" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/virtual-debit-card-Free-Debit-Card-step-1-1024x275.png" alt="virtual debit card - free debit card " class="wp-image-8721" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/virtual-debit-card-Free-Debit-Card-step-1-1024x275.png 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/virtual-debit-card-Free-Debit-Card-step-1-300x81.png 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/virtual-debit-card-Free-Debit-Card-step-1-768x206.png 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/virtual-debit-card-Free-Debit-Card-step-1-1536x413.png 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/virtual-debit-card-Free-Debit-Card-step-1.png 1895w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>
</figure>



<p>Then, select which debit card you need. we have Visa, MasterCard and PayPal. then, click on &#8220;next&#8221; to head to the second step.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><img decoding="async" width="956" height="654" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/Virtual-debit-card-free-dibit-card-step-2.png" alt="virtual debit card - free debit card " class="wp-image-8722" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/Virtual-debit-card-free-dibit-card-step-2.png 956w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/Virtual-debit-card-free-dibit-card-step-2-300x205.png 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/Virtual-debit-card-free-dibit-card-step-2-768x525.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 956px) 100vw, 956px" /></figure></div>


<p>On the second step, share the purchase link, username and password for the account + any additional info. CoinCannon will automatically delete your account information after your transaction is done. However, make sure to change your password later.</p>



<p>click on &#8220;next&#8221; one more time to head to the third step. Here, you get a final chance to review your order. </p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><img decoding="async" width="600" height="792" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/virtual-debit-card-free-debit-card-step-3.png" alt="virtual debit card - free debit card " class="wp-image-8723" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/virtual-debit-card-free-debit-card-step-3.png 600w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/virtual-debit-card-free-debit-card-step-3-227x300.png 227w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></figure></div>


<p>Remember, signing up on CoinCannon is not mandatory. But, CoinCannon offers various rewards for those who sign up! You will have discount codes, cashback and affiliate payments as a CoinCannon member. Ready to finish? head to the final step.</p>



<p>On the final step, you will need to make your payment. as you can see below, the CoinCannon wallet address is available to you. the payment settlement is automatic. As soon as you send your Payment, the transaction status will change to &#8220;processing&#8221;.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="603" height="817" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/virtual-debit-card-free-debit-card-step-4.png" alt="prepaid debit card  " class="wp-image-8724" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/virtual-debit-card-free-debit-card-step-4.png 603w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/virtual-debit-card-free-debit-card-step-4-221x300.png 221w" sizes="(max-width: 603px) 100vw, 603px" /></figure></div>


<p>Send us your chosen currency and our team will make the payment on your behalf Instantly. </p>



<p><strong>With that, you will have your online payment in just a few minutes. No need to sign up, no need to pay ANY extra fees.</strong></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-faq">FAQ</h2>



<p><strong>How much does a virtual debit card cost on CoinCannon?</strong></p>



<p>CoinCannon offers a completely free virtual debit card for all customer.</p>



<p><strong>How do I apply for a virtual debit card?</strong></p>



<p>CoinCannon does not require an application process. All you need for this service is to share an email address.</p>



<p><strong>How can I pay for my virtual debit card?</strong></p>



<p>You will have the ability to pay with USDT, BTC, ETH and 100+ currencies for your virtual debit card.</p>



<p><strong>What can I spend my funds in my virtual debit card?</strong></p>



<p>Absolutely everything! there is no limit at all! you can pay for an invoice, buy stuff off Amazon, charge your accounts online or pay for your kid&#8217;s school! the sky is the limit.</p>



<p><strong>Where can I see the transaction history?</strong></p>



<p>You can always check your user dashboard on CoinCannon or enter your track ID to see the history.</p>



<p><strong>Can I choose Visa or MasterCard as my virtual debit card?</strong></p>



<p>Yes, you will have the option to choose between Visa, MasterCard and also PayPal!</p>



<p><strong>Can I use CoinCannon virtual debit card in another country?</strong></p>



<p>Yes, you can use this service on CoinCannon wherever you are in the world!</p>



<p></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/virtual-debit-card/">Free Virtual Debit Card | No KYC</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/virtual-debit-card/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Instant Credit Card for Online Shopping [No KYC]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/credit-card-for-online-shopping/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/credit-card-for-online-shopping/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 08:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[credit card]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Master Card]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prepaid Mastercard]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prepaid paypal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prepiad visa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Visa Card]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=8708</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What if I told you that you don&#8217;t need a credit card for online shopping? All you need is someone with a credit card to pay for you right? then, CoinCannon does the work for you!At this point, you might think that you want a virtual prepaid credit card for online shopping but that&#8217;s complicated [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/credit-card-for-online-shopping/">Instant Credit Card for Online Shopping [No KYC]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>What if I told you that you don&#8217;t need a credit card for online shopping? All you need is someone with a credit card to pay for you right? then, CoinCannon does the work for you!<br>At this point, you might think that you want a virtual prepaid credit card for online shopping but that&#8217;s complicated too. <strong>The alternative we offer is instant, anonymous and comes with much lower rates than a prepaid card</strong>. Here&#8217;s how it works.</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>You want to buy something online that requires a credit card for online shopping.</li>



<li>You come to CoinCannon, send whatever currency you have like Tether USDT, Bitcoin or 100+ different currencies. Then you send us the link for your online shopping.</li>



<li>CoinCannon will go to the link and make the payment for you and send you the payment confirmation.</li>
</ul>



<p>Oh and by the way, it&#8217;s instant, with no KYC and comes with 24/7 support!</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-2 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button"><a class="wp-block-button__link wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/En/solutions/online-payment?cur_from=USDTTRC20&amp;cur_to=PPUSDI">Start Now!</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-limitless-virtual-credit-card">The Limitless Virtual Credit Card </h2>



<p>It&#8217;s a pain in the bottom I tell ya! having to buy virtual credit card, going through all the different websites to find the best one, filling out the forms, paying all the extra money for a card you can only use once. Not to mention all the time you waste on purchasing a card for purchasing another thing on the internet! ain&#8217;t nobody got time for that! </p>



<p>Here&#8217;s what we do instead, we can be your cool friend who already has a credit card. All you gotta do is pay your buddy CoinCannon however you like and we&#8217;ll handle the payment stuff like a champ! </p>



<p>That way, you don&#8217;t have to waste time or money and the capitalism gods will be happy! </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-not-to-apply-for-an-online-credit-card-for-shopping">How not to Apply for an Online Credit Card for Shopping</h2>



<p>Honestly, purchasing a virtual credit card is a big hassle for all of us. If you live in a country where payments processors like PayPal, Visa or MasterCard do not provide services, then the trouble gets bigger! </p>



<p>But thanks to our frightening genius, your online purchases will have no limits and shall remain liberated from all the bounds of regulatory nightmare that consumes our ever-expanding financial limbo scattered around the vast expanse of the interweb! (the author has studied literature and wanted to showcase his poetic abilities with this paragraph!) </p>



<p>Whether you&#8217;re a freelancer or representing a business, having an quick and easy alternative for the expensive online credit card for shopping will give you a boost in performance. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-credit-card-fees-vs-jolixo-fees">Credit Card Fees Vs. CoinCannon Fees</h2>



<p>Here&#8217;s a quick look at the associated fees for a prepaid visa card:</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Activation Fee</strong> – Typically $3 to $10.</li>



<li><strong>Purchase Fee</strong> – Some retailers charge an extra fee, usually around $5 to $15.</li>



<li><strong>Exchange Rate Fees</strong> – If you&#8217;re buying it with crypto or a foreign currency, you might pay an extra 1-5%.</li>



<li><strong>Third-Party Markup</strong> – If you’re buying from a reseller, they may charge an additional percentage.</li>
</ol>



<p>If you’re buying from an official provider like Vanilla Visa or a bank, you might just pay the face value ($1,000) plus a small fee. If you&#8217;re getting it from a crypto exchange or P2P seller, expect to pay more, sometimes up to <strong>5-15% extra</strong>.</p>



<p>Considering the fees mentioned above, when utilizing CoinCannon, you will ONLY pay a 1% to 5% exchange fee and there will be <strong>no extra charge at all</strong>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-do-i-need-to-purchase-a-prepaid-card">What do I Need to Purchase a Prepaid Card?</h2>



<p>When purchasing a credit card for online shopping, you will have to sign up on the retailer&#8217;s website and disclose lots and lots of your personal information. mind you, the process can take days! As mentioned before, there are many countries in which online credit cards or even prepaid cards do not provide services. Other than that, paying for the credit card does also require a specific currency. In that regard, you might have to exchange what you already have beforehand and pay for yet another exchange fee.</p>



<p>By using CoinCannon, you will not share any personal information and basically do not need anything to make the purchase. CoinCannon supports 100+ currencies for payment and will instantly make your purchase. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-24-7-online-support">24/7 Online Support</h2>



<p>In order to make sure everything goes as planned, CoinCannon provides online support available all day, everyday. So get started now and Enjoy Online Payments like never before!</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/credit-card-for-online-shopping/">Instant Credit Card for Online Shopping [No KYC]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/credit-card-for-online-shopping/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Discount on Discount &#8211; Up to 10% Discount on Online Payments during Black Friday!</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/discount-on-discount-up-to-10-discount-on-online-payments-during-black-friday/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/discount-on-discount-up-to-10-discount-on-online-payments-during-black-friday/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Leyli Mamikhani]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 08:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CoinCannon Special]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mastercard]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Payment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payment Solution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VisaCard]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=8684</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The CoinCannon team, as a leading provider of online payment solutions, is honored to announce an exciting campaign for the upcoming shopping season. Running from Black Friday, November 29, 2024, to Cyber Monday, December 2, 2024, the campaign offers users a 10% discount, up to $10, on payments made through its Online Payment service.   Black [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/discount-on-discount-up-to-10-discount-on-online-payments-during-black-friday/">Discount on Discount &#8211; Up to 10% Discount on Online Payments during Black Friday!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The CoinCannon team, as a leading provider of online payment solutions, is honored to announce an exciting campaign for the upcoming shopping season. Running from Black Friday, November 29, 2024, to Cyber Monday, December 2, 2024, the campaign offers users a <strong>10% discount, up to $10</strong>, on payments made through its<strong> <a href="https://hi.exchange/En/solutions/payment-gate">Online Payment service</a></strong>.  </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-black-friday-and-cyber-monday-a-global-shopping-phenomenon-nbsp-nbsp">Black Friday and Cyber Monday: A Global Shopping Phenomenon&nbsp;&nbsp;</h2>



<p>Black Friday and Cyber Monday mark the busiest shopping days of the year, where retailers and service providers offer incredible deals. While consumers rush to grab discounts on all types of services or products, <em>CoinCannon is bringing this festive spirit to online payments, making it easier and more affordable for users to complete essential transactions.&nbsp;&nbsp;</em></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-jolixo-online-payment-simplifying-transactions-worldwide-nbsp-nbsp">CoinCannon Online Payment: Simplifying Transactions Worldwide&nbsp;&nbsp;</h2>



<p>jolixo’s Online Payment service has been designed for users in countries like Russia, Iran, etc where accessing trusted international payment methods such as PayPal, Visa, or MasterCard can be difficult or even countries such as India, Malta or Hungary where security and privacy of online payments have a crucial rule.</p>



<p>By enabling payments with cryptocurrencies and handling the conversion process, CoinCannon eliminates the need for complex account setups or identity verifications.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<p><strong>How It Works:&nbsp;&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>1. Users pay with their preferred cryptocurrency.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<p>2. They select a payment method (Visa, MasterCard, or PayPal).&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<p>3. CoinCannon converts the payment and completes the transaction on their behalf.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<p>This service is fast, secure, and designed to make international payments accessible to everyone, regardless of regional restrictions.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-campaign-details-nbsp-nbsp">Campaign Details&nbsp;&nbsp;</h2>



<p>jolixo’s Black Friday to Cyber Monday campaign provides customers with a 10% discount, up to $10, on payments made through the Online Payment service.<strong><em>&nbsp;</em></strong></p>



<p><strong><em>This means Discount on Discount!!: Get CoinCannon’s Black Friday discount on usual Black Friday&#8217;s Discounts!!</em></strong></p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li> Start Date: November 29, 2024 (Black Friday).  </li>



<li> End Date: December 2, 2024 (Cyber Monday).  </li>
</ul>



<p>The campaign is open to both individuals and businesses, making it a valuable opportunity to save on essential transactions.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-who-should-take-advantage-of-this-campaign-nbsp-nbsp">Who Should Take Advantage of This Campaign?&nbsp;&nbsp;</h2>



<p>jolixo’s Black Friday campaign is perfect for:&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<p><strong>Personal Users:&nbsp;&nbsp;</strong></p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li> Gamers: Pay for premium accounts, in-game purchases, and subscriptions.  </li>



<li> Freelancers: Manage payments for tools, software, or services easily.  </li>



<li> Travelers: Book flights, accommodations, and tours effortlessly.  </li>



<li> Students: Pay tuition fees or purchase educational materials.  </li>



<li> Entertainment Enthusiasts: Access streaming, gaming, and betting platforms.  </li>
</ul>



<p><strong>Businesses:&nbsp;&nbsp;</strong></p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li> Hosting Services: Simplify hosting and VPS payments.  </li>



<li> Invoice Payments: Pay vendors smoothly and securely.  </li>



<li> Payroll Management: Send employee salaries globally without barriers.  </li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-this-campaign-matters-nbsp-nbsp">Why This Campaign Matters&nbsp;&nbsp;</h2>



<p>jolixo’s Black Friday to Cyber Monday campaign goes beyond just offering discounts. It provides a solution for users in restricted regions to enjoy the convenience of international payment methods while saving money.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<p>With CoinCannon, customers can avoid:&nbsp;<br></p>



<p>✅Complicated account setups.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<p>✅Long-lasting verification processes.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<p>✅Extra transaction fees associated with funding accounts.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<p>This <strong>Black Friday To Cyber Monday</strong>, CoinCannon invites individuals and businesses to experience a seamless and cost effective way to manage their online payments.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<p>Don’t miss out on this limited time offer! Visit CoinCannon from November 29 to December 2, 2024, and enjoy secure, fast, and discounted transactions on <a href="https://hi.exchange/En/solutions/payment-gate">Online Payment Service</a>.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/discount-on-discount-up-to-10-discount-on-online-payments-during-black-friday/">Discount on Discount &#8211; Up to 10% Discount on Online Payments during Black Friday!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/discount-on-discount-up-to-10-discount-on-online-payments-during-black-friday/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Online Payment: A Simple Payment Solution</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/online-payment-a-simple-payment-solution/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/online-payment-a-simple-payment-solution/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Leyli Mamikhani]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 08:55:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[CoinCannon Special]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mastercard]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Payment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payment Solution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VisaCard]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=8680</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In today’s interconnected world, online payments are the heart of global commerce. However, for many users in countries like Russia, Iran, Venezuela, and Cuba, accessing trusted international payment gateways such as PayPal, Visa, and MasterCard remains a significant challenge. These obstacles, often caused by laws, currency restrictions, or regional rules, leave individuals and businesses struggling [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/online-payment-a-simple-payment-solution/">Online Payment: A Simple Payment Solution</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In today’s interconnected world, online payments are the heart of global commerce. However, for many users in countries like Russia, Iran, Venezuela, and Cuba, accessing trusted international payment gateways such as PayPal, Visa, and MasterCard remains a significant challenge. These obstacles, often caused by laws, currency restrictions, or regional rules, leave individuals and businesses struggling to complete essential online transactions.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<p>Recognizing these difficulties, CoinCannon offers an innovative solution: <a href="https://hi.exchange/En/solutions/online-payment">Online Payment</a>, a service that allows users to avoid traditional barriers and complete payments quickly, securely, and without the need for challenging account setups or verifications.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-nbsp-what-is-online-payment-nbsp-nbsp">&nbsp;What Is Online Payment?&nbsp;&nbsp;</h2>



<p>Online payment refers to the process of transferring money digitally to pay for goods, services, or subscriptions. From PayPal and Visa to cryptocurrencies and Perfect Money, online payment methods&nbsp; respond&nbsp; to different needs like:&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Visa and MasterCard:</strong> Ideal for global shoppers, travelers, and businesses.  </li>



<li><strong>PayPal: </strong>A popular choice for freelancers and gamers due to its versatility.  </li>



<li><strong>Cryptocurrencies: </strong>Favored by privacy-focused users and tech-savvy individuals.  </li>



<li><strong>Perfect Money:</strong> Frequently used in hosting, VPS services, and entertainment platforms.  </li>
</ul>



<p>While these payment methods are powerful, accessing and managing them can be difficult—especially in restricted regions. This is where CoinCannon comes in.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-nbsp-how-does-jolixo-online-payment-work-nbsp-nbsp">&nbsp;How Does CoinCannon Online Payment Work?&nbsp;&nbsp;</h2>



<p>CoinCannon simplified online payments with its shortcut service, enabling users to make payments using cryptocurrencies while CoinCannon takes care of the rest.</p>



<p>This means users no longer need to have an existing account or go through the effort of creating a new one, funding it (and paying transaction fees in the process!), and then finally making their payment. CoinCannon Online Payment simplifies this challenging process, saving both time and effort. Here’s how it works:</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-step-1-you-can-pay-with-cryptocurrency-nbsp"><strong>Step 1: You Can Pay with Cryptocurrency</strong>&nbsp;</h3>



<p>Begin by selecting your preferred cryptocurrency, There is a wide variety of cryptocurrencies you can choose.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-step-2-choose-the-payment-method"><strong>Step 2: Choose the Payment Method</strong></h3>



<p>Select your preferred payment method, such as Visa Card, MasterCard, or PayPal. Once you’ve made your choice, provide us with the necessary link and details of your order, and we’ll take care of the payment for you.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-step-3-jolixo-converts-the-payment"><strong>Step 3: CoinCannon Converts the Payment</strong></h3>



<p>The platform processes the payment and converts it into the required format.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-step-4-payment-is-completed-via-preferred-method"><strong>Step 4: Payment Is Completed via Preferred Method</strong></h3>



<p>&nbsp;CoinCannon delivers the payment using Visa, MasterCard or PayPal —no account setup required.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<p>This simple procedure removes all barriers, making online payments possible to everyone, no matter their location or restrictions.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-nbsp-how-online-payment-helps-you-as-a-payment-solution-nbsp-nbsp">&nbsp;How Online Payment Helps You As A Payment Solution&nbsp;&nbsp;</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Hiex-Inside-Article-design-1024x423.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-8682" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Hiex-Inside-Article-design-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Hiex-Inside-Article-design-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Hiex-Inside-Article-design-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Hiex-Inside-Article-design-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Hiex-Inside-Article-design.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>jolixo’s Online Payment service is designed to handle key user issues such as:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Global Accessibility:</strong> Perfect for users in restricted regions who cannot access traditional payment methods.  </li>



<li><strong>No Account Setup Required:</strong> Skip the challenges of creating and verifying accounts on platforms like PayPal.  </li>



<li><strong>Versatile Options:</strong> Choose from a range of supported payment methods to suit your needs.  </li>



<li><strong>Fast and Secure: </strong>Payments are handled quickly, with secure systems to protect your funds.  </li>



<li><strong>No Identity Verification:</strong> Enjoy the freedom to pay without the burden of identity checks or document submissions.  </li>



<li><strong>No KYC Needed.</strong></li>



<li><strong>Skip Additional Fees: </strong>When you charge an account before making a payment, you often pay extra transaction fees. However, you can avoid these extra fees and save money by using CoinCannon&#8217;s direct payment method.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-nbsp-what-payment-methods-are-supported-nbsp-nbsp">&nbsp;What Payment Methods Are Supported?&nbsp;&nbsp;</h2>



<p>CoinCannon offers a large selection of payment options to provide all users flexibility:&nbsp;</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Visa Card  </li>



<li>MasterCard  </li>



<li>PayPal   </li>
</ul>



<p>With this diverse range, CoinCannon caters to personal and professional use cases, from individual transactions to large-scale business payments.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-nbsp-who-is-this-service-designed-for-nbsp-nbsp">&nbsp;Who Is This Service Designed For?&nbsp;&nbsp;</h2>



<p>jolixo’s Online Payment service is designed for a wide range of audience:&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-nbsp-personal-users">&nbsp;Personal Users:</h3>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Gamers: </strong>Pay for subscriptions, in-game purchases, and premium accounts.  </li>



<li><strong>Freelancers: </strong>Handle payments for tools, software, or client services effortlessly.  </li>



<li><strong>Entertainment Enthusiasts: </strong>Access platforms like betting, streaming, and gaming sites without restrictions.  </li>



<li><strong>Travelers:</strong> Manage bookings, tours, and accommodations conveniently.  </li>



<li><strong>Students: </strong>Pay tuition, purchase educational materials, or access learning tools.  </li>
</ul>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-nbsp-businesses-nbsp">&nbsp;Businesses:&nbsp;</h3>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Hosting and VPS Services:</strong> Manage hosting fees and virtual server payments seamlessly.  </li>



<li><strong>Invoice Payments:</strong> Pay vendor invoices quickly using cryptocurrencies.  </li>



<li><strong>Payroll Management:</strong> Ensure smooth salary payments to employees worldwide.  </li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-nbsp-why-jolixo-online-payment-nbsp-nbsp">&nbsp;Why CoinCannon Online Payment?&nbsp;&nbsp;</h2>



<p>jolixo’s Online Payment service is a reliable and versatile solution, especially for users in restricted regions who face barriers in accessing international payment platforms. By removing the need for account creation, verification, or funding, the service provides a truly simple experience. It supports a wide range of popular payment methods, ensuring compatibility with various user needs.</p>



<p>With effortless cryptocurrency integration, CoinCannon allows users to convert their crypto payments into traditional payment methods, such as Visa, MasterCard, or PayPal, ensuring smooth and efficient transactions. The platform emphasizes security and privacy, employing advanced protocols to protect your payments. Additionally, CoinCannon offers special features such as crypto exchange and digital payment solutions, making it an ideal choice for all your online payment needs.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-nbsp-conclusion-nbsp-nbsp">&nbsp;Conclusion&nbsp;&nbsp;</h2>



<p><a href="https://hi.exchange/En/solutions/online-payment">jolixo’s Online Payment</a> service offers a simple solution to the challenges of modern online transactions. Whether you’re an individual or a business, CoinCannon simplifies payments, avoiding restrictions and removing unnecessary steps.  </p>



<p>Say goodbye to the headaches of online payments—choose CoinCannon today and enjoy secure, fast, and effortless transactions!&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/online-payment-a-simple-payment-solution/">Online Payment: A Simple Payment Solution</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/online-payment-a-simple-payment-solution/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Payeer USD to PayPal [2024 Update]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/how-exchange-payeer-usd-to-paypal/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/how-exchange-payeer-usd-to-paypal/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 13:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[e-currency to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6043</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you looking to exchange Payeer USD to PayPal effortlessly?CoinCannon is here to help!With 24/7 online support and no hidden fees, CoinCannon makes swapping your digital funds quick and easy.In today&#8217;s digital world, relying on a single payment system just isn&#8217;t practical. We often need to use multiple services to meet various needs, each offering [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/how-exchange-payeer-usd-to-paypal/">How to Exchange Payeer USD to PayPal [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Are you looking to exchange Payeer USD to PayPal effortlessly?<br>CoinCannon is here to help!<br>With 24/7 online support and no hidden fees, CoinCannon makes swapping your digital funds quick and easy.<br>In today&#8217;s digital world, relying on a single payment system just isn&#8217;t practical. We often need to use multiple services to meet various needs, each offering unique benefits. However, transferring funds between different wallets can be a real pain and can cost you a pretty penny.Fortunately, CoinCannon offers a fantastic solution to this problem. </p>



<p>In this article, we’ll walk you through the simple steps to <a href="https://hi.exchange/services/payeer-to-paypal-exchange">exchange Payeer USD to PayPal </a>without any hassle and zero hidden fees.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://hi.exchange/En/services/payeer-to-paypal-exchange?cur_from=PRUSD&amp;cur_to=PPUSD"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="512" height="228" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/payeer-to-paypal.png" alt="exchange payeer usd to paypal - Payeer to PayPal " class="wp-image-8716" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/payeer-to-paypal.png 512w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/payeer-to-paypal-300x134.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 512px) 100vw, 512px" /></a></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-do-i-need-to-exchange-payeer-usd-to-paypal"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Payeer USD to PayPal?</strong></h2>



<p>For this transaction, you will be sending Payeer USD and Receiving PayPal in your desired currency. Naturally, you will need verified and active accounts for both Payeer and PayPal. Make sure that the exchange amount does not exceed your withdrawal and deposit limits on both accounts. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-exchanging-payeer-usd-for-paypal-2024-new-rules-and-updates"><strong>Exchanging Payeer USD for PayPal: 2024 New Rules and Updates</strong></h2>



<p>In 2024, there have been several updates and new rules that might affect the process of exchanging Payeer USD to PayPal. Here are the key points you need to know:</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>PayPal Policy Updates</strong>:
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Purchase Protection Program</strong>: Amendments to PayPal&#8217;s Purchase Protection Program became effective on May 20, 2024. These changes could impact how disputes and claims are handled when using PayPal.</li>



<li><strong>Charities and Online Card Payment Services</strong>: There have been updates to the terms and conditions for PayPal Confirmed Charities and Online Card Payment Services, also effective from May 20, 2024.</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li><strong>IRS Reporting Requirements</strong>:
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Starting January 1, 2024, the IRS has implemented new reporting requirements for payments received for goods and services. The reporting threshold has been lowered to $600 USD for the 2024 tax season, down from the previous threshold of $20,000 USD and 200 transactions. This means that if you receive $600 USD or more in payments through PayPal, it will be reported to the IRS.</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li><strong>Fee Structure Changes</strong>:
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Effective April 17, 2024, PayPal has updated its fee structure. For example, the fees for Advanced Credit and Debit Card transactions have been revised. This could affect the overall cost of transactions when exchanging funds between Payeer and PayPal.</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li><strong>Exchange Rates and Best Practices</strong>:
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>When exchanging Payeer USD to PayPal USD, it&#8217;s important to consider the exchange rates offered by different exchangers. Websites like BestChange.com provide a list of exchangers with the best rates at the top, along with reviews and reserves to help you make an informed decision.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ol>



<p>By staying informed about these updates and following best practices, you can ensure a smooth and cost-effective exchange process between Payeer USD and PayPal in 2024.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-exchange-payeer-usd-to-paypal"><strong>How to Exchange Payeer USD to PayPal?</strong></h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-1-1024x423.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-8381" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-1-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-1-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-1-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-1-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-1-2048x846.jpg 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Select Payeer from the box on the left and PayPal on the right.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-2-1024x423.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-8379" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-2-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-2-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-2-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-2-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-2-2048x846.jpg 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Enter the Payeer amount you want to exchange to PayPal and behold the most competitive exchange rates!</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-2-1-1024x423.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-8380" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-2-1-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-2-1-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-2-1-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-2-1-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-2-1-2048x846.jpg 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Before clicking &#8220;Next&#8221;, please read the instructions and &#8220;PayPal fees guide&#8221; carefully.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-4-1024x423.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-8382" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-4-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-4-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-4-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-4-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-4-2048x846.jpg 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>&nbsp;By clicking “Next” and enter your PayPal details and your email address. Please note that we contact you using the email address you provide therefore it&#8217;s important that you enter a valid email address.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-5-1024x423.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-8383" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-5-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-5-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-5-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-5-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-5-2048x846.jpg 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Once again, press Next, and you are taken to the next level where you are asked to review your order. Please click on Review and Check. Read and agree to the terms and AML policy.</li>



<li>By clicking on &#8220;Confirm&#8221; you are taken to the 4th and last step where you have to pay your order.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-6-1024x423.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-8384" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-6-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-6-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-6-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-6-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-6-2048x846.jpg 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Make sure to copy your order’s track ID and then click on the “Confirm Payment” button. You will be taken to Payeer payment gateway where you can pay your order.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-7-1024x423.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-8385" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-7-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-7-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-7-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-7-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/How-to-Exchange-Payeer-to-PayPal-7-2048x846.jpg 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Once you completed the payment, you will be redirected to CoinCannon and will see a message confirming your payment.</li>



<li>Now just sit back and enjoy the money that soon will be in your PayPal account.</li>
</ul>



<p><strong>Success!</strong></p>



<p>The Exchange process will start as soon as  you finish the steps above, your order will be checked and the PayPal will be send to your account.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-viva-la-jolixo"><strong>Viva La CoinCannon!</strong></h2>



<p>Of course, in order to <a href="https://hi.exchange/services/payeer-to-paypal-exchange">exchange Payeer to PayPal</a>, you will first need a reliable exchange platform. For that, CoinCannon is one of the best options out there.</p>



<p>Every exchange platform must maintain three important characteristics. Anonymity, affordability and reliability. We pride ourselves as a professional platform that offers all three.</p>



<p>For anonymity, CoinCannon requires no KYC or even a sign up process. The best way to protect your information is to not share them with anyone. And for that, we respect our customers and do not ask for their personal info.</p>



<p>As for affordability, CoinCannon utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. By doing so, we have managed to stay on top of the ranks on websites such as Bestchange and OkChanger.</p>



<p><a href="/">jolixo</a> usually takes care of your transaction in 1 hour but in some cases it might take up to 24 hours to complete your order. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/how-exchange-payeer-usd-to-paypal/">How to Exchange Payeer USD to PayPal [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/how-exchange-payeer-usd-to-paypal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Solana with PayPal [Best Exchange Rates]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-paypal/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-paypal/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 08:37:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4285</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you are looking to buy Solana with PayPal, this article will provide a step-by-step guide. Solana took the market by storm in 2020 as an Ethereum competitor. In terms of scalability it is one of the fastest blockchain networks. The network has massive institutional investors hooked in as a DeFi platform and SOL as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-paypal/">How to Buy Solana with PayPal [Best Exchange Rates]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you are looking to buy Solana with PayPal, this article will provide a step-by-step guide. Solana took the market by storm in 2020 as an Ethereum competitor. In terms of scalability it is one of the fastest blockchain networks. The network has massive institutional investors hooked in as a DeFi platform and SOL as the native token is incredibly successful. You can buy Solana with PayPal seamlessly and anonymously on CoinCannon.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>To get started, go to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> platform to buy Solana with PayPal.</p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-solana"><strong>What is Solana?</strong></h2>



<p>In short, Solana is a blockchain platform for decentralized applications (DApps). The network utilizes Proof of Stake consensus algorithm. However, in a world full of PoS blockchain networks, Solana has managed to achieve some impressive figures. The network can support up to 50,000 transactions per second (TPS) and requires 400 milliseconds to build a block. With the quickly increasing number of validators currently at 1,061, the network is one of the fastest out there.</p>



<p>SOL is currently the 4<sup>th</sup> cryptocurrency with an astonishing $67+ billion market cap. As of November 2021, Solana has had almost 10000% growth in one year.</p>



<p>Continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-solana/">What is Solana</a>” to learn everything about the network.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-buy-with-paypal"><strong>Buy with PayPal</strong></h2>



<p>PayPal is at this point the number one financial platform for digital currencies. In terms of security of your assets, they provide great services. As compared with a bank, keeping money in PayPal account can save you some tax payments in the future. It is widely accepted as a payment method and simply makes a lot of sense. Having enjoyed incredible returns on your SOL investment, you can easily transfer the asset to your PayPal account.</p>



<p>Furthermore, as of 2021, 392 million people have PayPal accounts. In terms of popularity, PayPal is by far the best.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-buy-solana-with-paypal-on-jolixo"><strong>Why Buy Solana with PayPal on CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p>An ideal exchange platform must have three primary characteristics. Privacy, good exchange rates and reliability. CoinCannon has worked hard to provide all three for the customers.</p>



<p>For privacy, the safest way to protect customer information is not asking for it at all. This might be a challenge in many aspects yet anonymity is our utmost priority. Therefore, CoinCannon requires no KYC or even a sign up process.</p>



<p>When it comes to exchange rates, our strategy is to be as competitive as possible. CoinCannon utilizes an automated system to determine the best possible exchange rates at any moment. But you don’t have to take our word for it. You can visit ranking websites such as Bestchange and OkChanger to see our rank for yourself.</p>



<p>Lastly, reliability does not come easy. In order to provide the best exchange services, we offer real 24/7 customer support.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-buy-solana-with-paypal-step-by-step-guide"><strong>Buy Solana with PayPal Step-by-Step Guide</strong></h2>



<p>Here are the five easy steps to make the purchase:</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the homepage first, then select PayPal and Solana from the currency pairs in the first step. enter the amount you want to exchange, after that the amount of SOL you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>



<li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your Solana wallet details, email, and phone number.</li>



<li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li>Complete the captcha test and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the PayPal gateway and pay online. After you have transferred your PayPal USD to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>



<li>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the SOL to your wallet ASAP.</li>
</ol>



<p>The exchange process does not take long. However, you can read some of our new, opinion, analysis or comedy articles on <a href="http://www.blog.hi.exchange/">HiExchage blog</a> while waiting.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-paypal/">How to Buy Solana with PayPal [Best Exchange Rates]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-solana-with-paypal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange DAI to PayPal [lowest commission]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 09:45:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange DAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Maker DAO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4432</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>if you&#8217;re Looking to cash out your stablecoins, you can exchange DAI to PayPal on CoinCannon with the lowest exchange fees. DAI is the latest stablecoin added to CoinCannon platform along with, USDC and TUSD. Created with a unique architecture, DAI is a different kind of stable coin that offers better reliability compared with others. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/">How to Exchange DAI to PayPal [lowest commission]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>if you&#8217;re Looking to cash out your stablecoins, you can <strong>exchange DAI to PayPal on CoinCannon</strong> with the lowest exchange fees. DAI is the latest stablecoin added to CoinCannon platform along with, USDC and TUSD. Created with a unique architecture, DAI is a different kind of stable coin that offers better reliability compared with others. In this article, we will go through everything you need to exchange DAI to PayPal on CoinCannon website. You can also exchange DAI to other currencies on the platform.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-dai"><strong>What is DAI?</strong></h2>



<p>DAI is an Ethereum-based stablecoin. A stablecoin is a cryptocurrency with a pegged value to another currency. In case of DAI, it is pegged to the US dollar and much like Tether and USDC, Dai will always be worth $1. Stablecoins are a crucial part of the crypto market as they offer very little volatility. In that regard, investors use stablecoins to save their funds in the form of a reliable and stable asset.</p>



<p>What makes DAI unique is a clever design that eliminates the biggest concerns for stablecoins. Generally speaking, conventional stablecoins require a massive reserve by the company. For example, for every Tether USD, the Tether company must hold $1 USD in their reserve. This is a huge issue for companies as it is difficult to provide liquidity and keep it consistent.</p>



<p>DAI offers a new solution for this problem. By using an automated system of smart contracts on Ethereum blockchain, DAI does now need a reserve. Using collateralized debt denominated in ETH allows DAI to maintain the 1:1 ration with USD. Simply speaking, users can deposit Ethereum or other cryptocurrencies can borrow against the value of their deposit and generate new DAI. The currency is this case is known as collateral.</p>



<p>Currently, DAI has a market cap of over $9 billion and is ranked as 19<sup>th</sup> cryptocurrency.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-exchange-dai-to-paypal"><strong>Why Exchange DAI to PayPal?</strong></h2>



<p>PayPal is an online trade company that, through online transfers, facilitates payments between parties. Its system allows clients to set up an account on its platform that is linked to the user’s credit card or checking account. Upon confirmation of identification and proof of funds, through the website or application of the company, users can begin sending or receiving payments online to and from other PayPal accounts.</p>



<p>As mentioned above, in order to transfer money to others using the receiver’s email address or mobile phone number, PayPal account holders can use the website or mobile application of the company. Within only a matter of minutes, transactions go through and the company promises that transfers are immediately available for payment or withdrawal to a bank account.</p>



<p>The ease of use and the wide acceptance makes the exchange cryptocurrencies to PayPal one of the best options when you need some cash to spend online.</p>



<p>All that said, you also have the ability to exchange DAI to Perfect Money USD, Payeer USD or Webmoney USD.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-jolixo"><strong>Why CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p><strong>CoinCannon is an online exchange that offers everything you need from a platform.</strong></p>



<p>Truthfully, it is a rare combination for an online exchange to offer anonymity, lowest exchange rates and unparalleled reliability altogether.</p>



<p>We respect our customer’s privacy by not asking for their personal information. The best way for anyone to protect their information is to not disclose them at all. In that regard, not having KYC or sign up is the best method.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the platform utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at all times. Our words sound too good? Just pay a visit to ranking websites such as BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>Lastly, according to Murphy’s law “anything that can go wrong will go wrong”. To stay ahead of any problems, we offer 24/7 customer support.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-exchange-dai-to-paypal"><strong>How to Exchange DAI to PayPal?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select DAI on the left field and PayPal on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your PayPal account details, email, and phone number.</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your DAI to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>At this point, our team will process the order and make the payment to your account. PayPal payments might take some time. We suggest you read some of the articles on <a href="blog.hi.exchange">CoinCannon Blog</a> as you wait for the transaction.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/">How to Exchange DAI to PayPal [lowest commission]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Exchange Polygon (MATIC) to PayPal [No Sign Up]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-polygon-matic-to-paypal/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-polygon-matic-to-paypal/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 08:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4396</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>CoinCannon is proud to announce yet another great cryptocurrency to the exchange list. As of December 10, you can exchange Polygon (MATIC) to PayPal on the platform. MATIC has been one of the top performers in 2021 thanks to the innovative Polygon network. The network managed to successfully executed the “Ethereum’s internet of blockchains” idea. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-polygon-matic-to-paypal/">Exchange Polygon (MATIC) to PayPal [No Sign Up]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>CoinCannon is proud to announce yet another great cryptocurrency to the exchange list. As of December 10, you can exchange Polygon (MATIC) to PayPal on the platform. MATIC has been one of the top performers in 2021 thanks to the innovative Polygon network. The network managed to successfully executed the “Ethereum’s internet of blockchains” idea. Subsequently, the native token of the network MATIC found massive success.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> to exchange Polygon (MATIC) to PayPal</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Polygon?</strong></h2>



<p>Polygon is a protocol that aims to connect all Ethereum-compatible blockchains together. It acts as a scaling solution for the ERC20 network that utilizes layer 2 sidechains alongside the main chain. Essentially, Polygon network improves scalability with faster and more efficient transactions. In many ways, the network resembles the Polkadot network but it is exclusively working for the Ethereum network.</p>



<p>The founders call Polygon “Ethereum’s internet of blockchains”. The approach is to develop scalable solutions for the multichain Ethereum ecosystem. To make this happen, the network is interoperable with all Ethereum-based blockchains. Using layer-2 solutions, sidechains and sovereign blockchains, the network will maintain interoperability.</p>



<p>MATIC is the native token of Polygon network. As of December 10 ,2021, MATIC is ranked 14<sup>th</sup> with a market cap of over $15 billion USD.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Polygon (MATIC) to PayPal?</strong></h2>



<p>PayPal is an online trade company that, through online transfers, facilitates payments between parties. Its system allows clients to set up an account on its platform that is linked to the user’s credit card or checking account. Upon confirmation of identification and proof of funds, through the website or application of the company, users can begin sending or receiving payments online to and from other PayPal accounts.</p>



<p>As mentioned above, in order to transfer money to others using the receiver’s email address or mobile phone number, PayPal account holders can use the website or mobile application of the company. Within only a matter of minutes, transactions go through and the company promises that transfers are immediately available for payment or withdrawal to a bank account.</p>



<p>The ease of use and the wide acceptance makes the exchange cryptocurrencies to PayPal one of the best options when you need some cash to spend online.</p>



<p>All that said, you also have the ability to exchange MATIC to Perfect Money USD, Payeer USD or Webmoney USD.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p><strong>CoinCannon is an online exchange that offers everything you need from a platform.</strong></p>



<p>Truthfully, it is a rare combination for an online exchange to offer anonymity, lowest exchange rates and unparalleled reliability altogether.</p>



<p>We respect our customer’s privacy by not asking for their personal information. The best way for anyone to protect their information is to not disclose them at all. In that regard, not having KYC or sign up is the best method.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the platform utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at all times. Our words sound too good? Just pay a visit to ranking websites such as BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>Lastly, according to Murphy’s law “anything that can go wrong will go wrong”. To stay ahead of any problems, we offer 24/7 customer support.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Polygon (MATIC) to PayPal?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Polygon (MATIC) on the left field and PayPal on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li><li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your PayPal account details, email, and phone number.</li><li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li><li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li><li>On this step, please spend the time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li><li>Transfer your MATIC coin to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you.</li><li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>You’re All Set!</strong></h2>



<p>It takes a short while for our team to make the payment to your wallet. In the meantime, you can visit our blog to read a wide variety of articles. Our recommendation? Read some of our <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/category/jolixo-special/">Friday Special</a> articles which are satire pieces regarding stereotypical characters in the crypto market.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-polygon-matic-to-paypal/">Exchange Polygon (MATIC) to PayPal [No Sign Up]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-polygon-matic-to-paypal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Make PayPal Payment Without a PayPal Account [Video]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-payment/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-payment/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 06:42:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Essentials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Videos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payment Service]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal Invoice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal Payment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5123</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>These days, PayPal Payment is a dominant method of transaction on the internet. A vast majority of online platforms support PayPal as payment method for their goods and services. However, that doesn’t mean that everyone gets equal access to PayPal payment services. Unfortunately, many countries do not have access to PayPal services and subsequently face [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-payment/">Make PayPal Payment Without a PayPal Account [Video]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>These days, PayPal Payment is a dominant method of transaction on the internet. A vast majority of online platforms support PayPal as payment method for their goods and services. However, that doesn’t mean that everyone gets equal access to PayPal payment services. Unfortunately, many countries do not have access to PayPal services and subsequently face payment issues. Furthermore, there are those who rarely need PayPal services and just don’t feel compelled to create an account. But, when the time comes, they might need to make a PayPal payment instantly. Fortunately, CoinCannon PayPal Invoice service is the perfect solution to all problems stated above. It offers multiple benefits and does not cost extra commission. Stay with us as we go over everything to know about our PayPal invoice service.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="How to Make PayPal Payments without a PayPal Account" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Yy3JjVEEHHI?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Make PayPal Payment Without a PayPal Account on<br><a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Can I Make PayPal Payment Without an Account?</strong></h2>



<p>Yes, you don’t necessarily need an official PayPal account in order to make a payment. In order to do this, you will need an exchange platform to make the payment for you. This service is specifically designed for those who do not have access to a PayPal account at the moment. This could be caused by a suspended account for short-term or sanctions imposed on a country which would suspend all PayPal services indefinitely. In any case, you can use the PayPal invoice service to make the PayPal payment instantly.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Does It Better</strong></h2>



<p>However, using the PayPal invoice service is only a good solution as long as you utilize a good exchange platform. Since this is a unique service, the exchangers might take a lot more commission for it as compared with a regular exchange operation. On the other hand, since you are making a purchase, the exchanger will know exactly what you purchased and how much you paid for it. Hence, your anonymity is compromised.</p>



<p>Thankfully, CoinCannon comes to the rescue! CoinCannon does not have any extra commission for the PayPal Payment and the commission rate remains the same as a regular PayPal exchange. Which means, you get to enjoy very low exchange commission with your payment.</p>



<p>In terms of privacy and anonymity, CoinCannon does not require KYC or even Sign Up. Therefore, you do not disclose any personal information with the platform.</p>



<p>Lastly, we offer 24/7 online support. So, in case you have any questions or issues, simply send us a message through the Live Chat section on the <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">main page</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Make a PayPal Payment?</strong></h2>



<p>In order to make PayPal payments without an account, you can use a crypto wallet and pay with Tether or Bitcoin, or a Perfect Money account. We will keep you updated upon adding other options for the payment. Make sure to visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a> regularly to stay up to date. But as a quick hint, there will be a lot more similar services available on CoinCannon very soon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Do I Have to Pay Commission?</strong></h2>



<p>No, there will be no extra commission or hidden exchange fees to use the PayPal Invoice service. The commission rate is the same as making a standard PayPal exchange on the platform which is already pretty low. Please bear in mind, making payments via Bitcoin will have a higher transaction fee due to Bitcoin network fees.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How Can I Make a PayPal Payment Without an Account?</strong></h2>



<p>In short, since you don’t have access to a PayPal account, you send your assets to CoinCannon and the platform will make the payment from its own PayPal account. Currently, we support Bitcoin, Tether TRC20 or Perfect Money USD. Following that, CoinCannon will receive your funds and make the PayPal payment on your behalf.</p>



<p>The process is very simple!</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Enter the CoinCannon Platform. Then, select either Perfect Money, Bitcoin or Tether TRC20 in the “I Give” section. After that, select PayPal USD (Invoice) from the “I Get” Section.</li><li>Type the Sending Amount for the payment. Then, wait until the rates automatically apply and see how much PayPal USD you will have for the payment. By the way, our exchange rates are awesome!</li><li>Click on Exchange and your will go to the second step. Add your invoice link (URL address) in the dedicated section. For example, if you’re buying a service online, add the link to the product page. Type your email address and the phone number section is optional. However, remember that there are many<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> benefits</a> for customers who sign up.</li><li>Review the exchange information carefully. Prove that you’re not a robot (nothing personal J) and click on “Exchange”</li><li>On the forth step, you receive your Track ID. You can see the order status. Click on “Pay Order”. If you make the payment via Perfect Money, you will be directed to the Perfect Money gateway. If you’re sending BTC or Tether, you will receive CoinCannon’s wallet address. At that point, make the payment and attach a screenshot of the payment in the dedicated section.</li><li>Kindly, agree to our terms and conditions and click on “Pay Order”.</li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>That’s It!</strong></h2>



<p>At this point, our team will process your order and make the PayPal payment. The process might take a short while. If you have any questions or issues, you can contact our online support team via the live chat section on the website. Our services expand by the hour! Make sure to visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a> for the latest announcements.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-payment/">Make PayPal Payment Without a PayPal Account [Video]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/paypal-payment/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You Don’t Need PayPal Account for PayPal Payments!</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/no-paypal-account-for-paypal-payments/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/no-paypal-account-for-paypal-payments/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 06:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal Account]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal Invoice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal Payments]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5632</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With over 370 million users, having a PayPal account is pretty important for everyone looking to make a purchase. Now, we all know how it is also bombarded with regulations and restrictions. Despite the popularity, PayPal is not available in some countries which raises a big issue. Currently, we need a PayPal account for so [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/no-paypal-account-for-paypal-payments/">You Don’t Need PayPal Account for PayPal Payments!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>With over 370 million users, having a PayPal account is pretty important for everyone looking to make a purchase. Now, we all know how it is also bombarded with regulations and restrictions. Despite the popularity, PayPal is not available in some countries which raises a big issue. Currently, we need a PayPal account for so many online services and products that are absolutely crucial to us. With the restrictions and sanctions, millions of people are left out in need of a reliable payment system. Fortunately, CoinCannon has got the best solution for all these problems. Enter, the PayPal Invoice service. An awesome solution to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/paypal-payment/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">make PayPal payments without a PayPal account</a>. Here are some common questions about PayPal Invoice service:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Learn How to Make <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/paypal-paymenst-in-russia/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">PayPal Payments in Russia</a></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I need to Make PayPal Payments Without PayPal Account?</strong></h2>



<p>Good news is, <strong>you do not need a PayPal account to make PayPal payments online</strong>. For the payment, you can pay with Perfect Money USD or Bitcoin. For that, you will need either a Perfect Money account or a crypto wallet.</p>



<p>As for CoinCannon, it is not mandatory to sign up on the platform or go through KYC. So, all you need is to make the payment via PM USD or BTC.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">No PayPal Account<strong>? No Problem!</strong></h2>



<p>Let’s say you want to buy something online like a gift card. You go to make the purchase and the only way you can pay for it is via PayPal. In the meantime, you don’t have a PayPal account.</p>



<p>At this point, you can head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a>, and select our PayPal Invoice service. Now, with this service, you share the purchase link with CoinCannon team. Then, we go to that website and make the PayPal payment on your behalf. To stick to the example, we buy the gift card you wanted for you. Following that, we send you the gift card to your email.</p>



<p>Using this service, users will not be stuck when they have to buy something with PayPal.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Can I Buy with PayPal Without a PayPal Account?</strong></h2>



<p>Almost everything! But, we recommend online services such as gift cards and accounts since you can immediately have your purchase via email. For example, if you buy a gift card, CoinCannon will send you the username and password in an email. Or, let’s say you want to pay for an application and buy a premium account, with PayPal Invoice, you will have the username and password for the account.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Information Should I Enter in PayPal Invoice?</strong></h2>



<p>Basically, you will need to enter everything required for the purchase. First and foremost, the link for the purchase is necessary. On top of that, you should share account information on the website you want to buy something. The information may include username and password for login on that website. So, keep in mind not to miss anything regarding the purchase on the website you have in mind. However, if you missed something or wanted to talk more about the purchase, contact our support team immediately via the Live Chat on the main page.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Does CoinCannon Hold My Information?</strong></h2>



<p>No, CoinCannon platform will not save neither use your information after the PayPal Invoice order. The data will be sent directly to your email address. Privacy and security are our utmost priority and we make sure to provide them for our customers.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Do I Need to Sign Up on CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p>It is not mandatory to sign up on CoinCannon. Furthermore, there is no KYC required. This is there to ensure anonymity and privacy for the user. The only thing you need is a verified email address and your wallet address. However, there are many benefits to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/paypal-paymenst-in-russia/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Sign Up on HiEcxhange</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>PayPal Invoice Fees</strong></h2>



<p>Fortunately, this service will not cost you any extra fees. The transaction fee for PayPal Invoice is as much as a normal PayPal transaction. In order to see how much you send and how much you receive, simply enter the amount in the exchange box and you will see the transaction fees immediately.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/no-paypal-account-for-paypal-payments/">You Don’t Need PayPal Account for PayPal Payments!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/no-paypal-account-for-paypal-payments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange AdvCash to PayPal &#8211; Volet USD to PayPal in 2025</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-paypal/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-paypal/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 04:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Videos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advance Cash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AdvCash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy AdvCash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange AdvCash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4538</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As the latest addition to CoinCannon, you can now exchange AdvCash to PayPal with the lowest exchange rates. Advance Cash or in short AdvCash or Volet USD is yet another offshore payment provider company that offers quick and cheap transactions. They offer an intuitive platform for online payments and have been successful at that. Good [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-paypal/">How to Exchange AdvCash to PayPal &#8211; Volet USD to PayPal in 2025</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>As the latest addition to CoinCannon, you can now exchange AdvCash to PayPal with the lowest exchange rates. Advance Cash or in short AdvCash or Volet USD is yet another offshore payment provider company that offers quick and cheap transactions. They offer an intuitive platform for online payments and have been successful at that. Good news is that all customers can deposit and withdraw AdvCash (Volet) on CoinCannon and take advantage of the many benefits.</p>



<p></p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-3 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button"><a class="wp-block-button__link wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/En/services/advcash-to-paypal-exchange?cur_from=ADVCUSD&amp;cur_to=PPUSD" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange AdvCash to PayPal</a></div>
</div>



<p></p>



<p></p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="Exchange AdvCash to PayPal on CoinCannon [No KYC]" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7xMrZ9YTSfE?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<p></p>



<p></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-advcash-volet-usd"><strong>What is AdvCash (Volet</strong> USD)</h2>



<p>AdvCash (Volet) is a currency used for online payments. It is based in Belize which provides immunity from national laws of other countries for it. As an offshore currency, it is also encrypted much like cryptocurrencies and benefits from better anonymity and security. The Advance Cash company provides an account for users that allows for a variety of currencies to operate through it. In many ways, it is a lot like Payeer.</p>



<p>And much like Payeer, AdvCash (Volet) supports transfers in both fiat and cryptocurrency form. With a virtual wallet, users can transfer funds and make payments with very low commission. What makes it interesting, is that Advance Cash is also compatible with other payment systems such as WebMoney or Perfect Money. With free international transfers, users get to enjoy a wide variety of currencies all in a virtual wallet. Furthermore, there are both physical and virtual bank cards available for quick and cheap international Visa/Mastercard payments.</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-4 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button is-style-fill"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-white-color has-text-color has-link-color wp-element-button">Learn How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></div>
</div>



<p>The company was founded in 2014 as a competitor for PayPal and much like its peers, it has gained notable success in the past few years. As the need for virtual banking grows, online payment processing companies continue to narrow the gap with PayPal. Although, such companies are not as popular as PayPal, they offer a lot more freedom.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-exchange-volet-usd-to-paypal"><strong>Why Exchange Volet USD to PayPal?</strong></h2>



<p>PayPal is an online trade company that, through online transfers, facilitates payments between parties. Its system allows clients to set up an account on its platform that is linked to the user’s credit card or checking account. Upon confirmation of identification and proof of funds, through the website or application of the company, users can begin sending or receiving payments online to and from other PayPal accounts.</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-5 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button"><a class="wp-block-button__link wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/En?cur_to=PPUSD&amp;cur_from=ADVCUSD">Exchange Volet USD to PayPal </a></div>
</div>



<p>As mentioned above, in order to transfer money to others using the receiver’s email address or mobile phone number, PayPal account holders can use the website or mobile application of the company. Within only a matter of minutes, transactions go through and the company promises that transfers are immediately available for payment or withdrawal to a bank account.</p>



<p>The ease of use and the wide acceptance makes the exchange cryptocurrencies to PayPal one of the best options when you need some cash to spend online.</p>



<p>All that said, you also have the ability to exchange AdvCash to Perfect Money USD, Payeer USD or Webmoney USD.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-use-jolixo-platform"><strong>Why Use CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>CoinCannon is an online exchange that offers everything you need from a platform.</p>



<p>Truthfully, it is a rare combination for an online exchange to offer anonymity, lowest exchange rates and unparalleled reliability altogether.</p>



<p>We respect our customer’s privacy by not asking for their personal information. The best way for anyone to protect their information is to not disclose them at all. In that regard, not having KYC or sign up is the best method.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the platform utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at all times. Our words sound too good? Just pay a visit to ranking websites such as BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>Lastly, according to Murphy’s law “anything that can go wrong will go wrong”. To stay ahead of any problems, we offer 24/7 customer support.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-exchange-advcash-to-paypal"><strong>How to Exchange AdvCash to PayPal</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select AdvCash (Volet USD) on the left field and PayPal on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your PayPal account details, AdvCash (Volet) wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your AdvCash to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-transaction-successful"><strong>Transaction Successful!</strong></h2>



<p>Having completed the steps above, our team will process your order and send the assets to your PayPal address. The process might take some time due to PayPal payment system. In the meantime, you can spend some time reading the latest crypto news on CoinCannon Blog. If you have any questions or problems with how to exchange Volet USD to PayPal, our support team is online 24/7.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-paypal/">How to Exchange AdvCash to PayPal &#8211; Volet USD to PayPal in 2025</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-paypal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PayPal Vs. Perfect Money, Exchange Crypto the Right Way</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-the-right-way/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-the-right-way/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 08:19:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perfect Money]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5585</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When you are done hodling, comes the time to exchange crypto and cash out your profit. But, with so many options around, users may face some confusion as to what they should do. Essentially, both PayPal and Perfect Money are very practical payment systems but depending on the use case, they have some fundamental differences. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-the-right-way/">PayPal Vs. Perfect Money, Exchange Crypto the Right Way</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>When you are done hodling, comes the time to exchange crypto and cash out your profit. But, with so many options around, users may face some confusion as to what they should do. Essentially, both PayPal and Perfect Money are very practical payment systems but depending on the use case, they have some fundamental differences. As an exchange platform, we offer both solutions but here is our guide as to which one is better for you to exchange crypto.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Crypto to PayPal</strong></h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="840" height="400" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Make-PayPal-Payments-in-Russia-No-Commission.jpg" alt="exchange crypto" class="wp-image-5104" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Make-PayPal-Payments-in-Russia-No-Commission.jpg 840w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Make-PayPal-Payments-in-Russia-No-Commission-300x143.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Make-PayPal-Payments-in-Russia-No-Commission-768x366.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 840px) 100vw, 840px" /></figure>



<p>PayPal is a digital payment service that can be used by customers while they shop online. The platform stores payment information, such as bank account or credit card numbers, so that every time they buy something, customers do not have to type the numbers out. Also, it hides from companies this financial information, adding a layer of security to online shopping. PayPal payments can be incorporated into online checkout process by small companies and similarly by large corporations.</p>



<p>Now, while PayPal does not offer lots of anonymity, they are the top secure payment system by a mile. Considering the huge amount of regulations as well as the largest user base in the world, PayPal keeps it safe. Thankfully, transactions are reversible and the quality of service remains the benchmark in the industry.</p>



<p>Distinguishably, PayPal has so many hassles and requirements, but your assets are very safe. For that, you will face many restrictions on buying cryptocurrencies the next time yet the security is worth it.</p>



<p>So, if you want to cash out for a long time and want your assets available on various platforms, PayPal is the way to go.</p>



<p>Learn how you can <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/how-exchange-bitcoin-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Bitcoin to PayPal</a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Crypto to Perfect Money</strong></h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="840" height="400" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/How-to-Exchange-Perfect-Money-to-PayPal-Lowest-Fees.jpg" alt="exchange crypto" class="wp-image-4698" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/How-to-Exchange-Perfect-Money-to-PayPal-Lowest-Fees.jpg 840w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/How-to-Exchange-Perfect-Money-to-PayPal-Lowest-Fees-300x143.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/How-to-Exchange-Perfect-Money-to-PayPal-Lowest-Fees-768x366.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 840px) 100vw, 840px" /></figure>



<p>On the other hand, Perfect Money is all about lesser regulations and lesser hassle. With PM, what you get is a lot more financial freedom and privacy all while your assets are available to you as the owner at all times. Unfortunately, most people think of Perfect Money as a gray area for payment systems that is sketchy. However, PM has been around for years and for what is worth, it is actually very much reliable.</p>



<p>Sadly, in this day and age, we do not actually own our money since it’s not in our pockets. Instead, we have to trust digital networks to hold them for us and hopefully let us have it when we want them. While we praise PayPal for the security, they tend to passive-aggressively restrict our financial activities with thousands of regulations and requirements. For example, there are numerous constraints on buying cryptocurrencies with PayPal all in the name of regulations.</p>



<p>And this, is where Perfect Money shines. PM allows the user to buy and exchange crypto on platforms like <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> in full privacy.</p>



<p>Continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/guide-to-exchange-perfect-money/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Perfect Money</a>”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Verdict</strong></h2>



<p>In this case, it’s actually very simple to pick one. If you’re looking to store your assets for a long time, go with PayPal. PayPal offers the highest security of funds but also suffers from a vast variety of regulations. In that regard, it would be more difficult to buy cryptocurrencies the next time with PayPal. Conversely, if you want to get back in the market quick, exchange crypto to Perfect Money. Despite the reputation, PM has consistently remained as a reliable payment system. On top of that, the financial liberty is a rare gem these days and Perfect Money knows it!</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-the-right-way/">PayPal Vs. Perfect Money, Exchange Crypto the Right Way</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-the-right-way/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
