<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Exchange Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/category/exchange/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/category/exchange/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 07:23:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Instant Credit Card for Online Shopping [No KYC]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/credit-card-for-online-shopping/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/credit-card-for-online-shopping/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 08:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[credit card]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Master Card]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prepaid Mastercard]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prepaid paypal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prepiad visa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Visa Card]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=8708</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What if I told you that you don&#8217;t need a credit card for online shopping? All you need is someone with a credit card to pay for you right? then, CoinCannon does the work for you!At this point, you might think that you want a virtual prepaid credit card for online shopping but that&#8217;s complicated [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/credit-card-for-online-shopping/">Instant Credit Card for Online Shopping [No KYC]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>What if I told you that you don&#8217;t need a credit card for online shopping? All you need is someone with a credit card to pay for you right? then, CoinCannon does the work for you!<br>At this point, you might think that you want a virtual prepaid credit card for online shopping but that&#8217;s complicated too. <strong>The alternative we offer is instant, anonymous and comes with much lower rates than a prepaid card</strong>. Here&#8217;s how it works.</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>You want to buy something online that requires a credit card for online shopping.</li>



<li>You come to CoinCannon, send whatever currency you have like Tether USDT, Bitcoin or 100+ different currencies. Then you send us the link for your online shopping.</li>



<li>CoinCannon will go to the link and make the payment for you and send you the payment confirmation.</li>
</ul>



<p>Oh and by the way, it&#8217;s instant, with no KYC and comes with 24/7 support!</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-1 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button"><a class="wp-block-button__link wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/En/solutions/online-payment?cur_from=USDTTRC20&amp;cur_to=PPUSDI">Start Now!</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-limitless-virtual-credit-card">The Limitless Virtual Credit Card </h2>



<p>It&#8217;s a pain in the bottom I tell ya! having to buy virtual credit card, going through all the different websites to find the best one, filling out the forms, paying all the extra money for a card you can only use once. Not to mention all the time you waste on purchasing a card for purchasing another thing on the internet! ain&#8217;t nobody got time for that! </p>



<p>Here&#8217;s what we do instead, we can be your cool friend who already has a credit card. All you gotta do is pay your buddy CoinCannon however you like and we&#8217;ll handle the payment stuff like a champ! </p>



<p>That way, you don&#8217;t have to waste time or money and the capitalism gods will be happy! </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-not-to-apply-for-an-online-credit-card-for-shopping">How not to Apply for an Online Credit Card for Shopping</h2>



<p>Honestly, purchasing a virtual credit card is a big hassle for all of us. If you live in a country where payments processors like PayPal, Visa or MasterCard do not provide services, then the trouble gets bigger! </p>



<p>But thanks to our frightening genius, your online purchases will have no limits and shall remain liberated from all the bounds of regulatory nightmare that consumes our ever-expanding financial limbo scattered around the vast expanse of the interweb! (the author has studied literature and wanted to showcase his poetic abilities with this paragraph!) </p>



<p>Whether you&#8217;re a freelancer or representing a business, having an quick and easy alternative for the expensive online credit card for shopping will give you a boost in performance. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-credit-card-fees-vs-jolixo-fees">Credit Card Fees Vs. CoinCannon Fees</h2>



<p>Here&#8217;s a quick look at the associated fees for a prepaid visa card:</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Activation Fee</strong> – Typically $3 to $10.</li>



<li><strong>Purchase Fee</strong> – Some retailers charge an extra fee, usually around $5 to $15.</li>



<li><strong>Exchange Rate Fees</strong> – If you&#8217;re buying it with crypto or a foreign currency, you might pay an extra 1-5%.</li>



<li><strong>Third-Party Markup</strong> – If you’re buying from a reseller, they may charge an additional percentage.</li>
</ol>



<p>If you’re buying from an official provider like Vanilla Visa or a bank, you might just pay the face value ($1,000) plus a small fee. If you&#8217;re getting it from a crypto exchange or P2P seller, expect to pay more, sometimes up to <strong>5-15% extra</strong>.</p>



<p>Considering the fees mentioned above, when utilizing CoinCannon, you will ONLY pay a 1% to 5% exchange fee and there will be <strong>no extra charge at all</strong>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-do-i-need-to-purchase-a-prepaid-card">What do I Need to Purchase a Prepaid Card?</h2>



<p>When purchasing a credit card for online shopping, you will have to sign up on the retailer&#8217;s website and disclose lots and lots of your personal information. mind you, the process can take days! As mentioned before, there are many countries in which online credit cards or even prepaid cards do not provide services. Other than that, paying for the credit card does also require a specific currency. In that regard, you might have to exchange what you already have beforehand and pay for yet another exchange fee.</p>



<p>By using CoinCannon, you will not share any personal information and basically do not need anything to make the purchase. CoinCannon supports 100+ currencies for payment and will instantly make your purchase. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-24-7-online-support">24/7 Online Support</h2>



<p>In order to make sure everything goes as planned, CoinCannon provides online support available all day, everyday. So get started now and Enjoy Online Payments like never before!</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/credit-card-for-online-shopping/">Instant Credit Card for Online Shopping [No KYC]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/credit-card-for-online-shopping/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange WebMoney to PayPal [2025 Update]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/how-exchange-webmoney-to-paypal/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/how-exchange-webmoney-to-paypal/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 11:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=3181</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the world of payment systems which emerged at the dawn of e-commerce, WebMoney and PayPal are two of the most popular. Each payment system is more common and widely accepted in different geographical areas. Such factor, makes WebMoney to PayPal exchange essential for some. Here at CoinCannon, we will help you make that happen [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/how-exchange-webmoney-to-paypal/">How to Exchange WebMoney to PayPal [2025 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In the world of payment systems which emerged at the dawn of e-commerce, WebMoney and PayPal are two of the most popular. Each payment system is more common and widely accepted in different geographical areas. Such factor, makes WebMoney to PayPal exchange essential for some. Here at CoinCannon, we will help you make that happen so you can easily use the money you are keeping in your WebMoney account.</p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="https://hi.exchange/En/services/webmoney-to-paypal-exchange?cur_from=WMZ&amp;cur_to=PPUSD&amp;track_id=xch_MXkm5RHR9pWAoyG"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="512" height="228" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Exchange-Webmoney-to-PayPal.jpg" alt="Webmoney to PayPal - WebMoney" class="wp-image-8732" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Exchange-Webmoney-to-PayPal.jpg 512w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Exchange-Webmoney-to-PayPal-300x134.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 512px) 100vw, 512px" /></a></figure></div>


<div style="height:13px" aria-hidden="true" class="wp-block-spacer"></div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-the-difference-between-webmoney-and-paypal">What is the difference between WebMoney and PayPal?</h2>



<p>Both PayPal and WebMoney are e-wallets, but while Webmoney is more common in Russia, PayPal is a mainstream international e-wallet. There is a major difference between them, for instance, while PayPal does accept charge-back, Webmoney does not offer such a service. PayPal is focused on credit and debit cards, and those clients without such cards are not able to use PayPal services.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-transfer-wmz-to-paypal">Why transfer Wmz to PayPal?</h2>



<p>Exchanging WebMoney to PayPal can offer several benefits, depending on your needs and circumstances:</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Global Accessibility</strong>: PayPal is widely accepted across the globe, making it convenient for international transactions and online purchases. By exchanging WebMoney to PayPal, you gain access to a broader range of merchants and online services.</li>



<li><strong>Ease of Use</strong>: PayPal is known for its user-friendly interface and seamless payment process. Transferring funds between PayPal accounts is quick and straightforward, making it convenient for both personal and business transactions.</li>



<li><strong>Security</strong>: PayPal offers robust security measures to protect your financial information and transactions. With features like buyer and seller protection, encryption technology, and fraud monitoring, PayPal provides peace of mind when conducting online transactions.</li>



<li><strong>Integration</strong>: PayPal integrates with various e-commerce platforms, payment gateways, and online marketplaces, making it an ideal choice for businesses and freelancers. By exchanging WebMoney to PayPal, you can easily connect your payment methods to popular platforms like Shopify, WooCommerce, and eBay.</li>



<li><strong>Currency Conversion</strong>: PayPal supports multiple currencies, allowing you to exchange WebMoney to PayPal and convert funds into your preferred currency. This flexibility makes PayPal suitable for international transactions and currency conversion at competitive rates.</li>
</ol>



<p>Overall, exchanging WebMoney to PayPal offers convenience, security, and global accessibility, making it a popular choice for individuals and businesses alike. Whether you&#8217;re shopping online, receiving payments, or managing your finances, PayPal provides a reliable platform for digital transactions.</p>



<div style="height:13px" aria-hidden="true" class="wp-block-spacer"></div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-exchange-webmoney-to-paypal">How to exchange WebMoney to PayPal?</h2>



<p>It was difficult to exchange WebMoney to PayPal in the past. Normally, you can&#8217;t just transfer the money in your WebMoney account to a PayPal account. In order to do so, you have to transfer your WebMoney holdings to a bank account which is connected to your PayPal and then use the money in your PayPal account. This process is not possible for everyone and is quite expensive in many cases.</p>



<div style="height:15px" aria-hidden="true" class="wp-block-spacer"></div>



<p>You only have to go to the WebMoney for PayPal Exchange<a href="/directions/popular/exchange-webmoney-paypal" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> </a>page and follow these directions: </p>



<p><strong>Step 1: </strong>Select WebMoney from the box on the left and PayPal (USD/EUR/GBP) on the right.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-1-1-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Exchange WebMoney to PayPal 1" class="wp-image-8304" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-1-1-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-1-1-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-1-1-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-1-1-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-1-1-2048x846.jpg 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p><strong>Step 2 : </strong>Enter the amount you want to exchange to PayPal and get the most competitive exchange rates!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-2-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Exchange WebMoney to PayPal 2" class="wp-image-8306" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-2-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-2-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-2-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-2-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-2-2048x846.jpg 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p><strong>Step 3 : </strong>Click “Next” and enter your PayPal details and your valid email address.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-3-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Exchange WebMoney to PayPal 3" class="wp-image-8307" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-3-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-3-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-3-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-3-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-3-2048x846.jpg 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p><strong>Step 4 :</strong> Once again, Click on Next button, and you are taken to the next level where you are asked to review your order. Please click on Review and Check. Read and agree to the terms and AML policy.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-4-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Exchange WebMoney to PayPal 4" class="wp-image-8308" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-4-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-4-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-4-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-4-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-4-2048x846.jpg 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p><strong>Step 5:</strong> By clicking on “Confirm” you are taken to the 4th and last step where you have to pay your order.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-5-1024x423.jpg" alt="WebMoney WMZ" class="wp-image-8310" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-5-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-5-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-5-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-5-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-5-2048x846.jpg 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>At this stage we ask you to read the instruction carefully. Please do read them carefully!</p>



<p><strong>Step 6:</strong> Make sure to copy your order&#8217;s track ID and then transfer the exchange amount to CoinCannon Webmoney Purse which is mentioned on this page. Don&#8217;t forget to mention your CoinCannon track ID when sending the WebMoney.</p>



<p><strong>Step 7 :</strong> At this stage, please write your WebMoney purse address in the section dedicated to it and click on &#8220;Confirm Payment&#8221; button.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-6-1024x423.jpg" alt="How to Exchange WebMoney to PayPal 6" class="wp-image-8309" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-6-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-6-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-6-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-6-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/How-to-Exchange-WebMoney-to-PayPal-6-2048x846.jpg 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p><gwmw style="display:none;"></gwmw>After you have successfully sent the amount, your order is done and we transfer the money to your PayPal account sooner than you can imagine. </p>



<p>By fulfilling all the steps above, your WebMoney to PayPal exchange will be performed quickly. You can also go directly to the landing page dedicated for Exchange WebMoney to PayPal for a quicker and smoother exchange.</p>



<p>In case of any questions and problems, you can always count on to our support through WhatsApp, Telegram,  Email, Skype, Contact Form, and Live chat on the bottom right corner of the display.</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-2 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button"><a class="wp-block-button__link wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/En/services/webmoney-to-paypal-exchange?cur_from=WMZ&amp;cur_to=PPUSD&amp;track_id=xch_MXkm5RHR9pWAoyG">Transfer WMZ to PayPal Now!</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-tips-to-have-a-secure-webmoney-transfer">Tips to have a secure WebMoney Transfer</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Tips-1024x423.jpg" alt="Transfer WMZ" class="wp-image-8312" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Tips-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Tips-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Tips-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Tips-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Tips-2048x846.jpg 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Choose a Trusted Exchange Service</strong>: Select a reputable exchange platform with a proven track record of reliability and security. Research customer reviews and ratings to gauge the trustworthiness of the service provider before initiating the exchange.</li>



<li><strong>Verify SSL Encryption</strong>: Ensure that the exchange website uses SSL encryption to secure your data during the transaction. Look for &#8220;https://&#8221; at the beginning of the website URL and a padlock icon in the browser address bar to confirm the encryption.</li>



<li><strong>Check for Secure Payment Gateways</strong>: Verify that the exchange service uses secure payment gateways to process transactions. Payment gateways such as PayPal often have robust security measures in place to protect users&#8217; financial information.</li>



<li><strong>Enable Two-Factor Authentication (2FA)</strong>: If the exchange platform offers two-factor authentication, enable it for an extra layer of security. 2FA adds an additional verification step, typically involving a code sent to your mobile device, which helps prevent unauthorized access to your account.</li>



<li><strong>Verify Transaction Details</strong>: Before confirming the exchange, carefully review the transaction details, including the exchange rate, fees, and recipient account information. Ensure that all information is accurate to avoid errors or potential fraud.</li>



<li><strong>Use Strong Passwords</strong>: Create strong, unique passwords for both your WebMoney and PayPal accounts to prevent unauthorized access. Avoid using easily guessable passwords and consider using a password manager to securely store and manage your passwords.</li>



<li><strong>Beware of Phishing Attempts</strong>: Be cautious of phishing attempts that mimic legitimate exchange websites or emails. Always access the exchange platform directly through a secure link and avoid clicking on suspicious links or providing sensitive information in unsolicited emails.</li>



<li><strong>Monitor Account Activity</strong>: Regularly monitor your WebMoney and PayPal accounts for any unauthorized or suspicious activity. Report any unusual transactions or signs of unauthorized access to the respective customer support teams immediately.</li>



<li><strong>Keep Software Updated</strong>: Ensure that your devices and software, including web browsers and security software, are up-to-date with the latest security patches and updates. Regular updates help protect against known vulnerabilities and security threats.</li>
</ol>



<p>By following these tips, you can enhance the security of your exchange from WebMoney to PayPal and minimize the risk of unauthorized access, fraud, or other security breaches.</p>



<div style="height:15px" aria-hidden="true" class="wp-block-spacer"></div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Why to Choose CoinCannon to Exchange Webmoney to Paypal</h2>



<p>At CoinCannon, we&#8217;re dedicated to providing our users with a seamless and rewarding experience. </p>



<ul style="background-color:#f8f1eb" class="wp-block-list has-background">
<li><strong><em>No Exchange Fees:</em></strong> We don’t charge you anything more than stated in the order details</li>



<li><strong><em>24/7 Online Support: </em></strong>Need support? We’re always there for you. Reach out to CoinCannon any time of the day</li>



<li><strong><em>Hassle-Free KYC:</em></strong> At CoinCannon everything is fast and furious! No headache or extra steps to slow you down</li>
</ul>



<p>Note that by signing up with us, you gain access to a range of exclusive benefits designed to enhance your trading journey:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>With the ability to view your order history, you can track your transactions effortlessly and gain valuable insights into your trading patterns.</li>



<li> What&#8217;s more, our innovative affiliate program empowers you to earn money simply by sharing your unique referral link. </li>



<li>Every order made by those who register through your link contributes to your earnings, allowing you to maximize your profits effortlessly. </li>



<li>Plus, stay tuned for exciting updates as we introduce personal wallets and cashback options in the near future, further enriching your trading experience.</li>
</ul>



<p> Join CoinCannon today and unlock a world of possibilities in the digital currency market!</p>



<p></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/how-exchange-webmoney-to-paypal/">How to Exchange WebMoney to PayPal [2025 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/how-exchange-webmoney-to-paypal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Dogecoin to Tether [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dogecoin-to-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dogecoin-to-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 11:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6439</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking for the best platform to exchange Dogecoin to Tether? CoinCannon is all you need. For the past two years, DOGE has been a hot topic of conversation. Despite all the huge growth in short periods of time, Dogecoin remains as a highly volatile crypto asset. In that regard, most investors tend to convert DOGE [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dogecoin-to-tether/">How to Exchange Dogecoin to Tether [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking for the best platform to exchange Dogecoin to Tether? CoinCannon is all you need. For the past two years, DOGE has been a hot topic of conversation. Despite all the huge growth in short periods of time, Dogecoin remains as a highly volatile crypto asset. In that regard, most investors tend to convert DOGE to Tether USDT in case they’re looking to hold assets for a while. However, it’s not easy to find an anonymous exchange platform that offers low exchange fees. In this article, we will go over everything you need to know on how to exchange Dogecoin to Tether USDT.</p>



<p>So, get started! Head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Dogecoin and Tether on the box and you’re good to go.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Dogecoin to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive USDT. Most likely, your Dogecoin wallet supports USDT, so you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Dogecoin (DOGE)?</strong></h2>



<p>Dogecoin started off as somewhat of a joke, but it developed a following after it was created. By the end of 2017, Dogecoin was a part of the cryptocurrency bubble that sent up the prices of several coins dramatically. Dogecoin lost much of its value after the bubble burst in 2018, but it still has a core of supporters who trade it and use it to tip Twitter and Reddit content.</p>



<p>Dogecoin (DOGE) is an open-source, peer-to-peer cryptocurrency. It is called an altcoin and as mentioned, many believe it is an almost sarcastic meme coin. Although it was seemingly developed as a joke, the blockchain of Dogecoin still has value. It derives its underlying technology from Litecoin. The low price and infinite supply of Dogecoin are noteworthy features of this cryptocurrency, which uses a scrypt algorithm.</p>



<p>You can read more about <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-dogecoin-how-it-work/">What is Dogecoin</a> at our article fully dedicated to this Cryptocurrency in case you need to do your research about this coin.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Dogecoin to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>At this point, it’s good to briefly introduce Tether. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Dogecoin to Tether?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Dogecoin (DOGE) on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your DOGE to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether USDT to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dogecoin-to-tether/">How to Exchange Dogecoin to Tether [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dogecoin-to-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 06:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AdvCash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6369</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking to exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin? CoinCannon is the ultimate platform for the job. These days, online platform accept a confusing variety of digital assets including cryptocurrencies. With that, comes to need to exchange these assets into one another on a regular basis. Yet, it could be difficult to find an exchange platform that offers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking to exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin? <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is the ultimate platform for the job. These days, online platform accept a confusing variety of digital assets including cryptocurrencies. With that, comes to need to exchange these assets into one another on a regular basis. Yet, it could be difficult to find an exchange platform that offers great exchange rates and anonymity at the same time. Fortunately, CoinCannon offers the most competitive exchange fees all while providing a hassle-free KYC process for the customers. Today, we will go over how to exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin with no hidden fees, no KYC and 24/7 online support.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange AdvCash to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange direction, you will need a verified AdvCash account. Make sure that the transaction amount does not exceed your withdrawal limit. Furthermore, you will need a reliable crypto wallet to hold Bitcoin. There are multiple options out there, but we do suggest Trust Wallet as a suitable wallet.  As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email address and there is no KYC (know your customer) required. However, there are numerous benefits for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. Want a good reason why? You can win $100 gifts on CoinCannon every single month!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is AdvCash?</strong></h2>



<p>AdvCash is a currency used for online payments. It is based in Belize which provides immunity from national laws of other countries for it. As an offshore currency, it is also encrypted much like cryptocurrencies and benefits from better anonymity and security. The Advance Cash company provides an account for users that allows for a variety of currencies to operate through it. In many ways, it is a lot like Payeer.</p>



<p>And much like Payeer, AdvCash supports transfers in both fiat and cryptocurrency form. With a virtual wallet, users can transfer funds and make payments with very low commission. What makes it interesting, is that Advance Cash is also compatible with other payment systems such as WebMoney or Perfect Money. With free international transfers, users get to enjoy a wide variety of currencies all in a virtual wallet. Furthermore, there are both physical and virtual bank cards available for quick and cheap international Visa/Mastercard payments.</p>



<p>The company was founded in 2014 as a competitor for PayPal and much like its peers, it has gained notable success in the past few years. As the need for virtual banking grows, online payment processing companies continue to narrow the gap with PayPal. Although, such companies are not as popular as PayPal, they offer a lot more freedom.</p>



<p>Continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-advcash/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is AdvCash</a>” to learn everything about Advanced Cash.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Is Bitcoin a Good Investment?</strong></h2>



<p>Well, there is hardly anyone these days who is not familiar with the definition of Bitcoin and what the cryptocurrency is capable of carrying out. However, let’s briefly go through what bitcoin is and where it comes from, then we can focus on the benefits of using this cryptocurrency and explain why to buy Bitcoin with Perfect Money.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a Cryptocurrency that was created after the housing market collapse in January 2009. It follows the ideas set out by the enigmatic and pseudonymous Satoshi Nakamoto in a whitepaper. The identity of the individual or individuals who developed this cryptocurrency is still under wraps. Unlike government-issued currencies, Bitcoin provides the guarantee of lower transaction costs than conventional online payment systems and is regulated by a decentralized authority.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a tempting opportunity for investment and great tool for doing financial transactions. In that regard, it has been a solid choice for investment as an asset that is truly decentralized. On top of that, there are countless online platform that accept Bitcoin as payment which makes BTC a utilitarian option for online payments.</p>



<p>So, if You&#8217;ve decided to invest in BTC, you can exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin in only a matter of minutes on CoinCannon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon to the Moon!</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon homepage</a> first, then select AdvCash USD and Bitcoin from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of BTC you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>



<li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your AdvCash and BTC wallet details and email. The phone number is optional.</li>



<li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li>Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the AdvCash gateway and make the payment to our AdvCash account. Having transferred your AdvCash USD to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>



<li>By finishing all the steps above, our team will send the Bitcoin to your wallet as soon as possible.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-you-re-all-set"><strong>You’re All Set!</strong></h2>



<p>Just like that, you have now exchanged AdvCash to Binance Coin. Give it a few minutes and the BNB will be in your account ASAP. In the meantime, you can follow up on your order using the Track ID provided for you. Simply enter the track id in the required section on homepage to see at which point your order is. Remember not to share your Track ID with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange AdvCash to Bitcoin [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-bitcoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 07:12:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6362</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In case you’re looking to exchange Ethereum to Tether, CoinCannon is the ultimate platform! In general, holding volatile assets for long is a risky move. With that, stablecoins are a great solution to hold digital assets without the risk of volatility. Speaking of risks, Tether has been the oldest and the most popular stablecoin simply [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In case you’re looking to exchange Ethereum to Tether, <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is the ultimate platform! In general, holding volatile assets for long is a risky move. With that, stablecoins are a great solution to hold digital assets without the risk of volatility. Speaking of risks, Tether has been the oldest and the most popular stablecoin simply because of its unparalleled reliability. Despite all that, investors need an exchange platform that doesn’t compromise on their privacy. Although you can exchange ETH to USDT in numerous platforms, CoinCannon offers top-tier anonymity all while charging no hidden fees. In this article, we will go over everything you need to know on how to exchange Ethereum to Tether (USDT).</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn How to <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-do-i-need-to-exchange-ethereum-to-tether"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Ethereum to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive USDT. In case your Ether wallet supports Tether, you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Ethereum?</strong></h2>



<p>Ethereum is a decentralized blockchain platform that is open-source and known for its diversity and innovation. Its main purpose is to serve as a decentralized public ledger for verifying and recording transactions. Compared to previous platforms, Ethereum has improved upon scalability issues, high gas fees, and high transaction fees, making it a second-generation blockchain platform. It has no geographical restrictions and has been a leader in innovation, introducing essential services like smart contracts, NFTs, and decentralized apps. Additionally, its native token, Ether or ETH, is the second-highest in market value after Bitcoin.</p>



<p>In August 2022, Ethereum launched version 2.0, which switched the network to proof of stake. This upgrade has significantly improved scalability and lowered gas fees, while also addressing criticism about energy consumption. This upgrade is seen as a great investment opportunity, as ETH is likely to rally. Ethereum is the second most popular cryptocurrency globally due to its innovative team, potential for attracting capital, and providing great returns.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Ethereum to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to exchange Ethereum to Tether (USDT), let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon for the Win!</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Ethereum on the left field and Tether (USDT) on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your Ethereum to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>You’re All Set!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the USDT to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top Forex Brokers that Accept Payeer</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/forex-brokers-accepting-payeer/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/forex-brokers-accepting-payeer/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 08:28:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Accept Payeer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Forex Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer USD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5561</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Forex traders are no stranger to Payeer as an efficient payment system. In general, Payeer offers three types of services. First, Payeer Transfers is the most popular one that allows users around the world to transfer funds with low fees. Second, Payeer Merchant is basically a payment solution for e-commerce. And third, Payeer Prepaid which [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/forex-brokers-accepting-payeer/">Top Forex Brokers that Accept Payeer</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Forex traders are no stranger to Payeer as an efficient payment system. In general, Payeer offers three types of services. First, Payeer Transfers is the most popular one that allows users around the world to transfer funds with low fees. Second, Payeer Merchant is basically a payment solution for e-commerce. And third, Payeer Prepaid which is a personal ATM card with zero fees that can be used anywhere. However, if you want to add money to forex, not a lot of platforms accept this payment system. In this article, we will introduce some of the best forex brokers that accept Payeer USD.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color"><a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/buy-cryptocurrencies-with-payeer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Learn how</a> to buy cryptocurrencies with Payeer USD on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a></mark></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Is Payeer a Good Payment System?</strong></h2>



<p>Short answer is yes. As of 2022, the Payeer has over 7 million users which can transfer funds to each other for free. The strength however, lies in diversity. Payeer is far ahead of any similar platform in terms of scale of operation and diversity in supported payment methods. With more than 50 payment approaches, the Payeer wallet offers users various services in one place.</p>



<p>You can read our 2022 <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/payeer-review/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Payeer review</a> to see how it stacks up against the competition in 2022.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Forex.com</strong></h2>



<p>Fortunately, this is one of the few platforms that is operational in the United States. In terms of user experience, Forex.com pretty much maintains the highest scores across the board. The minimum deposit is at $50 which allows for competitive spreads with an average of 1.3 pips on EUR/USD. However, users can enjoy better spreads with Direct Market Account (DMA) by paying more commission. Lastly, the maximum leverage on the platform is 1:50 across all accounts.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>FXTM</strong></h2>



<p>This platform is one of the most popular brokers in the world. With a minimum deposit of only $10 and no commission for basic accounts, it is very much hassle-free. But, hassle free does not mean basic in this case. They offer, micro, advantage and advantage plus accounts with spreads starting from 1.5 pips which is pretty good. As for the commission, the micro and advantage plus have no added commission. The Advantage account however will charge between $0.4 and $2 per side per lot. As for the best part, depending on the account and location, FXTM will offer a maximum of 1:2000 leverage.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Grand Capital</strong></h2>



<p>Based in Saint Vincent and the Grenadines Seychelles Grand Capital is a STP | ECN type broker. They offer a $10 minimum deposit while the average spread for EUR/USD is 17 pips on standard, the spreads for other instruments are variable. As for leverage, they offer up to 1:500 on Standard, Swap Free, and Micro accounts. However, the best part about Grand Capital is the competitive trading fees. For stocks, the platform charges 0.1% for all accounts while for crypto it is 0.5%.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>AZAForex</strong></h2>



<p>AZAforex is a legally registered forex broker located in Saint Vincent and the Grenadines, but not regulated by any government agency. It is a STP | ECN type broker that offers an impressive $1 minimum deposit. AZAforex is a broker that offers ultra-high leverage of up to 1:1,000, low spreads. But, the range of instruments can be a bit limiting for traders as compared to the competition. As of now, they only offer 6 crypto pairs. Another benefit for this platform is the simple registration and verification process.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Best Exchange Platform for Payeer</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p><a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-payeer-usd-to-paypal-no-kyc-or-sign-up/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Learn</a> how to exchange Payeer USD to PayPal [Video Guide]</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/forex-brokers-accepting-payeer/">Top Forex Brokers that Accept Payeer</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/forex-brokers-accepting-payeer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Tether with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-perfect-money/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-perfect-money/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 05:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perfect Money]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6105</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The allure of stable coins like Tether (USDT) continues to grow in the ever-volatile cryptocurrency market. For those looking to enter the world of stable coins or diversify their digital assets, using Perfect Money offers a unique and often overlooked pathway. This updated 2024 guide is your one-stop resource for navigating the process of buying [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy Tether with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The allure of stable coins like Tether (USDT) continues to grow in the ever-volatile cryptocurrency market. For those looking to enter the world of stable coins or diversify their digital assets, using Perfect Money offers a unique and often overlooked pathway. </p>



<p>This updated 2024 guide is your one-stop resource for navigating the process of buying Tether with Perfect Money smoothly and securely.</p>



<p>We&#8217;ll demystify the steps involved, highlighting the most reputable exchanges and platforms facilitating this specific exchange. </p>



<p>Whether you&#8217;re a seasoned crypto enthusiast familiar with Perfect Money&#8217;s features or a newcomer intrigued by its potential, this article provides the insights and practical tips you need. Let&#8217;s dive in and explore how to acquire Tether using Perfect Money in 2024.</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-3 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button is-style-outline is-style-outline--1"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-black-color has-text-color has-background has-link-color wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/?step=1" style="background-color:#f7954f">Buy Tether with Perfect Money Right Now!</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-do-i-need-to-buy-tether-with-perfect-money"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Tether with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>For this transaction, you will need a verified and active PM account. </p>



<p>Furthermore, you will have to have a reliable crypto wallet. </p>



<p>Make sure that the transaction amount does not exceed your withdrawal limit on Perfect Money. </p>



<p>As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on <a href="https://hi.exchange/">jolixo</a>. </p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-exchange-perfect-money-to-tether-usdt"><strong>Why Exchange Perfect Money to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>Tether USDT is currently the most popular stablecoin in the world. The value of USDT is pegged to the US dollar which means that it will always be worth $1. What it does is a cryptocurrency with a stable value to store investor’s funds. In that case, the investors can hold their capital in form of Tether USDT without worrying about the volatility.</p>



<p>However, volatility is not the only reason to buy Tether USDT. It is very quick and cheap to buy cryptocurrencies with Tether USDT. The transaction fees are next to nothing and it basically takes a few seconds to buy crypto with Tether. In general, Tether USDT has lots of utility whether you’re a crypto trader, Forex trader or a long-term holder.</p>



<p>Furthermore, numerous merchants have started accepting Tether payments in the past few years. Whether in online stores or physical shops, you can use Tether USDT payments. In that regard, having Tether in your crypto wallet is basically as good as cash in 2022.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-buy-tether-with-perfect-money"><strong>How to Buy Tether with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 1:</strong> Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Perfect Money USD on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange PM to Tether on CoinCannon step 1" class="wp-image-8457" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 2:</strong> Click on Next button and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your email.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfecMoney-Tether-2-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange PM to Tether step 2" class="wp-image-8459" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfecMoney-Tether-2-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfecMoney-Tether-2-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfecMoney-Tether-2-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfecMoney-Tether-2-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfecMoney-Tether-2.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 3:</strong> Click on “Next” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-3-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange PM to Tether on CoinCannon step 3" class="wp-image-8460" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-3-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-3-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-3-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-3-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-3.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 4:</strong> At this point, after clicking &#8221; View and Check&#8221; you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-4-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange PM to Tether on CoinCannon step 4" class="wp-image-8461" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-4-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-4-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-4-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-4-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-4.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 5: </strong>On this step, Confirm the transaction and please spend the time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="423" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-5-1024x423.jpg" alt="Exchange Perfect Money to Tether step 5" class="wp-image-8462" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-5-1024x423.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-5-300x124.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-5-768x317.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-5-1536x634.jpg 1536w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/PerfectMoney-Tether-5.jpg 1744w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Step 6:</strong> Done! You can track your order now.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-all-good"><strong>All Good!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether USDT to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-2024-updates-and-rules-about-how-to-buy-tether-with-perfect-money">2024 updates and rules about How to Buy Tether with Perfect Money</h2>



<p>While specific regulations surrounding cryptocurrency can vary by jurisdiction, some 2024 updates and general rules apply when buying Tether with Perfect Money:</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Know Your Customer (KYC) and Anti-Money Laundering (AML) Regulations:</h3>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Expect stricter KYC and AML compliance when using platforms for buying Tether with Perfect Money.#### Stablecoin Regulations:</li>



<li>The regulatory landscape for stablecoins is evolving rapidly. informed about any new rules or guidelines issued by governing bodies in your region. and fees. wallet to store your purchased USDT.<strong>In summary, while buying Tether with Perfect Money remains possible in 2024, it&#8217;s crucial to stay informed about evolving regulations, prioritize security, and choose reputable platforms for a smooth and compliant experience.</strong></li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-jolixo-platform"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Every exchange platform must maintain three important characteristics. Anonymity, affordability and reliability. We pride ourselves as a professional platform that offers all three.</p>



<p>For anonymity, <a href="https://hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> requires no KYC or even a sign up process. The best way to protect your information is to not share them with anyone. And for that, we respect our customers and do not ask for their personal info.</p>



<p>As for affordability, CoinCannon utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. By doing so, we have managed to stay on top of the ranks on websites such as Bestchange and OkChanger.</p>



<p>Lastly, reliability is ensured for our customers with 24/7 online support. In case anything goes wrong, you will have our immediate support until the issue is resolved.</p>



<p></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy Tether with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-tether-with-perfect-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange AdvCash to Webmoney [No KYC]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-webmoney-wmz/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-webmoney-wmz/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 08:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AdvCash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange AdvCash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Webmoney]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=6071</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking to exchange AdvCash to Webmoney? CoinCannon is the best platform for the job. With hundreds of payment platforms to choose from, exchanging them can cost you a lot of money. Furthermore, not all exchangers offer the direction you need. Thankfully, CoinCannon does not charge any additional fees on transactions and offers amazing rates. In [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-webmoney-wmz/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange AdvCash to Webmoney [No KYC]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking to exchange AdvCash to Webmoney? <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is the best platform for the job. With hundreds of payment platforms to choose from, exchanging them can cost you a lot of money. Furthermore, not all exchangers offer the direction you need. Thankfully, CoinCannon does not charge any additional fees on transactions and offers amazing rates. In the meantime, you will not have to compromise on your privacy since the platform does not ask for any personal information. With that, you can easily exchange AdvCash to Webmoney in four easy steps. Continue reading to learn more.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/how-exchange-webmoney-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Webmoney to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange AdvCash to Webmoney?</strong></h2>



<p>Naturally, you already have both payment accounts. However, make sure that both accounts are verified and active. On top of that, pay attention to the transaction amount and whether it will exceed your withdrawal limit on AdvCash. As for CoinCannon, all you need is an email-address since no KYC (know your customer) is necessary. However, bear in mind that there are many advantages available for those who sign up on CoinCannon. Want a good reason why? How about winning $100 ever month!</p>



<p>Learn more about our <a href="https://hi.exchange/campaign/tether-giveaway" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Tether Giveaway</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is AdvCash?</strong></h2>



<p>AdvCash is a currency used for online payments. It is based in Belize which provides immunity from national laws of other countries for it. As an offshore currency, it is also encrypted much like cryptocurrencies and benefits from better anonymity and security. The Advance Cash company provides an account for users that allows for a variety of currencies to operate through it. In many ways, it is a lot like Payeer.</p>



<p>And much like Payeer, AdvCash supports transfers in both fiat and cryptocurrency form. With a virtual wallet, users can transfer funds and make payments with very low commission. What makes it interesting, is that Advance Cash is also compatible with other payment systems such as WebMoney or Perfect Money. With free international transfers, users get to enjoy a wide variety of currencies all in a virtual wallet. Furthermore, there are both physical and virtual bank cards available for quick and cheap international Visa/Mastercard payments.</p>



<p>The company was founded in 2014 as a competitor for PayPal and much like its peers, it has gained notable success in the past few years. As the need for virtual banking grows, online payment processing companies continue to narrow the gap with PayPal. Although, such companies are not as popular as PayPal, they offer a lot more freedom.</p>



<p>Keep in mind that you can also <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-advcash-to-payeer-usd/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange AdvCash to PayPal</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Webmoney?</strong></h2>



<p>WebMoney is an online payment system and a comprehensive tool for online business operations. It was originally developed as a money transfer system for US dollars in Russia in 1998 and since then, nearly 40 million people from all over the globe have joined the program.</p>



<p>WebMoney provides digital currency purses that can hold popular national currencies. The payment platform provides a P2P credit purse, global payment solutions, retail services, local payment products, online billing, and direct integration with other global financial service providers. On top of that, a number of countries worldwide are currently working on WebMoney and consumers pay WebMoney for the services of different companies from Spain, Poland, and Belgium.</p>



<p>Continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-tether-to-webmoney/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Webmoney</a>”.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon to the Moon!</strong></h2>



<p>Every exchange platform must maintain three important characteristics. Anonymity, affordability and reliability. We pride ourselves as a professional platform that offers all three.</p>



<p>For anonymity, CoinCannon requires no KYC or even a sign up process. The best way to protect your information is to not share them with anyone. And for that, we respect our customers and do not ask for their personal info.</p>



<p>As for affordability, CoinCannon utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. By doing so, we have managed to stay on top of the ranks on websites such as Bestchange and OkChanger.</p>



<p>Lastly, reliability is ensured for our customers with 24/7 online support. In case anything goes wrong, you will have our immediate support until the issue is resolved.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange AdvCash to Webmoney?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Enter the homepage first, then select AdvCash USD and Webmoney (WMZ) from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of WMZ you will receive will automatically calculate.</li><li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your AdvCash and Payeer wallet details and email. The phone number is optional.</li><li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li><li>Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the AdvCash gateway and make the payment to our AdvCash account. Having transferred your AdvCash USD to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li><li>By finishing all the steps above, our team will send the Webmoney to your wallet as soon as possible</li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Finished!</strong></h2>



<p>Just like that, you have now exchanged AdvCash to Webmoney. In general, WMZ payments are inconsistent in terms of how long they might take. Give it a few minutes and the Webmoney will be in your account ASAP. In the meantime, you can follow up on your order using the Track ID provided for you. Simply enter the track id in the required section on homepage to see at which point your order is. Remember not to share your Track ID with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-webmoney-wmz/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange AdvCash to Webmoney [No KYC]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-webmoney-wmz/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Skrill to PayPal [No KYC]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-skrill-to-paypal/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-skrill-to-paypal/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 07:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Skrill]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Skrill to PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Skrill USD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5677</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As the latest addition to CoinCannon services, you can now exchange Skrill to PayPal on the platform. Skrill has been one of the rising platforms of payment services and users can use Skrill USD to make online purchases for goods and services. However, despite the growing popularity, Skrill is still falling short in terms of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-skrill-to-paypal/">How to Exchange Skrill to PayPal [No KYC]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>As the latest addition to CoinCannon services, you can now exchange Skrill to PayPal on the platform. Skrill has been one of the rising platforms of payment services and users can use Skrill USD to make online purchases for goods and services. However, despite the growing popularity, Skrill is still falling short in terms of having a user base as compared with PayPal. With that, the practical applications may still be a bit limited for Skrill USD. Thankfully, you can exchange Skrill to PayPal on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> and take advantage of both payment systems.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color"><a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a> on CoinCannon with No Added Fees</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Skrill?</strong></h2>



<p>Skrill is a payment system based in London. It started out back in 2001 with focus on money transfers. However, soon the payment system expanded services into e-commerce and online purchases.</p>



<p>However, what Skrill offers as a payment system is a safe and cheap way of transferring funds. The anti-fraud system is in fact a successful way to provide security for the users. This is for the most part to prevent data theft and stay on top of all suspicious activity. Currently, Skrill is active is the United States which maintains some of the highest security standards for payment systems.</p>



<p>As for convenience, there are two key factors in favor of Skrill. First, users can link their bank account to the payment system and take advantage of easy payments. Second, having an e-wallet ensures that transactions are quick, cheap and smooth. All transactions within the e-wallet have very low fees and are done instantly.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Skrill to PayPal?</strong></h2>



<p>PayPal is an online trade company that, through online transfers, facilitates payments between parties. Its system allows clients to set up an account on its platform that is linked to the user’s credit card or checking account. Upon confirmation of identification and proof of funds, through the website or application of the company, users can begin sending or receiving payments online to and from other PayPal accounts.</p>



<p>As mentioned above, in order to transfer money to others using the receiver’s email address or mobile phone number, PayPal account holders can use the website or mobile application of the company. Within only a matter of minutes, transactions go through and the company promises that transfers are immediately available for payment or withdrawal to a bank account.</p>



<p>The ease of use and the wide acceptance makes the exchange cryptocurrencies to PayPal one of the best options when you need some cash to spend online.</p>



<p>All that said, you also have the ability to exchange Skrill USD to Perfect Money USD or Tether USD.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p>Of course, in order to exchange Bitcoin to Ethereum, you will first need a reliable exchange platform. For that, CoinCannon is one of the best options out there.</p>



<p>Every exchange platform must maintain three important characteristics. Anonymity, affordability and reliability. We pride ourselves as a professional platform that offers all three.</p>



<p>For anonymity, CoinCannon requires no KYC or even a sign up process. The best way to protect your information is to not share them with anyone. And for that, we respect our customers and do not ask for their personal info.</p>



<p>As for affordability, CoinCannon utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. By doing so, we have managed to stay on top of the ranks on websites such as Bestchange and OkChanger.</p>



<p>Lastly, reliability is ensured for our customers with 24/7 online support. In case anything goes wrong, you will have our immediate support until the issue is resolved.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Skrill to PayPal</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Enter the Homepage on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>. Select Skrill USD on the left field and PayPal on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li><li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your PayPal account details, email, and phone number.</li><li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li><li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li><li>On this step, please spend the time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li><li>Transfer your Skrill USD to the CoinCannon Skrill address that is provided for you.</li><li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>All Good!</strong></h2>



<p>Just like that, you have now exchanged Skrill USD to PayPal. In general, PayPal payments are inconsistent in terms of how long they might take. Give it a few minutes and the PayPal USD will be in your account ASAP. In the meantime, you can follow up on your order using the Track ID provided for you. Simply enter the track id in the required section on homepage to see at which point your order is. Remember not to share your Track ID with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-skrill-to-paypal/">How to Exchange Skrill to PayPal [No KYC]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-skrill-to-paypal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You Don’t Need PayPal Account for PayPal Payments!</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/no-paypal-account-for-paypal-payments/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/no-paypal-account-for-paypal-payments/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 06:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal Account]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal Invoice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal Payments]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5632</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With over 370 million users, having a PayPal account is pretty important for everyone looking to make a purchase. Now, we all know how it is also bombarded with regulations and restrictions. Despite the popularity, PayPal is not available in some countries which raises a big issue. Currently, we need a PayPal account for so [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/no-paypal-account-for-paypal-payments/">You Don’t Need PayPal Account for PayPal Payments!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>With over 370 million users, having a PayPal account is pretty important for everyone looking to make a purchase. Now, we all know how it is also bombarded with regulations and restrictions. Despite the popularity, PayPal is not available in some countries which raises a big issue. Currently, we need a PayPal account for so many online services and products that are absolutely crucial to us. With the restrictions and sanctions, millions of people are left out in need of a reliable payment system. Fortunately, CoinCannon has got the best solution for all these problems. Enter, the PayPal Invoice service. An awesome solution to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/paypal-payment/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">make PayPal payments without a PayPal account</a>. Here are some common questions about PayPal Invoice service:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Learn How to Make <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/paypal-paymenst-in-russia/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">PayPal Payments in Russia</a></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I need to Make PayPal Payments Without PayPal Account?</strong></h2>



<p>Good news is, <strong>you do not need a PayPal account to make PayPal payments online</strong>. For the payment, you can pay with Perfect Money USD or Bitcoin. For that, you will need either a Perfect Money account or a crypto wallet.</p>



<p>As for CoinCannon, it is not mandatory to sign up on the platform or go through KYC. So, all you need is to make the payment via PM USD or BTC.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">No PayPal Account<strong>? No Problem!</strong></h2>



<p>Let’s say you want to buy something online like a gift card. You go to make the purchase and the only way you can pay for it is via PayPal. In the meantime, you don’t have a PayPal account.</p>



<p>At this point, you can head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a>, and select our PayPal Invoice service. Now, with this service, you share the purchase link with CoinCannon team. Then, we go to that website and make the PayPal payment on your behalf. To stick to the example, we buy the gift card you wanted for you. Following that, we send you the gift card to your email.</p>



<p>Using this service, users will not be stuck when they have to buy something with PayPal.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Can I Buy with PayPal Without a PayPal Account?</strong></h2>



<p>Almost everything! But, we recommend online services such as gift cards and accounts since you can immediately have your purchase via email. For example, if you buy a gift card, CoinCannon will send you the username and password in an email. Or, let’s say you want to pay for an application and buy a premium account, with PayPal Invoice, you will have the username and password for the account.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Information Should I Enter in PayPal Invoice?</strong></h2>



<p>Basically, you will need to enter everything required for the purchase. First and foremost, the link for the purchase is necessary. On top of that, you should share account information on the website you want to buy something. The information may include username and password for login on that website. So, keep in mind not to miss anything regarding the purchase on the website you have in mind. However, if you missed something or wanted to talk more about the purchase, contact our support team immediately via the Live Chat on the main page.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Does CoinCannon Hold My Information?</strong></h2>



<p>No, CoinCannon platform will not save neither use your information after the PayPal Invoice order. The data will be sent directly to your email address. Privacy and security are our utmost priority and we make sure to provide them for our customers.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Do I Need to Sign Up on CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p>It is not mandatory to sign up on CoinCannon. Furthermore, there is no KYC required. This is there to ensure anonymity and privacy for the user. The only thing you need is a verified email address and your wallet address. However, there are many benefits to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/paypal-paymenst-in-russia/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Sign Up on HiEcxhange</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>PayPal Invoice Fees</strong></h2>



<p>Fortunately, this service will not cost you any extra fees. The transaction fee for PayPal Invoice is as much as a normal PayPal transaction. In order to see how much you send and how much you receive, simply enter the amount in the exchange box and you will see the transaction fees immediately.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/no-paypal-account-for-paypal-payments/">You Don’t Need PayPal Account for PayPal Payments!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/no-paypal-account-for-paypal-payments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange AdvCash to PayPal &#8211; Volet USD to PayPal in 2025</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-paypal/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-paypal/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 04:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Videos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advance Cash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AdvCash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy AdvCash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange AdvCash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4538</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As the latest addition to CoinCannon, you can now exchange AdvCash to PayPal with the lowest exchange rates. Advance Cash or in short AdvCash or Volet USD is yet another offshore payment provider company that offers quick and cheap transactions. They offer an intuitive platform for online payments and have been successful at that. Good [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-paypal/">How to Exchange AdvCash to PayPal &#8211; Volet USD to PayPal in 2025</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>As the latest addition to CoinCannon, you can now exchange AdvCash to PayPal with the lowest exchange rates. Advance Cash or in short AdvCash or Volet USD is yet another offshore payment provider company that offers quick and cheap transactions. They offer an intuitive platform for online payments and have been successful at that. Good news is that all customers can deposit and withdraw AdvCash (Volet) on CoinCannon and take advantage of the many benefits.</p>



<p></p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-4 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button"><a class="wp-block-button__link wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/En/services/advcash-to-paypal-exchange?cur_from=ADVCUSD&amp;cur_to=PPUSD" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange AdvCash to PayPal</a></div>
</div>



<p></p>



<p></p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="Exchange AdvCash to PayPal on CoinCannon [No KYC]" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7xMrZ9YTSfE?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<p></p>



<p></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-advcash-volet-usd"><strong>What is AdvCash (Volet</strong> USD)</h2>



<p>AdvCash (Volet) is a currency used for online payments. It is based in Belize which provides immunity from national laws of other countries for it. As an offshore currency, it is also encrypted much like cryptocurrencies and benefits from better anonymity and security. The Advance Cash company provides an account for users that allows for a variety of currencies to operate through it. In many ways, it is a lot like Payeer.</p>



<p>And much like Payeer, AdvCash (Volet) supports transfers in both fiat and cryptocurrency form. With a virtual wallet, users can transfer funds and make payments with very low commission. What makes it interesting, is that Advance Cash is also compatible with other payment systems such as WebMoney or Perfect Money. With free international transfers, users get to enjoy a wide variety of currencies all in a virtual wallet. Furthermore, there are both physical and virtual bank cards available for quick and cheap international Visa/Mastercard payments.</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-5 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button is-style-fill"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-white-color has-text-color has-link-color wp-element-button">Learn How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></div>
</div>



<p>The company was founded in 2014 as a competitor for PayPal and much like its peers, it has gained notable success in the past few years. As the need for virtual banking grows, online payment processing companies continue to narrow the gap with PayPal. Although, such companies are not as popular as PayPal, they offer a lot more freedom.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-exchange-volet-usd-to-paypal"><strong>Why Exchange Volet USD to PayPal?</strong></h2>



<p>PayPal is an online trade company that, through online transfers, facilitates payments between parties. Its system allows clients to set up an account on its platform that is linked to the user’s credit card or checking account. Upon confirmation of identification and proof of funds, through the website or application of the company, users can begin sending or receiving payments online to and from other PayPal accounts.</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-6 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button"><a class="wp-block-button__link wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/En?cur_to=PPUSD&amp;cur_from=ADVCUSD">Exchange Volet USD to PayPal </a></div>
</div>



<p>As mentioned above, in order to transfer money to others using the receiver’s email address or mobile phone number, PayPal account holders can use the website or mobile application of the company. Within only a matter of minutes, transactions go through and the company promises that transfers are immediately available for payment or withdrawal to a bank account.</p>



<p>The ease of use and the wide acceptance makes the exchange cryptocurrencies to PayPal one of the best options when you need some cash to spend online.</p>



<p>All that said, you also have the ability to exchange AdvCash to Perfect Money USD, Payeer USD or Webmoney USD.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-use-jolixo-platform"><strong>Why Use CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>CoinCannon is an online exchange that offers everything you need from a platform.</p>



<p>Truthfully, it is a rare combination for an online exchange to offer anonymity, lowest exchange rates and unparalleled reliability altogether.</p>



<p>We respect our customer’s privacy by not asking for their personal information. The best way for anyone to protect their information is to not disclose them at all. In that regard, not having KYC or sign up is the best method.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the platform utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at all times. Our words sound too good? Just pay a visit to ranking websites such as BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>Lastly, according to Murphy’s law “anything that can go wrong will go wrong”. To stay ahead of any problems, we offer 24/7 customer support.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-exchange-advcash-to-paypal"><strong>How to Exchange AdvCash to PayPal</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select AdvCash (Volet USD) on the left field and PayPal on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your PayPal account details, AdvCash (Volet) wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your AdvCash to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-transaction-successful"><strong>Transaction Successful!</strong></h2>



<p>Having completed the steps above, our team will process your order and send the assets to your PayPal address. The process might take some time due to PayPal payment system. In the meantime, you can spend some time reading the latest crypto news on CoinCannon Blog. If you have any questions or problems with how to exchange Volet USD to PayPal, our support team is online 24/7.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-paypal/">How to Exchange AdvCash to PayPal &#8211; Volet USD to PayPal in 2025</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-paypal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PayPal Vs. Perfect Money, Exchange Crypto the Right Way</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-the-right-way/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-the-right-way/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 08:19:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perfect Money]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5585</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When you are done hodling, comes the time to exchange crypto and cash out your profit. But, with so many options around, users may face some confusion as to what they should do. Essentially, both PayPal and Perfect Money are very practical payment systems but depending on the use case, they have some fundamental differences. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-the-right-way/">PayPal Vs. Perfect Money, Exchange Crypto the Right Way</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>When you are done hodling, comes the time to exchange crypto and cash out your profit. But, with so many options around, users may face some confusion as to what they should do. Essentially, both PayPal and Perfect Money are very practical payment systems but depending on the use case, they have some fundamental differences. As an exchange platform, we offer both solutions but here is our guide as to which one is better for you to exchange crypto.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Learn How to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Crypto to PayPal</strong></h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="840" height="400" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Make-PayPal-Payments-in-Russia-No-Commission.jpg" alt="exchange crypto" class="wp-image-5104" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Make-PayPal-Payments-in-Russia-No-Commission.jpg 840w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Make-PayPal-Payments-in-Russia-No-Commission-300x143.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/How-to-Make-PayPal-Payments-in-Russia-No-Commission-768x366.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 840px) 100vw, 840px" /></figure>



<p>PayPal is a digital payment service that can be used by customers while they shop online. The platform stores payment information, such as bank account or credit card numbers, so that every time they buy something, customers do not have to type the numbers out. Also, it hides from companies this financial information, adding a layer of security to online shopping. PayPal payments can be incorporated into online checkout process by small companies and similarly by large corporations.</p>



<p>Now, while PayPal does not offer lots of anonymity, they are the top secure payment system by a mile. Considering the huge amount of regulations as well as the largest user base in the world, PayPal keeps it safe. Thankfully, transactions are reversible and the quality of service remains the benchmark in the industry.</p>



<p>Distinguishably, PayPal has so many hassles and requirements, but your assets are very safe. For that, you will face many restrictions on buying cryptocurrencies the next time yet the security is worth it.</p>



<p>So, if you want to cash out for a long time and want your assets available on various platforms, PayPal is the way to go.</p>



<p>Learn how you can <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/how-exchange-bitcoin-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Exchange Bitcoin to PayPal</a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Crypto to Perfect Money</strong></h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="840" height="400" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/How-to-Exchange-Perfect-Money-to-PayPal-Lowest-Fees.jpg" alt="exchange crypto" class="wp-image-4698" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/How-to-Exchange-Perfect-Money-to-PayPal-Lowest-Fees.jpg 840w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/How-to-Exchange-Perfect-Money-to-PayPal-Lowest-Fees-300x143.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/How-to-Exchange-Perfect-Money-to-PayPal-Lowest-Fees-768x366.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 840px) 100vw, 840px" /></figure>



<p>On the other hand, Perfect Money is all about lesser regulations and lesser hassle. With PM, what you get is a lot more financial freedom and privacy all while your assets are available to you as the owner at all times. Unfortunately, most people think of Perfect Money as a gray area for payment systems that is sketchy. However, PM has been around for years and for what is worth, it is actually very much reliable.</p>



<p>Sadly, in this day and age, we do not actually own our money since it’s not in our pockets. Instead, we have to trust digital networks to hold them for us and hopefully let us have it when we want them. While we praise PayPal for the security, they tend to passive-aggressively restrict our financial activities with thousands of regulations and requirements. For example, there are numerous constraints on buying cryptocurrencies with PayPal all in the name of regulations.</p>



<p>And this, is where Perfect Money shines. PM allows the user to buy and exchange crypto on platforms like <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> in full privacy.</p>



<p>Continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/guide-to-exchange-perfect-money/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Perfect Money</a>”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Verdict</strong></h2>



<p>In this case, it’s actually very simple to pick one. If you’re looking to store your assets for a long time, go with PayPal. PayPal offers the highest security of funds but also suffers from a vast variety of regulations. In that regard, it would be more difficult to buy cryptocurrencies the next time with PayPal. Conversely, if you want to get back in the market quick, exchange crypto to Perfect Money. Despite the reputation, PM has consistently remained as a reliable payment system. On top of that, the financial liberty is a rare gem these days and Perfect Money knows it!</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-the-right-way/">PayPal Vs. Perfect Money, Exchange Crypto the Right Way</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-crypto-the-right-way/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
