<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Altcoin Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/altcoin/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 12:43:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Revealing Arthur Hayes&#8217; Top Altcoin Picks for 2024</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/revealing-arthur-hayes-top-altcoin-picks-for-2024/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/revealing-arthur-hayes-top-altcoin-picks-for-2024/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Leyli Mamikhani]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 12:43:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=8188</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As the bearish trend of 2024 unfolds, Arthur Hayes, the former CEO of Bitmax, has shared insights into his chosen altcoins for the year. Departing from his Bitcoin focus, Hayes is now eyeing strategic investments in Solana and Bonk, signaling a shift in his cryptocurrency portfolio. In a recent press release, Hayes expressed concern about [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/revealing-arthur-hayes-top-altcoin-picks-for-2024/">Revealing Arthur Hayes&#8217; Top Altcoin Picks for 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>As the bearish trend of 2024 unfolds, Arthur Hayes, the former CEO of Bitmax, has shared insights into his chosen altcoins for the year. Departing from his Bitcoin focus, Hayes is now eyeing strategic investments in Solana and Bonk, signaling a shift in his cryptocurrency portfolio.</p>



<p>In a recent press release, Hayes expressed concern about Bitcoin&#8217;s struggle to maintain its position above $40,000, predicting potential further declines in the upcoming weeks. In response to this market sentiment, he has diversified his investments into the promising altcoins Solana and Bonk.</p>



<p>Hayes anticipates a 30% correction from Bitcoin&#8217;s recent high of $48,000 in 2024, especially following the approval of Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs). He identifies potential support levels ranging from $30,000 to $35,000. Taking a proactive stance, Hayes has already exited positions in Solana and Bonk at $35,000, even if it meant a modest loss.</p>



<p>Positioning Bitcoin and cryptocurrencies as the last bastion of global open markets, Hayes asserts their ability to predict better fluctuations in the dollar&#8217;s liquidity compared to traditional financial markets. In the event of Bitcoin falling below $35,000, Hayes plans to invest in Solana (SOL), an innovative contract platform, and Dogwifhat (WIF), a meme asset on Ethereum, employing a &#8220;fishing from the bottom&#8221; strategy.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote has-text-align-center is-style-default has-medium-font-size is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>&#8220;I would choose Solana and WIF over Bitcoin&#8221;  </p>
<cite>Arthur Hayes</cite></blockquote>



<p>Dogwifhat is trading at $0.343, showing a significant 50% increase in the last 24 hours. In contrast, Solana is priced at $86.16, reflecting a 5.5% uptick from the previous day. While Dogwifhat&#8217;s recent price movements have displayed volatility between $0.330 and $0.355, some experts predict a potential return to around $0.45, similar to mid-January levels. Despite Hayes&#8217; optimism, technical indicators offer mixed signals, introducing an element of uncertainty to Dogwifhat&#8217;s future price.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/revealing-arthur-hayes-top-altcoin-picks-for-2024/">Revealing Arthur Hayes&#8217; Top Altcoin Picks for 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/revealing-arthur-hayes-top-altcoin-picks-for-2024/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MATIC Price Analysis and Predictions; July 23, 2022</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/matic-price-analysis-july-23/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/matic-price-analysis-july-23/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 09:20:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5703</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>MATIC price fell as low as $0.32 on June 19 and with a strong support, it managed to bounce back. During the recovery, the price climbed all the way up to $0.62 but faced resistance and backed down. With that, MATIC fell down to $0.42 and found support at the trendline. Subsequently, Polygon set to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/matic-price-analysis-july-23/">MATIC Price Analysis and Predictions; July 23, 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>MATIC price fell as low as $0.32 on June 19 and with a strong support, it managed to bounce back. During the recovery, the price climbed all the way up to $0.62 but faced resistance and backed down. With that, MATIC fell down to $0.42 and found support at the trendline. Subsequently, Polygon set to recover and surpassed $0.65, $0.80 and finally reached $1 on July 1. Once again, it hit the downward trendline and dipped back down to $0.8. At this point, MATIC price is at $0.9 and is having solid support.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Buy and Sell Polygon (MATIC) on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> with No KYC</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>MATIC Price Action Analysis</strong></h2>



<p>Taking a look at the 4-hour chart, we see MATIC finding support at $0.42 and managing to surpass the trendline at $0.60. Following that, the price broke through $0.65, $0.75 and $0.80 then reached $1. At this level, it failed to go any further and had to back down.</p>



<p>Currently, the $0.80 is the first resistance level for MATIC. In case the price manages to surpass this level, we can expect another attempt to break the trendline. In which case, the $0.90 and $0.95 near the SMA100 will be key resistance levels. After that, the $1 is the critical level to beat.</p>



<p>On the other hand, if MATIC price fails to surpass $0.90 and $0.95 and loses the $0.80, we can expect further decline.</p>



<p>For the bearish scenario, the $0.75, $0.70 and $0.68 are key support levels for the price.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="700" height="311" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/MATIC-Price-Analysis-and-Predictions-July-23-2022.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-5705" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/MATIC-Price-Analysis-and-Predictions-July-23-2022.jpg 700w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/MATIC-Price-Analysis-and-Predictions-July-23-2022-300x133.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Technical Indicators</strong></h2>



<p>MACD indicator: at the time of writing this article the 4-hour MACD for MATIC is on a downward momentum.</p>



<p>RSI: the relative strength index is approximately 50.</p>



<p>Resistance levels: the first one will be at $0.95. Following that, we can expect $1 and then finally $1.20 and $1.30 to be resistance levels on the way.</p>



<p>Support levels: first and foremost, the $0.80 will support the price. After that, the $0.75 and $0.70 will be the next ones. And then finally $0.68 will support the price next.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/matic-price-analysis-july-23/">MATIC Price Analysis and Predictions; July 23, 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/matic-price-analysis-july-23/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase is Considering Listing 50 New Altcoins</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/coinbase-altcoins-listing/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/coinbase-altcoins-listing/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 09:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5229</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase has announce a list of possible altcoins for listing on the exchange. The crypto exchange titan is considering 50 altcoins to join the exchange list. So, if you’re a buy the rumor, sell the news investor, a Coinbase listing could jump start a rally for the chosen ones. A vast majority of these altcoins [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/coinbase-altcoins-listing/">Coinbase is Considering Listing 50 New Altcoins</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Coinbase has announce a list of possible altcoins for listing on the exchange. The crypto exchange titan is considering 50 altcoins to join the exchange list. So, if you’re a buy the rumor, sell the news investor, a Coinbase listing could jump start a rally for the chosen ones. A vast majority of these altcoins are in fact Ethereum-based while five of them are based on the Solana network.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Buy and Sell Top Altcoins on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> No KYC</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>New Altcoins on Coinbase</strong></h2>



<p>Although the exact information is still unclear, Coinbase says that they will provide information regarding the new listings in advance. This is to increase transparency on the new listings. These few dozen altcoins are set to go on Coinbase in the second quarter of 2022.</p>



<p>“Starting immediately and as part of an effort to increase transparency by providing as much information symmetry as possible, Coinbase will be using this blog post as a pilot to communicate assets under consideration for listing in Q2 2022.”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Who is on The List?</strong></h2>



<p>First and foremost, in the spirit of chivalry, Coinbase is considering adding two stablecoins issued by its competitors. Binance USD (BUSD) and Gemini Dollar (GUSD) are set for consideration by the US based exchange platform. But, there shall be no pump for a stablecoin!</p>



<p>Another noteworthy altcoin under consideration is Coin98 (C98) which is in fact not a code name for a virus. C98 is the native token of the decentralized finance platform Coin98 which has managed to make quite a reputation as a successful finance platform.</p>



<p>As for SOL-based digital assets, the most notable one may be STEPN (GMT) which is essentially a utility token. STEPN is a lifestyle crypto project.&nbsp; GMT has had a staggering 22,000% growth since March and is currently trading at $2.25.</p>



<p>As for others, most of them are less-known with low market capitalization as expected. Coinbase has previously stated that they were “bringing on more, often newly created assets or lesser-known tokens that could come with additional trading risks, including higher price swings and increased order cancellations”.</p>



<p>As of April 13, 2022, Coinbase supports 168 crypto assets on the platform.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Also, the platform offers 24/7 customer support.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/coinbase-altcoins-listing/">Coinbase is Considering Listing 50 New Altcoins</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/coinbase-altcoins-listing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Legislators Oppose the Upcoming Crypto Regulations</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-regulations-national-security/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-regulations-national-security/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 08:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4733</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto regulations are coming and they are coming like Miley Cyrus riding a wrecking ball. The Biden administration is gearing up toward a massive wave of regulations. In fact, crypto regulations are now urged to be treated as a matter of national security. Needless to say, this is the same administration that printed massive amounts [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-regulations-national-security/">US Legislators Oppose the Upcoming Crypto Regulations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Crypto regulations are coming and they are coming like Miley Cyrus riding a wrecking ball. The Biden administration is gearing up toward a massive wave of regulations. In fact, crypto regulations are now urged to be treated as a matter of national security. Needless to say, this is the same administration that printed massive amounts of money and caused the hyperinflation. Apparently, there is an executive plan to release soon with tasks for federal agencies regarding cryptocurrencies. For the most part, crypto regulations have been pretty light considering the stock market regulations. In the stock market, you could get crucified for pumping the market like Elon is doing DOGE on Twitter. Unfortunately, regulations are not good news for a market of cryptographic and anonymous transactions. Stay with us as we go over the details of the executive plan.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Buy and Sell Cryptocurrencies on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> as a Matter of Financial Security!</p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Crypto Regulations on the Horizon</strong></h2>



<p>Initially, an unknown source familiar with the plan told <a href="https://www.barrons.com/articles/white-house-executive-action-regulate-cryptos-national-security-51643312454" rel="nofollow">Barron’s</a> about the upcoming plan of action. Primarily, regulating cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum are now a matter of national security. Interestingly, Russia is taking a similar approach. As part of the national security memorandum which is to release in a few weeks, multiple government agencies must analyze digital assets and provide a framework. This includes cryptocurrencies, stablecoins, NFTs. Long and short of it, the plan is to task related agencies with analyzing, research and a proposal for the legal framework. Finally, the White House will make the subsequent decision and reach a consensus.</p>



<p>“<em>This is designed to look holistically at digital assets and develop a set of policies that give coherency to what the government is trying to do in this space,”</em> said the source.</p>



<p>The State Department, Treasury Department, National Economic Council and Council of Economic Advisers are contributing to the executive plan. However, The White House National Security Council is also investigating crypto regulations. So far, United States has remained very tolerant of cryptocurrencies but this news comes as a strong signal toward the crypto market.</p>



<p>“<em>Because digital assets don’t stay in one country, it’s necessary to work with other countries on synchronization</em>.”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Crypto Regulations Are That Serious<strong>?</strong></h2>



<p>Undoubtedly, at least for the United States, a national security matter is of utmost urgency and significance. In that regard, it is hard to maintain an optimistic view. On the other hand, it could also be a blessing in disguise. At this point, there are too many agencies with jurisdiction on the crypto market.</p>



<p>“<em>Various agencies oversee the industry, including the Securities and Exchange Commission and the Commodity Futures Trading Commission. But there’s no consensus on matters such as whether some tokens should be registered as securities, or how to oversee exchanges, stablecoins, and high-yield lending products.</em>&#8220;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">US Legislators Oppose </h2>



<p>As of March 19th, more than half a dozen United States congressmen are objecting this decision. Primarily, they are against the severe regulatory pressure for the harm it could impose on developers. </p>



<p>With a letter sent to US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) head Gary Gensler, Tom Emmer from Minnesota leads this bipartisan group. In essence, the legislators are saying that the over-extensive information requirements are a risk for stifling domestic technological innovation in this sector.</p>



<p><em>“Crypto startups must not be weighed down by extra-jurisdictional and burdensome reporting requirements.</em></p>



<p><em>The SEC must ensure that its information-seeking requests to private crypto and blockchain firms are not overburdensome, unnecessary, and do not stifle innovation.”</em></p>



<p>SEC&#8217;s Gary Gensler has clearly took a stand against cryptocurrencies calling them <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/secs-gary-gensler-skeptic-of-crypto-signals-crackdowns/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">wild west</a>. However, the Minnesota congressman pointed out in a Tweet that the SEC must honor a 1980 law that protects americans from overwhelming documentation requirements. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">While the SEC has authority to obtain info from market participants for rulemaking purposes, it must ensure that these inquiries don&#39;t infringe on the standards established in the Paperwork Reduction Act, which limits the burden the govt. imposes on private businesses &amp; citizens.</p>&mdash; Tom Emmer (@GOPMajorityWhip) <a href="https://twitter.com/GOPMajorityWhip/status/1504117937174683651?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 16, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Brace Yourselves?</strong></h2>



<p>Not quite yet! The executive plan will provide the agencies between three to six months to study the matter and work on a cohesive regulation framework. Realistically, the plan would take at least three quarters to have any meaningful impact. Despite the national security level of importance, navy seals cannot take Bitcoin down.</p>



<p>Frankly, the US has been acting strange about cryptocurrencies and crypto regulations. In a perfect world, regulations would be imposed on a market with the same rate of growth in market cap. In this case, it seems that the country has not been taking crypto seriously and all of a sudden they feel threatened. This lack of attention and possible negligence can seriously harm the investors since it could create a sudden bearish shock wave. Anyhow, at least the US will not ban crypto overnight like China or Russia did right? Right?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.okchanger.com/exchangers/jolixo" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">OkChanger</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. We are on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bestchange</a> and are always amongst the top exchanges.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-regulations-national-security/">US Legislators Oppose the Upcoming Crypto Regulations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-regulations-national-security/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>No Altcoin Season Yet! Investor Sentiment is Shifting</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/investor-sentiment-altcoin-season/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/investor-sentiment-altcoin-season/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 06:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin Season]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4796</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Seasons come and go, as the sun circles around us quarter by quarter, we await a season not in our calendars but in our hearts. Indeed, the altcoin season, the holy season of returns is once again delayed. According to CoinShares, the bear market in the recent months is encouraging crypto investors towards Bitcoin and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/investor-sentiment-altcoin-season/">No Altcoin Season Yet! Investor Sentiment is Shifting</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Seasons come and go, as the sun circles around us quarter by quarter, we await a season not in our calendars but in our hearts. Indeed, the altcoin season, the holy season of returns is once again delayed. According to <a href="https://coinshares.com/research/digital-asset-survey">CoinShares</a>, the bear market in the recent months is encouraging crypto investors towards Bitcoin and Ethereum and away from altcoins. Generally speaking, the investor sentiment could take some time to shift in favor of an altcoin season. Especially, the highly volatile market can turn on a dime. However, it seems that previous speculations are shattered as BTC dominance continues to grow.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote is-style-default"><blockquote><p><span class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Exchange cryptocurrencies to PayPal on <a href="http://www.hi.excahnge/">jolixo</a>. No KYC required.</span></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Tis Not the Altcoin Season</strong></h2>



<p>The digital asset manager CoinShares has done a recent study of investor sentiment. Interestingly, investor sentiment in Bitcoin and Ethereum improved in December 2021 following the deep price correction. On the other hand, the appeal to invest in majority of altcoins especially ADA and Solana decline in the meantime.</p>



<p><em>“During the month of December 2021, when market prices were declining sharply, investor sentiment improved for the larger digital assets Bitcoin, Ethereum and multi-asset, while sentiment declined for the smaller assets such as Cardano, Solana and other altcoins.”</em></p>



<p>However, investor sentiment in Polkadot remained unchanged according to the survey.</p>



<p>What does it say about the investors? Considering the higher volatility of such altcoins and Bitcoin’s dominance, investors are more inclined to buy Bitcoin and Ethereum. In that sense, the deep correction spooked the altcoin season away.</p>



<p>Furthermore, allocations to digital assets are correlated to investor sentiment according to the study.</p>



<p>“<em>Allocations to digital assets mirrored the growth outlook for digital assets, where allocations were minimally increased for the larger coins at the expense of altcoins.”</em></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Regulations Coming</strong></h2>



<p>At this point, it is certain that a vast majority of countries would impose heavy regulations on the crypto market. Primarily, the speculation over regulations is single handedly pushing the market down.</p>



<p><em>“There has also been an almost doubling in the number of investors concerned about regulation.</em></p>



<p><em>Regulation has taken the top spot for the key risks amongst investors despite greater clarity on MiCA [Regulation of Markets in Crypto-assets] and the recent decision from the SEC [U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission] to allow a Bitcoin futures ETF [Exchange-Traded Fund].”</em></p>



<p>The growing concerns and frustrating speculations are now amplified as regulators remain quiet and unclear about the upcoming regulations.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.okchanger.com/exchangers/jolixo" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">OkChanger</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. We are on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bestchange</a> and are always amongst the top exchanges.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/investor-sentiment-altcoin-season/">No Altcoin Season Yet! Investor Sentiment is Shifting</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/investor-sentiment-altcoin-season/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Which Altcoin Holders Are Underwater?</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/altcoin-holders-underwater/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/altcoin-holders-underwater/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 07:59:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin Holders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATIC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shib]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBA INU]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4707</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If this is your first market crash, we welcome you to the weary tribe of wounded altcoin holders with a firm embrace. The crash has wiped out over $1.5 trillion dollars from liquidated traders so far. Despite the lingering pain of staring at our traumatized portfolios, there are interesting statistics to read regarding this crash. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/altcoin-holders-underwater/">Which Altcoin Holders Are Underwater?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If this is your first market crash, we welcome you to the weary tribe of wounded altcoin holders with a firm embrace. The crash has wiped out over $1.5 trillion dollars from liquidated traders so far. Despite the lingering pain of staring at our traumatized portfolios, there are interesting statistics to read regarding this crash. And NO, we will not talk about the <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/22/01/25179039/whats-the-bitcoin-pikachu-pattern-everyone-is-talking-about" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Pikachu pattern</a>. In this article, we’ll go over which altcoin holders are currently underwater with a higher rate than others. And they are certainly a wild bunch when you consider each one. Cardano (ADA), Polygon (MATIC) and Shiba Inu (SHIB) holders are predominantly in the red.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><span class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Exchange cryptocurrencies to PayPal with the lowest fees on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>.</span></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Altcoin Holders in the Gulag</strong></h2>



<p>New research data revealed by <a href="https://app.intotheblock.com/coin/ADA" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">IntoTheBlock</a> shows some very interesting facts and data about the latest correction. Except for Bitcoin and Ethereum, a vast majority of altcoin holders are underwater. Primarily, Cardano, Polygon and Shiba Inu holders are in performing worse than others which makes sense to be honest.</p>



<p>In this case, underwater means that the average purchase price is higher than the current price. This term is also regarded as “out of money” which is something you really don’t want to be called. The opposite of this term is called “In the Money”.</p>



<p>With that said, 81% of ADA holders are underwater which is the worst one thus far. If you’re an ADA holder, we shall press “F” in our keyboards and respectfully recommend you hold your breath. Only 12% are in the money and about 8% are even-steven. There is good reason as to why ADA holds the top spot and we will discuss it later in this article.</p>



<p>Polygon (MATIC) takes the silver medal since about 51% of holders are currently underwater. 37% are still in the profit and 12% are breakeven.</p>



<p>And as for the bronze, Shiba Inu holders are slightly behind MATIC holders. Currently, 50% of SHIB army are in the red while 39% are still in profit and 11% are right back where they started.</p>



<p>And the honorary mention goes to Dogecoin holders. 44% of Doggy Coin lovers are out of money, 52% are in profit and 5% are breakeven.</p>



<p>Despite the plunge, a majority of BTC and ETH holders are still enjoying their stonks. 58% of Bitcoin holders are still in the profit which could be a bit alarming. On the other hand, ETH is doing better as 61% of holders are in the money and 30% are out of money.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>He Who Shall Be First</strong></h2>



<p>Clearly, all these numbers and statistics show direct relationship with one thing and that is timing. It is less about practicality or utility and more about when was the last hype that resulted a wave of buying demand. Looking back, ADA, Polygon and Shiba Inu had recent hypes that eventually attracted lots of new buyers. In that regard, those who made earlier investments are still in profit as demonstrated by Ether and Bitcoin.</p>



<p>Interestingly, the three musketeers tend to illustrate the three kinds of crypto investors. ADA for the educated and utilitarian, Polygon for the tech lovers and Shiba for the risk-takers. The beauty of that is the fact that crypto crash does not discriminate!</p>



<p>On a serious note, these statistics are not to be taken lightly. The previous crash in the summer of 2020 was quite detrimental for the market. However, a pretty much similar crash can seriously damage investors’ trust and cause a long-term bear market.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><strong><a href="http://hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies</strong>. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.okchanger.com/exchangers/jolixo" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">OkChanger</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. We are on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bestchange</a> and are always amongst the top exchanges.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/altcoin-holders-underwater/">Which Altcoin Holders Are Underwater?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/altcoin-holders-underwater/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Looking Back at Bitcoin Rally on October</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/looking-back-at-bitcoin-rally-on-october/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/looking-back-at-bitcoin-rally-on-october/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Rally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4135</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin rally on October was pretty much expected in the community. With a strong 50% growth, the term uptober turned out to be right on the money. A recent report by the crypto exchange Kraken now reveals why and how the gains were made. You can learn how to exchange your Bitcoin into Paypal by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/looking-back-at-bitcoin-rally-on-october/">Looking Back at Bitcoin Rally on October</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Bitcoin rally on October was pretty much expected in the community. With a strong 50% growth, the term uptober turned out to be right on the money. A recent <a href="https://kraken.docsend.com/view/z7pn3uzfxhkn9j72">report</a> by the crypto exchange Kraken now reveals why and how the gains were made.</p>



<p>You can learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/how-exchange-bitcoin-to-paypal/">exchange your Bitcoin into Paypal</a> by reading our instructional article.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Bitcoin Rally</strong></h2>



<p>October was that fresh breath of air after a long time spent down in the dumps. Bitcoin finally illustrated some significant bull runs and even reached an all-time high. With over 50% growth, BTC managed to reach a $1.1 trillion market cap. As of the last day of October, the price stands at $60,800 and a majority of analysts maintain a bullish outlook for it. All data provided by <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bitcoin/">CoinMarketCap</a>.</p>



<p>The Kraken team revealed in their studies that the primary cause for this surge is a supply shock. According to the research, large mining pools refusing to sell the mined coins for profit is primarily the reason for the price hike. Subsequently, the hodling has led to a supply shock in the market that has boosted the price to new heights.</p>



<p>The research has found recurring patterns for hodl waves, an indication of stagnant coin supplies in a specific time frame. In fact, giant miners such as Riot Blockchain (NASDAQ:RIOT), Marathon Digital (NASDAQ:MARA) and Hut 8 Mining (NASDAQ:HUT) seem to have been holding their BTC since September. Data according to a <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2021/10/28/crypto-miners-are-stockpiling-bitcoin-amid-recent-rally-kraken-says/">CoinDesk</a> report.</p>



<p>Subsequently, with the rise in price, a growing interest in cryptocurrencies and higher number of transactions was also responsible for the Bitcoin rally.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Altcoin Rally</strong></h2>



<p>Bitcoin was not the only one to skyrocket. A vast majority of <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/altcoin-season-looms-ahead-as-rallies-continue/">altcoins</a> had massive gains in October. Furthermore, <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/ethereum-finally-reaches-a-new-ath/">Ethereum</a> also reached an ATH on October. As part of a cohesive market, Bitcoin’s dominance causes altcoins to move pretty much in the same direction. Considering that, Ethereum’s rally was partially due to Bitcoin’s and partially caused by the upgrades in the system and approaching Ethereum 2.0.</p>



<p>All in all, October was just what the doctor ordered after a rough year for cryptocurrencies. Numerous altcoins reached new ATHs as Bitcoin continued on being an incredible asset throughout the month.</p>



<p>Learn <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/">how to exchange</a> your cryptocurrencies to PayPal on CoinCannon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><a href="http://hi.exchange">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.okchanger.com/exchangers/jolixo">OkChanger</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. We are on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/">Bestchange</a> and are always amongst the top exchanges.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/looking-back-at-bitcoin-rally-on-october/">Looking Back at Bitcoin Rally on October</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/looking-back-at-bitcoin-rally-on-october/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Altcoin Season Looms Ahead as Rallies Continue</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/altcoin-season-looms-ahead-as-rallies-continue/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/altcoin-season-looms-ahead-as-rallies-continue/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 07:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altseason]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SCRT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBA INU]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4095</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Altcoin season seems to be closer than we expected. By the looks of it, the Bitcoin rally seems to be over for now. On the other hand, we can see significant surges in price happening for altcoins. Bitcoin dominance is currently at 46.24% As of October 27 according to CoinMarketCap. Secret and Shiba Inu Celebrate [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/altcoin-season-looms-ahead-as-rallies-continue/">Altcoin Season Looms Ahead as Rallies Continue</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Altcoin season seems to be closer than we expected. By the looks of it, the Bitcoin rally seems to be over for now. On the other hand, we can see significant surges in price happening for altcoins. Bitcoin dominance is currently at 46.24% As of October 27 according to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bitcoin/">CoinMarketCap</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Secret and Shiba Inu Celebrate the Altcoin Season</strong></h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Secret</h3>



<p>The altcoin project ironically named Secret (SCRT) has had a 97% rally in only one week. A staggering growth considering the state of the market in the past week. Data provided by <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/secret/">CoinMarketCap</a>. As of now, SCRT is on the 94<sup>th</sup> spot in the ranks with a market cap of $1,175,009,075.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="627" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Secret-1024x627.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-4098" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Secret-1024x627.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Secret-300x184.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Secret-768x470.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Secret.jpg 1173w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>As one might assume, the project is focused on secrecy and providing privacy for DApps and Smart Contracts.</p>



<p>The Blockchain platform is a Proof of Stake that Utilizes Cosmos SDK and Tendermint consensus algorithm. Speaking of <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/cosmos/">Cosmos</a>, it is currently approximately 9% up in one day and 16.4% in one week.</p>



<p>The price surge for the SCRT began with the launch of the first series of anonymous NFTs on the secret network. A success that owes itself to the partnership with NFT platform OpenSea.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Shiba Inu</h3>



<p>Well, turns out Shiba Inu wasn’t done making headlines. Following the <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/shiba-inu-on-a-roller-coaster-of-emotions/">fluctuations</a> of the past few days, the Shiba network introduced the Shiboshi Social Club. It is an exclusive club for Shiboshi NFT owners that has rewards and perks for all members.</p>



<p>Learn all about <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-shiba-inu/">Shiba Inu</a> Coin.</p>



<p>It was quite a strategic move for the network to keep the party going and the wheels turning at the same time. Generally speaking, making headlines and staying on the news has been causing rallies for SHIB.</p>



<p>Subsequently, SHIB is now priced at $0.00005784 with 37% growth in only 24 hours and 107% in one week. Data provided by <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/shiba-inu/">CoinMarketCap</a>.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="621" src="https://blog.hi.exchange/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Shiba-Inu-1024x621.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-4097" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Shiba-Inu-1024x621.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Shiba-Inu-300x182.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Shiba-Inu-768x465.jpg 768w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Shiba-Inu.jpg 1178w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Brace Yourselves, Altcoin Season is Coming (Probably)</strong></h2>



<p>As Bitcoin is consolidating just below the ATH, the 45% dominance is good enough for an upcoming altseason. Speaking from experience, memecoin rallies have seldom been indicators of an upcoming altcoin season. Furthermore, we can see large institutional investments suddenly flow into DeFi platforms. As of now, price surges are occurring in a diverse group of altcoins regardless of their identity and function. Considering all the elements, it is very probable for an altseason to be just around the corner.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><a href="http://hi.exchange">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.okchanger.com/exchangers/jolixo">OkChanger</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. We are on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/">Bestchange</a> and are always amongst the top exchanges.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/altcoin-season-looms-ahead-as-rallies-continue/">Altcoin Season Looms Ahead as Rallies Continue</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/altcoin-season-looms-ahead-as-rallies-continue/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Bitcoin Rally Could Cause Damage for Altcoins</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/a-bitcoin-rally-could-cause-damage-for-altcoins/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/a-bitcoin-rally-could-cause-damage-for-altcoins/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 07:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4056</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin is stealing the spotlight once again and it could be a threat for the altcoin market. As BTC approaches another ATH, there will be many investors pulling their money out of altcoins to jump onboard. This is the opposite of an altcoin season. You can buy or sell Bitcoin anonymously on CoinCannon with the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/a-bitcoin-rally-could-cause-damage-for-altcoins/">A Bitcoin Rally Could Cause Damage for Altcoins</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Bitcoin is stealing the spotlight once again and it could be a threat for the altcoin market. As BTC approaches another ATH, there will be many investors pulling their money out of altcoins to jump onboard. This is the opposite of an altcoin season.</p>



<p>You can buy or sell Bitcoin anonymously on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> with the best exchange rates at any moment.</p>



<p>You can learn how to exchange your BTC into PayPal from our <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/">step by step guide</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>DonAlt on Bitcoin</strong></h2>



<p>The pseudonymous analyst DonAlt had a piece on <a href="https://technicalroundup.com/">TechnicalRoundup</a> newsletter explaining how and why this could happen.</p>



<p>According to him, Bitcoin is only in the middle of a strong rally and reaching new all-time highs are very likely. Furthermore, the Latest Bitcoin exchange-traded fund was not an “sell the news” event.</p>



<p>“Overall, our view is that new all-time highs are likely…” said DonAlt.</p>



<p>Naturally, the rapid growth can motivate almost everyone to invest into BTC. In that regard, opening positions on altcoins is currently not wise. Eventually, the altcoin market will bleed out capital as everyone rushes to buy the king of all digital assets.</p>



<p>“First, if Bitcoin breaks out, we expect a puke in altcoins as holders sell them to catch the move. This will likely cause a liquidation cascade in the short term and set up a really nice mean reversion play for when the Bitcoin breakout stops printing [green candles].”</p>



<p>In this case, according to DonAlt, it could be a good strategy to buy the dip for wounded altcoins. In terms of timing, we should all wait for the Bitcoin rally to stop before touching the subordinates. He did not state whether the end of this bullish phase would lead to altcoin season.</p>



<p>“To summarize, we don’t like altcoins as long as the majors look like they’re going to print big candles (hopefully green ones) at any moment. If they do, altcoins will become attractive either on a post-liquidation bounce basis, or on a larger rotational basis once the dust has settled.”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Best Strategy</strong></h2>



<p>The DonAlt analysis sounds very solid and likely. We can already see as BTC is experiencing massive surges, altcoins are not following accordingly. On the other hand, if the dominant cryptocurrency is making huge waves in the market, it will bleed the others.</p>



<p>We should follow the market closely and look for possible signs. As of now, everything is about BTC.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>jolixo</strong></h2>



<p><a href="http://hi.exchange">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.okchanger.com/exchangers/jolixo">OkChanger</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. We are on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/">Bestchange</a> and are always amongst the top exchanges.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/a-bitcoin-rally-could-cause-damage-for-altcoins/">A Bitcoin Rally Could Cause Damage for Altcoins</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/a-bitcoin-rally-could-cause-damage-for-altcoins/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is Polkadot?</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-polkadot/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-polkadot/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 08:11:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4030</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Polkadot is a unique blockchain network that allows the users to create their own blockchains.  Essentially, it is trying to create a network of blockchains that are connected and interoperable. The goal is to create interoperability among blockchain networks. The network utilizes proof of stake algorithm and has been very successful. If you are looking [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-polkadot/">What is Polkadot?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Polkadot is a unique blockchain network that allows the users to create their own blockchains.  Essentially, it is trying to create a network of blockchains that are connected and interoperable. The goal is to create interoperability among blockchain networks. The network utilizes proof of stake algorithm and has been very successful.</p>



<p>If you are looking to buy or sell DOT coin, you can <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/">learn how</a> to exchange DOT or other digital currencies with complete anonymity on <a href="http://hi.exchange">jolixo</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Content</strong></h2>



<ul class="wp-block-list"><li><strong>Polkadot the Young</strong></li><li><strong>How the Polkadot Network Functions</strong></li><li><strong>Blocks and Chains Everywhere</strong></li><li><strong>Polkadot CoinCannon</strong></li><li><strong>The Blockchain Trilemma</strong></li><li><strong>DOT Coin</strong></li><li><strong>Buy and Sell Polkadot on CoinCannon</strong></li></ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Polkadot the Young</strong></h2>



<p>Initially found in 2016 and launched in 2020, Polkadot is another one of those cases where an Ethereum co-founder decided to walk down the road not taken. And much like <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-ada-a-guide-to-the-cardano-project/">ADA</a>, Gavin Wood was able to make waves in the industry with a revolutionary innovation. As of October 2021, Polkadot Coin is the 7<sup>th</sup> cryptocurrency by market cap, priced at $42. Considering the very young age, Polkadot has deep roots in the industry as a serious blockchain network. In a time period of less than two years, the network has fulfilled all of the advertised promises and is delivering astonishing results.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How the Polkadot Network Functions</strong></h2>



<p>Blockchain networks such as Ethereum allow the users to create their decentralized applications. Polkadot however, takes it a step further by allowing users to create their own blockchain network on the main network. This allows for the new blockchain to take advantage of the already existing security measures of the Polkadot blockchain. DApps on the other hand, require newly created security since they cannot have access to the main network’s security protocols.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Blocks and Chains Everywhere</strong></h2>



<p>The Polkadot network or in other terms the internet of blockchain networks contains two different blockchain types. The primary blockchains, or the main networks are called relay chain. The transactions are relay chains are permanent and they are limited in nature. They act as foundation for the user created blockchains to be built upon them. The second type or the user created blockchains are called parachains</p>



<p>Utilizing this smart design,parachains can be heavily customized, they have the benefit of having security protocols of the main network since day one. This witty structure allows for lower gas fees since there is far less need for computational horsepower .</p>



<p>On the other hand, the efficiency in design allows for more privacy as the user data is not on public networks.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Polkadot CoinCannon</strong></h2>



<p>Relays and parachains aside, the Polkadot network is certainly not shy. The relay can make CoinCannons into other networks such as Bitcoin and Ethereum using parachains. In that regard, they are able to interact and gain access to almost any blockchain they want. This design allows for a future of interoperability for blockchain networks. Certainly, it would be much appreciated in the future where the technology expands. In that case the need for communication and interoperability will surely increase. Furthermore, other blockchain networks can also benefit from these connecting CoinCannons.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Blockchain Trilemma</strong></h2>



<p>The blockchain trilemma suggest that creators must compromise by choosing two out of three essential qualities of decentralization, speed and security. We can see the Ethereum network dealing with high transaction fees and lower transaction speed. Or as of late, it turned out that despite the low fees and high transaction speed, the Solana network was very much centralized.</p>



<p>The interoperability strategy that the Polkadot proposes, can potentially deal with all the aforementioned issues. After all, if all blockchains networks unite, no one can defeat them.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>DOT Coin</strong></h2>



<p>As no blockchain network is complete without a native token, the DOT coin is the running blood in the veins. With a market cap of $42 billion, DOT is 7<sup>th</sup> in the ranks with a price of $42 according to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/polkadot-new/">CoinMarketCap</a>.</p>



<p>In terms of fundamental analysis, considering the utility of the network, it is a safe assumption to have a long position on DOT.</p>



<p>Think 1 million transactions per second, or transaction fees much lower than any other network. On top of that, you have a network that connects all other networks. The team behind the network has demonstrated that they can deliver. And with the fast pace developments of blockchain technology, Polkadot network is a great medium for both development and communication.</p>



<p>In that scenario, we are bullish on DOT.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Buy and Sell Polkadot on CoinCannon</strong></h2>



<p><a href="http://hi.exchange">jolixo</a> is a decentralized online platform to exchange your cryptocurrencies and e-currencies. We utilize an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at any moment. Furthermore, CoinCannon does not require KYC or a sign-up process. Backed by 24/7 customer support, our great reviews on <a href="https://www.okchanger.com/exchangers/jolixo">OkChanger</a> and <a href="https://www.trustpilot.com/review/hi.exchange">Trustpilot</a> is a testament of our good will. We are on <a href="https://www.bestchange.com/">Bestchange</a> and are always amongst the top exchanges.</p>



<p>To learn how to <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/exchange-currency-assets-to-paypal/">exchange your cryptocurrencies to PayPal</a> you can read our instructional article.</p>



<p>For more instructional content, you can always visit <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange">CoinCannon Blog</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-polkadot/">What is Polkadot?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-polkadot/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana, Luna and Algorand Remain Bullish and Reach ATH</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-luna-and-algorand-remain-bullish-reach-ath/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-luna-and-algorand-remain-bullish-reach-ath/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 07:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorand]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Luna]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=3705</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Solana, Luna and Algorand managed to climb high in a bearish week of the crypto market and bring hope to the investors. In the early hours of September 7, 2021, the day El Salvador officially announced Bitcoin as a legal tender, the market had a tragic crash. Bitcoin fell from almost $52,000 to $43,000. Subsequently, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-luna-and-algorand-remain-bullish-reach-ath/">Solana, Luna and Algorand Remain Bullish and Reach ATH</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Solana, Luna and Algorand managed to climb high in a bearish week of the crypto market and bring hope to the investors.</p>



<p>In the early hours of September 7, 2021, the day El Salvador officially announced Bitcoin as a legal tender, <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/over-3-54-billion-liquidated-in-a-shocking-day-for-bitcoin/">the market had a tragic crash</a>. Bitcoin fell from almost $52,000 to $43,000. Subsequently, a vast majority of altcoins had to suffer as well. For the past few days, Bitcoin and the majority of altcoins have been consolidating yet the overall outlook remains bearish.</p>



<p>The Solana, Luna and Algorand however, managed to remain bullish and even reach all-time highs.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Solana Reaches ATH at $190</strong></h2>



<p>Solana has been on a roll lately, skyrocketing from $25 to $180 in less than 7 weeks. With an astonishing <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/solana/">405% growth in 3 months</a>, It has managed to reach #6 in the ranks. We did extensively <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/solana-price-reaches-over-100-sol-8th-in-the-ranks/">introduce the Solana network and the reason for this profound success</a> in a recent article. However, to give you the gist of it, The Solana network is a next-gen DeFi infrastructure that serves as a great alternative for Ethereum. It significantly cuts down on gas and transaction fees. In that regard, they have managed to attract quite a bit of institutional investors.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the Solana network has proven to be a hotspot for the NFTs and they have recently opened their own NFT marketplace <a href="http://www.solsea.io/">Solsea</a>.</p>



<p>All in all, the Solana chart is defying the laws of gravity in a week when altcoins are struggling.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Luna Reaches ATH at $41</strong></h2>



<p>Less than two weeks ago, we reported on the amazing success Luna had flying up to $35. Today, despite the bear market, <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/terra-luna/">Luna is at $41 with an eye-watering 653.50% growth in 3 months</a>.</p>



<p>If you want to know more about Luna and the Terra network, <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/luna-price-reaches-all-time-high-at-35/">you can read our article here</a>. However, the Terra network is pretty much the same in function as the Solana. The terra network was developed as a blockchain network for payments through stablecoins. It was essentially built for the Asian e-commerce market and boy oh boy did Asian billionaires love it. The Terra network radically cuts down on transaction fees and as a results, service providers can save millions of dollars per year.</p>



<p>The Terra network is yet another fierce competitor for Ethereum and looks to have great potential for growth.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Algorand Reaches ATH at $2.14</strong></h2>



<p>Currently ranked as 17<sup>th</sup> cryptocurrency by market cap, Algorand has surged 86% this week and 139% this month according to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/algorand/">CoinMarketCap</a>.</p>



<p>As a blockchain for DeFi applications, <a href="https://algodesk.medium.com/algodesk-io-v-2-0-is-live-on-mainnet-e3aed1aa17a3">Algorand announced an upcoming version of their asset management platform on Thursday</a>. However, the bullish run seems to stem from a recent shoutout by a former Trump administration official Anthony Scaramucci on CNBC.</p>



<p>“There’s a lot of great stuff happening in this space… as more digital applications happen, some of those altcoins, stuff like Algorand or Cardano, or things like Ethereum, will continue to rise because there’s actually great use cases for them.” Said the SkyCoinCannon Capital founder.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The Recurring Pattern</strong></h2>



<p>Taking a look at some of the best-performing altcoins, we can see that most of them are blockchain networks for DeFi infrastructures that can be considered as alternatives for Ethereum. The high gas and transaction fees of the Ethereum network has investors and service providers looking for more efficient alternatives. In that regard, we should wait and see how Ethereum 2.0 will turn out. If it fails to make sufficient improvements, competitors might flip it pretty soon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Where can I Buy Solana, Luna and Algorand?</strong></h2>



<p>Good news is that we will very soon have these three altcoins on <a href="hi.exchange">Hi.exchange</a>. Make sure you <a href="blog.hi.exchange">check our blog</a> on a daily basis as well as on social media to stay up to date with our latest announcements, Opinion articles, news and technical analysis.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-luna-and-algorand-remain-bullish-reach-ath/">Solana, Luna and Algorand Remain Bullish and Reach ATH</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/solana-luna-and-algorand-remain-bullish-reach-ath/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
