<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>IOTA Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/iota/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 06:41:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>How to Buy IOTA with Payeer [Private and Secure]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-iota-with-payeer/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-iota-with-payeer/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 10:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy IOTA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IOTA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MIOTA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Payeer]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4374</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You can directly buy IOTA with Payeer USD on CoinCannon if you have a Payeer account. The exchange will be fully private and backed by 24/7 customer support. IOTA has been around for a while but only recently the network experienced a massive growth in popularity. Having signed partnership contracts with companies like Volkswagen and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-iota-with-payeer/">How to Buy IOTA with Payeer [Private and Secure]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>You can directly buy IOTA with Payeer USD on CoinCannon if you have a Payeer account. The exchange will be fully private and backed by 24/7 customer support. IOTA has been around for a while but only recently the network experienced a massive growth in popularity. Having signed partnership contracts with companies like Volkswagen and Bosch, IOTA platform is nothing short of extraordinary. Good news is that you can Buy and Sell MIOTA on CoinCannon with the best rates at any time.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Head on over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> to buy IOTA with Payeer.</p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-iota"><strong>What is IOTA?</strong></h2>



<p>To explain IOTA, we must first discuss distributed ledgers. A distributed ledger is simply a database that is shared by multiple participants like sites, servers, institutions etc. It is essentially a network within which the transactions can be witnessed and saved by all participants.</p>



<p>IOTA is a distributed ledger which executes and records the transactions between devices and computers in the internet of things (IoT) ecosystem. In simpler terms, it is a network that utilizes its own cryptocurrency called MIOTA for transactions.</p>



<p>In terms of utility, it benefits from a massively improved scalability and transaction speed. The platform has a system of nodes (proof of stake) for consensus called Tangle.</p>



<p>As of December 2021, MIOTA is currently ranked as the 47th cryptocurrency with a market cap of $3.2 billion.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-buy-iota-with-payeer"><strong>Why Buy IOTA with Payeer?</strong></h2>



<p>First and foremost, Payeer is considered an online digital wallet for better asset management. Be it crypto of fiat, the payment processor is quick, reliable and cheap. In that regard, in a short lifespan of almost 8 years, Payeer is now recognized as one of the very best amongst competitors. Payeer utilizes built-in payment services with giant financial services such as Mastercard, VISA and PayPal.</p>



<p>As of 2021, the Payeer has approximately 7 million users which can transfer funds to each other with extremely low fees. The strength however, lies in diversity. Payeer is far ahead of any similar platform in terms of scale of operation and diversity in supported payment methods. With more than 50 payment approaches, the Payeer wallet offers users various services in one place.</p>



<p>To learn more about Payeer, continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-payeer/">What is Payeer</a>?”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-buy-iota-with-payeer-on-jolixo"><strong>Why Buy IOTA with Payeer on CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p><strong>CoinCannon is an online exchange that offers everything you need from a platform.</strong></p>



<p>Truthfully, it is a rare combination for an online exchange to offer anonymity, lowest exchange rates and unparalleled reliability altogether.</p>



<p>We respect our customer’s privacy by not asking for their personal information. The best way for anyone to protect their information is to not disclose them at all. In that regard, not having KYC or sign up is the best method.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the platform utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at all times. Our words sound too good? Just pay a visit to ranking websites such as BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>Lastly, according to Murphy’s law “anything that can go wrong will go wrong”. To stay ahead of any problems, we offer 24/7 customer support.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-step-by-step-guide"><strong>Step-by-Step Guide</strong></h2>



<p>Select Payeer USD on the “I Give” field on the left and IOTA on the “I Get” field on the right.</p>



<p>Enter the desired amount for the exchange and wait for the site to calculate the <strong>amazing exchange rates</strong>!</p>



<p>Click “Exchange”</p>



<p>Enter your IOTA Wallet address and E-mail address</p>



<p>Click “Exchange”</p>



<p>Read the Information</p>



<p>Complete the CAPTCHA</p>



<p>Click “Exchange”</p>



<p></p>



<p>At this point, please check the transaction information and terms and conditions carefully.</p>



<p>You will be able to see the track id and CoinCannon Payeer account</p>



<p>Open your Payeer account, click on the account menu and copy the account number that begins by the letter “p” and paste it in the required field.</p>



<p>Go back to your Payeer account and send the exchange amount to CoinCannon Payeer account.</p>



<p>Once you have sent the exchange amount, go to the history menu on your Payeer account and copy the operation id for the payment. Then paste the operation id in the required field.</p>



<p>Kindly agree to the terms and conditions and click on “Pay Order.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-finished"><strong>Finished!</strong></h2>



<p>At this point, our sales team will immediately get to work and make the IOTA payment to your wallet. The process does not take long, however, you can spend some time reading articles on <a href="blog.hi.exchange">CoinCannon Blog</a>. The blog has a wide variety of subjects from technical price analysis to satire pieces about the market.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-iota-with-payeer/">How to Buy IOTA with Payeer [Private and Secure]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-iota-with-payeer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy IOTA with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-iota-with-perfect-money/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-iota-with-perfect-money/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 06:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Videos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy IOTA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buy MIOTA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IOTA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MIOTA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perfect Money]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4528</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking to buy IOTA with Perfect Money? IOTA is a groundbreaking cryptocurrency focused on the Internet of Things (IoT), offering secure and feeless transactions between devices. In this 2024 updated guide, we&#8217;ll provide a step-by-step walkthrough on buying IOTA with Perfect Money. Whether you&#8217;re new to cryptocurrencies or an experienced investor, we&#8217;ll cover all the necessary details, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-iota-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy IOTA with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking to <strong>buy IOTA with Perfect Money</strong>?</p>



<p>IOTA is a groundbreaking cryptocurrency focused on the Internet of Things (IoT), offering secure and feeless transactions between devices. In this 2024 updated guide, we&#8217;ll provide a step-by-step walkthrough on <strong>buying IOTA with Perfect Money</strong>. </p>



<p>Whether you&#8217;re new to cryptocurrencies or an experienced investor, we&#8217;ll cover all the necessary details, from setting up your Perfect Money account to selecting reliable exchanges that support IOTA. By the end of this guide, you&#8217;ll have the knowledge to confidently <strong>purchase IOTA</strong> using Perfect Money. </p>



<p>Let&#8217;s explore the exciting possibilities of buying IOTA with Perfect Money in 2024!</p>



<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-1 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button is-style-outline is-style-outline--1"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-black-color has-text-color has-background has-link-color wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/" style="background-color:#f49d3f">Buy IOTA with Perfect Money Right Now!</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-buy-iota-with-perfect-money"><strong>Why Buy IOTA with Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>Perfect Money is an e-currency used for making payments on the internet. It is widely accepted as payment option by countless platforms. With Perfect Money, you can do a lot! Be it transferring funds to others or pay for goods and services. Or how about buying cryptocurrencies or even buying fiat currencies. It is a seriously popular payment method for online users. An additional capability is to loan and receipt issuance throughout the system.</p>



<p>The biggest downside of Perfect Money, however, is that you cannot cash Perfect money to your bank account on its website directly. For that, you will need a platform like CoinCannon to exchange your Perfect Money to PayPal and other e-currencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-buy-iota-with-perfect-money"><strong>How to Buy IOTA with Perfect Money</strong></h2>



<p>There are five easy steps for this process:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Enter the homepage first, then select Perfect Money and IOTA (MIOTA) from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, the amount of IOTA you will receive will automatically calculate.</li>



<li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your IOTA wallet details, email, and phone number.</li>



<li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li>Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the Perfect Money gateway and make the payment to our Perfect Money account. Having transferred your Perfect Money to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>



<li>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will send the IOTA to your wallet as soon as possible</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will immediately follow up your order and make the payment to your wallet. The process might take a short while.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-jolixo-platform"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Cryptocurrencies are a financial apparatus to maximize privacy and efficiency. Sadly, regulations have been severely disrupting the market as they compromise both.</p>



<p><a href="https://hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> seeks to be a platform that offers privacy and efficiency simultaneously while offering some of the most aggressive exchange rates in the market.</p>



<p>To make this happen, the platform does not require KYC or a sign up process. This way, all customers can easily make transactions without a possible compromise on their personal information.</p>



<p>However, privacy is a crucial element and not a luxury. In that regard, the platform offers some of the most competitive rates amongst all online exchanges. The rates ar automatically determined utilizing an automated system and are updated as soon as change in value is detected.</p>



<p>Last but not least, by offering true 24/7 support, all customers will be in touch with the team in case anything goes unplanned.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-iota-with-perfect-money/">How to Buy IOTA with Perfect Money [2024 Update]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-iota-with-perfect-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange IOTA to PayPal [Lowest Fees]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-iota-to-paypal/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-iota-to-paypal/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 06:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange IOTA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange to PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IOTA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MIOTA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4360</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We are proud to announce the latest addition to the supported crypto currencies on CoinCannon. As of December 4, you can exchange IOTA to PayPal or Buy IOTA. IOTA has been consistently on the news lately as a platform that offers extraordinary utility. Having signed impressive contracts with companies such as Volkswagen and Bosch, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-iota-to-paypal/">How to Exchange IOTA to PayPal [Lowest Fees]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>We are proud to announce the latest addition to the supported crypto currencies on CoinCannon. As of December 4, you can exchange IOTA to PayPal or Buy IOTA. IOTA has been consistently on the news lately as a platform that offers extraordinary utility. Having signed impressive contracts with companies such as Volkswagen and Bosch, the platform surely has a promising future. <strong>You can Exchange IOTA to PayPal with the lowest possible fees anonymously</strong>.</p>



<p>Enter the <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/">jolixo</a> platform to get started.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is IOTA?</strong></h2>



<p>To explain IOTA, we must first discuss distributed ledgers. A distributed ledger is simply a database that is shared by multiple participants like sites, servers, institutions etc. It is essentially a network within which the transactions can be witnessed and saved by all participants.</p>



<p>IOTA is a distributed ledger which executes and records the transactions between devices and computers in the internet of things (IoT) ecosystem. In simpler terms, it is a network that utilizes its own cryptocurrency called MIOTA for transactions.</p>



<p>In terms of utility, it benefits from a massively improved scalability and transaction speed. The platform has a system of nodes (proof of stake) for consensus called Tangle.</p>



<p>As of December 2021, MIOTA is currently ranked as the 47<sup>th</sup> cryptocurrency with a market cap of $3.2 billion.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange IOTA to PayPal?</strong></h2>



<p>PayPal is an online trade company that, through online transfers, facilitates payments between parties. Its system allows clients to set up an account on its platform that is linked to the user’s credit card or checking account. Upon confirmation of identification and proof of funds, through the website or application of the company, users can begin sending or receiving payments online to and from other PayPal accounts.</p>



<p>As mentioned above, in order to transfer money to others using the receiver’s email address or mobile phone number, PayPal account holders can use the website or mobile application of the company. Within only a matter of minutes, transactions go through and the company promises that transfers are immediately available for payment or withdrawal to a bank account.</p>



<p>The ease of use and the wide acceptance makes the exchange cryptocurrencies to PayPal one of the best options when you need some cash to spend online.</p>



<p>All that said, you also have the ability to exchange AVAX to Perfect Money USD, Payeer USD or Webmoney USD.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why CoinCannon?</strong></h2>



<p><strong>CoinCannon is an online exchange that offers everything you need from a platform</strong>.</p>



<p>Truthfully, it is a rare combination for an online exchange to offer anonymity, lowest exchange rates and unparalleled reliability altogether.</p>



<p>We respect our customer’s privacy by not asking for their personal information. The best way for anyone to protect their information is to not disclose them at all. In that regard, not having KYC or sign up is the best method.</p>



<p>Furthermore, the platform utilizes an automated system to determine the best exchange rates at all times. Our words sound too good? Just pay a visit to ranking websites such as BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>Lastly, according to Murphy’s law “anything that can go wrong will go wrong”. To stay ahead of any problems, we offer 24/7 customer support.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange IOTA to PayPal?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1"><li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select IOTA on the left field and PayPal on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li><li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your PayPal account details, email, and phone number.</li><li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li><li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li><li>On this step, please spend the time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li><li>Transfer your IOTA coin to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you.</li><li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li></ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Your Work Here is Done!</strong></h2>



<p>After finishing all the steps above, our sales team will immediately process your order. It usually takes a short while for the transaction. You can spend the time by paying a visit to <a href="blog.hi.exchange">CoinCannon Blog</a> and read the latest crypto news.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-iota-to-paypal/">How to Exchange IOTA to PayPal [Lowest Fees]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-iota-to-paypal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
