<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Crypto Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/crypto/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 12:47:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Analysis of Bitcoin&#8217;s Continued Drop Amid ETF Approval Expectations</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/analysis-of-bitcoins-continued-drop-amid-etf-approval-expectations/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/analysis-of-bitcoins-continued-drop-amid-etf-approval-expectations/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Leyli Mamikhani]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 06:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=8056</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Despite the most recent changes regarding the Bitcoin ETF, the landscape of virtual currencies is once more in the midst of a profound shift. The most valuable cryptocurrency in the world of digital assets, Bitcoin, has recently declined, losing more than 2.4% of its value. This year has witnessed a stunning 156% acquisition in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/analysis-of-bitcoins-continued-drop-amid-etf-approval-expectations/">Analysis of Bitcoin&#8217;s Continued Drop Amid ETF Approval Expectations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Despite the most recent changes regarding the Bitcoin ETF, the landscape of virtual currencies is once more in the midst of a profound shift. The most valuable cryptocurrency in the world of digital assets, Bitcoin, has recently declined, losing more than 2.4% of its value.</p>



<p>This year has witnessed a stunning <strong>156% acquisition</strong> in the value of the most popular digital currency, Bitcoin. The primary cause for these changes is the conjecture that the launch of ETFs could generate a new wave of demand. Undoubtedly, not all of this can be considered entirely beneficial because there is a lot of speculation in the market on whether or not the approval of these ETFs would lead to profit-taking strategies. Such speculation can potentially negatively impact the shifts in the value of bitcoin.</p>



<p><strong>CryptoQuant</strong> described what happened as a possible<em> <strong>&#8220;sell the news&#8221;</strong></em> incident, referring to the wave that formed upon the news.</p>



<p>The term used above refers to a well-known phenomenon in the capital markets: the rising sentiment, leverage, and asset prices before a positive event, followed by a sharp decline in prices.</p>



<p>This is because smart traders take advantage of overloaded long deals, ensnaring leveraged traders and pressuring them to sell out or liquidate during drops.</p>



<p>The announcement that an ETF for Bitcoin is being approved can be seen as beneficial since it allows institutions to start investing in the cryptocurrency, increasing buying pressure.</p>



<p>The memo stated that &#8220;Bitcoin short holders are experiencing an unrealistic 30% profit margin, which has historically been before price corrections (areas marked with red circles).&#8221; Furthermore, short-term holders keep spending Bitcoin profitably, and returns typically materialize once short-term losses are realized.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Conclusion</h2>



<h1 class="wp-block-heading">ETF Approval: What to Expect from Bitcoin?</h1>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Bitcoin has recently declined, losing 2.4% of its value, and is currently trading at $42,400</li>



<li>2023 has witnessed a stunning 156% acquisition in Bitcoin&#8217;s value</li>



<li>The main cause of this decline can be the conjecture of the launch of ETFs and the newly generated wave of demand.</li>



<li>Bitcoin short holders are experiencing an unrealistic 30% profit margin.</li>



<li>CryptoQuant described what happened as a possible &#8220;sell the news&#8221; incident, referring to the wave that formed upon the news.</li>



<li>Lots of speculation in the market on whether or not the approval of these ETFs would lead to profit-taking strategies that can potentially negatively impact the shifts in the value of bitcoin.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/analysis-of-bitcoins-continued-drop-amid-etf-approval-expectations/">Analysis of Bitcoin&#8217;s Continued Drop Amid ETF Approval Expectations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/analysis-of-bitcoins-continued-drop-amid-etf-approval-expectations/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Dogecoin to Tether [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dogecoin-to-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dogecoin-to-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 11:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6439</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking for the best platform to exchange Dogecoin to Tether? CoinCannon is all you need. For the past two years, DOGE has been a hot topic of conversation. Despite all the huge growth in short periods of time, Dogecoin remains as a highly volatile crypto asset. In that regard, most investors tend to convert DOGE [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dogecoin-to-tether/">How to Exchange Dogecoin to Tether [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking for the best platform to exchange Dogecoin to Tether? CoinCannon is all you need. For the past two years, DOGE has been a hot topic of conversation. Despite all the huge growth in short periods of time, Dogecoin remains as a highly volatile crypto asset. In that regard, most investors tend to convert DOGE to Tether USDT in case they’re looking to hold assets for a while. However, it’s not easy to find an anonymous exchange platform that offers low exchange fees. In this article, we will go over everything you need to know on how to exchange Dogecoin to Tether USDT.</p>



<p>So, get started! Head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Dogecoin and Tether on the box and you’re good to go.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Dogecoin to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive USDT. Most likely, your Dogecoin wallet supports USDT, so you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Dogecoin (DOGE)?</strong></h2>



<p>Dogecoin started off as somewhat of a joke, but it developed a following after it was created. By the end of 2017, Dogecoin was a part of the cryptocurrency bubble that sent up the prices of several coins dramatically. Dogecoin lost much of its value after the bubble burst in 2018, but it still has a core of supporters who trade it and use it to tip Twitter and Reddit content.</p>



<p>Dogecoin (DOGE) is an open-source, peer-to-peer cryptocurrency. It is called an altcoin and as mentioned, many believe it is an almost sarcastic meme coin. Although it was seemingly developed as a joke, the blockchain of Dogecoin still has value. It derives its underlying technology from Litecoin. The low price and infinite supply of Dogecoin are noteworthy features of this cryptocurrency, which uses a scrypt algorithm.</p>



<p>You can read more about <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-dogecoin-how-it-work/">What is Dogecoin</a> at our article fully dedicated to this Cryptocurrency in case you need to do your research about this coin.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Dogecoin to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>At this point, it’s good to briefly introduce Tether. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Dogecoin to Tether?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Dogecoin (DOGE) on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your DOGE to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether USDT to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dogecoin-to-tether/">How to Exchange Dogecoin to Tether [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dogecoin-to-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The US Banking Crisis: The Role of Crypto</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/us-banking-crisis/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/us-banking-crisis/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 08:47:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Money]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6429</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The role of cryptocurrency in the failures of banks Silvergate, Silicon Valley, and Signature has been highlighted in a recent report by the Congressional Research Service (CRS). The report examines the impact of crypto on the US banking crisis and reveals that the banks&#8217; exposure to crypto was minimal, but the perception of risk &#8220;may [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/us-banking-crisis/">The US Banking Crisis: The Role of Crypto</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The role of cryptocurrency in the failures of banks Silvergate, Silicon Valley, and Signature has been highlighted in a recent <a href="https://crsreports.congress.gov/product/pdf/IN/IN12148" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">report</a> by the Congressional Research Service (CRS). The report examines the impact of crypto on the US banking crisis and reveals that the banks&#8217; exposure to crypto was minimal, but the perception of risk &#8220;may have driven non-crypto firms/individuals to make significant withdrawals.&#8221; Interestingly, the statement sheds light on a critical issue regarding crypto assets. Despite all the bullish predictions, the failure of crypto-friendly banks outlines the severe lack of trust in crypto still dominant among retail investors.</p>



<p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Limited Exposure to Crypto</strong></h2>



<p>According to analyst Paul Tierno from CRS, the banks&#8217; exposure to crypto &#8220;was somewhat limited.&#8221; Tierno noted that &#8220;volatility in crypto markets may expose banks to liquidity risks that could ultimately lead to fatal losses.&#8221; However, it was the dwindling deposits from crypto firms that led banks to sell securities at a loss, exacerbating liquidity issues and solvency.</p>



<p>In November 2021, the crypto market reached an all-time high of around $3 trillion. However, by December 2022, the market lost more than two-thirds of its market capitalization. The report highlighted that the fall in digital asset prices led to centralized crypto platforms and stablecoin issuers experiencing redemptions, causing them to draw down deposits held at these banks.</p>



<p>To meet the withdrawal demand, banks sold securities for losses, affecting their liquidity and, in some cases, solvency. For instance, Silvergate&#8217;s deposits fell by over half, while Signature&#8217;s deposits dropped by 15% in Q4 2022. The CRS report emphasized that the losses were not realized on crypto-related assets but were caused by crypto deposit withdrawals.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="1024" height="703" src="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/US-Banking-Crisis.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-6431" srcset="https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/US-Banking-Crisis.jpg 1024w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/US-Banking-Crisis-300x206.jpg 300w, https://hi.exchange/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/US-Banking-Crisis-768x527.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-crypto-s-impact-on-us-banking-crisis"><strong>Crypto’s Impact on US Banking Crisis</strong></h2>



<p>The CRS report reminds us that the crypto market chaos affected US bank stocks. SVB, Silvergate, and Signature were pushed over the edge by fear, uncertainty, and doubt. The report concluded that &#8220;banks must be prepared for the potential of rapid withdrawal of deposits. This can exacerbate liquidity issues and, ultimately, threaten solvency.&#8221;</p>



<p>In conclusion, the CRS report serves as a reminder that the crypto market&#8217;s volatility can impact US banks. Although the banks&#8217; exposure to crypto was limited, the perception of risk was enough to drive non-crypto firms/individuals to make significant withdrawals, leading to the banks selling securities at a loss. This affected their liquidity and, in some cases, their solvency. </p>



<p>However, it’s also important to analyze the fear and the lack of trust in crypto. Perhaps, the volatility is the key factor here. Yet, the <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ftx-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">FTX collapse</a>, may have been a big wake up call for investors. Portraying how easy it is to run a multi-billion dollar scam, Sam Bankman-Fried may have permanently stained the face of crypto. considering this congressional report, we can see how limited exposure to crypto can have negative effects on their business. With all that in mind, we can see how banks may be hesitant to integrate crypto asset into their systems.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/us-banking-crisis/">The US Banking Crisis: The Role of Crypto</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/us-banking-crisis/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange BNB to USDT [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bnb-to-usdt/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bnb-to-usdt/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 08:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6412</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Here’s the easiest way to exchange BNB to USDT instantly with full anonymity! Binance Coin (BNB) is one of the top crypto assets by market cap. For the most part, this popularity stem’s from Binance’s massive scale as an exchange platform. Now, while users can easily exchange BNB to USDT on Binance platform, they will [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bnb-to-usdt/">How to Exchange BNB to USDT [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Here’s the easiest way to exchange BNB to USDT instantly with full anonymity! Binance Coin (BNB) is one of the top crypto assets by market cap. For the most part, this popularity stem’s from Binance’s massive scale as an exchange platform. Now, while users can easily exchange BNB to USDT on Binance platform, they will have to compromise on their privacy to do the job. Primarily, Binance requires a much stricter KYC process to authenticate users. On top of that, they will have to comply with multiple governments and share user data with the authorities. Fortunately, CoinCannon cuts down all complications by offering a truly hassle-free KYC process. Furthermore, privacy will not come as a luxury sine CoinCannon offer the lowest exchange fees. With all that, here is a full guide on how to exchange Binance Coin to Tether USDT in only a matter of minutes.</p>



<p>So, head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, choose Binance Coin (BNB) on the left field and Tether (USDT) on the right one and start your exchange.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange BNB to USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive USDT. Most likely, your Cardano wallet supports USDT, so you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Binance Coin (BNB)?</strong></h2>



<p>Before we go over how to exchange BNB to USDT, let’s go over a brief introduction on Binance Coin. Initially found in China, Binance began as an online cryptocurrency exchange with a strong emphasis on altcoin trading. It didn’t take long for Binance to be crowned as the number one exchange in the world. Amongst the numerous motivating factors and reasons for this profound success, the primary one was high liquidity, low transaction fees and additional discounts for users who made payments by its native coin, BNB. The massive platform has a staggering capacity to process approximately 1.4 million orders per second, offering trading for more than 500 cryptocurrencies and virtual tokens.</p>



<p>As for trading, Binance offers seven trade orders of Limit order, Market order, stop limit order, stop market order, Trailing stop order, Post only order and Limit TP/SL order. Despite the varying transaction fees for withdrawal based on the currency and its amount, there is no transaction fee for deposits.</p>



<p>Initially introduced as an ERC20 Ethereum based cryptocurrency in 2017, BNB has now moved on to Binance’s own blockchain named Binance chain. As the native coin for Binance exchange, BNB was primarily a utility token to motivate users for transaction fee discounts. However, the applications for Binance coin have now expanded dramatically since you can now use Binance Coin for financial services, entertainment, online services and many more.</p>



<p>With all this development happening in a short time period, the 26,500% overall price increase (correct as of January 2022) since being introduced in 2017 is well justified. As of June 4th 2021 BNB has a market cap of $53.7 billion dollars and is only ranked behind Bitcoin and Ethereum.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange BNB to USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>At this point, it’s good to briefly introduce Tether. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange BNB to USDT</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Cardano on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your ADA to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-and-you-re-all-set"><strong>And You’re All Set!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bnb-to-usdt/">How to Exchange BNB to USDT [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-bnb-to-usdt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cryptocurrency Regulations: The SEC is Divided!</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrency-regulations/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrency-regulations/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 11:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6409</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency regulations have been a hot topic in recent years, with governments and regulatory agencies around the world grappling with how to approach this rapidly evolving industry. In the United States, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) plays a key role in regulating the cryptocurrency market. For the most part, the SEC has been showing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrency-regulations/">Cryptocurrency Regulations: The SEC is Divided!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Cryptocurrency regulations have been a hot topic in recent years, with governments and regulatory agencies around the world grappling with how to approach this rapidly evolving industry. In the United States, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) plays a key role in regulating the cryptocurrency market. For the most part, the SEC has been showing an anti-crypto attitude. However, Commissioner Hester Peirce, a well-known advocate for innovation in the crypto space, has recently <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/statement/peirce-rendering-inovation-2023-04-12" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">voiced her dissent</a> against Chair Gary Gensler&#8217;s anti-crypto agenda. Of course, we can be sure about an upcoming shock wave of regulatory action coming for crypto. However, recent debates show how there is internal conflict within the SEC regarding crypto assets.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Commissioner Pierce on Cryptocurrency Regulations</strong></h2>



<p>In a recent speech, Commissioner Peirce criticized the SEC&#8217;s proposal to adjust the definition of &#8220;exchange&#8221; to include decentralized finance (DeFi) protocols. According to Peirce, this change would be counterproductive, promoting stagnation and centralization rather than embracing the potential of new technology.</p>



<p>&#8220;Stagnation, centralization, expatriation, and extinction are the watchwords of this release. Rather than embracing the promise of new technology as we have done in the past, here we propose to embrace stagnation, force centralization, urge expatriation, and welcome extinction of new technology. Accordingly, I dissent,&#8221; said Peirce.</p>



<p>Commissioner Peirce further highlighted that the SEC&#8217;s proposal could potentially violate the First Amendment protections by categorizing blockchain ecosystems as a &#8220;group,&#8221; creating ambiguity around their speech rights.</p>



<p>&#8220;The release&#8217;s ambiguity undermines fundamental First Amendment protections. Because the release makes everybody involved in the relevant blockchain ecosystem part of a &#8216;group,&#8217; it creates significant ambiguity around what speech requires government pre-approval, which will unavoidably chill constitutionally-protected speech,&#8221; Peirce explained.</p>



<p>Peirce also emphasized the importance of the SEC remaining open to the idea of tweaking its rules to accommodate new technologies, something she believes the Commission understood in the 1990s.</p>



<p>&#8220;The Commission of the 1990s understood this basic principle and created space for significant innovations in securities trading. This release, on the other hand, takes the view that any business model that cannot meet the specific requirements of our existing regulatory model does not belong in our markets,&#8221; Peirce stated.</p>



<p>In essence, Peirce argues that the SEC&#8217;s current approach to cryptocurrency regulations is hindering innovation and preventing cutting-edge businesses from entering the market. She believes that a Commission serious about regulating, rather than destroying, the cryptocurrency market should reflect on its past regulatory failures and be open to adapting its rules to accommodate the unique characteristics of cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-sec-s-iron-fist"><strong>The SEC’s Iron Fist</strong></h2>



<p>Peirce&#8217;s dissenting voice within the SEC sheds light on the internal conflict within the regulatory agency regarding how to approach cryptocurrency regulations. Chair Gary Gensler has taken a more stringent stance on cryptocurrencies, expressing concerns about investor protection and market integrity. On the other hand, Commissioner Peirce has been a vocal advocate for embracing innovation and allowing the cryptocurrency market to flourish.</p>



<p>The debate over cryptocurrency regulations is not limited to the SEC. Governments and regulatory agencies worldwide are grappling with how to effectively regulate the rapidly growing cryptocurrency market. Some countries have taken a more progressive approach, recognizing the potential of cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology, while others have adopted a more cautious stance, expressing concerns about risks such as money laundering and fraud.</p>



<p>In the United States, the lack of clear and consistent cryptocurrency regulations has created uncertainty for businesses and investors operating in the crypto space. Many argue that a well-regulated cryptocurrency market could provide significant benefits, such as increased investor protection, market transparency, and economic growth. However, excessive regulation could stifle innovation and hinder the development of the cryptocurrency market.</p>



<p>The SEC, as a key regulatory agency in the U.S., plays a crucial role in shaping cryptocurrency regulations. Commissioner Peirce&#8217;s dissenting voice highlights the need for a balanced and pragmatic approach to regulating cryptocurrencies. While it is important to address risks and protect investors, paralyzing a whole industry does not sound like a democratic approach either.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrency-regulations/">Cryptocurrency Regulations: The SEC is Divided!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/cryptocurrency-regulations/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Solana to Tether [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-solana-to-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-solana-to-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 07:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6403</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sure, you can exchange Solana to Tether on so many platforms, but CoinCannon is better! Solana (SOL) is one of the fastest blockchain networks out there. It offers lightning speed transaction speeds and super cheap transaction costs. With all that in mind, SOL has a loyal group of institutions using it for their global transactions. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-solana-to-tether/">How to Exchange Solana to Tether [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Sure, you can exchange Solana to Tether on so many platforms, but CoinCannon is better! Solana (SOL) is one of the fastest blockchain networks out there. It offers lightning speed transaction speeds and super cheap transaction costs. With all that in mind, SOL has a loyal group of institutions using it for their global transactions. Subsequently, Solana is one of the top cryptocurrencies by market cap. In this article, we will go over how to exchange Solana to Tether on CoinCannon platform. At CoinCannon, you can have the lowest exchange rates, full anonymity and 24/7 online support all together.</p>



<p>So head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Solana on the left box and Tether on the right and get started!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Solana to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive USDT. Most likely, your Solana wallet supports USDT, so you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Solana?</strong></h2>



<p>In short, Solana is a blockchain platform for decentralized applications (DApps). The network utilizes Proof of Stake consensus algorithm. However, in a world full of PoS blockchain networks, Solana has managed to achieve some impressive figures. The network can support up to 50,000 transactions per second (TPS) and requires 400 milliseconds to build a block. With the quickly increasing number of validators currently at 1,061, the network is one of the fastest out there.</p>



<p>Found in 2017 by Anatoly Yakovenko, a former Qualcomm member, along with Eric Williams and Greg Fitzgerald, the network aimed to create a more efficient and scalable platform.</p>



<p>The team consists of former members of companies such as Google, Apple, Microsoft, Qualcomm, Dropbox, Intel and more.</p>



<p>In that regard, the network is backed by many years of experience in some of the best companies around the world.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>    Continue reading “<a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/what-is-solana/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is Solana</a>” to learn everything about the network.</p>
</blockquote>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Solana to Tether</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to exchange Solana to Tether USDT, let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Solana to Tether?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Solana on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your SOL to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-you-re-all-set"><strong>You’re All Set!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-solana-to-tether/">How to Exchange Solana to Tether [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-solana-to-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cardano-ada-to-tether/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cardano-ada-to-tether/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 08:39:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6393</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking for the best platform to exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether? CoinCannon is all you need. Cardano is one of the top cryptocurrencies by market cap and has a pretty strong community of investors. Today, it’s hard to find an online exchanger that doesn’t have ADA on their supported currency list. Despite that, it is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cardano-ada-to-tether/">Exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking for the best platform to exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether? CoinCannon is all you need. Cardano is one of the top cryptocurrencies by market cap and has a pretty strong community of investors. Today, it’s hard to find an online exchanger that doesn’t have ADA on their supported currency list. Despite that, it is still difficult to find a platform that offers the lowest exchange rates and full anonymity. Fortunately, you can instantly exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether without compromising on anything! In this article, we will go over everything you need to know on how to convert ADA to USDT.</p>



<p>So, head over to <strong><a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a></strong>, choose Cardano (ADA) on the left field and Tether (USDT) on the right one and start your exchange.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive USDT. Most likely, your Cardano wallet supports USDT, so you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Cardano (ADA)?</strong></h2>



<p>The Cardano project launched in 2017. It was the third generation of blockchain networks. One that successfully dealt with some of the greatest challenges of previous generations. Issues such as high gas fees and scalability by introducing the Ouroboros, a proof of stake algorithm to mine blocks which will be further explained in the article.</p>



<p>In 2017, the Cardano project started as a third-gen open-source and public blockchain platform. ADA is the native token of the platform. It is Led by Charles Hoskinson, one of the co-founders of Ethereum. Cardano had a great emphasis on being future-proof by being peer-reviewed and methodically developed by academic experts in the field. Cardano views itself as the updated version of Ethereum. Moving towards building a connected and decentralized system and providing banking services to the unbanked.</p>



<p>ADA is the native token of the network. Currently, ADA stands in 7th place in the ranks with a market cap of 13.5 billion USD.</p>



<p>To learn everything about Cardano and ADA continue reading “<a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/what-is-ada-a-guide-to-the-cardano-project/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">What is ADA?</a>”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether (USDT)?</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT, let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon for the Win!</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Cardano on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your ADA to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-all-good"><strong>All Good!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cardano-ada-to-tether/">Exchange Cardano (ADA) to Tether [Instantly]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cardano-ada-to-tether/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Exchange AdvCash to Tether USDT [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-tether-usdt/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-tether-usdt/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 08:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AdvCash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6389</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking for the ultimate platform to exchange AdvCash to Tether USDT? CoinCannon is the ultimate platform for the job! So far, AdvCash has been one of the most crypto-friendly payment processors out there. Regardless, the anonymity factor remains an issue as users may be concerned with their privacy. Fortunately, our platform eliminates all the downsides [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-tether-usdt/">&lt;strong&gt;Exchange AdvCash to Tether USDT [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Looking for the ultimate platform to exchange AdvCash to Tether USDT? <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a> is the ultimate platform for the job! So far, AdvCash has been one of the most crypto-friendly payment processors out there. Regardless, the anonymity factor remains an issue as users may be concerned with their privacy. Fortunately, our platform eliminates all the downsides associated with converting AdvCash to crypto assets. You can instantly convert your AdvCash to Tether USDT with the lowest exchange fees and a hassle-free KYC process that maximizes privacy. On top of that, you will have 24/7 online support for the utmost reliability. In this article, we will go over everything you need to know on how to exchange AdvCash to Tether USDT.</p>



<p>So get started! Head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select AdvCash on the left box and Tether on the right one and you’re good to go!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">how to exchange AdvCash to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange AdvCash to Tether?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange direction, you will need a verified and active AdvCash account. Make sure that the transaction amount does not exceed your withdrawal limit. In order to receive Tether (USDT), you will need a reliable crypto wallet. There are too many options out there, but CoinCannon suggests customers to use Trust Wallet. Furthermore, make sure you pay attention to the TRC20 and ERC20 variants for Tether as they use different networks for transactions and require different wallet addresses.</p>



<p>On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is AdvCash?</strong></h2>



<p>Before we talk about how to convert AdvCash to Tether USDT, let’s have a brief introduction on what the payment processor is. AdvCash is a currency used for online payments. It is based in Belize which provides immunity from national laws of other countries for it. As an offshore currency, it is also encrypted much like cryptocurrencies and benefits from better anonymity and security. The Advance Cash company provides an account for users that allows for a variety of currencies to operate through it. In many ways, it is a lot like the payment processor Payeer.</p>



<p>And much like Payeer, AdvCash supports transfers in both fiat and cryptocurrency form. With a virtual wallet, users can transfer funds and make payments with very low commission. What makes it interesting, is that Advance Cash is also compatible with other payment systems such as WebMoney or Perfect Money. With free international transfers, users get to enjoy a wide variety of currencies all in a virtual wallet. Furthermore, there are both physical and virtual bank cards available for quick and cheap international Visa/Mastercard payments.</p>



<p>The company was founded in 2014 as a competitor for PayPal and much like its peers, it has gained notable success in the past few years. As the need for virtual banking grows, online payment processing companies continue to narrow the gap with PayPal. Although, such companies are not as popular as PayPal, they offer a lot more freedom.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange AdvCash to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon is the Best Exchange!</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange AdvCash to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select AdvCash on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>By now, you will go to the AdvCash gateway. Transfer your AdvCash to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-you-re-all-set"><strong>You’re all Set!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-tether-usdt/">&lt;strong&gt;Exchange AdvCash to Tether USDT [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-advcash-to-tether-usdt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT Instantly</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether-usdt/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether-usdt/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 07:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6386</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>CoinCannon is the ultimate platform to exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT instantly! Exchanging crypto assets into one another is a seemingly simple task. However, finding a platform that offers the best exchange rates and anonymity at the same time is no easy feat. With all the strict user verification out there, user privacy is slowly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether-usdt/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT Instantly&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>CoinCannon is the ultimate platform to exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT instantly! Exchanging crypto assets into one another is a seemingly simple task. However, finding a platform that offers the best exchange rates and anonymity at the same time is no easy feat. With all the strict user verification out there, user privacy is slowly losing its value. Fortunately, our platform provides a hassle-free KYC process that speeds up your exchange process and massively improves security. On top of that, we offer 24/7 online support to ensure the utmost reliability for our customers. In this article, we will go over everything you need to know on how to exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT on CoinCannon.</p>



<p>So get started, head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Ethereum ETH on the left box, and Tether USDT on the right one and you’re good to go!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-paypal-2/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Exchange Ethereum to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-do-i-need-to-exchange-ethereum-to-tether-usdt"><strong>What Do I Need to Exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive USDT. In case your Ether wallet supports ETH, you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-dai/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is Ethereum (ETH)?</strong></h2>



<p>As an open-source decentralized blockchain platform, Ethereum is perhaps the most diverse and innovative one out there. In its essence, it is a decentralized public ledger for verifying and recording transactions. The Ethereum is considered as a second-gen blockchain platform, improving upon the high gas fees, scalability issues and high transactions fees of previous platforms. This open-source platform has no geographical restrictions and has always been the tip of the spear as far as innovation goes. Essential services such as Smart contracts, NFT`s and decentralized apps were first introduced on the Ethereum platform. As for the cherry on top, the native token of the Ethereum platform called Ether or ETH is second in terms of market value standing only behind Bitcoin.</p>



<p>With the Ethereum 2.0 launch in August 2022, the network totally switched to proof of stake. With that, Ethereum network will have much better scalability and very low gas fees. On top of that, all the criticism regarding energy consumption will go away. Many consider the 2.0 upgrade as a great investment opportunity since ETH is very much likely to have a rally. Nonetheless, Ethereum is the second most popular cryptocurrency in the world for good reason. Their team has always been on the forefront of innovation which could potentially attract capital and provide great returns.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<p>Before reading about how to exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT, let’s take a quick look at what Tether is and how it operates. Tether is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain whose crypto coins in use are backed by an equivalent amount of traditional fiat currencies, such as the Dollar, Euro, or Japanese Yen that is retained in a specific bank account. The Tether tokens, the Tether network’s native tokens, trade under the USDT symbol.</p>



<p>In contrast to the wide swings observed in the prices of other popular cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum, Tether belongs to a new race of cryptocurrencies called stablecoins that aims to keep cryptocurrency valuations stable. Instead of being used as a means of speculative investment, this would allow Tether to be used as a medium of exchange and a mode of storage of value.</p>



<p>Tether was specifically developed to create the necessary CoinCannon between fiat currencies and cryptocurrencies, providing users with stability, transparency, and minimum transaction fees. It is pegged against the US dollar and, in terms of value, maintains a 1-to-1 ratio with USD. There is, however, no guarantee provided by Tether Ltd. for any right to redeem or exchange real money for Tethers, i.e. Tethers cannot be exchanged for U.S. Dollars.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Ethereum on the left field and Tether USDT on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your USDT wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your Ethereum to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Done!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Tether to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether-usdt/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Exchange Ethereum to Tether USDT Instantly&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-ethereum-to-tether-usdt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Faces Lawsuit for “Dogecoin Pyramid Scheme”</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/dogecoin-pyramid-sheme-elon/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/dogecoin-pyramid-sheme-elon/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 06:55:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dogecoin pyramid scheme]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ELON]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[elongate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=5550</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There is a literary theory called formalism which is pretty boring but has a practical message. One should take everything at face value instead of acknowledging endless extrinsic benefactors. Now, taking Elon’s clownery on Twitter at face value, he was undoubtedly promoting a Dogecoin pyramid scheme. But guess what, nobody can prove it just like [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/dogecoin-pyramid-sheme-elon/">Elon Musk Faces Lawsuit for “Dogecoin Pyramid Scheme”</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>There is a literary theory called formalism which is pretty boring but has a practical message. One should take everything at face value instead of acknowledging endless extrinsic benefactors. Now, taking Elon’s clownery on Twitter at face value, he was undoubtedly promoting a Dogecoin pyramid scheme. But guess what, nobody can prove it just like nobody can prove Epstein didn’t kill himself. Today, the world of finance is taking a serious beating from social media due to well-coordinated pumps and dumps. And Elon, standing on top of the world, is running his own Dogecoin pyramid scheme to compensate for all of his far-fetched projects. After all, someone has to raise trillions of dollars to send humans to mars where extreme solar radiation will give you cancer. However, one investor has sued Elon and his companies for a lot of money and all we can say to him is Godspeed!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p><mark style="background-color:#ffffff" class="has-inline-color has-vivid-cyan-blue-color">Buy and Sell Dogecoin Instantly on <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a><br>No KYC</mark></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-dogecoin-pyramid-scheme"><strong>Dogecoin Pyramid Scheme</strong></h2>



<p>Ha ha it’s so funny, Elon posted a meme on Twitter. Welp, Keith Johnson doesn’t think so. Mr. Johnson has bravely sued the meme mongering clown billionaire and his companies for a fair $258 billion. Basically, he is claiming that they promoted a Dogecoin pyramid scheme with their support for DOGE.</p>



<p>According to <a href="https://assets2.pacermonitor.com/filings/Johnson_v_Musk_et_al/Johnson_v_Musk_et_al__nysdce-22-05037__0001.0.pdf?X-Amz-Security-Token=IQoJb3JpZ2luX2VjELn%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2FwEaCXVzLWVhc3QtMSJHMEUCICe8v9QbE5ucxkNw%2F4uIyKQkjJprelAClmtWXaGaR63yAiEAmtTds26Or20TjflZQuFt8E5KHvARjGVAJVpAzkBd4iYq3AQIwv%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2FARADGgw5MjQ2NTE0MDgzOTgiDHdleGUYt3IzNA4WxCqwBMxc7LYGv%2F3FmkzepvB1iEhKy4WrV60iR%2BC6sgRWd7KRvpeKutlBGRhY%2BSpmfSN2P5eTxK1sprMAOk4RMJbwXMB2IwFCatBro0IJPS26eMo3TpqDLwCVQAfqVqTxlvqdgOv%2Fvesj6yET6XWuPEY08iW2ZbF%2F9fqXXy3ujKokd2%2BOMPORrbBGZ3wYx5E1Ux7GsuU7a55EJfmihcgkf22mcb2yW%2F25nolZn26PATe1SVfwfc%2BJPOFpch%2BpIDZDINfzNgnYW%2BNc60KcB%2FWBluXiuINNUw%2FqBPcx4FgwyAyTTt0%2BbPFpQnYc%2FzQ9XDwgOOge%2FK8mT3q3svyKADAW4LOmGnjxCMshOnxLrcWVA5pdQT6Xp1V56%2Br%2BSXD986u3EHnCTGoTiIP311bCYq1o4pcpjdcrCZE%2F%2F3rtF%2FehTr%2By3Iy9%2FdH3Dbp4RUl7%2BP16eOQvUeCCEukWX8M9OgFLYcvrdsAox1l%2Fw%2FUQ3dfLYpia7fVObcoo%2FRUN8ak85FMqBkgyKGB7mfCqDLM6vU%2Bw5Hianz3hWo9WuCcTEvKsqv%2FY6L0rIAC1uFw%2FC%2F4%2F%2Bs3qDpJhu%2BnvZGCCGv9%2FVPfjwvAI9XcQ6%2Bc2TC7kx5%2BPm7PyY0SKBM5C4a6JTMPcKog44sq9HTTeMawq1fBvsbBITYxKmjxRuE4rFCn2seFta5Elc54qv1Y0X5P0oQkjOESiNWyArByjoh4KLwtS9xiAA9Uh5Av0sFrFeGm5LKvXQaQz5YXAMOG6rZUGOqkB0oSanITZYUmLZlbgCjFCckfK8%2FTGfAR1DMznAy%2FFM1HNAh9Bi6glBFifnM68QF9sBoXrOZOICHPvTnPyEPQjClub0Bg1Fj9%2BH%2FL3rYsdeci303GLJtGoeuG5dMfIQI9hzTVw7qOi81%2FF68mt0OeLODNJNcw2j1nyQmb8%2FfWKut0BOzkDDZIchN9jIbI3ViOdimrq960jFJj7YVWSOD%2FrDKyHANsocddz9A%3D%3D&amp;X-Amz-Algorithm=AWS4-HMAC-SHA256&amp;X-Amz-Date=20220616T172931Z&amp;X-Amz-SignedHeaders=host&amp;X-Amz-Expires=599&amp;X-Amz-Credential=ASIA5OSMEZQHHGKLHKVM%2F20220616%2Fus-east-1%2Fs3%2Faws4_request&amp;X-Amz-Signature=e89dbab48532f1335e571cea705859ffa86dd08c2139a572d86c7cdbfb8c62c4" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">court documents</a>, Keith Johnson argues that Dogecoin is “simply a fraud whereby greater fools are deceived into buying a coin at a higher price. The documents are currently held with the US district court in southern district of New York.</p>



<p>Johnson is calling for the court to clarify the case as a class-action lawsuit. With that, he is asking for $86 billion in damages for the class, as well as $172 billion for treble damages.</p>



<p>Initially, Keith Johnson argues that Elon and his companies utilized “unethical, torturous and criminal conduct in promoting Dogecoin. Hence, billions of investors lost billions of dollars into the Dogecoin pyramid scheme. As for the numbers, Johnson states that musk made $86 billion “as a result of their wire fraud, gambling enterprise, false advertising, deceptive practices, and other unlawful conduct.”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Too Vague, and Silly!</h2>



<p>Billionaire Elon Musk is seeking to have the multi-billion-dollar lawsuit against him dismissed, which alleges he illegally promoted Dogecoin pyramid scheme. The lawsuit, which was filed by a group of investors, accuses Musk of perpetrating a scandal.</p>



<p>Attorneys representing the Tesla CEO are arguing that the lawsuit is baseless, and Musk&#8217;s statements about Dogecoin were too vague and silly to be considered actual endorsements of the cryptocurrency. Additionally, the lawyers contend that DOGE is a legitimate cryptocurrency with a market cap of around $10 billion. </p>



<p>Musk&#8217;s legal team stated, &#8220;There is nothing unlawful about tweeting words of support for or funny pictures about a legitimate cryptocurrency that continues to hold a market cap of nearly $10 billion. This court should dismiss the complaint and put a stop to plaintiffs&#8217; fantasy.&#8221; this statement matters a lot. Because apparently the court is dealing with a bunch of 12 year olds in this lawsuit!</p>



<p>The lawsuit filed by investors claims that Musk purposely drove the price of Dogecoin up by 36,000% over a two-year period before letting it crash. The suit also alleges that Dogecoin was a security, and Musk knew that it had no intrinsic value.</p>



<p>In addition, the Dogecoin Foundation is another defendant in the lawsuit and is also seeking to have it dismissed.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-elongate"><strong>Elongate</strong></h2>



<p>Elon may be the richest man on earth, but, almost all of his wealth is tied up in stocks for his companies. And, ding ding ding, all his stocks are holding the biggest bubbles in history. Don’t believe it? Then why would Bill gates hold a $2-billion-dollar short position on Tesla? Despite Elon’s wealth, his companies are constantly desperate for cash flow because bubbles take lots of money to continue.</p>



<p>Previously, Elon has stated that he holds Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH) and Dogecoin (DOGE). To make it more interesting, he had previously <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/elon-musk-says-the-us-should-do-nothing-about-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">said</a> that the US lawmakers should “do nothing” about crypto.</p>



<p>As to why he loves DOGE, he had said that it is the “people’s crypto”. You would think that in this day and age, communist style of deception would not work but you would be wrong. Today, everything is “people’s thing” everyone is doing it for “the people” just like the gulags were for the “people”.</p>



<p>In the world of insane maximalists and mislead retail investors, Elon’s Dogecoin pyramid scheme was an unfair one. While the current bear market is purging market from all the crazy NFT money and stimulus checks, Elon will continue to take from “the people”.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/dogecoin-pyramid-sheme-elon/">Elon Musk Faces Lawsuit for “Dogecoin Pyramid Scheme”</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/dogecoin-pyramid-sheme-elon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Bitcoin with Dai [Instantly]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 10:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[crypto to crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6379</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you are looking to buy Bitcoin with Dai, CoinCannon is the ultimate platform for the job. Bitcoin has finally managed to bounce back and move above the critical resistance level at $25k. Subsequently, investors are once again eager to invest in the top crypto asset by market cap. On top of that, the mass [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Buy Bitcoin with Dai [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you are looking to buy Bitcoin with Dai, CoinCannon is the ultimate platform for the job. Bitcoin has finally managed to bounce back and move above the critical resistance level at $25k. Subsequently, investors are once again eager to invest in the top crypto asset by market cap. On top of that, the mass adoption of BTC has turned it into a utilitarian digital asset. Today, thousands of credible online stores accept Bitcoin as payment. Fortunately, you can now pay for goods and services via BTC and there’s lots of stuff you can <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-with-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">buy with Bitcoin</a>. However, if you’re holding DAI, you can instantly exchange Dai into Bitcoin in only a matter of minutes. Want to get started? Head over to <a href="http://www.hi.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">jolixo</a>, select Dai on the left box and Bitcoin on the right and you’re good to go!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-pullquote"><blockquote><p>Learn <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-cryptocurrency-to-paypal/">How to exchange cryptocurrency to PayPal</a></p></blockquote></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What Do I Need to Buy Bitcoin with Dai?</strong></h2>



<p>For this exchange, you will need a crypto wallet to receive Bitcoin (BTC). In case your Dai wallet supports BTC, you can also receive funds in the same wallet. Make sure that you are using a reliable crypto wallet to hold your assets. On the other hand, for CoinCannon platform, all you need is an email address. CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or sign up. However, there are benefits and rewards for those who <a href="https://blog.hi.exchange/reasosn-sign-up-jolixo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sign up on CoinCannon</a>. How do you like winning $100 gifts ever single month?</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What is DAI?</strong></h2>



<p>Before we go over how to buy Bitcoin with Dai, let’s take a brief look at Dai as a stablecoin.</p>



<p>DAI is an Ethereum-based stablecoin. A stablecoin is a cryptocurrency with a pegged value to another currency. In case of DAI, it is pegged to the US dollar and much like Tether and USDC, Dai will always be worth $1. Stablecoins are a crucial part of the crypto market as they offer very little volatility. In that regard, investors use stablecoins to save their funds in the form of a reliable and stable asset.</p>



<p>What makes DAI unique is a clever design that eliminates the biggest concerns for stablecoins. Generally speaking, conventional stablecoins require a massive reserve by the company. For example, for every Tether USD, the Tether company must hold $1 USD in their reserve. This is a huge issue for companies as it is difficult to provide liquidity and keep it consistent.</p>



<p>DAI offers a new solution for this problem. By using an automated system of smart contracts on Ethereum blockchain, DAI does now need a reserve. Using collateralized debt denominated in ETH allows DAI to maintain the 1:1 ration with USD. Simply speaking, users can deposit Ethereum or other cryptocurrencies can borrow against the value of their deposit and generate new DAI. The currency is this case is known as collateral.</p>



<p>You can <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/exchange-dai-to-paypal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exchange Dai to PayPal</a> on CoinCannon with the lowest exchange fees ever!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Why Invest in Bitcoin?</strong></h2>



<p>Well, there is hardly anyone these days who is not familiar with the definition of Bitcoin and what the cryptocurrency is capable of carrying out. However, let’s briefly go through what bitcoin is and where it comes from, then we can focus on the benefits of using this cryptocurrency and explain why to buy Bitcoin with Perfect Money.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a Cryptocurrency that was created after the housing market collapse in January 2009. It follows the ideas set out by the enigmatic and pseudonymous Satoshi Nakamoto in a whitepaper. The identity of the individual or individuals who developed this cryptocurrency is still under wraps. Unlike government-issued currencies, Bitcoin provides the guarantee of lower transaction costs than conventional online payment systems and is regulated by a decentralized authority.</p>



<p>Bitcoin is a tempting opportunity for investment and great tool for doing financial transactions. In that regard, it has been a solid choice for investment as an asset that is truly decentralized. On top of that, there are countless online platform that accept Bitcoin as payment which makes BTC a utilitarian option for online payments.</p>



<p>So, if You’ve decided to invest in BTC, you can buy Bitcoin with Dai in only a matter of minutes on CoinCannon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>CoinCannon Platform</strong></h2>



<p>Say goodbye to the hassle of searching for the perfect online exchange. CoinCannon is here to offer you everything you need and more. With a combination of anonymity, unbeatable exchange rates, and reliability, it’s a platform like no other.</p>



<p>At CoinCannon, your privacy is our top priority. We understand the importance of keeping personal information safe, and that’s why we don’t require it from our customers. With no KYC or sign-up required, you can trade confidently and securely.</p>



<p>Looking for the best exchange rates? CoinCannon is right there for you. Our platform uses an automated system to ensure that you always get the best value for your trades. Don’t just take our word for it, visit ranking websites like BestChange and OkChanger and see for yourself.</p>



<p>We believe in being proactive and keeping ahead of any potential problems. That’s why we offer 24/7 customer support. No matter the issue, our team is always here to help. So go ahead, make your trades with peace of mind knowing that CoinCannon has got your back.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-buy-bitcoin-with-dai"><strong>How to Buy Bitcoin with DAI?</strong></h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list" type="1">
<li>Enter the Homepage on CoinCannon. Select Dai (DAI) on the left field and Bitcoin (BTC) on the right one. Enter the exchange amount and wait for the rates to apply.</li>



<li>Click on Exchange and you will be forwarded to the next step where you will need to enter your BTC wallet address, email, and phone number (optional).</li>



<li>Click on “Exchange” one more time as you go to the next page to review your order.</li>



<li>At this point, you will obtain your Tracking ID, an address and an explorer URL.</li>



<li>On this step, please dedicate some time to review our terms and conditions and the instructions.</li>



<li>Transfer your DAI to the CoinCannon wallet address that is provided for you. Then, make sure to upload a screenshot of the payment.</li>



<li>Finally, click on the “I’ve paid” button.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>You’re All Set!</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will process your order and send the Bitcoin (BTC) to your wallet address. The transaction may take a few minutes. In the meantime, you will have a track id to follow up on your order. Simply enter the main page and type in your track id in the specified field to see your live order status. Keep in mind that your track id is private information and you should not share it with anyone else.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/">&lt;strong&gt;How to Buy Bitcoin with Dai [Instantly]&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/buy-bitcoin-with-dai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aiden Pleterski; Canada’s “Crypto King” Kidnapped</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/aiden-pleterski/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/aiden-pleterski/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 09:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchange News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Canada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hi.exchange/blog/?p=6376</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What goes up, must come down, and in case of Aiden Pleterski, he came down hard. In fact, his fell from grace is something you can see in a crime thriller. And a lot like a crime thriller, his story is as typical as it gets. A young man who became a millionaire overnight, then [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/aiden-pleterski/">&lt;strong&gt;Aiden Pleterski; Canada’s “Crypto King” Kidnapped&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>What goes up, must come down, and in case of Aiden Pleterski, he came down hard. In fact, his fell from grace is something you can see in a crime thriller. And a lot like a crime thriller, his story is as typical as it gets. A young man who became a millionaire overnight, then took a lot of money from a lot of people and scammed them. That would be the first chapter, but then he loses the money as the movie goes on. </p>



<p>And here comes the climax, the self-proclaimed &#8220;Crypto King&#8221; Aiden Pleterski was kidnapped, tortured, and held for ransom after allegedly exploiting investors out of millions. Funny enough, Aiden owned a neon green Lamborghini Urus which is officially the stereotypical vehicle of choice for all social media scammers. Not that we’re pointing fingers but Aiden’s case does not look good for all Lamborghini Urus owners.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Aiden Pleterski; A Classic Tale</strong></h2>



<p>Last August, Pleterski declared bankruptcy after being accused of running a fraudulent investment scheme. The 23-year-old allegedly convinced investors that he would pool their funds and invest them in cryptocurrency and foreign exchange positions. However, since bankruptcy proceedings began, $25 million Canadian worth of claims have been filed against him. This is according to the official <a href="https://docs.grantthornton.ca/document-folder/viewer/docul8LWsxcWho7J/155791662019177193?_gl=1*cbjbqk*_ga*MTczODA4NTY0NS4xNjc5ODY3MjA2*_ga_JLRBBJ6PTP*MTY3OTg2NzIwNi4xLjAuMTY3OTg2NzIwOS41Ny4wLjA.&amp;_ga=2.75019794.1613509646.1679867206-1738085645.1679867206" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">court documents</a> file against him.</p>



<p>Pleterski&#8217;s alleged deceitful behavior was revealed as it was discovered that he only invested less than 2% of the total amount he received, which amounted to $670,000. This is in stark contrast to what he promised investors, leaving many with significant financial losses. The alleged investment scheme has brought into question the regulation and security of the cryptocurrency market, which has become increasingly popular in recent years, as investors look to capitalize on its high returns.</p>



<p>In the meantime, Aiden Pleterski did what every 23-year-old dreams to do one day. Allegedly, Aiden spent around 16 million on his “personal lifestyle” which is all part of the plan. After all, he had to convince investors on social media by flexing hard. His extravagant lifestyle included renting private jets and going on awesome vacations. But, the hallmark of all crypto millionaires is perhaps their car collection. Other than the mandatory neon green Lamborghini Urus, his exotic vehicle collection consisted of “​​a Ferrari, four Audis, three Lamborghinis, three McLarens, a Land Rover, and a BMW.” Now, Maybe the author is jealous, but honestly why three McLarens? McLarens tend to lose value very quickly overtime due to their poor reliability.</p>



<p>All that said, using cheat codes in real life can have devastating consequences.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-kidnapped-tortured-and-held-for-ransom"><strong>Kidnapped, Tortured and Held for Ransom</strong></h2>



<p>In a shocking turn of events, Pleterski&#8217;s troubles seemed to have escalated beyond his financial mismanagement. Pleterski&#8217;s father testified that his son had been kidnapped, held captive for three days, tortured, and beaten by unknown assailants in December 2021. He was only released on the condition that he quickly find money to pay his kidnappers and refrain from contacting law enforcement.</p>



<p>Pleterski reportedly reached out to his landlord, Sandeep Gupta, while in captivity, asking for $3 million to pay his kidnappers. According to Pleterski&#8217;s father, his son was eventually released with the threat that he needed to come up with some money fast and not involve law enforcement.</p>



<p>The kidnapping has further complicated the ongoing bankruptcy proceedings against Pleterski. The case has already seen $25 million Canadian worth of claims filed against Pleterski. Now, with the added layer of criminality, the situation has become even more complex. It remains to be seen what impact the kidnapping will have on the bankruptcy case and how it will affect the investors who have lost their money due to Pleterski&#8217;s alleged fraudulent investment scheme.</p>



<p>Perhaps, the downturn in his situation began with the <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/ftx-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">FTX Collapse</a> back in November 2021. As the crypto market started to deteriorate, Aiden claimed that he has lost all his crypto investments. Obviously, the self-proclaimed crypto king of Canada assured his investors that he was taking aggressive measures to give people back their money.</p>



<p>“I essentially tried to redeem myself [&#8230;] but obviously in doing so, I guess you could say greed took over,” he testified. “I was trying to make returns that obviously weren&#8217;t feasible or weren&#8217;t necessarily possible at the time, and it just caused more losses.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">How to Prevent Future Aiden Pleterski!</h2>



<p>Now that he’s sorry, his regret is not helping anyone get their money back. Unfortunately, one of the biggest stains in the face of crypto is fraudulent social media personalities. Young people with flashy lifestyles, green Lamborghini Urus selling a false promise of success is a big problem for the longevity of cryptocurrencies. Now, while governments are obsessively imposing <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/crypto-regulations-sec-cftc/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">crypto regulations</a>, nobody is doing anything about false social media marketing. It’s always sad to see hopeful investors with less technical knowledge losing their life savings. And in case of crypto, nine times out of ten the money will go missing in the oblivion and never recovered. We’ve seen similar cases on a larger scale with FTX and Terra.</p>



<p>On one hand, crypto personalities emphasis on the need for the lack of regulatory supervision on the market. However, People like Aiden Pleterski prove that unregulated markets need more regulation.</p>



<p>But, here is the best financial advice you will ever get. Don’t trust people who own a green Lamborghini Urus!</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/aiden-pleterski/">&lt;strong&gt;Aiden Pleterski; Canada’s “Crypto King” Kidnapped&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/aiden-pleterski/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
