<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>voucher Archives - CoinCannon Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hi.exchange/blog/tag/voucher/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 08:49:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>How to Create Perfect Money E-Voucher [Including Video]</title>
		<link>https://hi.exchange/blog/create-perfect-money-e-voucher/</link>
					<comments>https://hi.exchange/blog/create-perfect-money-e-voucher/#respond</comments>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 11:36:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[e-currency to e-currency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange Articles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Videos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Payment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-Voucher]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perfect Money]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[voucher]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.hi.exchange/?p=4954</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Boomer terms, a Perfect Money E-Voucher is basically like a bank check but digital. Basically, users can create a Perfect Money E-Voucher with a certain value and use it as a redeemable transaction for a variety of purposes. Thankfully, these vouchers are instantly redeemable via a code and a pin which could easily be [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/create-perfect-money-e-voucher/">How to Create Perfect Money E-Voucher [Including Video]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In Boomer terms, a Perfect Money E-Voucher is basically like a bank check but digital. Basically, users can create a Perfect Money E-Voucher with a certain value and use it as a redeemable transaction for a variety of purposes. Thankfully, these vouchers are instantly redeemable via a code and a pin which could easily be sent via SMS, E-mail or any form of online messaging. In terms of use cases, the applications are endless since it is an accessible form of payment for both the sender and the receiver. In this article, we will go through everything you need to know about the Perfect Money E-Voucher and how to make one instantly.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="How to Create Perfect Money Voucher on CoinCannon [No KYC]" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/iDN2gUZgupw?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<div class="wp-block-buttons alignwide is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-is-layout-1 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-text-align-center wp-element-button" href="https://hi.exchange/En/solutions/buy-sell-perfectmoney-voucher?cur_from=USDTTRC20&amp;cur_to=PPUSD">Buy Perfect Money Voucher Now!</a></div>
</div>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-perfect-money-e-voucher"><strong>Perfect Money E-Voucher</strong></h2>



<p>it is easy, it is affordable and it is anonymous a lot like the CoinCannon Platform! The E-Voucher is the solution to some of our biggest payment problems. The electronic voucher is a method of payment that is redeemable instantly. The user pays a specific amount of funds and creates a voucher. Then, the information for the voucher can easily be delivered to the receiver and they will have the choice to redeem the payment anytime they want. Much like a gift card or a bank check, the voucher will hold the value permanently since the payment has already been made.</p>



<p>Although there are numerous applications for this, here are some of the common utilities:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>You can create a voucher to make payments when you don’t have access to your Perfect Money account.</li>



<li>Perfect Money E-Voucher is a good method of payment when you don’t carry cash or traveling abroad.</li>



<li>As a service provider, users can receive vouchers if they don’t wish to reveal their account address.</li>



<li>Send your loved ones a voucher instead of a gift card</li>
</ul>



<p>Perfect Money E-Voucher does not cost users a lot of money to make! You can simply go to CoinCannon and create your voucher immediately with the lowest fees. On top of that, unlike a majority of exchanges, CoinCannon does not require KYC (know your customer) or even a sign up process. It is truly fast and truly anonymous.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-is-perfect-money"><strong>What is Perfect Money?</strong></h2>



<p>Perfect Money is an e-currency for making payments on the internet. It is widely accepted as payment option by countless platforms. With Perfect Money, you can do a lot! Be it transferring funds to others or pay for goods and services. Or how about buying cryptocurrencies or even buying fiat currencies. It is a seriously popular payment method for online users. An additional capability is to loan and receipt issuance throughout the system.</p>



<p>The biggest downside of Perfect Money, however, is that you cannot cash Perfect money to your bank account on its website directly. For that, you will need a platform like CoinCannon to exchange your Perfect Money to PayPal and other e-currencies.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-jolixo-does-it-better"><strong>CoinCannon Does It Better!</strong></h2>



<p>Essentially, you need three primary qualities in an ideal exchange platform. Anonymity, good rates and reliability. The CoinCannon team consists of traders and professionals who have felt the need for an ideal exchange and pursued their vision.</p>



<p>First and foremost, all users need to protect their personal information especially when it comes down to financial transactions. Unfortunately, a vast majority of exchange apps and platforms make massive profits off of selling user data. Best case scenario, they are legally bound to disclose user information with national authorities for any reason. In that regard, the best method to protect your privacy is to not disclose them with anyone at all. CoinCannon does not require customers to go through KYC (know your customer) or even a mandatory sign up. In that regard, it is simply as safe as one can get making an exchange.</p>



<p>On the other hand, privacy is not a reason to pay more on your exchange. With that in mind, the platform offers some of the most competitive exchange rates you can find anywhere. Don’t take our word for it. You can simply pay a visit to ranking websites such as BestChange or OkChanger and see compare our rates with others.</p>



<p>Last but not least, not everything goes as planned in the digital world. Subsequently, the platform provides true online 24/7 customer support for the users.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-create-perfect-money-e-voucher"><strong>How to Create Perfect Money E-Voucher?</strong></h2>



<ol style="list-style-type:1" class="wp-block-list">
<li>Enter the homepage first, then select Perfect Money and Perfect Money E-Voucher from the options in the first step. Enter the amount you want to exchange. Following that, you will see how much USD will be in your E-Voucher</li>



<li>Press Exchange and you will go to the next stage where you will enter your E-mail address and phone number (it’s optional).</li>



<li>One more time, click on the “Exchange” button and you will go to the next step where you will review your order.</li>



<li>Complete the captcha and click on exchange to go to the next step where you will obtain a tracking ID. Press the “Pay Order” button to go to the Perfect Money gateway and make the payment to our Perfect Money account. Having transferred your Perfect Money to CoinCannon, your order will process very quickly.</li>



<li>By finishing all the steps above, our team of professionals will create your e-voucher and send the details to you via E-mail.</li>
</ol>



<p>Keep in mind, you can also see your E-Voucher information in Admin description section after that your order completed by using your Track ID. Also, if your Perfect Money account <strong>isn&#8217;t</strong> <strong>verified</strong>, your <strong>send fee will be 1.99</strong> %</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-done"><strong>Done</strong></h2>



<p>When you finish the steps above, our team will immediately process your order and create your e-voucher. The process will take between 3 to 20 minutes. In the meantime, you can spend some time reading some of the latest crypto news on CoinCannon Blog. Remember that our support team is online 24/7 to answer all your questions.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog/create-perfect-money-e-voucher/">How to Create Perfect Money E-Voucher [Including Video]</a> appeared first on <a href="https://hi.exchange/blog">CoinCannon Blog</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

					<wfw:commentRss>https://hi.exchange/blog/create-perfect-money-e-voucher/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>


			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
